Subtitle Production - God of Heaven and Earth
"Ajin" means a person who cannot die
Call the new mankind
No matter how hard I try
I just die temporarily.
It has the feature to reproduce again
It was first discovered in Africa 26 years ago
Currently, 46 people are identified worldwide
The Japanese government established the Ain management committee
I have been studying to solve the mystery.
Toho Presents
in association with Production I.G.
A Katsuyuki Motohiro picture
Heart rate normal
Experiment 003
Confirm pupil dilation
Reset is complete
Cut the right arm
Please press
- Yeah
I have a ringer.
Examine the sample
I'll cut it.
The heart rate is three times
Reduction of bleeding 50
Supplement
I would like 30 times
Yeah
Sample of blood enters the emotions
Cutting is done.
Next, cut the legs
What are the individual differences with 002
This is the latest software
Comparison data
Get started
There is no big difference.
Yeah
No change.
Decreases by 38
No response
Reset
Or
When do you do it?
Reset is complete
Cut the left shoulder
What are you doing?
Since when did you...
Call an ambulance!
What's up?
Something's weird.
I just want to live quietly.
What, is he dead?
Aren't you?
Ajin
I need to take a picture.
Ajin is ajin!
why me?..
Reset it.
Ajin
About 1 pm this afternoon,
In the streets of Nakagawa City ..
3rd in Korea
Ajin is protected
On this Ajin's discovery
The world is paying attention
It's Ajin to hit a truck.
Nagai lives an ordinary life
This ability to learn alone
Experiment 003
Nagai 26 years old
Kyoto University Hospital
Working in the family,
Mother and one sister
In a traffic accident three days ago
It is witnessed to regeneration after death.
It turned out to be Ajin.
It's not a good feeling.
Yeah
Ajin is the key to human evolution
To be a valuable being
Do you remember work two years ago?
The expense is full.
The reaction is weak.
Reset it.
- Yeah
You're in the meeting room.
This is it.
Nagai-kai is protected
It's in front of Ajin Lab.
Tozaki
Do you understand?
Three of them are being protected.
The people believe so.
If this experiment is open to the public
Of course I know
What you need to worry about is
I'm your grip. Tanaka-kun
Yes
What's up!
Check it out!
I beg your pardon.
Just leave it to me.
An intruder! An intruder!
It's been a while.
Here comes Tanaka.
I rescued you.
Three years or so?
Are you there? Tozaki
Take the people to the safe room.
Okay
I came to the Nagai Islands.
right
Tonight's situation in Japan
It's going to be very different.
That's what I declare.
Establish guard to block passage
For intruders
Allow the use of lethal anesthetics
It captures after fortune.
come!
Go!
I'm sleepy.
Hit
I got it.
Tanaka Tanaka
How's it going?
Absolutely
It's not going to work.
Good to see you.
who?
My name is Sato.
It's like you.
Are you... are you here to rescue me?
At first glance, it looks like twenties.
But you are better than that.
Did you buy a lot more?
Yeah..
I understand that body.
This country lied, breathing.
The government protects Ajin...
And then...
We do not think of us as mice.
Fight together
For Ajin's future
Do not shoot!
I'm outta here.
You do it
I gave you pain.
You have the right to kill.
stop
Kill .. right ..
No... Do not shoot!
I'll quit.
because
When I shot these guys,
I thought they were just bothering them.
Then there is no merit.
Yes, you are unique.
why?
I like it a lot to kill.
Childhood
You play with worms?
I'm outta here ..
Sorry
But is it okay?
You are...
You are below expectation!
I'll kill you.
Run away!
Hide and seek.
I'm outta here.
You'll know.
How much human beings
I'm scared and pointless.
Those who have tested you are also at home.
If you go there, you will have loved ones.
At first, I thought I should try the Ajin experiment
I accept it, but soon my mind will change.
Once you know it's human evolution,
My heart will set.
The human mind
It is weak forever.
I did not forget what you did.
It's the first time I'm escaping here.
Gib and take it
I'll be the bait, you run away.
Then mark me the direction to escape.
I'm outta here.
but..
Where is it?
It will not be easy.
Okay, that's me.
Kill two of them quickly.
I'm outta here.
Do you really?
It will not be good.
I'm outta here.
Is that me?
Are you listening?
I'm sick.
Well, it was not bad.
But the finish is still poor.
It's good.
Congratulations on your first reset
What are you doing? He's coming!
I can not help it. It's a promise.
Post the remaining expenses
You are here.
Someone will keep me.
Okay
you can do it
This way!
I really did run away.
It's fast.
I have not seen it yet.
What is this...
Game over with this
It came out of me.
There are so many
I'm great.
Black .. Ghost ..
This is Ajin's ability.
It's Iya. It's good.
But I do not think you're familiar with it yet.
Hey move the ghost
end!
Now let's go!
Hey ghost
Once more
Is there anything I can do twice?
Free.
I'm out of here ..
I'm outta here.
I'll finish hide and seek.
It's on the roof!
It's me!
What is it?
Nagai-ke that is branded as Ajin
Information about Nagai-kei
I heard an explosion in the lab.
What happened to the Ajin Institute
I'm still in the process
I wonder if Nagai...
It's late. What was Sato doing?
Sorry
what? What about Nagai-ke?
More than expected
I wanted to put it as a colleague
I was expecting something.
character,
Let's start the show.
Who is it?
Over the wheelchair over there
Are not you Tanaka?
I've been looking at it for two years.
Tanaka, right?
Are you Tanaka?
If you do not stop...
If this is the press
I can not act like this.
To the people today
I have something to say.
My name is Sato
It's 'Ajin'.
Ajin ?!
There are three people in Korea.
One person has not been publicized yet.
Are you...?
I will not tell you.
So what you're trying to say is
The national power of this country
Using Ajin to test human body
We are forcing
I do not...
Instead of Ajin's cooperation with the government
Are not you promised protection?
It's just surface.
The reality is totally different.
For example, the pharmaceutical company Grand Pharmaceutical
Ajin is human
Developed a new drug
In addition, POSHI Heavy Industries
Performance test using Ajin
Manufactured prohibited poison gas
National food, medical equipment, automobile
Several companies use Ajin
We are conducting a human experiment.
The government has a huge budget.
And the victim
This is Mr. Tanaka Koji.
He came in for protection.
Two years before I asked
Non-human human experiments
I had to continue.
The evidence is all on my website
I uploaded it to 'AJIN.COM'
'AJIN.COM'?!
Ah! It's up.
Everyone
What is Ajin?
Is it a mouse?
We are absolutely immortal.
But, I feel pain.
Because of Ajin,
I can not allow you to act.
Our wish is one.
Give Ajin the citizenship
To designate a special autonomous district
Please
Listen to this wish
At the National Institute
Mr. Sato who said himself to be a person
After hiding in front of the press
I can not find the place.
About Ajin special district designation
Domestic intellectuals...
I can not help it anyway.
Never borrow an autonomy
I can not give it to you.
If what they say is true
It's a serious human rights violation by the government.
The former President
Ishimaru Takio
We contribute to the world.
It is a medical instrument that is believed.
Dangerous things like toxic gas
Can not you make it?
Is that you? That's...
[Forge Heavy Industries Public Relations Office Call Center]
Hello YouTube
'Ajin Autonomous Region'
Let's learn more about
What?
What I did. .
- Good-bye
- Good night.
awhile
What the hell is that?
Come on.
The '
[The rain is wonderful]
When it rains or when it rains
Any life means good.
Good.
is not it?
Yeah
Is it really okay? Even if you take care of ..
There was one grandchild with a similar height.
I kept it precious.
is that so
I'll make rice balls.
Do you eat Umeboshi?
Oh, I can not eat it.
Do not eat it.
Wait a minute.
I do not know.
about me
Currently missing Nagai-kai's
We have not heard from you yet.
Sato, a man named Aito
About Speeches
We are waiting for government announcement
Wherever you go, it's just a story about you.
How will the government come?
Killed 20 people
22 people
To go
Well, I'll go.
Tanaka-gun
I beg you.
25 people
Yeah
26 people
"Enoki General Hospital"
Our Lines
My brother's soon
I hope to hear from you
Did not you get in touch?
There is not
Is that so
now..
It's not my brother.
About your brother
Nothing has changed.
But
It's hard.
I understand the mood
Even if you do not sympathize...
In the immediate vicinity
You suffer the same
There were people who suffered.
That word is around
Are you talking about Ajin?
You do not.
Please do not say it properly.
Even if you come in contact with your brother
I will not tell you.
I saw TV.
You guys had a human experiment with Ajin.
Look good
see
Is there a problem?
What happened?
Hey... Hey...
Hey what's going on!
This brings Nagai into this.
You, you better get out of there.
You pretended to be human?
Kurochan!
You're far.
Go
sister
Mr. Nagai! Mr. Nagai, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
What happened? It's okay?
It's okay.
You're hurt!
What is this?
Hey!
I mean, it's not true at all.
The government uses Ajin to conduct human experiments.
I was forced to...
But do you have a clear picture?
How do you explain that?
Yes
Reset it.
There is no reaction.
a lot of people..
For government manipulation of public opinion
It is judged to be a CG composite image
That ghost ..
How do I get out?
It came out.
M4 carbine in 10 tablets
50 magazines
Be thrilled
This big deal has been a long time.
What are you going to do?
Here's what I promised
Ten kidneys and five kidneys
I do not know where I always get it.
How do you get it this way?
You better not know.
I do not want to know
I hope you do not know.
If we pick out a weed, it'll fly again.
You can just leave it.
I do not even have time to do it.
That's a guy.
is that so
Do not fret
What should we do next?
In the hospital,
A member of
Nagai-kei kin
It was reported to be hospitalized.
Eriko
'Come up on the roof'
Are you okay? Looks exhausted.
You were worried.
It's not mine.
I'm sorry.
The woman in front of me
Because he was Ajin.
I could live.
I will not tell anyone.
I was embarrassed.
Yes
Is your brother Ajin?
Huh
I do not know why.
Why was it cold
What are you going to do now?
I feel like asking from here.
You know
I desperately studied
Into the department of medicine
I was trying to be a real doctor.
I was suddenly a bitch
I'm being chased by strangers.
My life plan is all gone.
What is Ajin?...
Why did I...
I still have words.
I was a little funny.
Sato may attack again someday.
Huh
Because the media is loud.
If you stay here, you can not live quietly.
So what do you do
Tanaka-gun
Yeah
Are you ready?
Start
I see you again.
Nice to meet you, Sato.
then
I have a government
It's already been five days since I requested it.
However,
I did not even come back.
So,
I will.
The content is
Ajin research data collection agency
Destroy the Ministry of Health and Welfare
November 25, 3 pm
This is our first wave.
You better watch out.
And
If you have a heart to share with me
I hope you'll come that day.
Fight together.
And humans.
Prepare for shock
It's okay. It's stable.
Thanks
He was your doctor.
He's still an apprentice.
It's great.
It looks different
Thank you very much
It's okay.
A beautiful granddaughter
It feels like it.
It'll be cold in the thick
I'll get you some clothes.
He's a good person.
I've been walking a long time.
I need you to fast down today.
My brother healed my illness.
So I'm trying to be a doctor.
then..
Unlike the real thing
There's a warm part.
I'm sure you'll get better.
Yeah
Hey, ghost
Ask this
Is that so
No...
You bring me
Sato Ajin Research Institute
He's the one who made it.
Sato and Tanaka then went to Nakai
Likely to have made a colleague
Pick this up.
Pick up
I'll be back someday.
What are you doing ..
What is that guy ..
That house.
It is listed in the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare
3 pm is coming soon ..
It's the time that they decided to destroy
It's about 3 o'clock in the afternoon.
Police and gentlemen are strict
I'm packing expenses.
I do not see any movement
Today, outsiders are completely blocked
Only the person concerned enters.
The weather is sunny.
It was from Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare
Hello
This report was from
Soon to be
It's 3 o'clock.
Please see any motion
There is not
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You said it was okay.
Ajin horses
What can I do?
But...
Good.
Secretary...
It's an airplane!
The plane is now in labor!
The plane crashed into the building!
You guys run away!
run!
The plane just crashed into Labor.
Something dangerous has happened.
Currently, the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare
I can not reach you.
What is the matter?
Thriller
The thrill of the plane is fun.
I broke it.
Wait for me.
Did you really do it?
You came here.
I was moved.
There you are.
Welcome party
This is not the end.
Arrive at 2 minutes
then
This country's top troops
Is it self-defense?
No wrong
I have never experienced
The ones that do not exist are out of the question.
If so, then ..
Special Officer of the Metropolitan Police Department
First of all,
Elite troops to mobilize
Known as 'S.A.T'
I'll get back to you later.
Then the next news
Fellow citizens
I'll show you my heart.
This is the second wave
And..
I'm outta here.
Are you looking?
Watch it carefully.
The power of Ajin
character,
S.A.T Will you start your first fight
Start operation
launch
Advance each squad
Secure target
Sato is killing before he gets resurrected.
I ordered
If you can not kill
Can not be resurrected
We are free from freedom.
Yeah
2nd squad shoots forward
It's a sniper!
I do not have a hunch about shooting.
At 7 o'clock 7 o'clock, the sniper
Good morning
Slow
- hurry
- Go ahead.
Pretty much.
Mr. Sato, you're not completely human.
Well, it's because he's a boy.
I know about you guys.
It's Ajin!
I know you're here!
All right
I've got a lot of good luck.
Hey... Where are you going?
brother?
Eriko Gaza
Get ready.
Are you yours?
Did you know?
I knew.
Then why are you...
If you have a person
It's natural to help.
Run away with Eriko.
I'll try to do it somehow.
Thank you, Granny.
Get dressed upright.
Because it's your life.
thanked
Come on.
You
Wait
Open your grandmother's door!
hurry!
I'm tired.
The reset is awesome too.
You are the last
I hope that this is my heart.
Then we ask the Japanese government again.
Tomorrow will be a part of Tokyo until 8 pm
Assign it to Ajinu Special Self-governing Province
If you refuse,
I will spread A.J.V.X throughout Tokyo.
Genocide is the most effective.
This is not a threat.
We take it as a stepping stone to Tokyo
It is an innovation that makes human land uninhabitable.
It's the third wave
Do you think so?
So, good reply ~
The collapse of the Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare
It is Sato and Tanaka party with Ajin.
In addition to sato...
It's the video just before the crash that we go out now.
Nagai Kei also anti-government
May be a member of a group
You can fight against Ajin
Is there a means?
What difference do they have with a murderer?
They are.
With human beings
There is no intersection or empathy.
I wish I did.
Could not be quarantined
- Because it's a weird creature.
- I do not know.
Are not you with the cops?
Ajin might be around.
Are not those guys dying?
Upset
You're not caught yet?
Who is Ajin? do not know
character
Thanks
Should I keep running?
Ajin only
I've never done anything wrong.
[Crisis Management Center]
Move
Start
I started recording
Connect
Hey, Tosaki.
I did decide
Mr. Sato
We are trying to reconcile with you.
After repeated discussions
I made a difficult decision.
Uninhabited island in southern Kyushu
Or in part of Hokkaido
I will enact a special municipality.
Really? really?
Yes, Kyushu and Hokkaido
Either way, it's delicious.
But what I want is
It is Tokyo.
Hey wait, now this is similar
It is a special measure that can be legislated.
The above conditions are...
If so, negotiation is broken.
bye
Failed to track location
It seems to use a special proxy
Are you crazy?
Tokyo is in favor of negotiations
Is it a means to do that?
I do not remember.
Certainly, that would be fun.
I'm yours
Me too
Then what about the others?
Do not be ridiculous
I'll take it.
Now what?
What if you cut your hair and put it in the drum?
It's cute.
Good idea.
[Cabinet Office Meeting Room]
Excuse me
Because of your mistakes
The negotiations broke down.
That's the government's decision.
I only negotiated.
The excuse is a wicked toad
Take responsibility.
You can not handle it as far as you can.
In other words
Although there is no matter
There are no people to blame you.
right
It's not what we have to do.
Special Ajin Special Forces
I decided to hurry up and make it.
Once you know that.
The Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare
In a crash
The first target of Ajin capture
Dae-in special group
Announced it will launch.
- Dia is a Special Forces of GSDF
- People who have been informed by Ajinato
It was crowded with people who wanted to go to Tokyo.
- And in the tunnel.
- Have you seen it? Tokyo is the end.
- Dae-Ae Specialties
- I will run away.
- How dangerous is this.
I can not afford to take a video
Dangerous enough
Tokyo, run away.
Bai ~
Hey, is not that a toazaki tea?
Just say a word.
Mr. Tozaki, I have a deal.
I'm here to go.
I think I'll trust Ajin.
You'd be a winner.
To me?
For what?
Stop Sato
What can you do
One immortal soldier says to be a fellow.
You know, it's not a bad thing for you.
And there's a plan.
I thought it was a deal.
What is your request?
I have two requirements.
One is sister Eriko
Government protection
And the other one is after Sato
Give me a new identity and magazine
Promise not to
That's it.
I saw him. The last time he saw
Sato's battle, he knew the battle.
I will affirm.
The power to stop Sato without my cooperation
It's not in this country right now.
I can not credit you either.
Mr. Tozaki, I've been looking into you.
There was only one co-worker.
If you do not keep your promise,
My ghost will kill her.
Garbage
It's just Gib and Take.
I knew what I wanted to say.
But just know this.
My name is not Tozaki.
Tosakida
Eriko told me he was here.
Great
You met.
It's okay now.
sister..
I thought it was strong.
It's surprisingly nice.
We have a small number of elite
Fight against Sato as a unit
[Ajin Institute meeting room]
You can not play baseball with this guy.
You've hit Sato before?
Head count does not make sense.
If there are many, it is likely to be exposed over there.
These people?
It's like a mercenary.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Well, then,
Sato
Nerve gas A.J.V.X throughout Tokyo
I'm trying to drain it.
However,
It does not exist in the headquarters of Forge Heavy Industries.
In other words, Sato must be at Posy Heavy Industries
I'll come to get the gas.
Because we are Ajin
I have a plan.
It's okay if Ajin's alive.
Sato is here Nagai-ke
I would not expect to be there.
That's great for him.
It will be a disadvantage.
Dae-ajin specialties group
What does 'diamond' add?
I guess we can get out of here, right?
It is not known whether permission will be issued.
I can only think of it as a backup.
I'm sorry to put water on the plan.
What is it?
Sato does not follow
Is not it possible to choose a method?
exactly..
If you do not come to Forge Heavy Industries...
It will not happen.
right
A.J.V.X is a ..
Sato's human experiment
It's done in the center.
Sato has suffered the same pain as humans
I might try to show you some taste.
there
What kind of person is Sato?
No, I was supposed to work together.
I do not think I know anything yet.
Does it feel like you are born?
You idiot.
OK
It's not like that.
Two years after I was caught in government
Numerous human experiments have been done everyday.
Grant all people on the planet
That's enough pain.
He is such a pain.
20 years
20 years?
Since I was born as a baby
To be an adult
I had to die every day.
It will be okay if the earth disappears
Experimented over the window
I was watching you.
I will never fight
The day will come.
This is what I have to say.
How does it feel not to die?
I'm going to ask you in reverse.
This dangerous
How do you feel about participating in the operation?
I do not think deeply.
It's the same.
There's no answer.
is it
You got a good operation?
I'll move on.
After killing Sato,
Do you want to have a toast?
I'll give it to you.
I do not want to meet you anymore.
Let's go though.
You need that waste.
What?
I'm surprised.
What is it?
You're holding hands with someone.
He looks cold, but it is not.
In the circumstances of oneself
Choose something that is really important to you
I just do all the power.
I do not hate that guy.
It's a little dangerous operation.
Huh
Protect me
No matter what
Thank you for your prompt response.
[Forge Heavy Industries]
[49th President's Office]
Come on.
It's funny.
You're outta here.
Nice to meet you.
They should not notice?
I just increased my expenses.
I did not tell anyone.
Of course I will do my best.
But
The worst victims will come.
I can not help it.
Tokyo is kidnapped by monsters
It's a crossroads.
[2nd Floor Entrance]
I wonder if Okuyama has gone in.
- uh? what is this?
- Upset
Sato's amulet.
- charm?
- this?
A man who does not know what he's thinking.
Where is it now?
Well
I can not come near this place.
Each floor has its own staff.
The doors are only open from the opposite side.
Nobody can open this safe.
I do not know what the enemy will do.
It is only aimed at robbery of gas
It is imperative that this president's office
I will aim for this safe.
That's why it's one square...
[49th floor secretariat]
It will appear in the room.
here?
If you bring me here...
It's our victory.
[20th Floor Server Room]
Turn sigh
I fight with that monster.
I can not be at ease.
What's up?
Suddenly there was an error on the server.
Go down and log
I'd better check it out.
Is it hacked?
There is a possibility
Prepare yourself.
[Dolphin Spring Water]
The place is the president's office, 49th floor.
Good
It's a dolphin spring water.
Not
what
Wait a second
Hey what are you doing!
It's a war start!
Hey Gandha!
Hey, this way!
Hey Takahashi!
Okay
It's dangerous.
Shoot
Hey, open up.
I'll borrow it.
Mr. Tanaka
Takahashi
Goes!
Bai Bai ~
An outsider broke into the building.
Will not open
Intrusion complete
Come on, you can not lift an elevator.
Stop it!
You can not miss it!
[9th floor security room]
attack!
Do not give way!
Takahashi goes
♬ There are memories, Lan Lara Rana ~ ♪
♬ Let's run to the hill ~ ♪
♬ I drink clear air ~ ♪
♬ The sky is clear blue sky ~ ♪
Shoot!
[12th floor office]
Stop it!
Shoot
okay!
Stop it!
I can not.
Do not shoot
Retreat!
Karah Takahashi!
Do you mind? okay!
Let's traffic accident!
K! Reset it!
Hey!
Good morning
What was it still alive?
stop!
Nice great!
Noisy
Go
Mr. Tanaka, we are the best.
Well,
tired
Mr. Tosaki's 22nd floor has been broken.
Just one thing is weird.
What?
I broke in as expected.
But there's no Sato.
Moving alone
Otherwise..
What about the server side?
The server system of the building
Be operated remotely
I'm tracking the source.
I can not continue operations if I do this.
I'll find this one.
Come on.
I will.
Talk to me at once.
I found the location. It's 40 stories.
Send Expense
You went too.
Yeah
This?
Mr. Tozaki.
Disturbed
Are you working hard?
who?
Nice to meet you.
To go
[30th floor machine room]
I found Mr. Tosaki.
The hacker seems to be alone on the 33rd floor.
okay
Sorry
What should I do
I'm outta here.
The system recaptured.
Then we start operations.
wait
This is all done.
Mr. Hirasawa, I'll leave it to the rest.
Leave it to me.
Let's go here.
Yeah
Good
It is now
Turn the fan on.
Yeah
What?
What is this ?!
Ajinu powder ?!
Nagai ?!
The ghost can only be seen by Ajin.
In such a large amount
What ?!
Tanaka!
What is visible?
I do not see it!
The attack is coming!
Take care of Takahashi!
Garbage!
Dangerous
run! Takahashi! This way!
clear
So far, four people have been destroyed.
But even this time
I do not see Sato.
There is only one entrance to this side.
When you have all your troops on your side,
He can not help it.
Wood shredder
I crush the logs by five centimeters.
Good.
Thanks
Is he just a man to sleep
I'll let you know about me.
If Ajin is destroyed
It will play from the biggest flesh
is that so
You'll see a rare sight.
Mr. Spock Transmit
Hello! I'm back
Satoda
Sato showed up.
Yeah?
Come to the office quickly.
What happened?
A hasty man is not popular.
Nagai
I'll send it to you right now.
Our
It's a victory.
wake up
That's it.
launch
Miser
Did you do it?
Wait a minute!
It's okay. It's okay.
He's asleep.
Well
What is happening Hirasawa
Now, let's fight back.
Report
Hirasawa
Hirasawa!
Sato! How do I...
Amulets helped.
They are...
then
Let's open
This will change everything.
It's a lot of excitement.
I'll be back.
Is not it going back?
You've come all the way here.
Enjoy the end roll.
End roll?
Tanaka-gun
Yeah
I'll take care of it.
Mr. Hirasawa
I'll stop.
Run away
Do not speak
Sato guy
I know.
If you do not fight...
Do not tell me!
And..
Your life...
I live.
Do not be ridiculous
I wanted to have a toast.
Wow ~ I'm outta here.
Are you there?
The last one is really fateful.
How did you get here?
I've given my left hand a charm.
If you think a little, you'll know.
I got the gas.
I'll spray it now. Like spraying pesticides.
Where are you
Pest control is most effective in the yard.
I got it by the gas.
I thought Bonus Stage
Shaking
I'm outta here.
You too.
The best end roll comes
Where is Nagai?
Nagai
We will request the dispatch of diamond.
Mr. Tozaki, I'll be waiting for you.
[Top helicopter landing area]
Excited
You came here.
Happy
The last boss appears.
You will not be surprised.
Good.
Let's start the game
Yeah
[Restaurant on the 34th floor]
Come on!
Kurochan!
I meet again.
Why are you Ajin and sticking over there?
Neither.
I thought you guys were right.
You're not doing this.
I'm outta here.
What do you think Ajin is
It is a human chosen to evolve.
How was you before
The next life of a human being
How was your life changed by Ajin?
You now
It's alive.
Let's enjoy
For me, the final wave is you.
I'm outta here.
But before that, 'purification'
That's too bad.
How long are you going to pretend to be a human?
While struggling and suffering
You hate humans too!
I have one question.
Why so
Are you on your side?
Ajin
You can enjoy it more.
It's a human or a human being.
I like that kind of thing.
I just
I hate you!
You are also unique.
Come on, ghost.
Shimomura!
Proceed to reset!
You did not protect me.
That's not the point.
Sorry
Do not leave me.
How many times...
Can you get it out?
Now, too
I was nervous.
Hey ghosts!
Come out!
come out!
It looks good.
character,
Game Over
I barely managed to get here.
Can not recover
Are you willing to state
Nagai-ke did it.
I have Sato as the point of attack of Dia
I ordered you to drive it.
But he's got this situation.
After you make it
I want Nagai to take it.
That's the government
It was a condition to permit.
What's your appointment with Nagai-ke?
To stop Sato...
I do not know.
It's me!
Do not shoot!
Nagai!
Subtitle Production - God of Heaven and Earth
Thank you ^ - ^