Improved & Synced by BanglarBagh
(SERENE MUSIC PLAYING)
Jo!
CLARE: Mommy!
- CLARE: Mommy!
- MOM: Clare.
Mommy! (GIGGLES)
How far can I go?
Just down the street and back.
- You gonna visit the nest for me?
- Yes!
- (GIGGLES)
- MOM: Okay.
Go on, big girl.
Whee! (GIGGLES)
Come on, Max.
(MAX BARKS)
Hey, I'll keep an eye on her for you.
CLARE: Max! Max!
CLARE: I win.
- (BABY BIRDS CHIRPING)
- Come on, back in.
Come on!
Come on, boy!
- (DOG BARKING)
- Max, come on!
Come on.
Mrs. Deluca they hatched!
That is so great sweetie!
CLARE: Come on, Max!
(MOM SOBBING)
Momma?
(MAX WHINES)
(MOM SOBS)
Mommy?
(STAIRS CREAKING)
Momma?
(STOOL THUDS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(SIGH)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
CLARE: Morning!
MRS. DELUCA: Aw, you look so nice.
- Bye!
- Bye, Mrs. Deluca.
♪ She moved like the ocean ♪
♪ Keepin' the rhythm,
The rhythm naturally ♪
♪ Hittin' every emotion ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ L-E-T-S-G-O ♪
BOY: Oh!
Hot!
♪ Let's go, let's go ♪
BOY: Hotter.
Yeah!
♪ Go get it, L-E... ♪
Hi, Uncle August.
- No, I'll get the paper.
- UNCLE AUGUST: Thank you, Clare.
♪ Let's go, let's go ♪
♪ Go get it, get it ♪
(CAR APPROACHING )
(HONKING AND TIRES SKIDDING)
BOY: Go get off the road, winner!
I'm trying to drive here!
(OTHERS LAUGH)
(CAR ACCELERATING)
(GROAN)
Ow!
Oh, gosh...
Are you alright?
Yeah, you know. It's...
it's Monday.
Here you go.
- Thanks
- Yeah.
See you around.
(CROWS CAWING)
(STUDENTS CHATTING AND LAUGHING)
(SIGHING)
DAD: I'll check these. See if there's...
You've gotta be kidding me.
Come on!
GIRL: Check it out.
(STUDENTS CHATTING AND LAUGHING)
CLARE: Dad!
You serious?
What'd I do now?
You promised that you wouldn't
do this at my school.
We're not at your school.
CARL: We're across the street
from your school.
Yeah, but people can still see you.
Well, who the hell's watching?
BOY: Yeah, her dad's
a dumpster driver.
Hey, what happened there?
I fell at Uncle August's house,
he saw the whole thing.
What did I tell you
about talking to Uncle August?
You said not to.
But I really don't see why.
Dad, you're killing me, okay?
Hey!
Come on, let's roll out, Shannon.
Thank you.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ You get so excited
by the prospect ♪
♪ Of a gentium way ♪
♪ So surprised by all the possibilities ♪
CLARE: So...
what do you guys think?
GIRL: So good.
- How long it take you?
- Ah, yeah, like weeks.
Clare, you try way
too hard, dude.
Jesus, it's better than
not trying at all.
- Will you guys help me hang it?
- GIRL: I got you.
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- Yeah, just give me one sec.
What is she doing?
It's called
Monster Mutant Slayer.
Dumbest game ever.
Hey! Don't mock what you
don't understand dude, okay?
If I kill Lurching Louisa
and Hacked-Up Harry
I level up to Mutant Killer.
And if I get Malformed Molly,
I'm a Monster Mutant Master, man!
I know. Awesome? Yes.
- (CAMERA CLICK)
- BOY: Got it.
- CLARE: Stop!
- BOY 2: Sorry. Don't mind him.
My bad.
Seriously? Bird ass!
Recycle first.
(CHUCKLES)
(GIRL WHISPERING) Recycle first.
BOY 2: Hey, Clare.
I liked your banner.
Yeah, I liked it too.
(SPEAKING CHINESE)
(CLASS SPEAKING CHINESE)
(TEACHER SPEAKING CHINESE)
(CROWS CAWING)
(METALLIC RATTLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Carl!
Look at this!
That would fetch
a ton at the swap.
I have a better idea.
(SINISTER RUMBLING)
- GIRL 1: Jesus, what's...
- GIRL 2: It's so bad.
- (CHUCKLING)
- GIRL 2: Put it away.
GIRL 2: I mean she's seriously smeggy.
Like ultimate smeggy.
- CLARE: I know!
- What was that?
Um...
nothing. No.
Um. Mm. But you were laughing.
Which is co-signing.
BLONDE GIRL: And we wanna know
what you were laughing about.
Go ahead.
Everyone's listening.
Okay.
GIRL: Clare, come on.
Go Clare. Yeah, do it.
What's so funny, winner?
Yeah, what's funny...
is that you're smegma.
But like...
ultimate smegma.
(ALL LAUGHING)
What does that even mean?
- Oh, Clare. I got it.
- Well..
Thank you.
Yeah, this is great. Um...
Smegma. It's a noun.
(CLEARING THROAT)
"A malodorous, opaque,
white or yellow substance
produced by the sebaceous glands
of male and female genitalia."
It's found beneath the foreskin and
glands of the penis in males,
and in the folds of skin surrounding
the clitoris in females.
(GASPING AND LAUGHING)
Oh, I... I...
I'm so sorry. Would you like me
to define "ultimate" for you?
(LAUGHING)
CROWD: Oooh!
Come on. Yeah.
GIRL 1: You got it, Clare!
GIRL: Get up! Get up!
(COUGHING IN PAIN)
(GROANING)
(ENRAGED YELLING)
GIRL 2: Beat her up, Clare!
Drop her like a red-headed baby
fresh out of the vagina!
(YELLING AND SCREAMING)
Get away from her!
Let her go!
Ooh!
(CROWD SHOUTING AND CHEERING)
(SHRIEKING AND GRUNTING)
(SHRIEKING)
Son of a bitch!
Get back here!
(GARBAGE DISPOSAL GRINDING)
What's in it?
It's broccoli, apple,
lemon and ginger.
'Cause we don't want
you to bruise.
You know what you need.
Please don't say it. Please.
A nice boy.
- You said it.
- Or a nice girl.
Come on, come on, come on.
You must like someone.
I do, but...
(SIGHING)
So what's his or her name?
Paul.
I think he said
hi to me once.
Well, that's something.
In the fifth grade.
CLARE: Hi, Max.
DAD: Hey.
There you go.
Man, you got the green stuff.
It's called "salad".
It's healthy and
you're welcome.
I got you a little
something, buddy.
It's up on your bed.
Dad, please...
we've talked about this already.
You've your space
- and then there's my space.
- I know!
I just found it at this fancy place.
It's got Chinese writing on it.
Figured since you're
taking Chinese...
If you don't want it,
Carl'll take it.
Shit, you're damn right.
(SIGHING)
Just consider it an
early birthday present.
CLARE: Come on, Max.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Whoa!
(RATTLING)
"Wishes...
seven."
♪ I see the lines
You try to hide from me... ♪
(PHONE BEEPS)
♪ And... ♪
♪ A little bit ♪
♪ Of my heart feels ♪
♪ Like we're all
messed up inside ♪
♪ And a little part,
Of the fear is gone... ♪
Of course that would happen.
♪ When you say goodnight... ♪
♪ These Night Lies
Ya little bit of my heart... ♪
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Seven wishes...
Why not?
(SIGHS)
I wish that...
Darcie Chapman,
would just...
(EXHALES)
I don't know, but just, like, go rot!
(MAX SCRATCHING AT DOOR)
Max?
- Come on! Come here!
- (MAX WHINES)
- Okay.
(MAX GROWLING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(METALLIC CLICK)
(CREAKING)
(OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIRRING AND TICKING)
(MOANING)
(WHIRRING)
(MOANING AND SIGHING)
(METALLIC CLICKING)
(BIRDSONG)
(GRUNTING)
(SNORING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Oh, my God!
- (SQUELCHING)
- Oh, my God.
(GASPING)
Oh, my God!
(OMINOUS CRESCENDO)
BOY: Darcie?
Darcie!
Oh! Ah!
- Oh, my God!
- DARCIE: Oh, my God!
GIRL 2: Necrotizing fasciitis.
- No!
- Yeah.
- What?
So apparently,
She-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named
picked up a case of
it at the spa.
And now she's at the ICU.
She might lose her toes, part
of her leg, and part of her face.
How sweet is that?
Ah, she's rotting!
Yeah.
Apparently Karma is a bigger
bitch than Darcie Chapman.
Who knew?
(GIRL CLEARS THROAT)
CLARE: Oh!
- It's for Darcie.
- Oh!
You said that like we should care.
Um, we're starting a GoFundMe.
(SIGHING)
Go fund this.
Yeah.
- Go on. Scooch. Bye.
- It's fine. It's fine.
- CLARE: Meredith.
- It's whatever.
- Oh, my God!
- You're proud.
(BELL RINGING)
- GIRL: I gotta go.
- All right.
Definitely have my
attention, lucky box.
(CAMERA CLICK)
Max, come here.
Max?
(BIRDSONG)
(DISTANT SOUNDS OF CHILDREN PLAYING)
Max? (KISSING SOUNDS)
Where are you? (WHISTLES)
(CLAPPING)
Max?
(KISSING SOUNDS)
- Ma...
- (CHAIN RATTLING)
Max, are you in there? Buddy?
Buddy?
You in there?
You know you're not
supposed to be down here.
Ow.
(OMINOUS MUSIC BUILDING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Max?
(SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(SQUEAKING)
Max!
(GRUNTING)
He was a good dog.
Mom gave him to me.
I know, buddy.
(BELL RINGING)
TEACHER: But the majority of the
characters are written in Ancient Chinese.
If you want an accurate translation,
you'll probably have to talk to a scholar.
- Got it. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
My cousin could hook it up.
Ancient Chinese is her thing.
She'd help you out, for a price.
I don't really have any money.
Who said anything about money?
He'll take a tit pic.
- Uh...
- And so will I.
- What?
- Um...
Never mind.
Sorry.
Offer still stands if
you change your mind.
- BOY: Dude, seriously?
- BOY 2: Just kidding.
MEREDITH: Hey guys,
do you feel that?
It's like the darkness
has been lifted
ever since Bitchface-Since-Birth
left the building.
GIRL: I heard they had to amputate
a few of her toes.
Sweet.
Guys, we shouldn't be
happy about this.
Clare, I never said
I was happy.
I'm freaking ecstatic, man!
Almost like being here.
(LAUGHS)
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SNIFFLING)
♪ Laying me down ♪
♪ Down on the floor ♪
♪ Waiting for a song to play ♪
♪ You keep on begging me for more ♪
♪ I love when you say my name ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me why ♪
♪ Were you trying to hide
From the fallout? ♪
♪ Someone tell me why
I'm on the other side ♪
♪ Is it countdown? ♪
♪ I'll wait up with you
I'll stay up ♪
I wish that
Paul Middlebrook
would fall madly in love with me.
♪ I'll wait up with you
I'll stay up with you ♪
♪ I'll wake up with you ♪
♪ You give it all,
you take it back ♪
♪ Why's it gotta feel so right? ♪
Oh!
Hey.
(METALLIC CLICKING)
(MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIRRING AND TICKING)
(WHIRRING)
(INAUDIBLE)
- Paul?
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
(GASPING)
- So I...
- Bell ringing.
I'll see you around Claire.
Yep!
Oh, my God. Oh, My God.
(WHIRRING AND OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC)
(METALLIC CLICKING)
TV PRESENTER: And now, this news
just coming in.
- A local resident...
- Hey.
...owner of the iconic
glass house estate in Gates Mills
- What's going on?
- August Anderson,
was found deceased in
his residence this afternoon.
CLARE: Are we going to the funeral?
Hey, as far as I'm concerned,
good riddance.
What's gonna happen to
all of his stuff?
If there's a will, trust me,
we ain't in it.
(SIGH)
Yeah.
Course not.
(METALLIC CLATTERING)
CLARE: Ow! Dammit, Dad! Come on!
- What?
- We don't have room for all of this crap!
Hey, hey, hey.
- CLARE: What?
- I'm going to use those.
What do you need these for, huh?
Dad, seriously.
You can't get rid of anything!
What would Mom say, huh?
Dad.
Dad! Are you listening to...
God!
You never listen to
anything I say!
(STOMPING ON STAIRS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
Come on.
I wish...
I wish that Uncle August
would leave me everything.
So there.
God, Clare, you're so stupid.
(PHONE RINGING)
Uh, thank you for calling.
What's going on, Dad?
You're never gonna believe this.
What?
Apparently, you weren't
cut out of his will.
How much do we get?
All of it, buddy.
No way.
Yes... way.
(EXHALES)
Yes!
Yes! Yes! What?
You're gonna...
- take the sax with us?
- Why not?
No, you just you haven't
played since mom...
You never know.
I'm so happy for you.
Sweetheart.
Come visit, or you'll
hurt my feelings.
- Of course.
- Okay.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
- Dad?
- Down here, bud.
- What are you waiting for? Get in!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God!
Call the girls.
♪ 'Cause all we ever wanted
Was to feel like this ♪
♪ All we ever wanted
All we ever wanted ♪
Was to feel like this ♪
♪ Feel like this
it's all we ever wanted ♪
♪ All we ever wanted ♪
Um, Clare, that thing is,
like, eight hundred dollars.
I know.
Yeah, so if you buy it,
you're an asshole.
Totally.
You want one?
No! Wait, I'm not that psycho shallow,
dude. Come on.
June?
I love you. You're my
bestest friend ever.
- Okay, let's go.
- Yeah, let's go.
Damn!
Peer pressure.
♪ All we ever wanted
Was to feel like this ♪
Out of the way, peasants.
♪ ... we ever wanted
All we ever wanted ♪
♪ All we ever wanted
Was to feel like this ♪
♪ Feel like this
it's all we ever wanted ♪
(CAMERA CLICKS)
- Bye, guys!
- BOTH: Bye!
(GRINDING)
(RATTLING NOISE)
(FAINT RATTLE)
(WHIRRING AND OMINOUS
ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(HISSING AND BUBBLING)
(MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(TICKING AND OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC)
(RATTLING NOISE)
Hmm...
(GRINDING SOUND)
(WHIMPERING)
(WAILING)
(MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRUNCHING)
(METALLIC CLICK)
(KNOCKING)
DAD: I found something you might like.
- CLARE: Yeah?
- Yeah.
They're your mother's.
I found them when I was
packing up our stuff.
Wow.
I forgot how good she was.
Where do you think
you get it from?
Some of these are so happy.
So was she.
Until she wasn't.
Why do you think she did it?
Buddy, I've been asking myself that
every single day for the last 12 years.
Still don't have an answer.
Do you think I'm like her?
Course you are.
No, no, no, sweetie, no.
Not like that.
What I mean is, you're smart and funny,
you don't take people's crap.
Well, statistically, if you have
a parent that committed suicide...
Clare, she was a good woman,
but she had a rough childhood.
And secrets, honey.
I think that...
I think maybe...
her secrets were too big
to live with and...
it was easier to just let go.
I'm sorry. Come here.
(SAXOPHONE PLAYING)
(OMINOUS RUMBLING)
(TICKING)
(MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(DISTANT OWL HOOTING)
(PANTING)
- GIRL: What are you talking about?
- PAUL: I'm just not into it any more.
It's not you... It's just...
GIRL: Are you breaking up with me?
PAUL: I can't date someone
I don't have feelings for.
Right.
Oh!
So, will you?
Will I, what?
Go out with me?
Look...
I know this is short notice but
Senior Scavenge is coming up,
I thought it would be fun if we went.
Paul, you just broke up
with your girlfriend.
Plus, I already have a team...
but thank you.
But, we can still go.
Yeah, I'll think about it.
- Yeah.
- (BELL RINGING)
Oh! Um...
I'll see you around.
(CHATTERING AND LAUGHING)
BOY: Nice.
SKATEBOARDER: Whoo!
- SKATEBOARDER: That's it.
- CLARE: Ryan!
What's the price?
Of?
Your cousin helping me
translate something.
Ah... well.
She's a slut for wontons.
Oh?
Done, yeah.
- When can we go?
- Let's go right now!
Awesome.
♪ Baby, I was so sad ♪
♪ Stuck on the couch ♪
So... I'm waiting.
For?
An apology. Been waiting for years.
CLARE: What did I do?
First grade. Sharing circle.
You farted.
I did not fart!
You farted and you blamed it on me
and everyone called me McFarts
until, like, the sixth grade.
I'm sorry.
Are you really?
Yeah.
Then apology accepted.
But maybe in the multiverse,
it never happened.
Or it did happen and you farted,
blamed it on me and
I got called McFarts.
Wait.
You dig on multiverses?
Yeah, I mean, the theory that,
you know, another you exists
in different circumstances
under different planes of reality,
yada, yada, yada.
Yeah, I dig.
Well, maybe in the multiverse,
neither of us farted.
Maybe we're even dating.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
(DOOR CREAKING)
Hey, Gina, it's me.
Let me up.
(DOOR BUZZES)
This.
Bitchin'.
CLARE: Yeah, I don't
know anything about it.
And I can't...
I can't really read
what it says, but...
Can you open it?
Well, it looks like a
version of a Chinese Wish Pot.
They're pretty common actually.
You take a piece of paper,
write down your wish,
put it in the pot,
and wait for it to come true.
Let's see. This one.
It's heavy.
Okay, it promises to
grant seven wishes.
And there are rules.
"Lay your hands upon me."
I guess you have to be touching it
to make a wish?
"Abandon, lose, or sell me and
all your wishes will be undone."
GINA: Huh.
Yeah, and what does...
What does this say?
That is not a word.
It's a name.
"Lu Mei"?
"The legend of Lu Mei."
"In 1910, bubonic plague swept
through mainland China.
Lu Mei and her family were suspected
of being infected
so they were
quarantined in a train car
where they died of heat stroke
and dehydration.
Lu Mei was the only survivor.
Local legend says she took the only
valuable thing the family owned,
a music box, and went to a temple
to pray for revenge.
She prayed for
seven days and seven nights
and on the seventh night,
a Yaoguai answered."
"Yaoguai"?
A demon of the Chinese persuasion.
GINA: If you believe in that sort of thing.
It says, "Lu Mei became very wealthy
and her enemies were vanquished.
In 1922, she died.
Suicide.
Opium."
Romantic.
RYAN: So...
what do these numbers
mean on the bottom?
I have no idea.
A mystery.
Um... It also says,
"When the music ends..."
something happens.
Like?
I don't know. It could be
a few different things but
my guy Mike at UWA,
he's pretty smart, so
I will let you know
what he says.
- CLARE: Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Here, get this.
- Thanks.
All right. Well, me and my 'tons
need some time alone.
I prefer to destroy
them in private.
Need anything else?
- No. We're out.
- GINA: Cool.
- It was great to meet you.
- GINA: You too.
Thanks.
Hey, hey.
She's cute.
Ask her out.
I'm trying.
- Good luck.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- Bye!
- GINA: Bye.
Aww.
Mmmm... Yum!
♪ Drive... ♪
What's up?
Nothing. I just...
I feel like Lu Mei's box...
- God!
- RYAN: Whoa.
(WHISTLE)
CARL: Good stuff in here.
CLARE: Dad, what are you doing?
Wha... What are you talking about?
I'm just hanging out with Carl,
picking up some stuff.
Dad, we live in a fricking mansion.
What else do you need?
Clare.
- It's not a big...
- No, forget about it.
♪ Just keep... ♪
♪ Keep me coming... ♪
You didn't see that.
No. Totally didn't see your dad
digging through the trash at all.
(SIGHS)
I wish that my Dad would just...
just stop being so embarrassing.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(THUNDER)
♪ Yo girl, colder than an ice cube ♪
♪ Yo girl, always got an attitude ♪
Mike, you are one prompt bastard.
♪ I ain't worried 'bout nothin', glitter
On my skin, makin' all the boys look ♪
Oh, well, that's messed up.
(TICKING AND WHIRRING)
(THUNDER)
(SIGHS)
Great.
You gotta be kidding me.
Ryan.
(THUNDER)
(OMINOUS WHIRRING AND TICKING)
(LOUD MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(SAXOPHONE MUSIC PLAYING)
Can I say something
totally inappropriate?
Sure, go for it.
Your dad is, like...
serious hot sauce.
Like Sriracha hot.
(THUNDER)
Yes!
Yo, it's Ryan. Leave a message.
Hey, it's Gina.
I got that translation for you and...
- it's messed up.
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
Fuck! Um...
it's so messed up, it's actually
beginning to freak me out.
So, ah, call me back
as soon as you can and...
- (THUNDER CRASH)
- (GASPING)
(PHONE CLATTERS)
(GASPS)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(LIGHTS FIZZLING AND TINKLING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(STRANGLED GASPING AND SICKENING CRUNCH)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(METALLIC CLICK)
Hey, Gina, it's me.
Let me up.
Hello?
(FAINT RINGING)
(RINGING TONE)
Gina!
Gina?
No. No, no, no, no!
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
- PAUL: Oh, hey. How you doing?
- Good. How are you?
- I'm well. Where you going?
- Um...
just the class that
we're in together.
Oh, yeah.
Duh! I'll walk you there.
- Sounds great. Thanks.
- (BELL RINGING)
- RYAN: Clare!
- Oh, hey, I'll see you at class.
- PAUL: Okay. Sounds good.
- Ryan, where have you been?
Is everything okay?
Can I ask you something?
It's gonna sound so...
stupid and so crazy but, um...
You know that wish box
your dad got you?
Have you made any wishes?
- What? Why?
- So, have you wished?
Why do you keep
asking me that?
Why don't you answer?
Has it played any music yet?
Ryan, who cares?
I...
"A blood price."
That phrase Gina couldn't
quite translate.
It says...
"When the music ends,
the blood price is paid."
Um...
tell her I said thanks.
What? What is it?
Ah, she's, uh...
She's dead, Clare.
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry.
When did...
A few nights ago.
I don't even know
what to say...
Did it play its music then?
(BELL RINGING)
I don't know what
you're talking about.
How'd you get to live
in that mansion, again?
We're gonna be late for class, Ryan.
Are you coming?
Have you?
Clare!
TEACHER: We're going to be studying
southern China, the area of Guangzhou.
First we're going to start
with the northernmost state...
(CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
Clare!
Come join us.
- Um, Paul...
- Okay.
Oh, did that just happen?
I think so.
- GIRL: Oh, oh.
- BOY: Oh! Burn.
Still a nobody.
How's it feel, winner?
BOY: We're outta here.
Haters gonna hate.
There's not much
you can do about it.
(PHONE BEEPS)
I wish that I was the
most popular girl in school.
Yeah. That'd be awesome.
(PHONE BEEPS)
♪ You wake the wild-hearted rebel in me ♪
♪ I know that without a doubt
I know that without a doubt ♪
♪ I feel, I feel the love ♪
♪ Wake up, such a beautiful thing? ♪
(INAUDIBLE)
♪ Wake up, such a beautiful thing?
Wake up, such a beautiful thing? ♪
♪ The way we move
Like we runnin' this place ♪
♪ Come out swingin', baby
Right out the gate ♪
♪ I know that without a doubt
I know that without a doubt ♪
PAUL: You coming with me, right?
- Where?
- Senior Scavenge.
- Yes.
- Finally. Say it again.
Yes.
- What?
- Nothing.
I was trying to think of something
dope to say before I kissed you.
That wasn't it.
♪ This path is difficult we travel on ♪
♪ Knowing when it's time to move along ♪
♪ No we can't stay in the same place ♪
♪ Where the light fades away
A little every day ♪
♪ Take the good and hold it near to you ♪
(MUSIC FADING)
(HAUNTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(ROPE CREAKING)
(HAUNTING MUSIC GETS LOUDER)
(CREAKING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
Hey!
Hey! Wait, hey!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello?
Who are you?
- (BRANCH CRACKS)
- (SCREAMS)
- DAD: Clare.
- Oh!
What's going on?
Nothing. I just...
Um...
I think that
someone's following me.
- What? Since when?
- Um...
Since I got the music box.
(KNOCKING)
Mrs. Deluca, are you home?
It's Clare.
Mrs. Deluca?
Ugh!
(GASPS)
(COUGHS)
Hello?
(FLIES BUZZING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
Hey. What's up?
- GIRL 1: So cute.
- GIRL 2: Beyond cute.
I don't know, Clare.
Why don't you go ask
your new friends?
I mean, seriously,
I don't get it.
Why is everyone so
into you lately?
You're not that special.
Truth.
Hey.
What's wrong?
(SIGHS)
I need to talk to you
guys about something.
I don't know what's
going on and...
I don't know
what to do.
This is it?
Don't... kick... that!
Don't do that! Okay?
Will someone say something?
All right.
I mean, have you ever
heard of coincidence?
- Oh, my God!
- That's all this is, Clare.
Coincidence.
JUNE: Yeah, Clare. I don't know.
I'm telling you,
I don't think so. I really don't.
You wanna know what
I think, Clare?
Yeah.
I think you're a selfish
bowl of bitch sauce.
If I had seven wishes,
you know what I'd have done?
I would have wished
for world peace
and I would cure cancer.
I mean, you've used four whole wishes.
- Five wishes.
- Five whole wishes already.
And you didn't wish for anything
for me and June.
Nothing. We're your best friends.
Come on! Like, you didn't think, like...
"Oh, well, I know Meredith wants
an internship at Everest Games
- and June wants to get into Brown."
- You don't believe in this anyway!
- So?
- Guys, are you serious?
Do you think that if...
if I believed this from
the very beginning
that I wouldn't have
wished for my mom to...
over you guys? I...
JUNE: It's okay. Say it.
Nothing.
Nothing. I just...
I don't...
think that I should
be wishing anymore.
I think you should
throw it away.
Doesn't that make
the most sense?
- Just get rid of it.
- Yeah.
It says if I get rid of it,
all of my wishes will be undone.
But if you really think
people have died...
aren't you a bad person if you keep it?
(PHONE BEEPS)
Yeah. By "bad person"
June means, "psycho bitch."
MEREDITH: Oh!
Nauseating Norma's outside,
and I'm so over this conversation.
Just throw it away.
You'll feel so much better.
I mean, it hasn't really worked.
I still feel miserable.
JUNE: Toss it and it's done.
You won't have to worry about it anymore.
(SAXOPHONE MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ I been up all night thinkin'
'Bout what we got in store tonight ♪
♪ It's about to be a celebration
Ain't no fakin' ♪
PAUL: I'll be right back.
- I'm gonna get us some cotton candy.
- Okay.
♪ Let you know ♪
♪ Ain't no fear we letting go ♪
- MEREDITH: Clare, hi.
- Hi.
Check this out.
Junie and I are still alive, dude.
- Go figure, right.
- Okay.
Just ignore her, Clare.
So, did you do it?
Did you throw it away?
Yeah, right after you guys left.
- JUNE: Cool.
- PAUL: Come on!
Hey, where you guys going?
The hunt's about to start.
Yeah. We'll be right back.
Hurry up.
Okay, be right back.
- Okay.
- Kids, man.
♪ Lightning in the fire ♪
♪ Somehow it always feels
Like the first time ♪
Wait, hang on. Paul, stop.
CLARE: Ow.
What's this?
Nothing.
Let me see your phone.
Now, or I'm out.
They're just pictures of you.
You're even cute when you're sleeping.
(CHUCKLE)
You've been spying on me.
- Well, yeah.
- What is wrong with you?
Are you mad?
Yes, I'm mad.
You're smokin'
when you're mad.
I think maybe that
we need a break.
I don't.
I was just trying to be nice.
Paul, I'm breaking up with you.
- I gotta get out of here.
- Clare, wait.
This isn't over. Clare!
(OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Where is she?
It's about to start.
(SCREAMING)
What? No.
Hey, what happened?
Junebug almost just got
barbecued and I saved her.
MEREDITH: Hey, got ninja, right?
Ow-wah.
(FIREWORKS EXPLODING)
Wait, guys. I just
got the first clue.
- Okay, let's go.
- Come on, let's go.
Hey, buddy. It's Dad.
I got a gig outside town so
I'm gonna be home around midnight. Okay?
I love you.
- (LOUD BANG)
- (TIRE SCREECH)
Shit!
- MEREDITH: Come on.
- JUNE: Are you sure?
Yeah, of course I'm sure.
Look.
- What goes up, must come down.
- CLARE: Yes.
You get it? Alright.
Come on, guys,
let's get this selfie.
Boom. Five down, five more to go.
Saxon's goin' down tonight.
- All right, where to next?
- (PHONE BEEP)
Oh oh oh!
- Holy... ballsack.
- What?
Malformed Molly's
in the building.
Twenty-sixth floor. I gotta go.
Are you kidding me?
Don't hate. Don't hate.
Meredith! Come on!
Clare! Just give me
five minutes, alright?
And when I'm back,
Monster Mutant Master. Right here.
Dammit.
I didn't do it.
Do what?
The box. I still have it.
I couldn't throw it away.
That's messed up, Clare.
I know.
I tried, I just... I couldn't do it.
(REVVING ENGINES)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(CRACKLES)
(SCREAMS)
Aw man! I'm the shit!
(SIGHS)
Great!
Shit.
(ELEVATOR PINGS)
(GRUNTS)
(CREAKING)
(MECHANICAL SCREECH)
(PHONE RINGS)
- Meredith?
- Hey. Um...
Clare, I'm stuck, okay?
Please get someone to help me.
I'm stuck in this stupid elevator.
Uh...
Yeah, sure.
(GRUNTS)
(CREAKING)
Argh.
(OMINOUS HORN SOUNDS)
(CREAKING)
(GRUNTS)
Crap!
(SCREECHING TIRES)
(SLAMMING)
(ELEVATOR PINGS)
Hey, um, never mind.
(PINGING)
(SCREAMING)
Dammit!
No!
Clare!
Meredith!
- Meredith!
- (ELEVATOR PINGS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(WHIRRING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
This is your fault.
All your fault.
Hey, come on.
No.
Come on. Let's get
you outta here.
Come on.
You know the number on the box
that we couldn't figure out?
Well, I did.
It's a military ID number belonging to
an airman by the name of Arthur Sands.
That's him.
He was stationed in China
at the end of World War ll.
A few years later he opened up a
very successful car dealership in Jersey.
He lost his best friend
in a freak accident.
Here's the kicker.
That's him six months later.
Oh, my God!
After his suicide,
his wife was institutionalized.
She swore a music box
had destroyed her family.
In the last five years or so...
the box resurfaced again in Cleveland,
with a man named Lawrence Hart.
He wins the lottery, marries his high
school sweetheart and has two daughters.
A perfect life.
Until people around
him start dying off.
His daughters drowned,
his wife died in a car accident
and Hart lost his mind.
He barricades himself in his house and
that's where he dies, in a massive fire.
You know what's weird?
What's left of his estate is
a few blocks from your house, Clare.
There was another phrase on the box
I don't think you saw.
It was a warning.
"After seven wishes,
the Yaoguai claims the soul."
(SCREAMS)
That's its final price.
(PHONE BEEPS REPEATEDLY)
- Hey.
- What?
How many wishes
have you made?
I've made five wishes.
Jesus, Clare.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I'm sorry, but...
"But" how is there a "but?"
People are dead!
It was just nice to be
normal for a while.
That's your excuse?
What'd you wish for, anyway?
- That nice house?
- No.
Oh now, bullshit! People are dead, Clare.
You can't just wish that away.
You can't take that back.
I know, and I said I was sorry.
I didn't know that any
of this would happen.
Know what I wish?
I wish I never met you.
That's what I wish.
It's my fault. And I know that
I have to get rid of it.
Will you please help me?
Please, Ryan?
(SIGHS)
Okay, let's do it.
Okay.
(METALLIC CLANG)
(YELLS)
Bitch!
(PANTS)
She was my best friend, Clare.
I'm sorry.
(FAINT TINKLING)
(SCREAMS)
What are you doing here?
PAUL: Why haven't you answered my texts?
You need to leave right now.
What if I said...
I don't want to live without you.
And I don't want you...
to live without me.
Please. Just, just leave.
- So, we're done?
- Oh, my God!
Yes.
(GASP)
I love you, Clare.
(SCREAMS)
RYAN: Where is it?
CLARE: What, what do you mean?
I don't know.
It's...
I don't know. It was
right there last night.
It was right in there. I...
Oh...
What does that mean?
I...
Maybe it's done with you.
Maybe it's over.
Well, what now?
What would I do? What...
You move on with your life.
You can do it.
That's easy to say, Ryan.
No, it's easy to wish.
I liked it.
I liked having it.
It made me feel special.
Is there anything you wished for
that you can't live without?
- No.
- See, you don't need it.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
Dad?
What's going on?
Well, it was fun
while it lasted.
It's unbelievable. I mean, who forgets
to pay their taxes for ten years?
Your mother's
crazy Uncle August.
Well, here we are.
Home sweet home.
♪ You're a curse
A disease, and I caught it ♪
♪ Like a drug, slowly pulsing ♪
Happy birthday, Clare.
♪ And I don't want it anymore ♪
♪ My feet on the dash, take a drag ♪
♪ I go round ♪
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
♪ Wondering why you don't gain ♪
♪ I'll stay this way for longest way ♪
Recycle first.
Gross.
Mmmm, hot.
♪ You're going somewhere,
You're going nowhere ♪
♪ They're always telling you,
You're going somewhere ♪
♪ You're going nowhere ♪
♪ You're going somewhere,
You're going nowhere ♪
♪ They're always telling you ♪
♪ You're going somewhere,
You're going nowhere ♪
You stole it?
You couldn't get rid of it.
You saw what it did to Meredith.
I'm just trying to
protect you, okay?
Okay, so you think
that you can control it.
You think you can, Clare?
Really?
Are you crazy?
Why would you bring it here
in the first place?
'Cause I have two
little sisters at home.
Give it back. Right now.
After everything that's happened?
Yes, June.
What's wrong with you?
No! Clare, no, stop it. Clare!
You see what it's done.
This is a bad idea.
- June, go away.
- Stop, listen to me! Just stop!
Clare, come on! No, no, no.
Clare, come here.
- Just give it to me, Clare. Stop.
- Let go, June!
- Let go! Let go!
- RYAN: Clare?
- RYAN: Clare!
- JUNE: No!
June?
June? Is she going to be okay?
What is wrong with you?
Clare?
- Go away!
- I thought we were done with this.
I'm not ready yet.
You can't keep it.
You know that.
- You have to get rid of it!
- You don't understand.
I'm not ready yet!
What about everything
we talked about?
I won't wish anymore, okay?
Okay, it'll be fine.
I just won't wish.
I'm gonna hang on
to it for a while.
Clare, please, you're
not hearing yourself.
You can't control it.
It's controlling you!
Go away! Okay?
Please go away.
I have two wishes left
and if you do not go away,
I will use one on you,
I swear I'll use it on you.
Go away!
You can't keep running from this!
I know, I know what to do.
(PHONE RINGS)
I know, I know what to do,
I know when to... Okay.
Okay.
(PHONE STILL RINGING)
If I had... No.
If I just don't make any more wishes,
everything will be fine.
(HYSTERICAL LAUGHTER)
Everything will be fine.
DAD: Clare? School just called.
(PHONE RINGS)
DAD: Clare? What's going on?
Get down here!
Okay.
I have two wishes left.
Two wishes.
I wish my mother never
committed suicide.
Oh, God.
(KNOCKING)
MOM: Clare?
(DOOR OPENS)
Mom?
I missed you so much!
You missed me so much? What?
TWINS: Happy birthday!
We got you cake!
- Sssh!
- And presents!
Okay, come on. What's the holdup?
Downstairs, kiddo. Chop-chop.
(DREAMLIKE MUSIC PLAYING)
Al'right. Here it is.
TWINS: Yay!
♪ Happy birthday... ♪
Happy birthday, kiddo.
Thank you, Dad.
Make a wish.
MOM: Clare?
I'm up here.
Come open your presents.
Okay.
(BELL TOLLS)
Mommy! Come on, Max!
(ROPE CREAKS)
(SCREAMS)
This is your fault.
Everything is your fault.
Oh, my God!
(OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
What?
(MUSIC BOX MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHAIN SAW ENGINE REVVING)
No. No!
Yeah, right there is good.
- Yeah.
- CARL: You think so, man?
No, no, no, no!
Dad! Dad!
- CLARE: Dad!
- (INTENSE CHAINSAW DRONING)
- Dad!
- (SQUELCHING)
(STRANGLED SCREAM)
- CARL: Oh, my God! My God!
- No!
CARL: Jon!
No...
CLARE: Argh!
- No!
- Are you...
What happened?
Are you...
MOM: Jonathan! No!
MOM: No! No!
(MOM SCREAMING)
(GROWLS)
I've got one wish left.
I know how to beat you!
I wanna go back!
I wanna go back before I got you!
I wanna go back.
My final wish is I wanna go back
to the morning my dad found you.
I wanna go back right now!
(GASPING)
- (MAX WHINES)
- Max?
Hi, Max!
Mmm... hi.
Oh, who's a good boy!
(KEYS JINGLING)
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait. Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Wait! Hang on, hang on!
MEREDITH: I'm not awake right now.
- What do you want?
- Nothing. Hi.
I just wanted to, you
know, hear your voice.
Seriously? You don't need a kidney
or some ridiculous words of wisdom?
- No, I just, no...
- Alright, you know
- I'm gonna go back to sleep, okay? Night!
- Okay, okay.
Dad!
- Hey!
- Hey. What's all this?
Um, nothing. I just... um I was just
wondering if I could go with you guys.
You know, like old times.
- Yeah. Get in.
- Awesome.
Sure, it'll be like old times.
Be our good luck charm.
MRS. DELUCA: Aw, you look so nice.
(SINISTER RUMBLING)
Clare, you find anything?
I found...
I found these. I don't know
what you could use them for.
Maybe around the house?
I don't know, they're kind of neat.
- Yeah, I can do something with these.
- Yeah?
Hey, Carl. Check it out.
Told you my kid has an eye.
You always were my good luck charm.
You gotta come with us again.
Yeah, maybe I will.
I have to get to school,
but have fun today. Love you.
Love you too, buddy.
- CLARE: Yeah, thank you so much.
- CARL: You got it.
RYAN'S FRIEND: Let's go buddy.
CLARE: Ryan! Ryan, hey.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Uh, sure.
Okay, um...
First off, I just wanted to say, um...
I'm sorry for the whole McFarts thing.
Wait. What? Really?
Yeah. Um...
But you know what, maybe in the
multiverse, that didn't happen.
- Hold on, you dig on multiverses?
- Yeah.
And, also, maybe in the multiverse,
we're really good friends.
Maybe... we're even dating.
Well... have we done it?
No, not yet.
I have also met your cousin, Gina.
Hung out in her loft and everything.
Okay, you're freaking me out right now.
Yeah, good.
'Cause I need a favor.
Okay, this is gonna sound crazy but...
please don't open this.
Just... just bury it. No shortcuts.
Uh... okay.
What's in it for me?
Dinner, if you want?
And maybe we could talk more
on this whole multiverse thing?
Yeah, and you can tell me how you
know my cousin and that she has a loft.
- Done.
- Cool.
Dude!
(LAUGHS)
I'll see you around.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(SHOUTING, SCREAMING)
I didn't see her.
I just didn't see her.
(OMINOUS ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC GETS LOUDER)
♪ Be careful what you wish for
Be careful what you wish for ♪
♪ Dreams as big as diamonds ♪
♪ Your pulse is getting silent, yeah ♪
♪ Be careful what you wish for
Be careful what you wish for ♪
♪ Reckless hearts feel so alive ♪
♪ Glitter shines like diamonds ♪
♪ No hesitation all the time ♪
♪ We are thunder, we are lightning ♪
♪ Here it comes 1000 volts
Get ready here we go ♪
♪ Rocking up on top the skies ♪
♪ Be careful what you wish for
Be careful what you wish for ♪
Seven wishes?
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Do you believe it?
Do you believe it? ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Do you believe it?
Do you believe it? ♪
♪ I tell you sugar sugar,
I knew this all along ♪
♪ You come around to date me
Come on strong ♪
♪ The feeling that you get
When someone fills your head ♪
♪ Imagination running wild
With every single day ♪
♪ When you fall in love
You fall harder than most ♪
♪ Is there any other way to go? ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Is there any other way to go? ♪
♪ Were you surprised? ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Do you believe it?
Do you believe it? ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Do you believe it?
Do you believe it? ♪
♪ Oh, my God ♪
♪ Were you surprised? ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Do you believe it?
Do you believe it? ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Here we are ♪
♪ Do you believe it?
Do you believe it? ♪
♪ Oh, my God ♪
Improved & Synced by BanglarBagh