Original subtitles by Sud_Arun
Colored and Improved by zer0_
(CROWD CHEERING)
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
PRESIDENT CARTER:
Exactly three years ago,
promised you a president
who feels your pain
and who shares your dreams.
I wanna talk to you about
a fundamental threat
to American democracy.
For the first time
in the history of our country,
a majority of
our people believe
that the next five years
will be worse
than the past five years.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
Shit.
(PA SYSTEM BEEPS)
(ON PA) Howdy, folks.
Apologize for the delay.
We’re number 11
for takeoff.
We'll try to make it up
in the air.
Just wake me up
over Texas.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
ON RADIO CONTINUES)
(BEEPING)
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
BARRY: (ON PA) Apologies
from the flight deck.
Just a little bit
of turbulence.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
BARRY: Thank you all
for flying TWA tonight.
Welcome to Baton Rouge.
ANNOUNCER: (ON RADIO)
The people '5 choice...
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
...and for you history buffs,
is in Louisiana...
(COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
BARRY: Hey, Luce.
Um, back here.
(EXHALES)
(MUSIC CONTINUES ON RADIO)
(SCOFFS)
BARRY: Thank you
for flying TWA.
Welcome to Vancouver.
Welcome to Bakersfield.
Welcome to Denver.
(BABY CRYING)
JIMMY: I hope they put us up
at the Holiday Inn tonight.
Those little
cocktail gals
are on fire.
Soon as they see
a man in uniform,
panties come off.
(JIMMY CHUCKLES)
(HUMMING)
About that landing
in Detroit.
Oh, man.
It was gusty that day.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
WOMAN: One in Kentucky.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Thanks, Bobby.
Hey. Chivas on the rocks.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING
CONTINUES)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Barry.
What was that?
Barry Seal.
That's right.
You have a drop off
and pick up service here
every other Thursday.
Cuban exiles.
They pay
commercial pilots to smuggle
homegrown contraband
through Canadian hubs.
Vancouver, Montreal.
Right?
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you‘re talking about.
No?
No.
You‘re smuggling cigars.
You have
an interesting
file, Barry.
"File"?
Starts off with a bang.
Top of your class in
the Civil Air Patrol.
Youngest pilot
in TWA history.
You were going places.
(CHUCKLES)
What is going on here?
Revolution's in the air,
Barry.
Central America, right now.
We're building nations
down there, Barry.
We‘re building nations.
It's America at
its fucking finest.
And we could use
someone like you.
(LAUGHING)
Goddamn.
You're CIA.
Shh.
(LAUGHING)
Holy shit.
BARRY: Hot damn!
Look at her.
MONTY: Well, they,
uh, they tell me
she's pretty fast.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's the fastest
twin-engine on the planet.
Mmm.
I mean, shit!
She looks like she's going
300 miles an hour
just sitting there.
(LAUGHS)
CIA owns this?
No. No.
Uh, Independent
Aviation Consultants.
IAC.
Yeah.
Well, what is that?
What do they call them?
One of them front groups?
Is that...
No, no, no.
It's as real as IBM.
Uh-huh.
You‘d run the company,
but after hours,
you work for us.
Yeah.
Takes pictures?
Mmm.
We say it
"collects intelligence."
Uh-huh.
(LAUGHING)
Where? Russia?
Uh...
South of the border,
north of the equator.
Let's just say, uh,
"enemies of democracy."
Look, the real work is covert.
You understand? So...
(LAUGHS) "Covert."
So, uh, anyone
finds out about it,
uh, family, friends,
even Lucy.
It's Lucy, right?
Yeah, that's right.
That'd be a problem.
What?
All this is legal?
If you're doing it
for the good guys, yeah.
(LAUGHS)
Just don't get caught.
(CHUCKLES)
You wanna take
her for a spin?
Fuck it! Take her
for a fucking spin!
(LAUGHS)
I want you to
take her for a spin.
(LAUGHING)
It's all for me.
Mmm-hmm.
It's new business.
It's gonna be my business.
Okay.
Logistical support
for airports.
That's right.
Okay. And you're
calling it IAC?
What do you know
about business?
You are
a TWA airline pilot.
That's how you
support this family.
This is gonna be
good for us, all right?
What about benefits?
Our healthcare?
We have great
healthcare with TWA.
(STAMM ERS) That's...
You know, I'm sure
that's not gonna
be a problem.
And what the hell
does IAC mean, anyway?
Independent
Aviation Consultants.
Well, that sounds
fuckin' made up, Barry.
It does?
BARRY: Flight controls
free and correct.
Warning and
enunciator lights.
Check on that.
Anti-skid lights.
That‘s off.
Landing gear.
Handle's down.
Three green.
Speed brake lever.
Stowed.
Thrust levers.
Cut off.
Engine start levers.
Slap trim
cut-off switches.
Normal.
Fire warning system?
(ALARM RINGS AND STOPS)
Check.
Radius
transponder radar?
Barry?
Radius transponder radar?
Yeah. Check, check.
Rudder, aileron trim?
Zero, zero.
Windows?
Closed.
Flight attendant briefing?
Yeah.
Barry?
You're gonna be
all right, Jimmy.
Where are you...
Where are you going?
Barry! Barry,
where are you going?
BARRY: (CHUCKLES)
Shit! I know, I know.
That was bold.
I do tend to leap
before I look.
Maybe, uh...
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Maybe I should have asked
a few more questions.
Anyway, it was back
in '78 and, uh...
It was September? October.
Anyway, it, uh...
That was the day
I joined the CIA.
Now, in those days,
the Cold War
was in full swing.
The Soviets were
backing communist
insurgents
all over Central America.
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLING)
And the CIA wanted snaps
of them insurgents.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(GUNS FIRING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
CIA OFFICIAL: Now, these
pictures are sensational.
Who's responsible?
They're mine.
GARY: Hey, Monty?
Yeah.
Go fuck yourself.
(GUNS FIRING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(BULLET RICOCHETS)
Whoa!
Oh, shit!
(ENGINE STALLING)
Come on, now.
(LAUGHING)
Fuck!
Whoo!
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
AN N OU N CE R:
The people's choice.
(LUCY MOANING)
MONTY: So, uh...
So then I show him this one.
And he goes,
"God damn it, Schafer,
I didn't ask for mug shots."
(LAUGHING)
I mean, they say
they're the best
reconnaissance photos
they have ever seen.
Does this mean
I get a raise?
You‘re doing great.
Hey, you got
a family, Schafer?
DOCTOR: Big push!
(SCREAMS)
Motherfucker!
(BABY CRIES)
Wife? Kids?
See, I, Uh...
I didn't tell Lucy
I ain't working
for TWA no more.
You‘re serving
your country.
I am gonna need
some more money
at some point.
You'll figure it out.
Oh. Uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
We, uh...
We're sending you
to Panama tomorrow.
BARRY: The CIA was so
happy with my work,
they gave me another job.
Bagman.
See, there was this colonel
down in Panama
named Noriega.
And he was selling
the agency's intel
on all the commies down there.
For your friends.
BARRY: Myjob wasjust
to drop off and pick up.
Just drop off
and pick up.
ANNOUNCER: (ON RADIO)
Right here in Baton Rouge.
You're listening to
the best Louisiana music.
BARRY: Hey, Luce,
pancakes are up.
LUCY: Thanks, baby.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Ho/a.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
In the car.
(HORNS BLARING)
(SIREN WAILING)
Hey, uh...
A donde vamos, fellas?
(MILD MUSIC PLAYING)
(OCHOA SPEAKS SPANISH)
Welcome.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Come on up.
Thank you for
coming to see me.
Sir, I... Ithink
there's been some sort
of mistake here, because I...
These fellas just
picked me up
at the airport, and...
No, no. No mistake.
Just, please, have a seat.
Coffee, Mr. Seal?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
You know my name?
You're the gringo
who flies to Central
America every week
taking pictures very low
with your fancy plane.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, yeah,
I mean, uh,
those photos...
See, l have a, uh...
Aviation company here
in South America that l...
Yes. Yes, the AIC.
IAC. Yes, sir.
Or is it CIA?
(CHUCKLING) What?
No...
No, no, no.
I'm just
a businessman here.
I'm a businessman.
Imports, exports,
cattle, horses.
But now...
Now, God above has blessed
this great country
with new riches, Mr. Seal.
And you could help us.
How's that?
You know the routes,
you can get in and
out of Estados Unidos
with your fancy plane.
What... What kind of riches
are we talking about here?
OCHOA: Cocaine, Mr. Seal!
We had a few
difficulties
getting our exports to
your country, Mr. Seal.
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)
Nine-nine-nine-six.
Ma'am, what's in the bag?
(BARKING)
We decided
to try new ideas.
We want you to
take off from here,
fly directly to Miami.
We'll pay you
$2,000 per kilo.
How much is a kilo?
2.2 pounds,
Mr. Seal.
BARRY: $2,000
every 2.2 pounds.
I... I'm sorry, fellas.
I didn't catch
y'all's names.
Jorge Ochoa.
Carlos Lehder.
Pablo Escobar.
A couple of billion dollars
from now,
they'd be known as
the Medellin Cartel.
Back then, they were
just three businessmen
trying to figure out
how to get
their merchandise
to the United States.
There was just
one small problem.
See, pilots,
they were killing themselves
trying to get off that runway.
| see you had a few other boys
try to make it outta here.
(CHUCKLES) SI, sI'.
Terrible pilots.
Yeah, well,
I'm sure they
were heavy, you know,
carrying a lot
of fuel to make it
to the States,
and merchandise, and...
Yeah, you know,
this airport, I mean,
it's high altitude
and a short runway.
And, I mean, shit, you got
trees and mountains
on both sides.
Is there, uh...
Is there somewhere else
I could take off from?
OCHOA: Nowhere the Army
wouldn't notice.
Well, uh...
Can you make
the runway longer?
(LAUGHS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(LAUGHING)
OCHOA: (IN ENGLISH) They say
I should get rid of you.
That you can't do it.
OCHOA: We have
our people in Miami.
BARRY: Yeah.
You‘re gonna land at
the Okeechobee airport
between 2:00 and 6:00 am.
BARRY: Look, there's, uh...
There's been
a change of plans,
'cause I ain't
landing in Miami in...
(ESCOBAR SPEAKS SPANISH)
Thank you. Gracias.
See, I ain't landing
anywhere with this stuff.
That's... That's how
y'all got in trouble.
Now, look,
just hear me out.
I know Louisiana.
Now, here's a map.
Now, I'm gonna drop
this stuff right where
"X" marks the spot.
All right?
Just... (GRUNTS)
What do you mean,
you're not gonna
land, huevon?
BARRY: Okay. Now, just...
Hey. Come here.
Look... Just look at this.
Look.
See right here?
See that there?
Hmm.
Right there is your
million-dollar door.
All right. You just
go around. Each side.
But tight.
No, no, no.
No more.
I said no more.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
But there's
plenty of room, gringo.
No, no, no.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Guys, guys, it ain't
about room, all right?
It's about weight.
Now, we agreed on 200,
I even put on 300.
No, no, no.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Keep pushing. Come on.
Need all the runway I can get.
Keep going. Keep going.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Hold! Hold!
Bien. Bien.
Gracias, gracias.
(IN ENGLISH) Oh, whoa.
Where the hell do you think
you're going, big fella?
Come on. Out.
He's gonna guard
our product.
(SIGHS)
This guy's fatter than fuck.
I'm already 1,500
pounds overweight.
Either I fly the big fella
or I fly your product.
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
IN SPANISH)
Good luck, hermano.
Christ will
keep you safe.
He ain't gonna make
this runway any longer.
Hey, Jorge.
Come here,
give me that.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(EXHALES)
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
(ALL CONTINUE
SPEAKING SPANISH)
Come on.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on!
(BEEPING)
(CONTINUES BEEPING)
Oh, Jesus!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(CHUCKLES) Whoo!
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(RADIO TUNING)
I've got a possible
target headed due north
25 miles offshore.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
That‘s platform 14.
One of Shell's helicopters.
You can disregard.
(BEEPS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MAN WHOOPS)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(LAUGHING)
(OCHOA SPEAKING SPANISH)
Cheers! Cheers!
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
Barry. (SPEAKS SPANISH)
Wow.
(LAUGHS)
For you.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Was that,
uh,VVednesday?
You want me to go...
He wants me to go
again on Wednesday?
Yes. Next Wednesday.
BARRY: Well, what about
the, uh, that runway?
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
Pablo! Jorge!
(ALL CONTINUE
SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GUNFIRE)
Oh... Whoa!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Wait here,
Barry. Wait here.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
BARRY: Are we running?
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
What...
What is that?
You want me to wait here?
Pablo?
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUNFIRE)
BARRY: Oh, God.
(MEN SHOUTING)
Don't shoot!
(SOLDIER SPEAKS SPANISH)
No, no, no.
SI, SI, SI, SI, SI.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(ALL CHEERING)
MONTY: Barry?
Barry Seal.
Schafer?
Barry Seal?
Yeah. No, no, no.
Oh, my God!
You look terrible.
It is so good to see you.
You missing a tooth?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
See these fellas
right here?
Yeah.
I think they
know that I am CIA.
You're not CIA.
You're a drug
smuggler, Barry.
Listen.
Louisiana PD was notified
of your arrest here.
They're gonna raid
your house at 6:00 am.
They're gonna pick up Lucy,
bring her in for questioning.
Maybe even keep
her overnight.
Oh, my God.
You gotta get
me out of here.
Well, maybe...
Maybe we could
figure something out.
BARRY: Okay, you can...
You can stop now ifyou want.
'Cause, believe me,
Shit gets crazy from here.
Do you remember
them fellas that
I told you I was
taking snaps of?
Turns out they was
a bunch of commies.
Called themselves Sandinistas.
These fellas managed
to get their shit together
and take control right here
in this little country
called Nicaragua.
Oh, no, that’s El Salvador.
Here you go. Nicaragua.
ANNOUNCER: Theirs is the
first successful revolution
in Central America.
BARRY: Now, that may have been
bad news for some people,
but not for me.
See, there was
a new sheriff in town.
My fellow Americans,
I must speak to you tonight
about a mounting danger
in CentralAmerica.
BARRY: Even after
everything that happened, I...
I still love Ronnie Reagan.
I mean,
any man that can make it
from that monkey movie
all the way to
the White House...
(BANGING)
What's the
matter with him?
BARRY: ...he's gotta know
What the hell he's doing.
And what he wanted was to kick
them commie Sandinistas
out of Nicaragua.
And he wanted the Nicaraguan
freedom fighters,
called Contras, to do it.
They need to know
that the U. S. supports them
with more than
just pretty words
and good wishes.
BARRY: But Congress,
well, they smelled
the makings of
another Vietnam,
and they outright refused
to let Ronnie have his war.
But do you think
them politicians
could tell
the Gipper what to do?
Hell no. He turned to the CIA,
and the CIA turned to me.
Schafer? Schafer,
that morning raid
on my family,
that's off now, right?
No, no. That's, uh...
That‘s still happening.
What?
6:00 am.
This fucking country!
Well, hold on, now.
Stop!
Now, we have a deal!
I'm not a cop, Barry.
I can't make
a search warrant
go away, you know?
Things are in motion here.
Come on, man.
What the hell
am I gonna do?
| suggest you get your
family outta Louisiana.
Well, where am I
supposed to take them?
We got a place for ya.
Mena.
Arkansas.
Arkansas?
BARRY: Hey.
Hey, Luce.
Mmm. Hey, baby.
Hey, hey, hey.
My God, baby,
what happened to you?
I'm okay.
Barry, you're
missing a tooth.
Hey, uh...
(CLOCK TICKING)
We‘re moving.
We gotta pack
everything up.
We gotta be outta here
before the sun comes up.
We, uh...
So, we'll get
these dresses and...
Do you, uh...
You need all them shoes?
Well, hey there, sunshine.
How you doing?
Now, look. I'm gonna
give you a plastic bag.
What I want you to do
is you go upstairs
and you put your
favorite toys...
Go on back to bed, honey.
Daddy done lost his mind.
No. Darlin',
you listen to Daddy.
You go do that
'cause we're
going on an adventure.
LUCY: No, we're not
Like the time we went
camping in the parish?
Not actually, but...
'Cause every adventure
is different.
Oh, my God.
You're actually
serious right now.
Barry, it's 4:00 am,
I'm not moving.
Christina's school
play is tomorrow.
Hey, do you trust me?
No!
But you love me.
You do love me.
Yeah, of course,
I fucking love you.
Then, listen,
we gotta move.
And we gotta get
outta here before
the sun comes up.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
(MUSIC CONTINUES ON CAR RADIO)
Look at that.
They got barbecue.
It's got a lot of charm.
This place has got
a lot of charm.
SHERIFF DOWNING:
Plenty. But all we got's
a porta-potty out back.
And I think that'd be cruel
and unusual punishment. Right?
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I'll be sure
to give 'em a good
what for on Monday, though.
All right?
CHRISTINA: Thank you.
BARRY: Front door's open.
(BABY CRYING)
(SHUSHING) It's okay.
That‘s... That's
an easy fix.
(HORN HONKING)
I gotta...
Get in. Come on.
Oh, shit.
We gotta make this quick.
She might leave me
before I get back.
So, this is all yours.
Including everything
between here
and your house.
Almost 2,000 acres.
What do you think?
I own all this?
Oh, yeah.
This whole airport?
Yeah. Congratulations.
MONTY: AK-47s.
Soviet-made for the PLO.
The Israelis captured these
and then secretly
traded them to us.
And you're gonna
fly 'em to Nicaragua.
You didn't say
nothing about guns.
It's a war, Barry.
Freedom fighters can't
put up much ofa fight
if they aren't armed.
This was the deal.
Or would you rather be
in a Colombian prison?
This is every current
law enforcement
invesﬁgauon
on the Gulf Coast.
FBI, ATF, DEA, Customs.
These maps will help
you avoid all of 'em.
Holy Shit.
You'd just fly
where they ain't.
Everything in
this hangar's mine?
Oh, yeah.
That truck's mine?
Mmm-hmm.
Tools are mine?
Yes, sir.
This airplane's mine.
Bag is mine.
What bag?
LUCY: lfed the kids.
They're Sleeping.
Unpacked the car.
That‘s good.
Fixed the sink.
Just a valve.
See? I told you
that was gonna be easy.
(GRUNTS)
Fuck, Barry!
Okay. All right.
All right. Okay.
I'm gonna come clean.
I don't work
for TWA no more.
No shit, Barry.
Are you going to prison?
No, ma'am. (CHUCKLES)
You've gotta take
care of this family.
'Cause I will take the kids.
I will go right
back to working
for Kentucky Fried Chicken.
Luce, what I'm
working on, it's...
Barry, I am six
months pregnant.
It's top secret.
I need a fridge.
I need beds
for our children.
I need a stove,
a fucking
washing machine...
Washing machine
over there, all right?
Now, let me just...
Is this all legal?
All right.
What I'm about to
tell you, you... You...
You gotta swear you
can't ever tell
anybody this, Lucy.
All right?
(WHISPERS) lam working
for the CIA.
(DOOR LOCK CLICKING)
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
IN SPANISH)
(MAN WHISTLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
BARRY: Ho/a.
Howdy, amigos.
I am here on
behalf of Uncle Sam.
(MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
BARRY: Look, Schafer,
I ain't no military expert,
but are you sure
these are the right guys?
'Cause they seemed
a damn sight more
interested in my boots
than in your guns.
MONTY: (OVER PHONE) Now, look.
This is getting big time.
Schafer, I just don't
think I'm the guy for this.
You just keep delivering
that pizza, hear me?
You just keep delivering.
(MEN SPEAKING SPANISH)
BARRY: Ho/a.
All right.
These are gifts.
All right? Gifts.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Back off. Off.
Amigos.
Now, these guns are
gifts from Uncle Sam.
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
I'm not fucking around.
(HORN BLARES)
Barry! Put the
bat down, huevdn.
We‘re all friends here.
Jorge.
What the hell
are you doing here?
OCHOA: This is
Don Adolfo Calero.
He works for your government
on the revolution
to bring down the Sandinistas.
Jorge tells me you
are the crazy gringo
who always delivers.
OCHOA: We have a new
business proposition
to you, Barry.
You bring your
American guns
to Colombia,
deliver our cocaine here,
to the Contras,
the Contras take it by
fishing boats to Miami,
and everybody's happy.
It's for the war effort,
Mr. Seal.
BARRY: Turns out,
the Contras didn't really
want to fight a war.
They just wanted
to make money.
Like the rest of us.
Meanwhile, the Medellin
Cartel wanted guns.
So they worked
out a little trade.
What was I gonna tell ’em?
I’m just a gringo
who always delivers.
Here '3 how
the operation worked.
I’d load up with guns in Mena,
then, using Schafer's intel,
I’d bypass any law enforcement
and fly straight to
the cartel's airstrip
in Medellin.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
BARRY: The Colombians,
well, they loved them guns.
(CHUCKLES)
And I'd load up
with fresh powder
and fly on to
the Contra training camp.
The Contras hid
the coke in fishing boats
and sailed it up to Miami.
Meanwhile, I'd get
another load of powder,
take it back to the States
with a quick stop
to refuel in Panama
under the protection
of my old friend,
Colonel Noriega.
Congratulations on
your promotion, General.
'Course,
he'd get his cut, too.
On the way back,
I'd keep an eye
out for the DEA
and then I’d dump it all
in the swamps of Louisiana.
The operation got so big
I had to get some help.
Pete Dubois manufactured guns
until he discovered
he had a knack
for selling pot.
Stan Mason flew dope
from Mexico to Arizona.
Bill Cooper.
He flew opium all around
Southeast Asia during Vietnam.
Then there’s Bob. Uh...
I don't know much about Bob.
Hell of a pilot, though.
I called these boys
my Snowbirds,
and we could fly
through anything.
Schafer!
Barry.
How's it going?
BILL: Hey, boss!
That was fucking crazy,
man! Whoo! (LAUGHS)
How's it, uh...
How's it going
down there?
Oh, you know...
Busy.
You?
Oh, yeah.
Busy.
Where are
they going?
We need to borrow
some of your land.
They want you to
fly 'em up here
to train.
For training.
Who?
The Contras.
You... You want me
to bring ‘em up here?
To Mena?
We‘re setting up a field
and operational
training ground.
Where? On...
On my land?
Yeah.
Starting immediately.
Which is great.
Is that a problem?
No.
Hey.
Whatever you need, boss.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
(PLANES PASSING OVERHEAD)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Hang on!
We're supposed to have 15.
I'm only counting 12 here.
Them Contras were damn excited
about being in the U. S. of A.
And they were
running away almost faster
than we could bring 'em in.
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
CIA MAN: Hey, you two!
Where you think you're going?
Wow. You wanna
quadruple the
shipments?
We're confident
the Contras can
win by summer
ifwe give 'em
what they need.
That's great.
WINTER: How much more can you
get out of your guy in Mena?
MONTY: Oh, we'll get
everything out of him.
That's what
I like to hear.
We're expanding
operations, Barry.
BARRY: Come on, now.
One at a time!
Just one at a time!
Hey, hold on! Hold on!
We‘ll take care of everybody.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Back!
Hands off!
Please. Back!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Everyonejust
calm the fuck down!
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(GUNFIRE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GLASSES CLINK)
Salud.
(IN ENGLISH)
Hey, Barry.
Yeah?
You think those
Contras can win?
No.
Eh...
(TV PLAYING)
SHERIFF DOWNING: Hi.
This just came.
"Go Razorbacks. Barry."
Season tickets.
Fifty-yard line.
Well, that was
awful nice of him.
How much property
has Seal bought up
since he came to town?
I don't know, 500 acres?
2,000 acres.
From the airport
to Ouachita.
What's he want with
all that worthless land?
It's... It's really none
of our business, really.
He's good people, Judy.
He's doing a lot
for the community.
I'd like to open
a bank account.
Oh. Bless you!
I'll be right back.
David!
LUCY: Come on, Christina!
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
MAN: Good job, guys, good job!
Whoo!
LUCY: Way to go, Christina!
Go, go, go!
Oranges.
You guys want some oranges?
LUCY: Hey, guys, I got pizza!
You guys want
some pizza?
KIDS: Yeah!
Here you go! All right.
Let me just put this right...
There you go.
(HORN HONKING MELODIOUSLY)
Nice wheels!
Oh, you like her?
(CHUCKLES) I do.
1982.
All the bells and whistles.
First one in
the state of Arkansas,
and she's yours.
She's mine?
She's yours.
Oh, my God, Barry!
Thank you!
Wow.
A little something
extra in there.
Fuck me, Barry!
(BARRY CHUCKLING)
What?
Okay. You need to behave.
LUCY: I brought some snacks
out for you, Christina.
BARRY: By the summer of '82,
business was a-boomin’.
Got us at Tuesday,
three o'clock.
Tuesday at three o'clock.
OCHOA: (ON PHONE) We need
to increase the shipments.
Can you add
a Friday delivery?
Friday? Okay.
Hold on, now.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yeah?
We wanna double the amount
ofguns we're bringing in.
BARRY: Double?
MONTY: Next batch by Friday.
(STAMMERS) Oh, hold on.
Does it have
to be Friday?
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
BARRY: I opened a few
front corporations.
I can't wait to learn
everything there is to know
about the Sign business,
Mr. Seal.
Me, too.
I spent 30 years working
the pumps at Gas N' Sip.
Well, sir, Ithink
it's about time you moved
to upper management.
But the money was
coming in faster
than / could launder it.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BARRY: l was taking pictures,
delivering guns,
dropping off and picking up.
(CHUCKLES) Damn,
I was building an air force.
New toy, boys!
(LAUGHS)
I wanted to get new books.
LUCY: You did?
What're you doing? Barry!
LUCY: Smile, Barry.
BARRY: Jorge!
(OCHOA SPEAKS SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) Lobsters!
Oh, you remembered!
What'd I tell you?
You think I'm
gonna forget that?
Your husband
is a genius.
Well, it absolutely,
positively has to be
delivered overnight.
Esposa, Lucy.
No, no, no.
Si, si, si.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
(FIREWORKS BURSTING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
BARRY: lhad my fingers
in every pie on the rack.
10 million in Mena National,
12 million in Mena State,
15 in Mena Trust.
I had 40 parked in Miami,
20 in Panama,
7 million in lawn bags,
8 in Samsonites,
4 buried in the woods
behind my house,
and 90 pounds of gold
in my closet.
Hot damn!
Oh, honey,
watch the yoke.
(LUCY PANTS)
If this ain't the greatest
country in the world.
Ah!
(GASPS)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
BARRY: Uh...
JB.
Uh...
Yeah.
He ,s' |
B! y Is.
What the fuck?
Look at you!
God damn!
Get in here.
Look at this fucking house!
Parking a Chevy's a lot harder
than it fucking looks, Luce.
Hey! Watch your mouth
around the kids.
Sorry.
(VIDEOGAME RUNNING)
That right?
JB: Yeah, man.
They had me
cramming those S-1OS
into every goddamn inch
of the fucking...
LUCY: Hey, you heard me!
I'm
S
o
rry|
Look, thing is
is that the cars
were so close to
each other, right?
You couldn't help
but scratch, right?
Yeah.
Then they would
take the scratches
out of my
fucking paycheck, man!
LUCY: Hey! JB!
JB: Sorry.
Well, I don't know how
you handle the pressure, JB.
You‘re staying here,
you're getting a job.
Or, you know,
I could just give you
some folding cash,
you go and do
what you want.
Don't you look
at him like that.
JB: What?
You are getting a job,
JB, not a handout.
My brother's
getting ajob, Barry.
You're getting a job.
Definitely.
Well, you hear that?
That‘s the law.
You're gonna
have to work, son.
Gonna have to work.
That's right.
JB: What is it I'll
be doing, exactly?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Yo, Barry!
Hey, Barry.
Barry!
What now, JB?
So this is a big hangar,
and I'm tired of sweeping.
You can take a break
when you get it done.
Let's go.
Get it done!
BILL: Hey, man, lgot
a newjob for you.
Get me a beer, man.
Dead soldier.
Here's your fucking...
(PLANE ENGINE WHIRRING)
LUCY: Barry?
Yeah?
Roscoe dug this up
in the backyard.
There are bills
blowing around everywhere.
I'll rake it up
in the morning.
I found three more of 'em
up in the fireplace.
(MAN WHOOPS)
(PANTING)
Shit.
(BARRY SIGHS)
We had cash flooding in
from every direction.
Who... Who thought that
was gonna be a problem?
I mean...
We were running out
of places to put it.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Easy. Whoa.
Don‘t get behind 'em.
These are dangerous animals.
No, maybe you
should call the trainer.
No, honey, I got this.
Come on, now.
Hang on.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON CAR RADIO)
JB: What you
think of that?
GIRL: Holy shit!
JB got a new car.
Did you give
that boy a raise?
JB: Hey, Barry, Luce!
What in the holy fuck?
Thatgirl is 15.
It's huge!
I told you it was huge!
You actually live here?
Uh-huh.
Hey! Can I talk to
you for a second?
Yeah.
What?
Come here.
LUCY: What the hell, JB?
What?
I haven't done
nothing yet!
JB. Come on.
Hi, Miss Seal.
Hi.
What... We were just
gonna go for a swim.
Come here.
Please don't tell my
mama that l was here.
LUCY: Come on, honey.
Let's go inside.
Where'd you get
the money for this car?
I'm gonna be
honest with you, Barry,
'cause I can't lie to you.
I stole it from
the hangar.
All right.
I opened up one of
the Samsonites.
I found so much fucking
money in there, man.
JB, JB, JB.
So much goddamn money.
JB, you can't do that.
PETE: 500 down 300.
Watch out for
that tree at the end.
BARRY: Yeah, I remember that.
No, Pete,
you gotta turn that off.
I can't see nothing
with it on.
PETE: Gotcha.
75.50.
Oh. Nicely done, boss.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
(YAWNS)
You boys
see this?
Oh! Fuck!
MAN: (ON RADIO) This is the
United States Drug Enforcement
Administration.
You are in
violation of the Air Defense
Identification Zone.
We are ordering you
to land immediately.
Follow us to
New Orleans NAS.
All right, boys.
It's gonna be
a long night.
Let‘s go back
out to sea,
105 knots.
Get them
flaps down.
MAN: lrepeat,
we are ordering you
to land immediately.
BARRY: The DEA was using
these fancy new jets
that we couldn't outrun.
MAN: Follow us to
New Orleans NAS.
BARRY: But all that speed
comes at a heavy price.
MAN: I repeat...
BARRY: They could go fast,
but we could go slow.
For a long time.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Low fuel. Low fuel.
(BEEPING)
We gotta turn around,
guys. We‘re bingo.
Those pricks are
right fucking there.
BARRY: (ON RADIO)
All right, boys.
DEA finally ran out of gas.
Time to head home.
PETE: Bill! The fuck, man?
Where you headed, buddy?
Come on.
BARRY: All right,
I’ll get him.
I'll get him.
Bill? Come on, turn around.
Come on, let’s go.
Bill? You hear me?
Oh, son of a bitch!
Bill's asleep.
(LAUGHS) God damn!
BARRY: Bill, wake...
Wake up, man!
PETE: That motherfucker
can sleep anywhere.
Wake up, Bill.
(PETE LAUGHING)
BARRY: Bill!
(GASPS)
BARRY: Morning, Bill!
BILL: Okay, I'm up, I'm up.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Welcome back.
Those bank financials
that you asked for.
McCALL: Yeah.
There's a lot of money
in Mena, Arkansas.
Thanks.
I think you're
gonna appreciate
what we've done here, Barry.
(SAW WHIRRING)
You're making me
my own vault?
Oh, no, no.
We're using this auxiliary
for all our other customers.
We gave you
the main vault.
How 'bout that!
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Aerostar 2- 1-9—3-golf.
Head for New Orleans
Naval Air Station at once.
Yeah. Come on,
come on, come on!
You better run,
you prick.
(CHUCKLES)
MAN: (ON RADIO)
This is the United States
Border Patrol.
BARRY: Shit.
MAN: We are ordering
you to land.
BARRY: Hey, boys.
I see you finally got smart
and got a slower plane.
Two of 'em.
MAN: That’s right, son.
We up here as
long as you want.
Aerostar, we are ordering you
to land immediately.
BARRY: Ha. All right,
motherfuckers. Let's land.
MAN: lrepeat, we are
ordering you to land...
What the fuck?
Stay on him.
(ENGINE STOPS)
Shit!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, shit!
(CAR HORN BLARES)
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHS)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(DOG BARKING)
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Is this your yard?
All right.
Well, that's
for the damage.
And, uh, here's
a little something extra
for your sister.
Hey, little darlin'.
And your bike.
(PLANE PASSING OVERHEAD)
All right.
You never saw me.
(SIRENS BLARING IN DISTANCE)
GARY: ”A plane crashed
in Louisiana
"with 200 kilos of
Colombian powder."
Two hundred.
Right.
Is that your boy?
I'm sorry, are you working
for the fucking DEA now?
Interesting read.
(SCOFFS)
I got it.
(PHONE RINGING)
OCHOA: Hello, amigo.
Si.
We had to get out of Colombia
in the middle of the night.
BARRY: [wasn't the
only one having trouble
with the DEA.
OCHOA: Escobar’s gone
crazy and declared war
on the government.
BARRY: Thanks
to Pablo Escobar’s
unique management style,
the cartel found themselves
kicked out of Colombia.
The only place
the DEA couldn't touch him?
That's right. Nicaragua.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
OCHOA: We're going to
meet SehorVaughan.
He's the Minister
of Interiors.
He controls
the airstrips.
It's how we get you in.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
(OCHOA SPEAKING SPANISH)
Barry, just sit and keep
your mouth shut.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON CAR RADIO)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Here's your butter, sir.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's up?
How you doing?
Stop running!
JB: Fuck!
(TIRES SCREECH)
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
(PAGER BEEPING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BOTH CONTINUE
SPEAKING SPANISH)
(PAGER BEEPING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Hey, Luce,
you hear me?
LUCY: Yes.
Honey? You all right?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Honey, I hate to
tell you this right now,
but JB has been arrested.
That little shit.
BARRY: What happened?
LUCY: ldon't know.
Got caught
with a whole lot of money.
That dumb fuck.
BARRY: Honey...
What do you want
me to do here, babe?
There ain't nothing
to do, really. Uh...
I'm just in a meeting.
And we'll go over that
when | get home.
All right?
I'll take care of that.
All right.
Hurry, Barry.
All right? You just
sit tight. I love you.
Okay.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
How much? (SPEAKS SPANISH)
(ESCOBAR SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH) That's 15...
OCHOA: 1,500 kilos, Barry.
1,500?
SI'.
In one go.
In one go?
BOTH: Si.
(SCOFFS)
Well, we ain't never
done that before. That's...
LEHDER: Sanctuary isn't cheap.
That's a lot.
Can you do it?
Yeah. I'm gonna...
Yeah. I'm gonna get home.
Right now. I'm gonna leave,
and then we'll
figure it out.
I'll figure it out.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
(BARRY SPEAKING SPANISH)
Get it fucking done!
Fucking lawyer
doesn‘t know Shit.
I got two fucking priors, man,
and he doesn't understand.
No, no, no.
He does understand.
And you gotta do
what he tells you to do.
(PHONE RINGING)
JB: No, he doesn’t, man.
One more strike,
man, one more strike
and I could go to prison
for life, man.
J B?
JB, just hold on.
(PHONE CONTINUES RINGING)
Barry? Barry,
are you there?
BOY: Daddy!
Hey, darlin'.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
What's that? Hold on.
Yeah?
00 H OA: Barry.
We've been trying
to get a hold of you, amigo.
Yeah, I know that, amigo.
Listen, could you hold on?
I'll be right back.
(SIGHS)
(KID CRYING)
JB?
JB: Yeah.
There '5 some people
that wanna talk to me.
No, no, no.
You don't talk to
anyone about anything.
Now, you do what that
lawyer tells you to,
and you keep your
fuckin' mouth shut.
I’m taking care of this.
Okay.
Listen, Jorge.
We gotta put on
the brakes for a bit.
Brakes? No, no, no.
No brakes.
We have product to move.
I understand, amigo.
But I got a family situation.
Your brother-in-law?
We know all about it.
We 'll handle it, amigo.
No, no, no. I don't
want you to handle it.
Barry, listen.
I got it. I got this.
Barry.
Listen to me.
We‘ll handle it. Okay?
No, no, no. Jorge.
So, don't worry.
Jorge... Jorge...
We ’ll talk business later.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
BOY: ldon't want to
see Daddy no more.
JB: Barry, they don't
know about all them
suitcases you got
or what you got
in them planes.
The guns you got.
They don't know
anything about it.
We‘re good, man.
I can't fix this,
you hear?
They're gonna give you
10 years for not talking.
That's 10 years people
gotta worry you will.
But I didn't
say anything, man!
You can talk to
the goddamn lawyer.
(JB BREATHING HEAVILY)
Where we going, man?
Jesus Christ!
I'm fuckin' family.
We're family!
That's right.
We're family.
What's this?
Inside's a passport,
first-class ticket
to Bora Bora,
and enough cash...
Enough cash to make
a damn good life for
yourself.
Now, you're gonna
get in that car
and you're gonna
drive straight to
Dallas/Fort Worth airport.
And nowhere else.
You don't even
stop to take a piss.
You hear me?
Yeah, I hear you.
Good luck, kid.
(MUMBLING)
I'll tell you
what, Barry.
I'm gonna send you
a goddamn address.
Okay, Barry?
You‘re gonna
start sending me cash
on the fucking regular.
You understand?
You hear me?
Fuckin' goddamn fuckin' dick,
all high-and-mighty.
Piece of shit.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
Oh, and Barry,
fuck you, man!
Fuck you and
my cunt sister.
Excuse me?
Did you just...
Hey! Hey!
Money every
week, asshole!
What the fuck?
What? Oh, shit.
(PANTING)
Hey! Hey. Barry.
(LOCKS DOOR)
Oh, my God.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
BILL: Barry. Barry!
What do you need, Bill?
What do you need?
Hey, man... Man,
I'm, like, freaking out, man.
What is going on with JB?
Huh?
Don't worry about JB.
What if he talks, man?
He ain't gonna.
Yeah, but what
if he does?
He ain't gonna
talk, Bill.
How do you know?
I am fucking positive.
Okay, man.
Good. I'm gonna trust
you on this one, man.
Good.
MAN: /n the calendar year,
your operations
have transported
10,500 Russian AKS
to the Contras.
Yeah.
5,000 of which
have found themselves
in the hands of
the Colombian cartel.
Right. But...
Out of the 916 Contras
brought into the United
States to train,
only half made it
back to Nicaragua.
Half is...
The other half
are in the wild.
(TRUCK APPROACHING)
What's going on here?
Oh, yeah. We had to
send the Contras home.
Home?
Yeah.
They weren't fighting.
That‘s the reality
of that situation.
(SIGHS) You know,
it didn't help that their
guns were in Colombia.
Did it, Barry?
(PAGER BEEPING)
So...
What now?
We'll call ya.
Call me?
Schafer?
Hey, Schafer!
Who the fuck's Schafer?
Okay, everybody,
you know the drill.
Everybody gets a burn bag.
Into it, you put anything
with Barry Seal's face
or name on it.
Come on, boys.
We gotta move.
We gotta get all
this stuff out of here.
Pete.
PETE: What? Everything?
Come on, boys, let's go.
We gotta move this out.
Let's go! Let's go!
MONTY: Into the burn bag. Go!
Purchase orders.
Aircraft invoices.
Be a team here.
Let's move it out.
Holy Shit, man.
Look at all these guns.
We gotta move all of it.
Where we supposed to
put all of this stuff?
Just get it off
my property.
Anything with
the word "Mena."
Fuel bills, memos,
names, directives,
photos.
Anything like that.
Anything which can
link us with him,
you put it in the burn bag.
And what do you do with it?
MAN: Burn it.
You burn it.
BILL: Bob, need
a little help back here.
BOB: In the back!
PETE: Give me
a hand with this shit.
BILL: Got it.
DEA AGENT 1: Seal! DEA!
Back away from the truck
with your hands in the air.
DEA AGENT 2: Drop
the fucking box,
shithead!
Show us your hands!
Drop the fucking box!
DEA AGENT 2: Nice and high!
ATF!
Drop your weapons!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! DEA!
Lower your guns!
ATF! Put your guns down!
Stand down!
DEA AGENT 1: It's cool!
Everybody's friends here.
DEA, all right?
This is our collar.
DEA AGENT 1: Bullshit!
No, no, no.
(SIREN BLARES)
OFFICER: State Police!
What the fuck are
y'all doing in my county?
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
McCALL: Nobody move!
FBI!
Ah, fuck.
Well, hey, boys,
how about my phone call?
(LINE RINGING)
(BEEPS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
We're sorry.
You have reached
a number that has been
disconnected or is
no longer in service.
Oh, shit.
If you feel you have
reached this recording
in error,
please check
the number and try...
Come on, Seal.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
You know who I am,
Mr. Seal?
No, ma'am.
I'm Dana Sibota,
state attorney general.
You‘ve got DEA, ATF,
FBI, all wanting
their pound of flesh.
Yes, ma'am. It's...
It's quite a room.
Yeah. Well, you hit
the trifecta, didn't you?
I mean, guns, drugs,
money laundering.
And the state of Arkansas
is gonna rip the bark
right off of you, boy.
We are gonna put you
in a four-by-six cell
for the rest of your life.
Ma'am, that's a long time.
Yeah.
WOMAN: (ON SPEAKER)
Miss Sibota, lhave
Governor Clinton on the line.
He says it’s urgent.
It's the Governor.
It's your governor.
(SNIFFS)
Put him through.
Clear the room.
Take him with you.
Yeah?
What do you need, Bill?
BARRY: Did y'all know
that Caddies have
more trunk space
than any other car
in the world?
I'll give each and
every one of you a Caddy.
(ALL SCOFF)
BARRY: Huh?
You'd do that
for all of us?
Yes, sir. lwould.
I'd get all y'all Caddies.
Have 'em here
this afternoon.
What are you
trying to do, Seal?
Add another 20 for bribery?
I'm just
offering y'all Caddies
for your troubles.
What troubles,
Seal, hmm?
Well, bringing me
down here, for one.
You see,
I'm gonna walk out of here.
(ALL LAUGHING)
And there ain't a damn
thing any one of you
can do about it.
ATF AGENT: All right.
Do it.
Wait. Wait...
Wait a minute.
No, no.
No, he‘s free
to go, boys.
What the fuck?
McCALL: What the hell
do you mean,
"He‘s free to go"?
DEA AGENT: You want
to explain what's
going on here?
DANA: He's free to go.
DEA AGENT 2: Free to go?
You boys should've
taken the Caddies.
I'll be seeing you, Seal.
Ma'am.
BARRY: I tell you,
it is good to see you boys,
I ain't gonna lie.
But I figured you'd
have to Show up, see?
'Cause ljust
know too much.
Schafer sent you, right?
Who the fuck
is Schafer?
All right,
all right now.
Seriously, fellas,
who are you?
Usually, [talk
with you from my office
in the West Wing
of the White House,
but tonight,
there '3 something
special to talk about.
And I’ve asked someone
very special to join me.
Are we going...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO)
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Nancy.
Not long ago,
I was asked by
a group of children
what to do if they
were offered drugs.
And I answered,
"Just say no. "
Drug criminals are ingenious.
So we must be
smarter and stronger
and tougher than they are.
Say yes to your life.
And when it comes
to drugs and alcohol,
just say no.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
You a pilot?
I've been known
to fly some.
Me, too.
Air National Guard.
'68, '69.
Oh.
VICE PRESIDENT BUSH: Junior?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well,
I'll see
you around, flyboy.
All right.
The Sandinistas are
burning the American
flag in the streets.
Please. There is no deal
if we don‘t get
the Sandinistas.
Then there's no deal.
Horseshit.
There's no deal
unless we get Medellin.
BARRY: Now, you may be
wondering why my ass wasn't
in jail at this point.
This is disgusting!
BARRY: But I gotta be honest.
Frankly, so was I.
RANGEL: Ollie...
COLONEL NORTH: Oh, please!
BARRY: This fella here
is with the DEA.
And this fella here
is a colonel
named Ollie North.
Reagan's go-to guy.
The DEA just wants to nail
the Medellin Cartel
once and for all.
Now, at the same time,
Colonel North wants to prove
the commies in Central America
are involved in
the drug trade.
Let me say that again.
This is disgusting!
BARRY: Colonel North
wants to prove the commies
are dealing drugs.
And why am I in the room?
'Cause I'm the gringo
who always delivers.
So, you want me
to keep going?
For your country.
We‘re gonna bring
these guys down.
And you're
gonna be a hero.
All right, then.
They put me right
back in business.
Now, I’m working
for the White House.
Fifty picture loads each.
You have one here in a bag.
The Sightline goes
straight down the back
to where those
gentlemen are now.
You have two more cameras
above each door.
Sightlines directly
in front of the door.
Each camera has a cord.
You just press this
button to take a picture.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
That's it.
Let's go.
I can see
the cords, Barry.
Yeah.
I can see this damn cord,
which means they
gonna be able to see it.
We'll hide it.
I'm not a photographer.
Your thumb work?
Yeah.
Well, you just
push the button.
When am I supposed
to push the button?
When the guys
are standing here
holding the powder.
You know what?
Fuck it, Pete.
I'll take the pictures.
Fuck!
BARRY: Listen.
What's gonna happen
with these photos?
Who exactly is going
to be looking at 'em?
These photos are gonna be
on a need-to-know basis.
Need-to-know.
They're gonna be
classified at the highest
levels, Barry.
BOY: Daddy! Daddy!
BARRY: Classified.
Daddy!
We do recognize
the dangers involved here.
No, you don't.
Well, you could
always tell us
to fuck off
and spend the next
30 years in Leavenworth.
PETE: Come on, boss!
Let‘s get this over with!
We‘ll see ya, Rangel.
LUCY: Smile, Barry!
SON: Bye, Daddy!
(SCREAMS EXCITEDLY)
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Shit! There's
a fucking army out there.
They're gonna
torture us.
Pull ourtongues
out through our necks.
That ain't
helping, Pete.
They're gonna cut us up
in little pieces and
feed us to the pigs.
I don't wanna be
fed to no pigs, Barry.
Gotta keep our shit
together. Hola!
(DOOR WHIRRING)
We're gonna get the yayo,
take these damn pictures,
then get the hell out of here.
Let‘s keep our shit together.
(MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
No, no, no.
(CLAMORING)
BARRY: Amigos...
They're going to hear
that goddamn camera, Barry.
Amigos.
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
Escobar. Ochoa.
(ALL CONTINUE
SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
BARRY: Hey, ho/a.
Amigo... Qué pasé?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(HORN HONKING)
BARRY: Hey, Jorge!
Jorge. Fuck!
Come on, man.
A little help.
Shoot the gringos.
What?
Shoot the gringos!
What's that?
(SHOUTING)
No, no, no!
(PANTING)
(LAUGHING)
You fucker.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Ochoa!
OCHOA: Senor.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
Pete, stand the fuck up.
OCHOA: (IN ENGLISH)
They are shaking.
You're shaking.
Look at this!
He pissed himself, man.
You got me.
That was a good one.
(OCHOA SPEAKS SPANISH)
I saved your life, Barry.
I saved your life, eh?
Yes, you did.
Remember that.
Yeah.
Remember.
Crazy gringo.
Come here, Barry.
BARRY: Hey, Jorge.
Now, let's go
say hi to Pablo.
Pablo's here.
Si, he's paranoid,
amigo. On edge.
Thinks everyone
is out to get him.
Hola! Pablo!
(BARRY SPEAKING SPANISH)
Let's do this.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
What?
Everything good?
I'm here.
(MOTORCYCLE REWING)
And I brought your Harleys.
(IN ENGLISH)
We‘re still friends?
That was a good one
that you pulled right there.
You really got me.
(OCHOA SPEAKS SPANISH)
Hey, you know,
I'm gonna have
to get you back.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
BARRY: Jorge,
look at this, my friend.
PETE: Say cheese,
motherfuckers.
BARRY: We're gonna
make history.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
RANGEL: Barry Seal!
MAN: Yeah!
Barry Seal!
He's a goddamn genius.
(ALL CHEERING)
There seems to be no crime
to which the Sandinistas
will not stoop.
(ON TV) This is
an outlaw regime.
The Sandinistas have even
involved themselves
in the international
drug trade.
I know every
American parent concerned
about the drug problem
will be outraged
to learn
that top Nicaraguan
government officials
are deeply involved
in drug trafficking.
This picture,
secretly taken at a military
airfield outside Managua
Shows Federico Vaughan,
a top aide to one of
the nine comandantes
who rule Nicaragua...
Fuck!
...loading an aircraft
with illegal narcotics
bound for the United States.
Those motherfuckers!
That's your
fucking face, Barry!
This is an outlaw regime.
Oh, my God!
(OCHOA SPEAKING SPANISH)
He betrayed us!
Pablo, we have to take
care of this immediately.
That son of a bitch.
I'm going to rip his head off!
RANGEL: (ON PHONE)
I am truly sorry, Barry.
North jumped the gun.
Yeah, well,
you boys fucked me good.
We all got fucked.
Those photos
weren't supposed
to be released,
and certainly not
until we had
the Colombians in custody.
Yeah, well, they ain't gonna
be coming for you.
Barry, you knew the risks
when you took those pictures.
You knew what
you were doing.
Barry?
Barry, you there?
Let‘s go get
some ice cream.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
BARRY: The feds,
they're gonna try
to take everything.
When they come,
you gotta put on
all yourjewelry.
All right? All your rings,
you know, your bracelets.
Necklace.
'Cause if you're wearing it,
they can't take it
away from you.
You understand?
All right, that's insurance
for you and the kids.
All right?
I understand.
All right. And don't
forget that it's
gonna be all right.
It's gonna be all right.
I love you.
BARRY: Sure enough, they came.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
And they took it all.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(CLATTERING)
(CLATTERING CONTINUES)
Hey, Luce, honey,
l was thinking
that you might like
to move back to Baton Rouge.
LUCY: You ain't gonna find
nothing in those drawers.
Try the hat boxes,
third shelf Up.
I mean, you
loved it there.
What about you?
Imean, I'm...
Me, uh...
Listen, you see...
Look, if! run,
they're, uh,
they‘re gonna come
for you and the kids,
I mean,
that's how
a thing like this goes,
but, Baton Rouge,
you're safe.
No.
(SCOFFS)
No, I ain't
going nowhere.
We're a family and
we're staying together.
I know. But...
No, sir.
Iain't doing this.
Listen, Luce. Luce.
No.
No, no. Honey,
hang on.
Don't do this now.
No, sir, sir! I'm sorry.
LUCY: You know what?
No, no, no, sir.
Come on, sir.
Excuse me,
she's wearing this now.
Luce, you gotta stop.
Hey, you know, fellas...
Sorry, hey...
Can ljust have a moment...
Can ljust have a moment
with my wife?
It's been a hell of a day.
(CHUCKLES)
MAN: Okay, Barry.
Yeah.
You got one minute.
All right. Luce?
Honey, now listen to me.
MAN: Let's give him a minute.
Baby, baby,
listen to me.
MAN: All right, folks.
Head on out.
Listen to me.
(SIGHS)
I'm gonna go to prison.
I'm gonna do
just a little time.
And I'm gonna
be fine there,
and we're gonna
work everything out,
but I gotta know
you're gonna be safe.
It's gonna be all right.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You gotta trust me.
I mean, you trust me, right?
Fuck no!
All right.
BARRY: Luce and the kids
finally did move
to Baton Rouge.
DANA: How can we
have a war on drugs
when the biggest
enemy of the state
is being protected
by our side?
BARRY: And that
lady prosecutor...
DANA: Why, he never
informed the FBI...
BARRY: ...she never,
ever did give up.
...that any such
sting operation
was underway.
BAILIFF: Defendant will rise.
JUDGE: Barry Seal.
Your Honor.
You are sentenced
to 1,000 hours
community service.
(GAVEL BANGS)
Dismissed.
DANA: Oh, that is bullshit.
JUDGE: Watch yourself, Sibota.
I'm sorry.
DANA: We are talking about
a drug smuggler here
of the highest order.
Uh, community service?
Exhibit D!
LAWYER: Mr. Seal's
planes are classified.
DANA: lam sick to fuck...
Sibota!
...of this Mickey Mouse
tap-dancin' bullshit.
JUDGE: Sibota, Iwill
hold you in contempt.
DANA: Sorry. I'm very sorry.
So, I'm walking out
of here. Now.
JUDGE: State ofArkansas
has spoken, Mr. Seal.
Do I have to go?
JUDGE: Goodbye.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
(BABY CRYING)
Hey, darlin'.
I do tend to leap
before I look.
Maybe, uh...
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Maybe I should have asked
a few more questions.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Excuse me, sir, ma'am.
Would y'all mind
moving out of the way?
I'm just gonna start my car.
Yeah.
MAN: What?
I really appreciate
that now.
WOMAN: Honey,
just keep walking.
Keep walking.
(CLICKS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Thank you.
Just startin' my car.
MAN: Uh-huh.
Appreciate it.
BARRY: lspent every day
in a different motel.
Would y'all mind
movin' outta the
way there?
Thank you.
(ENGINE STARTS)
A different motel every day.
It's just for
the safety of the children.
Thank you.
But / had to show up
to this Salvation Army
halfway house
every evening
at the same time.
Judge’s orders.
You here for
community service?
BARRY: Same time, same place.
Uh, what's your
name, sorry?
Louis.
Louis. Barry Seal.
Nice to meet you.
Sign in for me.
BARRY: 120 days in a row.
There you go.
Hey, you may wanna
move your truck, too.
Now, them Contras
were damn excited
about being in the U. S. ofA.
GUARD: Hey, Barry.
MAN: Oh.
Thanks, Barry.
Don't tell 'em
I gave you that.
Day 36.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES ON RADIO)
(MUSIC STOPS)
BARRY: You know,
I guess you could say
I helped build an army,
defend a country,
and create
the biggest drug cartel
this world's ever seen.
DEA, CIA, White House.
Imean, it's been
a hell of an adventure.
Yeah. Sometimes a little
more than [bargained
for. (CHUCKLES)
But God damn!
Now, you try telling me
that this ain't
the greatest country in the...
(GUNSHOT)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO
CHATTER)
We'll handle it
from here, Deputy.
ANNOUNCER: Authorities
believe last night's
machine gun killing
of Barry Seal
was ordered by drug bosses
in Medellin, Colombia.
Iran.
We get the Iranians
to arm the Contras.
'Schafer' got a promotion.
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO
CHATTER)
After his release, Pete
found God and became
a preacher in rural Alabama.
The other pilots
were never seen again.
The CIA continued to
use Barry's plane
to arm the Contras...
Shit! Come on,
you big, fat bitch! Pull up!
...until one was shot down
over Nicaragua.
The ensuing scandal was known
as the Iran-Contra Affair.
REPORTER: Mr. President,
what do you know
about money
going to the Contras?
All I know is
this is just
gonna taste wonderful
and I'm looking forward
to tomorrow.
REPORTER: Vice President Bush,
did you know about
the Contra aid or not, sir?
Lucy and the kids
settled back in Louisiana.
Want some sauce
with that?
Okay. Thank you.
Original subtitles by Sud_Arun
Colored and Improved by zer0_