Improved and corrected
English translations by zer0_
Now, let's talk about the STIC test
or Standardised Test for
International Colleges,
which tests for general
knowledge and
it is used to apply to bachelor
programmes in the U.S.
This year the association
overseeing the examination
has uncovered a
cheating scandal,
which has led to the exam leaking in
in various countries in Asia.
Further investigation
is pending...
That's not mine.
My name is Rinrada Nilthep.
I'm in Grade 12, class 3
at Krungthep Thaweepanya School.
You can call to check
my school records.
The STIC exam isn't
beyond my ability.
BAD GENIUS
Student Portfolio:
Ms. Rinrada Nilthep
This student has achieved a 4.00 GPA
in Grade 7, Academic Year 2011
GRADE 9
Straight A's since Grade 1.
Honour student since
Grade 7 to Grade 9.
Came in first place in the school
district's Maths Competition.
National Crossword Champion.
There's also achievements in sports...
this one is...
For swimming.
That's fine, Vit.
This is more than enough.
No need to ask whether we
would accept Lynn or not.
The important question is...
do you want to study here?
What do you say, honey?
I don't have to
decide now, right?
It's not that I don't
want to study here.
It's just that my old school
is more suitable for me.
If I move here, my dad
will have to pay 150,000 per year.
How is it 150,000?
One semester is only 60,000,
so it only comes up to 120,000.
Correct. However, my dad
taught at my old school,
So I can go with him to
school every morning.
If I study here, I'd have
to take the skytrain
including calling motortaxis from the
station to home is 80 baht everyday...
for 8 months, which is 170 days,
excluding holidays.
It's approximately
13,600 baht per year.
There's also lunch,
At my old school it only
costs 20 baht for 2 sides with rice.
Here it's 35 baht.
I'll also have to buy new
school supplies and uniforms.
I think all in all...
it might not be worth it.
Gold medal in maths.
Honey...
I can afford it.
No, you can't.
What if we let you study for free?
Vit, I'll add free
lunch as well, okay?
We want want to see that
we value geniuses like Lynn.
Is it worth it now?
Worth it.
Worth bringing all this.
It's worth it, right?
Letter of Authorisation
Lynn
GRADE 10
Alright, done.
One second!
This ID is gonna be
with us for 3 years.
You gotta look good.
Okay?
You just moved here, right?
I'm Grace.
I'm Lynn.
What are you doing?
Can I have a look?
Take off your glasses.
Trust me.
Wow!
Pretty!
Smile. C'mon.
Okay. Ready 1... 2.
Go.
You're next. Quickly.
Grace
My ID number is after hers, so
we sat next to each other for 3 years.
Actually, Lynn and I are really close.
But everyone says Lynn's a genius.
But I'm...
I'm good at extracurricular
activities.
Sometimes, people might
even call me stupid.
The Headmistress came
up with a new policy this semester.
To be in a school play, you
need at least a 3.25 GPA.
Why? Am I too stupid
to be in a school play?
I think...
acting is harder than studying.
Really?
Really.
Look, I've been tutoring
with Mr. Sophon for weeks,
but I still don't know shit.
And maths really pulls
my grades down.
The answer is C.
What! You got the answer
just by glancing?
Upside down, too!
It's super easy.
"A union B, intersect with C."
Do the one's in the parentheses first,
then "intersect with C"
is just whatever's left in C.
That's the answer.
Oh! I get it.
Scholarship kids really are smart.
Another one?
Lynn, will you be my tutor?
Why not?
If you teach me,
I'll buy you a milkshake
after school every day.
Nah.
You'll get to review the
lesson every evening.
Not enough.
What about...
If you agree,
I'll get to be your first
student, Mentor Lynn.
Mentor Lynn.
Mentor Lynn!
That got me.
I'll teach you all
of this today.
Grace told you I helped
with her studies?
That's right.
But tutoring my friend
isn't wrong, right?
MIDTERMS
It's the moment you've
been waiting for.
Pass the test paper.
That's enough. Take a deep
breath, clear your mind.
It's already crystal clear.
Students, you may
start the exam.
Maths
60 questions / 30 marks
Mathematics...
I've warned you before,
it's not that easy.
If you know you don't understand
and you still didn't
come tutor with me then.
Don't come to me now.
It's too late.
Grace.
The paper is exactly
the same as Mr. Sophon's sheets!
- Yeah!
- You can do it, right?
No.
Why not? I already taught you!
I can't remember.
What are you talking about?
No talking, no cheating!
I will not tolerate any
misconduct in my exam room.
Ms. Rinrada Nilthep
Grace.
(INAUDIBLE) Answers.
Do I have to write my name
on the scrap paper?
Of course!
Have you never taken a test?
Sorry, sir.
Student Report Card
3.87! 3.87! 3.87!
What did you get? What did you get?
4.0, no sweat.
Are you free tomorrow?
Let's celebrate.
Sure. Where?
Let's got to Pat's then.
It's convenient.
You have a swimsuit, right?
Pat, will it kill you to
just get in pool like a normal person?
Nope...
but it's not cool.
I got water in my ear.
Mr. Pat, dinner is served.
Just leave it.
Babe, I'm cold.
Pat
Are you coral watching, Grace?
To be honest, I've told Grace to invite
you over to my place a bunch of times.
We're all in the same class,
but we hardly ever talk.
But Grace though,
always Lynn this... Lynn that.
Shut up.
Are you jealous?
Grace says that you're
good at everything.
Without you, her grades
wouldn't have improved.
I even told her that...
I want to have a
friend like you.
I've seen you with
a bunch of friends.
You're right,
but no one lends me their
eraser during exams.
Why?
Why? You want to be in
the school play as well?
Smart people like you
don't understand.
Idiots like me,
we all want good grades.
Damn.
Hey, babe!
Dad said if I don't fail this semester
he'll will get me a new car.
Sounds good?
I know that we aren't tight...
but if you agree...
I'll pay you 3,000 per subject.
This is per person.
Per person?
Yeah.
What do you mean?
I've got 5 more friends.
What if the teachers find out?
Don't worry about that.
All my friends can be trusted.
And all my friends are willing to pay.
Think about it, this
is only one subject.
And each semester has...
how many subjects, Grace?
Not including PE...
13, right?
So each semester,
you'll get...
13 times...
234,000 baht.
Nice digits as well: 234,000.
In exchange for your brains.
Tick-tock.
Call it even for the
school's 'tea money'.
What tea money?
Seriously?
You really don't know?
Everyone pays.
The stupider you are,
the more you pay.
I paid 400,000.
And this dumbass donated 20
iMac's to the library.
But I got a scholarship.
The scholarship is for studying.
Don't forget about
the maintenance fees.
Receipt:
New Student Fee - 200,000 baht
Divorce Papers
What mood are you in?
You know, I was going to sell
it to buy a new car.
Since you never play it anymore.
I just remembered yesterday
was Mom's birthday.
Why were you so eager to
make me move to this school?
Most students from this school
get scholarships
to study abroad.
I wanted to give you
opportunities your old school couldn't offer.
I'm not like Mom, you know.
Have you ever thought that
I might be happier
at my old school?
Three points.
Don't be too loud and disturb
the neighbors. Eat dinner.
I'm going to bed.
Okay, I admit I paid Lynn.
But paying her for
piano lessons...
isn't against any laws, right?
Or is it?
Will you send me to
international court?
Have you ever heard
that classical music
helps with the
brain's development?
We'll use 4 songs
to represent
A, B, C and D.
Memorize my right hand movements.
This is A.
Remember that it starts with the pinky
and finishes with the thumb.
This is B.
B is 4 3 2 1 3, repeated twice.
This is C.
This one D.
I'll give you 3
answers and skip 1.
I'll repeat this pattern.
So that the scores are scattered.
This'll keep the marks in check,
and not alert any teachers.
You must complete every question
that is the multiple of 4.
I'll start giving the
answers at 9:15 a.m.
Meanwhile, complete the
remaining questions.
D.
Lynn.
This shirt is expensive.
Are you getting rich from
teaching piano?
You can wear new
clothes too, you know.
They tease you at school
that you're a scrooge.
I wouldn't mind a new
pair of trousers too.
"Classical Piano Lessons
by Mentor Lynn"
More people want to
join your piano class.
Congratulations to Scholarship
Students, Academic Year 2013
GRADE 11
Bank
Stay tuned for Teen Genius
after the break!
It's true that Lynn and I study at
the same school.
But we're not friends.
Actually, we're rivalries.
What's wrong, Bank?
Are you nervous?
Uh-huh.
Did you have noodles for lunch?
How'd you know?
You've got some on your shirt.
Dirty and wrinkled.
Here. A wet wipe.
For your shirt.
Hey! If we win we'd get 5,000 baht!
We'll actually get
less than that.
With 3% tax deduction:
which is 150.
So it's only 4,850
or 2,425 each.
It's still a lot.
It's enough for a salmon buffet.
If we win, you wanna
go this evening?
No.
I don't like eating outside.
It's a waste of money.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing. You sound
just like my dad.
Is that good or bad?
Of course, It's a good thing.
Messy hair, wrinkled
shirt. Exactly like him.
What? I'm just gonna
fix your hair.
We're going on TV, the least
you can do is look good.
Looking handsome.
Ready?
Hmm.
Final question.
Tell me the Pi value with as many
decimal places as possible.
3.141592653589793...
That's enough, that's enough!
And the winner of this
week's Teen Genius is...
Krungthep Thaweepanya School!
I'm really awestruck. How did
divide the Pi value so quickly?
I didn't divide it.
I just memorized it.
You memorized the value of Pi?
I used to play memory
games with my dad.
Pi's value, names of
people, and reservoir names.
Brilliant, this is why you're
our scholarship student.
Have a seat.
I didn't ask you to come
only to praise you.
I also have good news for you.
Next year, the Singaporean Embassy
is offering scholarships for Thai students.
No strings attached.
It's a full scholarship.
You can study a bachelors and
finish with a doctorate.
Considering your grades,
behaviour and determination,
There's only you two who are
the school's best representatives.
There's a catch though.
Each school can only send one
student for the scholarship.
But that shouldn't
be a problem, right?
Yesterday, you two
were teammates.
But from now on, you're now rivals.
Isn't this fun?
Little Bank Laundry Service
The washing machine broke again.
I can't finish the
laundry in time.
Don't worry. I'll
take care of it.
Your hands are all calloused.
It's understandable
if you think I cheated...
but thinking that Bank
would cheat too?
Aside from my father,
Bank is the only other honest
and hard-working person
I've ever known in my entire life.
Hey, Bank!
What's up, Tong?
Did you finish studying for the exam?
Me too, man.
I was sick and didn't
finish studying.
Exactly the same,
Go finish studying.
Dude, please help me!
Let me copy you.
I really can't fail this time.
I've tried...
but this piano code is
just too hard for me.
What piano code?
Oh-- No--
It's nothing.
Hey, I won't copy you for free.
I'll pay you.
3,000 baht, enough?
Letting me copy
won't lower your marks.
Wait! Listen to me!
Bank!
Damn it, Bank! Can't
you help a friend?
You're goddamn heartless!
Hurry, hurry.
Today you're all taking
the test together.
Don't sit next to
your classmates.
All right, you may
start your test.
Grade 11, class 1
Grade 11, class 4
Grade 11, class 3
Grade 11, class 6
40. Your exam paper is set 1.
Sir, how do we
answer question 40?
There are two sets
of test papers.
Just answer according
to the one you have.
A. Set 1
B. Set 2
Be careful of Tong copying.
Lynn! Which set did you get?
So, which set?
Set 1.
Leave set 1 here.
What?
Row 3.
Banjong.
Crew cut with glasses.
He's copying Rinrada, she's
sitting next to him.
I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
You can go.
What now?
30 minutes left.
A. Set 1
Tong.
Huh?
Switch the papers.
Now!
Banjong Wongpoom
20 minutes left.
Lynn. Lynn.
What?!
Should I erase your name
and write mine instead?
No! Just sit still.
10 minutes left.
Last 5 minutes.
B. Set 2
Time's up.
Stop writing!
Hey!
Put your pencils down!
That's enough!
Don't you already have enough A's?
That's it!
[Jeez, the teacher's playing hardball.]
[That was close. Thank you, Mentor Lynn]
Is it worth it?
Being this risky.
Well, it is 3,000 for 25 per person.
What do you think?
Rinrada!
You didn't write your
name on the scrap paper.
Rinrada, Grade 11, class 3
and Banjong Grade 11, class 1,
report to the Headmistress's
office immediately.
I assure you.
If you don't believe me, then
have Tong retake the test.
You'll know the truth.
I've called the
both of you in...
because Thanaphon said
there's been some cheating.
There are 2 sets of test papers.
There's no point of cheating.
I'm giving you a chance
to tell the truth.
Banjong, did you cheat?
We'll find out soon enough.
Thanaphon and Rinrada,
you're excused.
Banjong, you stay here.
Lynn, don't leave yet.
How did you do these problems
on your scrap paper?
Since these problems are
not on the set you got.
Please don't get caught us.
Don't worry about it,
The Headmistress probably wants
to discuss about the scholar--
We have evidence that
Lynn completed her
friend's paper.
Lynn.
Explain why you did it.
If you don't, then
I will expel you.
For the money.
Tong tried to hire
me to do his test.
3,000 baht.
I'm very disappointed in you.
Vit...
I accepted your
daughter because
she's an honor student.
But it's not just about
being an good student,
it's also about having good disipline.
You're a teacher, you
should understand.
Completing your friend's
exam paper is cheating.
It's a gross violation
of school policy.
To be honest,
I could expel you right now.
Seeing that this
is your first time,
I'll just cancel
your scholarship.
Yes, ma'am.
To be honest, having Tong and Lynn
retake the test should be enough...
Remember Lynn.
School is a place for studying,
not a place for making money.
What are you laughing at?
Where are your manners?
Nothing.
Mr. Pravit,
you're a teacher, didn't
you teach her manners?
Sorry.
I don't think I'm the only one
who uses the school
to make money.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about the
'tea money' that my dad paid.
It's not called 'tea money'.
It's the school maintenance fee.
Isn't school maintenance fee
included in the tuition fee?
Stop, Lynn!
That's enough.
Please let her study here.
I'll take care of the
remaining tuition.
Let's go.
Fine.
I have one condition.
You're banned from the
Singapore Scholarship.
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
What's the scholarship
have to do with it?
It's true that I let
my friend copy me,
but I've never copied anyone.
All the grades that I've gotten
reflect my actual abilities.
These abilities,
other students have them too.
There's also people who deserve
this scholarship like Thanaphon.
If you can't accept
this condition,
then you can resign.
All right, Mr. Pravit?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go, Lynn.
Good luck with the scholarship.
Well, if you found evidence...
I guess Lynn really did cheat.
But I have nothing
to do with it.
Being an honor student
doesn't mean...
we have the same behaviour.
Ms. Rinrada Nilthep
I knew it.
I knew you didn't do it just for 3,000 baht.
Piano lessons?
Did you ever think that it'd
actually be better to actually tutor them?
But the Headmistress
cheated us first.
How can you call it cheating,
when I paid willingly.
My friends also paid willingly!
Can't you see you did wrong?!
Ok.
I'll take the blame.
It's my fault.
Who am I to blame?
If I can't raise my daughter
to be a good person,
then why should I go ask for
scholarships for my daughter?
I'll sell the car to pay for
the rest of the tuition fee.
As for this shirt...
I don't want it anymore.
About going abroad,
just forget it!
You're not going anywhere.
You're staying here with me.
Return all the money to your
friends by the end of the semester.
You can think that
Lynn is a bad person,
but to me...
she's truly a good friend.
Sorry for being such a crybaby,
but I'm not just acting.
GRADE 12
So? Does it look refreshing?
Not bad.
I'm casting is tomorrow.
You didn't call me just
for this, right?
How are you guys getting along?
You can take care of yourselves
for last two semesters, right?
Pat and I have other
things to worry about.
Has Pat told you, yet?
We just got back from France.
The trip was so fun!
Yeah, 'cause you left your son behind.
Well, I've got to go shopping too.
- Mom.
- I got you something too.
- Pat.
- Yes?
Go fetch a red wine
in the cellar for me.
Why don't you ask
the housekeeper to do it?
Yes, sir.
Grace, would you like
any more dessert?
No, thank you.
We invited you over today
because we would
like to thank you.
Thank me for what?
For helping Pat
with his studies.
You have no idea...
how disappointed we've
been over his grades.
But ever since Pat's
been seeing you,
he's like a totally
different person.
I think you're better than
all those famous tutors.
To be honest, we've
been planning this for some time.
We wanted Pat to study at the
same university as I did, at Boston.
But looking at his previous grades...
I knew he wouldn't make it.
So, I thought that...
you should go with him.
So you can help him study there.
Sounds good, right?
Don't worry about the expenses.
Share the living expenses with Pat.
As for tuition fees...
if you need any help...
you can let us know. Anytime.
I've some information
for you already.
You can take a look at it.
If money isn't an issue,
say yes, all right?
You know of the
STIC test, right?
It's like GAT/PAT, used to
apply to American universities.
It's the same test
at the same time, worldwide.
I need to take the STIC...
and I need to take
it within this year.
If not...
I won't be able to apply
to the university in time.
I've already been
busted once, Grace.
I'm not comfortable
asking you for help either
but we really don't
know what to do.
But Pat said he'll pay
you 600,000 baht.
Could you return this to Pat?
Yes, alright.
Could I borrow a pen
and some paper as well?
"I really can't help you guys this time. Sorry!!"
Miss.
- Hi baby, I'm so glad that you called.
- Hi dad.
It's so bright there.
What time is it?
It's noon, dad.
I hope you have a lot
of fun in Thailand!
Can you see what's time
it is here? Can you see?
Why it's so dark there?
It's nap time here.
Okay. I've got to check in.
Okay. Can I call you back later?
Good night.
Bye-bye.
Time zones.
The STIC is taken at the same
time and date worldwide.
This means countries here will take
the test earlier than the rest.
Simply,
If you two take it in Thailand
while I fly over and take
the test somewhere earlier.
Like Sydney, Australia.
4 hours ahead of Thailand.
I will get to see
the exam first.
Complete it first.
And send you guys the answers,
along with the others taking the test in
Thailand. As many people as we want.
Oh my God.
Not only will you get
enough to pass for university,
but we can also get more money
from other clients.
After deducting the costs,
we'll split the profits.
Is it too risky?
What risk?
It's not risky at all.
Who is this?
This is Mentor Lynn.
This is the only way
that I can earn enough
money to go study with you
without asking anyone.
Oh, I forgot to mention...
I'm going to Boston
with you guys.
Going together will
be so much fun!
The job for you two is
just to find clients for us.
As for the exam,
I'll take care of it.
Wait.
Before we go looking
for clients,
Now that I understand this
time zone thing,
but I'm still confused as to
how the hell are you
gonna give us the answers?
Write them down?
Memorize them.
The best way is to memorise it.
It's the safest way
and it leaves no trail.
Sorry. Are you part of the X-Men?
The STIC has over 100 questions.
Are you gonna remember all that?
I can.
If there's enough time.
The problem now is that
after I finish the test...
there's only so much time.
The most I can remember
half of all the answers.
Only half?
There's only one person
who can help.
But he wouldn't do it.
What's up, Mom?
I'm done.
Mr.s. Rut's house?
Can it be another day?
Tomorrow... I have the
scholarship exam at 8:00 a.m.
Hmm, yeah.
Hey, you!
Your basket grazed by mirror!
If you said sorry--
250,000 for a passing score...
that's not expensive for you, right?
The tutoring fee for the STIC
is way more expensive.
We'll need approximately 30 clients.
If more than this,
it will be risky.
Anything less, it won't be worth it.
I've got almost 30 people
in my STIC group chat.
If you can get them to join,
you'll get 5,000 baht
discount per head
from your full payment.
But wait a minute.
You must make sure no one
else knows about this.
Especially, that loser Bank.
Don't mind that dumbass.
He won't say shit.
Why?
Didn't you hear?
That dumbass picked a fight in
the wrong neighborhood.
He's beaten up pretty badly.
The best part is...
he didn't make it to
the scholarship exam.
Seminar:
To Becoming Number One in Education - 2B COME WON
I believe that everyone here
wants to pass the STIC
for a brighter future you are hoping for.
Shit, it's Steve Pat.
I have a way for us all to
get satisfactory scores.
The only things you're
allowed in the exam room
is a 2B pencil,
eraser,
exam ID,
and passport.
Communication devices
are definitely not allowed.
So the phone that I will be using
to send the answers back to Thailand,
will be hidden inside the
toilet tank in the washroom.
I'll try and send the answers
in between the breaks.
The exam is split into 3 parts,
with 2 breaks.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How will the clients
use the answers in the exam?
Not everyone can
remember like you.
Barcode.
Everyone will receive a 2B pencil
with a barcode stuck on it.
The different widths
of the barcode
will represent the
answer choices.
Starting from the left to right.
The thickest is A,
then B, C, and D.
Sounds cool, huh?
But there's more.
The 4 pencils
will represent the answers
for the 4 section.
And the numbers next to the barcode
are for grid-in questions.
For the essay part,
they usually use
published articles.
I'll send you the
keywords and you can Google them.
Hey, it's mine.
It fell.
Hey, I'm saying for the essay.
You'll have to write them yourselves.
In short, on the exam day,
everyone will leave the meeting
point before 7:30 a.m.
to arrive at the exam
centres on time.
We will provide
motortaxis for you
to take you to the exam centres.
Finally...
everyone will have to pay
in cash within the next 2 weeks.
Otherwise, the deal is off.
I'd also like to emphasize that
what we are doing here
is highly confidential.
Any questions?
If there aren't...
I will end the seminar now.
We will become one,
to be number one in education in education.
We'll get the scores needed to
get in any universities.
We choose the university,
the universities don't get to choose us!
Whoa. That's rough, "Little Bank".
What's up?
I'm sorry.
That you missed out on
the scholarship.
Same.
On that day...
I really didn't mean to.
I don't know if you
meant it or not.
What I do know is that you
are also responsible
for what happened to me.
I have a proposition for you.
What is it?
Taking an exam.
Taking an exam or cheating an exam?
To me the word "cheat"
implies someone doesn't benefit.
But we will get money, and the
others will get good scores.
It's a win-win.
Bank.
To be honest,
we're both are losers here.
We're not born to win
like Pat or Grace.
We must try harder
to get what's ours.
Look, what happened to you?
It's not the same.
You cheated.
I was just unlucky.
True.
But don't you see? Even
if you don't cheat...
life cheats you anyways.
This is Grace's address.
I'll see you tomorrow if
you're interested.
Honest Commerce Printing"
Honest Commerce Printing
Sit here, please.
Aren't you gonna take a seat?
Here is what's gonna happen
First...
we'll fly to Sydney and
take the STIC together.
Hey, Lynn.
You're missing a document.
Dad.
You remember that
show, Teen Genius?
They want me to
compete in Sydney.
They need your bank statement
for visa purposes.
Who are you going with?
With Bank.
Huh?
It's not just the two of
us, there's a teacher too.
Second...
You and I
will have to memorise
the answers, half each.
Don't forget...
Bank memorizes the first half,
and Lynn memorizes the second half.
Section 1 has 52 questions.
Start!
SECTION 1
52 Questions
SECTION 2
44 Questions
SECTION 3
16 Grid-in Questions
As for the last section,
you need to leave the exam early to
send the essay question in time.
Time's up for section 4.
Start the essay.
Memorising the question and key words
shouldn't be a problem for you.
But the hard part is they
won't let you leave early.
To avoid any suspicion,
you have to act sick.
Sure.
I can throw up.
Do I have to puke now?
No!
How much am I getting?
1 million.
What about you guys?
2 million.
What do you say, Bank?
Everything is in your hands.
Okay.
We got it!
Right on time.
Yes!
You should've just said yes
from the beginner. Such a poser.
Hey, guys!
See you tomorrow at 1:00 p.m.
1:00 p.m., my ass.
The flight's at 11:00 p.m.
What's the rush?
There is one more thing
we need to rehearse.
Please stop.
You just can't keep on
grilling the weakling!
You must be enjoying...
seeing innocents
cry like this.
That's too much, Pat.
Way too much.
I've used up all my cards.
You guys are acting as if
we are really getting caught.
I told you I understand...
if you get caught,
we'll blame only you.
Last question before
heading to the airport.
Last question.
In character.
Ready?
What if Bank gets caught?
What will you say?
That's even more far-fetched.
I've never been friends with him.
I've seen him around
school for 4-5 years.
I've never seen
him with any friends.
He looks like ass.
And he's a weirdo.
Outside of school, he even got
beaten up and dumped in a landfill.
Are we done?
Stop!
Bank, stop!
I said stop!
Fucker!
Bank!
What the hell is wrong with you?
You're the one who
told me to say this.
So, why are you mad at me?
Pat, stop.
Bank...
Bank, that's enough.
Why?
I...
You what?!
never...
told anyone that I
woke up in a landfill!
Now you know what I'm mad about!
All of you set me up, right?
You guys set me up so I
wouldn't get the scholarship, right?
You were all in it, right?
You guys knew, right?
You knew, right?
Why the fuck aren't you answering?
Bank, Bank, Bank, Bank, Bank.
Calm down, Bank.
I don't want to fucking
hear what you have to say!
Bank, stop! Let's talk this out.
Let's talk this out. Let's talk this out.
Calm down. Calm down.
Okay?
I'm sorry, Bank.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think they'd
be so rough on you.
Bank, hear me out.
You're still taking
the STIC, right?
Fuck the STIC!
Bank, Bank, Bank, Bank, Bank.
Listen to me.
You listen to me!
I only have my mom.
She's like a hunchback,
doing laundry.
You--
I'm not rich like you.
That scholarship was my dream.
The dream for my mom
to live comfortably.
And then you came.
Bank...
If I don't pass the STIC,
my dad will kill me.
Please, Bank.
Please.
I win, you win.
It's a win-win for the both of us.
Bank, I beg of you.
Then...
You should send those thugs to
beat up your dad!
Why do you say shit like that?!
Didn't you tell me
that you needed him?
And if I didn't play dirty,
do you think he'd help you out?
Lynn!
Wait, let's talk about this.
Were you in on this?
I really didn't know.
Please try to understand Pat.
He did it because he wanted
to help with your plan.
Without considering
who would get hurt?
The Future of Laundry
Grace, refund the money.
I'm out.
Wait, Lynn.
Calm down.
Okay, I respect your decision.
If you're out, I'm out.
No more clients, okay?
It'll just be the 3 of us,
like we originally planned.
Don't you understand?
I said I'm out.
Okay.
I guess that's it.
I just have one request,
Don't be mad at me.
If I had half your brain,
I wouldn't do something
this stupid.
Please.
Flight leaves in 3 hours.
Let's get going, Lynn.
Bank.
I'll go through with it.
At least there's money in it.
I won't get beaten up for free.
What if I told you that...
I don't wanna do it anymore.
I'm not asking you.
The only reason I'm here
is because of you.
The only reason I ended up in a
landfill is because of you.
The only reason all of this
shit is happening is because of you.
Don't you think you're also responsible?
SYDNEY
Here's your phone.
Lynn.
Hmm?
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
Well...
Your nose.
Hmm.
You know...
I've never been abroad before.
From tomorrow onwards,
we can go anywhere we want to.
Come on, let's take a selfie.
FINAL TEST
This year, the STIC test is cancelled
in the many countries across Asia.
Such as China and Korea.
This is because the
College Board has acknowledged
the STIC question were
leak prior to the test date.
This year the College Board has to
increase security procedures for the test.
To ensure no more problems.
All applicants.
Please gather here.
Come on guys! Wake up!
Good!
Congratulations.
You are the last group of people
who can go inside
and take the test.
Anyone who gets here late will
not be allowed to do so.
All your belongings,
especially mobile phone,
must be kept here.
We will collect them downstairs.
All test takers,
Please make sure to fill out every blank space
with your information in your answer sheet.
Section 1 will be a reading test,
consist of 52 question.
You will have 45 minutes
to complete them.
Starting now!
5 minutes left!
Time's up!
Please put your pencils down.
Your answer sheet
will be collected
while you're on your
10-minute break.
Honest Commerce Printing
The first break is
from 5:15-5:25 a.m.
[We're ready.]
I need to take a sh--.
What you are doing man?
What the-- What?
[Bank?]
[I want another million.]
1 more million? You ass!
Fuck you!
Pat!
[What happened, Bank?]
Damn!
[Transfer the money into my account within 5 minutes]
[Otherwise, I'm not sending you the first half of the answers]
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
What the fuck?
Ask him! What the fuck
is wrong with him?!
Pat, Pat. Calm down.
I can't calm down!
Fuck you, Bank!
[This is Grace. I thought we already agreeed about the money.]
[First million is for hiring me]
[The second million is for getting beaten up.]
[This is all I've got.]
[You'll get the rest when you send the rest of the answers.]
The exam will start in 1 minute.
Please return to the exam room.
Okay.
A B B C C A
C A B C D B
B A C B C D
Now it's fair game.
Let's gget back to it.
You may start section 2 now!
Time's up for section 2.
You may start section 3 now!
Time's up!
10 minutes for the break.
[Next, grid-in answers]
Whoever is in there.
Please step outside.
Can you hear me?
Step outside, I said.
Now!
Someone has reported to us that
you are in there for too long.
Come out.
Now!
Get. Out. Now.
Can you hear me, boy?
Get out! Now, I said!
Hello?
Someone in there?
Please come outside, now!
You exam is about to start.
Please go back to class.
(IN ENGLISH) Thank you.
Look at me.
I'll give you a chance to
tell me everything!
What did you do?
Speak to me!
This doesn't have anything to do with you.
Go back to your test.
You may start section 4 now!
10 minutes left!
For Sale
Don't we need to leave
here before 7:30 a.m.?
Yeah!
It's 7 a.m., you're not paying enough!
I've already paid you everything.
Essay section starts now!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Come on. Are you okay?
I feel sick. Can we go home now?
If you leave now, your exam
score will be cancelled.
Do you understand?
Wait!
It's 7 a.m., why haven't
they sent the rest of the answers?!
How do I know--
Hello.
Is Lynn here?
I can't get in touch with her.
I haven't seen her.
She told me she went to
Sydney for a competition.
Oh yeah.
No wonder why we haven't seen her.
I'm sure she'll
bring back a medal.
But I found the
permission letter at home.
I called, but no one answered.
So, I came to the address on the sheet.
Can someone tell me what
Lynn is doing in Sydney?
Huh?!
Roger that. I can't see her.
Okay, okay, I'm
looking. Checking.
Yup. She's not here mate.
Keep looking. I'm coming up.
Did you find her?
I'm out.
If you don't answer me,
I'll go straight to the Headmistress.
Tell me, what are guys you up to again?!
Huh?!
Lynn and Bank are dating!
They went on a secret trip.
Lynn was afraid you
wouldn't let her go.
So, she lied.
I really didn't know
how to stop her.
I think it's best you talk to
your daughter, sir.
Okay.
C'mon!
Sir,
Love is a beautiful thing.
What's the matter?
It's 7 a.m. already.
The motortaxis are leaving.
They're saying we passed the agreed time.
You explain to them what's going on
Because I don't know a damn thing!
I'll talk to them.
What's with your leg?
It's almost 7:30.
Where at the barcodes?
I already paid the money.
What's the wait? What's the wait?
You'll get there in time!
- I promise.
- Pat!
Pat! We're out of stickers.
Here you go. 500 each.
We'll leave soon. We'll leave soon.
Shit!
(IN ENGLISH) Hey! Can you open the door?! Can
you open the door, please?!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
It's almost 7:30 a.m., Grace!
Do we have all the answers?!
No! 6 left.
- Why it does say EDGE?
- Huh?
It says EDGE!
What's EDGE?!
There's no reception.
What happens if
we don't make it?
And the money we paid?
We won't make it!
If we don't make it, we want our refund!
C'mon.
Did you get it, yet?
C
B
D
These 3 go to the
Bangkapi exam center.
These 2 rows to Suttisarn.
Did you get on, yet?
You didn't put your helmet on, put it on!
One set each, pass it on.
One set each!
We're ready!
Hurry up!
Wear your helmet!
Hey!
Are you okay?
(IN ENGLISH) No. I'm sick.
This doesn't matter.
You have to come back to
the test center with me.
Now!
I'm from the embassy.
A Thai student confessed to using
his phone as a dictionary.
We're resolving the situation.
(IN THAI) What will happen to him?
They'll probably
cancel his scores.
Worst case, he'll be banned
from the STIC forever.
As for you, they'll be questioning you.
If there isn't anything else, you may leave.
Just wait here.
I'll go talk to them.
Hold on.
What's the matter?
Huh?
May I use the toilet?
Of course.
Lynn!
Welcome back. Welcome back.
Mentor Lynn's FC here!
Thanks so much, Lynn.
We're celebrating at my house tonight.
Celebrate what?
Did you know that Bank got caught?
And my scores were cancelled, Pat.
Well...
we'll look for another
exam centre for you.
If you don't retake the exam,
you won't be able to apply
to university in time.
Hey, Lynn.
You have to retake the exam.
Pretty please?
I've changed my mind.
You've already got the
scores you needed.
But,
we can't go without you!
You do know, right?
That university exams aren't
multiple choices anymore.
Even if I went with you,
you wouldn't be able to copy me anyways.
I'll get back on my own.
Where's your boyfriend?
Where is he?
I wanted to invite him for dinner.
Where is he, huh?
Why didn't you tell me about him?
- Dad!
- Huh?
I have a confession to make.
What is it, honey?
What is it?
Why do you choose
to study in Education?
I want like to be a teacher,
like my father.
So, I can use my knowledge
in the best way.
Do you have experience in tutoring
or have you taught anyone before?
Yes, I have.
I scored 1,460 points on STIC
Being a teacher isn't
just about being good acedemically.
Do you think...
you can be a good example
in other things as well?
[Lynn. When are you coming?]
[Bank's taken his share, come get yours]
[Come quick, we already miss you]
I'm not going to lie.
I've done a lot a bad
things in the past.
But I will use them
to teach myself and others.
[Lynn left the chat]
It is such a waste,
To be honest, with
your knowledge and abilities,
You can apply for scholarships
to study abroad easily.
Aren't you interested
in any of them?
I think...
there's someone else who
deserves it more than me.
Student Expulsion Letter:
Thanaphon Viriyakul
Bank:
[Meet me at my place tonight.]
Come in.
The store looks
fresh, Little Bank.
Oh wait, it's Mister Bank now.
You laundering money?
You were expelled from
school because
the embassy reported you, right?
Hmm.
What's next?
That's the reason why
I asked you over.
Did you apply for
the GAT/PAT exams?
I have a proposition for you.
I have a fool-proof plan.
Much safer.
We can get the answers
out to more people.
More importantly, there're more
GAT/PAT clients than STIC clients.
But this plan...
can't be done without Mentor Lynn.
How much more of this do you need?
If your cut wasn't enough...
my cut is still with Pat.
You can go get it.
No.
Wait.
It's not about how much money we got.
It's about,
from now on,
how much more we can make.
Lynn.
From my calculations.
This round...
there's at least
10 million in it.
Don't you think it's
worth the risk again?
You were there.
Even if we get caught,
it doesn't mean we go to jail.
To be honest, Lynn.
Why would you endure
studying for 4 years
for a 5 figure salary?
When you can earn millions right now.
Why work a stupid desk job?
That's probably because for me,
no amount of money is worth it.
Lynn.
If you don't do this...
I'll tell everyone that
you're the mastermind
behind the STIC scandal.
I guarantee you.
You'll be banned from
studying abroad just like me.
Fine. We're even then.
It won't just be you!
This includes Grace,
Pat,
and all the clients who
took the STIC too.
Think about it...
if the board finds out,
they might even cancel all the
scores in Thailand.
One last thing, Lynn.
Your dad will be so
disappointed in you.
Don't be afraid, honey.
We'll get through
this, no matter what.
Smile.
Smile with me.
Ms. Rinrada?
You once told me...
if we win, we win together.
If we lose, we lose together.
I won't be the only one
taking all the blame.
If you won't do it,
I'll make sure you go down with me!
What do you say, Lynn?
What's it going to be?
Everything is up to you now.
You're right.
Everything is up to me.
We are here to record your confession
to the suspected cheating on the STIC test.
So, are you ready?
(IN ENGLISH) I'm ready.