The suspect opened fire.
I'm shot, but it's not serious.
The balcony door is open, inspector. He may run.
What do we do?
Go down and provide backup.
Freeze, police!
Stop!
Get down here!
Get back here.
Don't move! No funny business!
Little one. Avoiding my calls?
What's going on, Kai?
What else is there?
It's my handsome brother's birthday!
Happy birthday!
What are you doing?
What's with the attitude?
Forget it. Forget it.
Today's my first operation.
You've really picked the perfect time to call.
A real cop now, aren't ya?
You've taken the game quite seriously now.
That was when we were kids. This is for real.
It's been ages since I've been home.
How's the old man?
Talking about you every day.
Walk!
I gotta go. We'll talk later.
Who is it?
My buddy from Taiwan.
He's doing pretty well out here.
That's good!
What's wrong?
Isn't your brother a cop now?
That's good for us.
Fight on!
Earthquake!
An earthquake!
"L say, it's better to spend life on the sea"
you're always off-key.
"A better tomorrow 2018"
my boss is moving drugs.
My boss also fired that shot.
Hurry up-
I hear someone's been holding a shipment.
Transporting by sea
where is he going?
Japan.
Mr. okamura.
I'm sorry, we've come too early.
This is the Mr. okamura I've been
telling you about. Very powerful man.
He sets off an earthquake when he's angry.
Japan's an active earthquake zone anyway.
Because he's always angry.
Bullshit.
What a goddamn poser.
We can be posers, too.
You're expert smugglers,
but I'm not interested in that.
There's a great demand for synthetic drugs here,
and the risk is just as great.
We all love a good adventure.
So you want us to move cocaine.
Thanks,
but no thanks.
What was that?
What the hell was that?
Rubberband,
what the hell were you thinking,
introducing me to a client like this?
You...
Who can make the call?
Actually...
Excuse me.
Kai.
You people don't know what you're doing!
Actually, we know exactly what we're doing.
Turning down a chance to work with me...
You must be blind!
You want to poke my eye out?
I won't blink.
You sure have an interesting way
of doing things here.
I don't feel the earth shaking.
"Move a tad to the right. Back to the left."
I thought I told you to stop singing.
Kai,
you have the right to stop listening,
but you can't take away my right to sing.
I'll kick your ass.
The cantonese version is even better. Teach me.
Later.
If that jap really did
try to stick a toothpick into your eye,
would you be scared?
Of course I would, but I can't be intimidated.
You get scared, too.
Settle down.
Kai,
nice weather today! It's so peaceful.
I'm counting on you, as always,
boss.
You're the boss. So generous.
It's nothing. Good fortune for all.
Had many girls this time?
I'm not like you.
I heard that business is getting tougher
hi.
It's been a long time.
Your poor father,
getting dementia at such a young age.
You two brothers barely spare any time for him.
Is it so hard?
The cops trained me well, didn't they?
Barely out of the academy and already a workaholic.
What will happen when we get married?
Don't forget,
there's one more person you have to meet:
My brother.
Your brother is out at sea for a year at a time.
He never takes care of you.
Is his opinion that important?
It's very important.
Only on the sea can you appreciate its beauty.
The sea is my world,
my home,
my brother,
and my father.
Don't get all sentimental.
How was that sentimental?
Kai,
how does it feel to have a father?
Let me put it this way:
A father is like a port.
When you're out at sea, you don't think about it.
But when you have to get off the boat..
Come on, don't be so deep.
You're mocking me because I'm an orphan.
How about this:
Having a father is sometimes like having a brother.
Do you get it now?
Kai.
Why don't we...
Make a blood oath and become brothers?
Formalities are meaningless.
We're already brothers, aren't we?
No, you don't get it.
When I was a punk in Taiwan...
No matter how much the world changes,
brotherhood never changes.
Kai.
Kai. Can we talk somewhere?
We can talk here. We're among friends.
As ha said before,
we can't spend the rest of our lives at sea.
Exactly. Then we can all go legit.
That's not what I mean.
The japs are giving us a great opportunity here.
We're not discussing that.
You can't even show me a bit of respect?!
Why the hell do you deserve my respect?!
What the hell?
What the hell?!
You wanna play rough?
Takeit
you goddamn wimp,
you don't have the balls to shoot.
You Taiwan punk.
Kai,
someone from home's here.
Got it.
Shall we bring out the food?
Go ahead.
Changing course
slow it down.
I really want to be on the front line with them.
Careful
catch this.
See ya.
Take care.
When I was a kid,
i would wait for my brother by the shore.
Keep going.
My brother began working on boats
before he'd even finished high school.
Sometimes he'd be gone for a year.
But when he comes home,
he'd always brought me good food
and fun toys.
He'd tell me amazing stories, too.
Sounds like you really idolize your brother.
We used to play cops and robbers
when we were kids.
But I could never beat him.
Then your brother must be a natural criminal.
Kai.
This is the Chinese coast guard.
Stop your engine and prepare for inspection.
That's them.
This is the Chinese coast guard.
Stop your engine and prepare for inspection.
They remodeled their ship.
We can't catch up!
Push the engines.
We've raided these smugglers a few times.
Have they ever been caught with narcotics?
No, sir.
Hands on your head.
Don't move. Behave yourselves.
Fire a warning shot.
What is he doing?
That's enough. Let them go.
Understood.
We've lost them.
Let's go.
Welcome back, Kai.
Brought back something nice?
Thanks, Kai!
You must've had some fun, Kai.
Mei-lin must be eager to see you.
Piss off!
Good work.
"L say, it's better to spend life on the sea"
"i can't look back in fear of confusion"
"there's someone that loves you,
but you love someone else"
see you tomorrow.
I'm going to see ha first.
Don't drink too much.
You, too.
Mark.
Mark. It's been forever.
Miss me?
Police, freeze!
Let go.
Can you stop toying with me?
- Can you behave properly?
- Cut the bullshit.
You punk.
Think you're something now?
What? You always nabbed me when we were kids.
Why can't I nab you just once?
Catch me? It ain't that easy.
Is dad home?
He's in the hospital.
I came home to pick up some things.
What's wrong with him?
His dementia's acting up again.
Take me to the hospital.
Kai.
I have something to tell you.
I already know.
I got a present for your girlfriend. How is it?
When did you become so awfully nice?
You rascal.
It's about time I meet her.
Of course.
I want to know what you think of her.
Alright. Come down.
Practically a grown man
it's the boat's problem, not mine.
You know I've got skills behind the wheel.
Ha.
- Shut up.
- I'm awesomely skillful.
I've been in this game way before you have pubes.
Go play with the girls.
"Fate will decide whether you'll be rich or poor"
"it never seems right..."
"It's my pleasure to have you by my side"
"I'll smile as I depart with no regrets"
"i say, it's better to spend life on the sea"
"i can't look back in fear of confusion"
there's nothing wrong with me.
There aren't enough beds here.
I don't want to trouble them.
I should leave now.
No.
The doctor said you can go home tomorrow.
Be good.
We'll do whatever you want tomorrow.
Doc.
When I leave tomorrow,
will my son come pick me up?
Which son are you talking about?
I have two sons.
One is a sailor, and the other is a cop.
I hear the sailor was a real pain to deal with.
Such a pain.
I didn't hesitate to beat some sense into him,
so he ran off early.
The one who became a cop...
He must've been well-behaved.
I drove his brother away,
so he had a tough time growing up.
Those damn bullies.
Never mind.
Actually,
I've always wanted to
apologize to them.
Apologize to them.
You know.
By the way.
I got you some health food from abroad.
They're good for you. Remember to eat them.
You shouldn't have. This is too much.
It's not much.
What is this?
What's wrong with you? He cannot eat this stuff.
Who asked you to bring these?
I've written down the things he can eat.
Just follow the list.
This room is for family only.
Chao. Come over here.
Your friend is going to get your dad hurt.
I don't think he's trustworthy.
But he thinks you're trustworthy.
I don't want to talk to you.
That man is my brother.
Today's top story:
A joint raid by customs and the police
uncovered a shipment of smuggled goods.
Two suspects
fled the scene during the raid.
Now
the police are...
And then?
I've never seen these two.
Perhaps they don't belong to the same gang.
Inspector guo.
Superintendent song. The meeting's over?
How's your injury?
I'm fine.
An)' Progress?
No one's seen these guys before.
I'll keep looking into it.
My guess is... this is a team of smugglers
changing careers.
I'll send you a few more guys.
Sure.
Hang in there.
I'll be fine.
Hey, handsome.
Making repairs this time of night?
Hey, gorgeous.
Anything need fixing?
That ship's been ashore for a year.
It's probably broken already.
Let's give it a try.
All these years...
You're still dragging your feet.
And I've been at your Beck and call.
Where is your conscience?
Client
do you know what I hate the most?
I do.
Being lied to.
I never lied to you.
Are you my boyfriend or something?
You don't own me.
Enough already.
How long are you staying this time?
Ask my big brother.
Your big brother?
You mean Kai.
You'll do whatever Kai asks?
Of course.
And if Kai asks you to croak?
Then I'll croak.
I'm sorry, ha.
Sorry for being late.
This is...
This is my godson.
Kai.
Take a seat.
Your boy doesn't need a seat, right?
He's not my boy.
He's my brother.
Everyone here is my brother.
Sit down, everyone.
Looks like we're all here.
Hi, ha.
This is Kai's...
Hello, Mei-lin.
What's your name?
This must be your first time.
Just ca“ me gang.
Don't be a stranger, ok?
Looking sexy tonight, rubberband.
You've got a good eye.
Wore yourself out last night, mark?
Thanks, Mei-lin.
Kai, no alcohol for you tonight.
Have some tea.
I have something to attend to.
You'll have to excuse me.
Uncle, why don't I...
Listen, Kai,
cang just came here from the countryside.
You've got plenty to learn from Kai.
Don't learn from me
I'm getting behind on the times.
Things are changing too quickly these days.
Come on.
Thanks for your hard work, guys.
Good thing yesterday was a false alarm.
Watch your back more carefully from now on.
Cheers!
Good work!
Ha.
The world's changing.
Smugglers like us
are no better than those overseas shoppers.
And we risk our lives at sea.
The work isn't worth the pay.
Are you scared?
Just say what you want to say.
I'm making myself clear already.
I want to move something else.
Like what?
If we're going to keep moving cargo by boat,
we should move whatever brings in the most cash.
We've established a pretty clear set of rules,
haven't we, ha?
No drugs and no waste.
We're just looking to make a few bucks.
We're not to inflict harm upon anyone.
You're a noble one.
These are the rules.
Rules aren't sacred.
What are you doing?
What is this?
That's enough. Talk it out.
Ha,
are we running two boats or one?
You tell me.
Of course we're on the same boat.
But as ha said,
everyone knows that Kai
has made a fortune
running the Japan route.
You alone hold the contact list
of our clients in Japan.
Why don't you take it out?
Share the wealth.
So we can get rich together.
There's no point
in forcing anyone's hand.
What you want is in here.
Sure,
you can use it to make some extra cash.
But I have one condition.
Stay away from drugs, we stay on the boat.
If not, I'm getting off.
I, ha, care a great deal about loyalty.
Who do you think you are?
If he didn't have your back,
I'd kill you today.
I can kill you right now.
Bring it on.
You,
get out.
Did you forget that I'm right here?
Am I dead to you?
By the way.
I have a deal going down tonight.
I need you to take care of it.
What kind of deal?
Oh.
Those japs do everything by the book.
Do it for me.
Sure.
Consider it a last favor.
Stay out of the exchange tonight.
Sure.
You must be joking.
You've never kept me away from a deal before.
Unless...
Just stay away.
It'll be a simple exchange.
I still want to be there.
Are you gonna listen to me or not?
What's wrong?
This is a copy.
Never settle in one place. I'll just lose it.
Then give it to Mei-lin.
All women change,
except for yours.
He's not answering.
- Don't worry, inspector guo.
- We're going into overtime.
Gear up.
There's something I have to do tonight.
I can't pick up dad from the hospital.
I already brought him home.
Everything is alright now. He wants to see you.
I'll be home tomorrow.
By the way, your girlfriend's a nice girl.
Alright.
Table for four under zhou.
Two guests are here already.
Let's order
ls it too bright in here?
Those two japs look ice cold.
Pair of posers.
Mark.
Long time no see.
- Hey, boss.
- You're back.
Same old, same old.
Say, handsome,
you are not eating. What's with the toothpick?
Here you go.
Bill, please.
No worries, I'll keep it on your tab.
Thanks.
What is it?
Let's go somewhere else. We can't talk here.
We're here to talk business, not flirt.
I hope you'll respect our wishes.
What about cargo
that you've brought this time...
You can see it later.
I want to see it now.
L.
Go to the bathroom.
Kai,
my buddy told me that
rubberband already checked the cargo
with the Japanese.
He's already on the boat, on his way to Japan.
Those two guys are shady.
Watch your back.
I'll on my way.
I'm fine.
Wait, I need to use the bathroom.
Then“.
Let's go together.
Shall we?
Out of the way!
Go after him.
Push it open!
I can't open it!
Get down
hurry up-
police, freeze!
Come out.
Come out right now!
Run!
Freeze!
Or I'll fire!
Over here.
Kai.
Don't move.
Kai, let's just hide here.
That way's a dead end.
He'll make his way back here for sure.
You go that way.
I'll go this way.
No way. You're hurt.
Go! Right now!
I'm sorry.
They're going down tunnel four.
Rubberband set us up.
Stop the car.
Where are you?
Stay out of sight.
You better leave town.
Stop! You,
toss away the object in your hand.
Put your hands up.
Run if you can, Kai.
I won't get away.
Put both your hands up!
Bro,
looks like we won't see each other for a while.
I say again,
put both your hands up!
Take care of yourself.
Keep going or what, man?
Do you hear me? I'm talking to you.
Buddy, are you sure
you want to take the fall for this?
Who's the other person in the sewer?
He must have a backup copy.
Search again.
I only know that he lives here.
I don't know anything else.
You guys carry on.
I, ha, care a great deal about loyalty.
Thanks, ha.
What are you doing?
Just getting a shot, Mei-lin.
What are you guys doing?
Mei-lin.
Shut up.
I understand, inspector Cheng.
Lam going home.
You thieve!
I'll kill you!
Someone help! Thieve!
Stop screaming!
Dad!
Thank you.
Who are you?
What do you want?
It's none of your business.
Another one.
I hear a friend of yours got crippled
while avenging you.
This really happened?
No talking, 8015.
Few more bottles.
Put it on his tab.
It's chao.
I know. Officer.
What do you want?
Thanks.
What happened in the bar in Japan...
That was you, wasn't it?
I hear that the shooter
only shot the jap in the legs.
That's why he was let go.
Don't worry.
Your brother didn't say anything.
He's your brother, too.
Why don't you leave this city?
Why should I leave?
I just want you to stay out of trouble.
Nervous about something?
It's for your own good. And my brother's, too.
Again.
Police!
Get out of the car.
Don't move!
During yesterday's raid,
the police apprehended three suspects.
Here's a report from the scene.
What the hell is this?
I'm talking to you.
Stop running.
Got you.
A special gift.
Promise me.
Don't break it again.
No matter what you say, I stay true to myself
in the end, I believe that silence is golden
I hear you kept your mouth closed.
You must think you're real righteous.
I used to have a friend
that was just like you.
In the end,
before he met his maker,
he told me that
those who have the guts to repent
are the real heroes.
Everything in this world is cyclical.
We go through a cycle every few decades.
Where are you going, pal?
You need a car, buddy?
Public transport will take forever.
Where are we going?
Train station.
What for?
You need to leave this city.
Where is dad's grave?
I want to pay my respects.
Get out.
Do you remember what you said before?
You said you hate being lied to.
Liar...
What did you do to me?
What did you do to dad?
You got dad killed.
How dare you show your face to him?
Also,
you used to be preachy as hell.
How did you turn into a mute in prison?
You want to protect your buddies?
You want to be loyal?
I can tell you're pretty loyal to them.
You fraud.
Listen up,
you better stay away from me.
I never want to see you again.
Piss off!
You're home.
I thought you have meetings all day.
What happened to your hand?
Nothing. I was arresting a perp.
Why were you arresting a perp at a meeting?
You're hiding something from me.
How dare you show your face here!
How dare you!
I just wanted to see dad.
Stop it, chao.
Chao.
Come in, Kai.
Have some water.
Thanks.
Did dad say anything before he died?
If there's ever a rift
between you two.
Try your best
to forgive each other.
I'm telling you right now,
I'll never forgive you.
Dad.
Listen,
if you go back to your old ways,
I'll put you in handcuffs myself.
Forward, my brother!
Turn!
Get down now. I'm tired.
No way!
I want another ride!
Forward!
Kai,
that crippled man fixing boats at the docks
is your best friend, right?
What are you chatting about, 8453?
Nothing, sir.
Go mind your own business.
Is there someone named mark here?
Do you know anyone named mark?
He has a limp.
There.
There's the gimp.
Gimp!
"No one should be alone forever"
"it's my pleasure to have you by my side"
"ln the end, I believe that silence is golden"
still handsome after all these years,
and still singing off-key.
What's wrong?
Nothing
your leg...
Forget it.
I couldn't get away quick enough.
I'm fine now.
Look,
I can still kick asses
and I can still bend it.
It's fine.
I owe you one.
Don't say that.
I'm glad you're back.
I truly am.
We can work together again.
In what?
Our old business.
Let's do it.
I don't want to go back to that.
Let's do something legit.
Something steady.
Sure.
Something...
Steady...
Are you sure?
Are you afraid?
I suffered for three years.
I pondered for three years.
I waited for you for three years.
Now that you are back, and you want to go legit.
Even gang has made ne. Way to the top.
Did you know that?
Enough said, I get it.
Your little brother is a cop.
He's more important than me, right?
You used to listen to me.
You've changed.
"No matter how much the world changes,
brotherhood never changes." That's what you said.
I've repaired your boat.
It's sitting at the west pier.
Mei-lin insists on living there.
Go see her.
She's helpless.
Wait.
There you are, Kai.
It's been a while.
Out of my way.
Mark.
Kai.
- Pick him up.
- Leave me alone.
My man is out of line, Kai.
You are messing with my buddy in front of me.
What the hell!
I want to thank you for not snitching
on me years ago.
I also want you to know that
there's a spot for you on my team.
Brothers should make money together.
Let's get drinks some time.
Stand right there. I don't need your help.
Go away!
Go!
Get outta here!
What the hell is this?
Are you even real gangsters?
The repairman's back.
Why don't you fix me?
Fix me.
What the hell is this?
I'm living here.
I like the smell here.
What are you doing? Do I repel you?
I'm meeting a client.
I'll come see you later.
It's been three years.
What was I supposed to do?
I dare you to hit me!
Never.
Can we start with a clean slate
here,
try this.
No, thanks.
Please help me out, ha.
If you buy from me,
I can guarantee one hundred percent
customer satisfaction.
Isn't this
a waste of your talents?
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
Give me a better price next time.
I'll be a loyal customer.
Come in for some water.
Not bad, right?
Sea snail. 50 each.
Come back if you ever decide to quit.
I'll take all of this.
Coming right up.
I know.
Next time, then.
Look at them. Very lively.
Thanks, bro.
Hurry.
Wait, put that down.
This is my turf. What do you think you're doing?
Who the hell are you?
Wait. We're in the same line of work.
- You better open your eyes.
- No need for violence.
Maybe we want to get violent.
Pal.
Are you still buying this shipment?
Hey, put in some motor oil
and tune up the engine.
Clean up the cabin while you're at it.
Wait, I'm not done.
Be sure to clean the bed, too.
Answer me!
Are you done talking? Can we talk later?
What the hell does that mean?
Listen,
call your wife right now and tell her about me.
What do you want?
Do you love me more or your wife more?
Tell me the truth.
You told me you have a boat.
I thought you have a huge yacht.
You want the truth?
Alright, then.
Do you love me or my boat?
You gold digger
how dare you!
Is this what you wanted?
Are you happy?
True enough for you?
What?
You've never seen a couple fight?
Go on with your damn business.
Go on!
It's none of your business.
Are you okay, hone)”
where are you hurt? Let me see.
Why are you fighting?
How could you hit him?
What's going on?
This is my most important client!
You will not get even a cent this month.
I'm so sorry, Mr. cai.
We'll compensate you for your troubles.
My buddy says,
cang is making drugs.
Stay away from him.
I'm at the Fisherman's wharf every morning
buying seafood.
Come join me anytime.
Police!
Don't move.
Where did you get this?
Gang..-
have you seen him.
No.
Who's the dealer.
His name is cang.
Thanks.
There are four, five people named cang here.
One of them goes to a restaurant that
bought seafood from your brother.
This guy looks suspicious as hell.
Keep an eye on him.
What the hell, man?
How dare you show your face here again?
You're not gonna give up, aren't you?
So what?
What'd you say?
Do you know who's in charge here?
How dare you touch my big brother?
Let's go.
Let's work together.
I can't do this job anymore.
What's happened?
It's hard to stay afloat in this business.
Since the place is coming down,
might as well close for good.
The world's changing too quickly.
To see something so nice go to waste.
What a shame.
That's the way it goes.
Come on, drinks on me.
Sounds good.
Party time
let's celebrate.
For what?
- No matter how much the world changes.
- Brotherhood never changes.
I think we should make it offical.
Let's make the blood oath.
What a hard place to find.
Interesting spot you got here.
Kai, what a coincidence. Good to see you again.
Are you stalking me?
Stalking?
I have a lot of employees.
They have time on their hands.
What? You want to stir trouble again?
Bro,
I'm here to apologize.
What happened last time was my fault.
Just get to the point.
Sure.
You've been away for the past few years,
but the business has to go on.
That's why I had to
take over your Japan route.
But I've expanded the range of cargo.
Now I move whatever makes the most money.
You're just like rubberband.
How can that be?
Rubberband is always too rash.
Kai,
you know...
Okamura's a decent man with principles.
What happened last time
they know it wasn't personal,
so they are willing to let it go.
Kai, I can tell
that they're impressed with you.
Stop stalling,
I've left that behind long ago.
Just tell me why you're really here.
You're clever, Kai.
Your little brother chao works
in the narcotics unit.
He's getting a little too close.
So...
Why don't you invite him out for a drink?
Make some new friends.
You want a cop to help your operation?
The world's changed. Money is everything.
Money is what makes heroes nowadays.
You've really mellowed.
We've got a deal, then, Kai.
I hear that ha isn't your godfather...
But your real father.
Is that so?
What are you guys chatting about?
Not much.
So you're hanging out with them again.
I'm not.
I told you,
if you go back to your old ways, I'll...
You've got it wrong.
What happened was...
What happened was that I saw you with them.
Can you let me finish?
Go ahead.
Chaon.
Don't call me chao.
I'm a police officer.
Sir.
Officer.
Where I live and whom I've met.
Go find out yourself
lwill.
Why won't you believe me?
I did, once.
Then what happened?
Why can't you give me a chance?
I'm a man of my word.
Sure.
I'll give you a chance.
A chance to leave this city.
There are plenty of opportunities out there.
I'm not leaving this city.
This place is my home
officer, I know where you can find drug dealers.
Let's talk outside.
My number. Call me if you need me.
Wait.
Who is he to you?
Who is he to you? Your brother!
- So what?
- What the hell do you mean?
Look at how he's treated you.
Look at how you've treated him.
Don't touch me!
I'll do what I want!
Do you have a brother?
What do you know?
I don't have a brother of my own,
but I know your big brother better than you.
I know.
You are partners in crime.
Of course you understand him.
It's been years. He paid his debt.
Why can't you forgive him?
I just don't.
What's wrong with you?
Assaulting a police officer?
Look, I can arrest you right now.
Go ahead!
You want to arrest your brother anyway,
so start with me.
You think I want to arrest him?
Do you have any idea how terrible I felt
when I arrested him three years ago?
He's a wreck, too.
So, I don't want to do it again.
I don't want to cuff him again.
Stop it already!
What do you want to know, handsome?
Do you know gang'?
Just hear me out
we didn't finish our conversation the other day.
The cops are on my ass.
Can you help me, Kai?
Who do you think I am?
I don't run the police.
I know,
but your little brother and his friends
are getting in my way.
They're pushing me hard
and if they force my hand,
it won't be my fault.
What are you trying to say?
Tell me exactly
what you're gonna do.
If anyone makes my life miserable
then I'm gonna make sure his life is, too.
Besides,
I know where
your little brother lives.
For the sake of his safety...
Kai,
you should do something,
seeing how you're his brother and all.
Be careful.
Don't mess it up.
Got it.
Ain't an easy place to find, is it?
What are you up to now?
You really have some balls, don't you?
He's in conference room one, right?
Cheng, he's looking for inspector guo.
Let him wait. Inspector's in a meeting.
I'll ask for backup from special forces.
Then I'll lead this operation.
Sir,
this is urgent. It really is.
Those guys have guns.
What's going on?
What do you want?
Can you send him away?
Why can't you tell me?
If a cop's older brother is a criminal,
the cop should recuse himself, right?
What do you mean by criminal? Get to the point.
Calm down, chao. Let's talk.
Go on.
Why are you so anxious?
Take a seat.
Have some water.
Go ahead.
I'll tell you everything you want to know.
In exchange,
keep chao off this case.
Tell me, what does Kai want?
This is my idea.
What do you want?
Lam just bored. I wanted to take a walk.
I dare you to untie me.
Let him go. See what he'll do.
"The number you're dialing can't be reached..."
The superintendent sent you brother home.
What did he say?
He said the other man in the sewer back then
was gang.
Go grab a bite with me.
This takeout sucks.
Listen,
sit out of this afternoon's operation.
Superintendent's orders.
Fire!
Come on!
Help!
I told you to be careful.
You're in big trouble when cang comes back.
Sir,
how do I get to this place.
He was gone when I turned around.
Take a left, then another right.
- Did you order takeout?
- That's right.
Police, freeze!
Who's inside?
Six people inside, all armed.
All on the second floor.
Police!
Stop!
Stop the car!
Split up.
Freeze!
Are you alright?
Who the hell are you?
Get out.
My car's been jacked!
Police. I need your car.
What are you looking at? Get out!
Get on. I will drive.
You amature. Get out!
Hurry up!
Freeze! Police!
We're going towards the tunnel.
I thought you were told to sit this one out.
You really are something.
Don't ram him in the city.
We don't want any casualties.
He's got nowhere to go.
Stop!
I haven't been on the sea in ages.
The sea still looks beautiful from here.
Right?
The last time you were beat up like this
was ten years ago.
Right.
That was the first time you saved me.
It's been that long?
Look at you, still love to play the hero.
That's not true.
I just want a simple life.
I have to finish what I've started.
You've already lost one leg.
I will see it through even if I lose both legs.
Don't be stupid.
You are afraid
that's right.
I'm terrified.
I've already lost my father.
I'm afraid of losing my little brother, too.
He'll be just fine.
I don't know.
All I know
is that he won't stop what he's determined to do.
The more I try to stop him, the harder he'll go.
You two are exactly the same.
No way.
You want to go legit,
but he won't believe you.
You want him to forgive you,
but he wants to arrest you.
As for me,
you'll always be my big brother,
no matter what you do.
You'll have to choose a little brother to keep.
Police. Please cooperate.
I know.
My buddy says,
cang will go to Japan tomorrow
via a cargo ship.
Is he trying to flee?
That's right?
What do we do?
It's perfect. We'll finally have peace.
You'll let him get away?
That guy is nuts.
No one can stop him.
Kai.
I can't just let him get away.
Listen to me for once.
Stay out of this.
It's over.
Sure,
I'll listen to you on this.
What's going on?
That's what I should be asking you.
Where the hell is cang?
You must know.
Where are you?
Let's talk face-to-face.
Fine.
Meet in front of the park in ten minutes.
I'll wait for you.
Well?
We've searched all over.
Our big fish is gone.
"L say, it's better to spend life on the sea"
out of my way.
Out of my way.
Doc.
Where's the emergency room?
How is he?
They say that
he's conscious. He's not in any danger.
But the test results haven't come back yet.
Has he said anything?
He's still in a daze.
He just kept mumbling,
"can9~"
I'd better go inside.
We set out tonight.
Got it.
Let's do it!
Slow down.
Stop right there!
Jump.
Jump!
Help!
Let me help you, Kai.
I got it.
Help!
I can't breathe!
Save me!
Help me!
Please!
Take care of yourself.
Are we almost there?
This is the fastest way.
I think we'll arrive after nightfall.
Have you told chao?
No rush.
I forgot to ask you,
where did you get that gun?
I brought it back from Japan.
I hid one in your boat, too,
but you never found it.
Officer!
This is a personal feud.
Come save your wife yourself
if you have the balls.
Quan, help me trace this number
and tell me the current location.
Don't tell inspector guo.
Never thought this would happen to you, did you?
My boys saw what you did.
I gotta talk to you.
Your brother...
Not about him.
Mei-lin...
She was a special girl.
But after she touched drugs,
anyone can have her.
I won't fight back.
Come on.
I wanted you to know that
anything that you can have,
lcan,too.
By the way.
One night,
she called out the wrong name.
She called me Kai.
Where's Lulu?
She's not here.
You can talk to me instead.
Why the hell should I do that?!
Don't be so anxious.
Let's talk.
Mr. ha.
You impress me.
You really showed up
unarmed
where is Lulu?
Bring her out.
Don't be afraid, I'm right here.
Don't be scared, Lulu.
Tell me your terms.
Well, it was originally quite simple.
I just wanted you to leave my son alone.
But then,
your big brother had to take him.
That complicates things.
That puts me in a bind.
How so?
You tell me what I should do.
You want to take me as hostage?
That sounds about right.
But you have to let Lulu go.
You think I'm some dumb kid?
The cops will raid this place once we let her go.
Fine.
I can't believe the way
you two brothers have treated me.
A loyal bunch you are.
Where are you?
The old bar
your are familiar with.
I'm warning you, do not hurt my brother.
Get gang back to me
without a single hair missing.
I'm on my way.
I'm waiting right here. I'm ready.
I, ha, care a great deal about loyalty.
What's going on, Kai?
The two of you are going back
even if it means certain death?
You're a righteous bunch.
The times have changed.
Shit happens to those who play heroes.
Will it be ok?
You can get off the boat first.
You want to take him on alone?
No way.
Don't blame me for being naggy.
Gang'
you just don't listen, do you?
You don't have to make all the money in the world.
You're causing me a lot of grief.
We've tried our best, chao.
We wanted to catch him for you,
but we didn't think...
Really, Kai,
you should've just left like you said you would.
Now you've capsized it.
That ain't right.
I have no choice.
You're steering it.
Enough bullshit. Send cang to me.
Ha,
from the looks of this,
I'm guessing we are not walking out of here alive.
I doubt that the two of you
came empty-handed.
Now that we're here,
we're going to have some fun.
We're ready to play.
Sure.
Let's make a bet.
You know,
I have some toys of my own.
How about that?
Let's play-
hell yes.
Looks like
a bloodbath is going down tonight.
You chicken?
I wanted to leave a beautiful corpse,
so I got myself a haircut.
When do we move?
Wait and see.
Don't move!
Put your guns down.
Cops aren't even here yet,
you're already done?
I told you,
I got some fun toys
you want to mess with me?
I, ha, care a great deal about loyalty.
But that depends on whom I'm speaking to
you want to play with me?
You're not qualified.
Too bad you can't see me take to the sea.
Come out.
Don't move.
Put down the gun.
No sudden moves.
Are you two ok?
I'm fine.
I'm ok, too.
Get outta here.
I'm sorry.
But it's ok.
Loyalty doesn't exist anymore.
The world's changed.
You come between me and my money, you die.
He's really lost his mind.
We gotta go.
Lulu's still on the boat.
Come out,
zhou Kai!
I'm gonna kill you, then board my boat.
What the hell are you looking at?
I'm the boss now.
Kill!
Chao.
Do you have your phone?
We're in the middle of nowhere.
Backup will take a while to get here.
Don't do anything.
Just stay here.
We'll deal with them.
I'm a cop.
Who the hell do you think you are?
If you go in,
how is it different from a gangland gunfight?
It is different.
Because we're brothers. Get it?
I appreciate that,
but people are killed here today.
So what?
We'll take responsibility.
That's enough.
Hey guys,
I'm running out of Patience.
Get your asses out here.
You know,
your girl is on the boat.
Maybe I should do something about that.
I'm going to do one last thing for you.
I'm going to get her out.
I'm going with you.
No.
I can do this myself.
Stay here and watch him.
No way.
Don't you know that is suicide?
You're disobeying me again.
That's right.
We're blood brothers.
We'll die together.
What is wrong with you people.
You know you'll get yourself killed,
but you still want to play heroes.
No one could stop you.
Don't you know how dumb that is?
These days, whoever has money is the hero.
You're dinosaurs, get it?
As long as
this boat brings in money, it'll never sink.
Zhou Kai,
looks like you won't be able to save anyone.
Am I right?
Let's end it here.
Gang'
I spared you once.
I beg you...
Please let go of my two brothers.
You can take my life.
Look at this,
even to the very end,
you two brothers couldn't have a proper reunion.
The brotherly oath.
Brother.