(LOTTE ENTERTAINMENT & DEXTER STUDIOS PRESENT)
(A REALIES PICTURES & DEXTER STUDIOS PRODUCTION)
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd. Enjoy The Flick.
(ORIGINAL STORY BY JU Ho-min)
(When a person reaches
the Afterlife,
they are judged 7 times
over the course of 49 days.)
(Tried by deceit, indolence, injustice
betrayal, violence, murder, and filial impiety,
only the souls who pass
all trials are reincarnated.)
(- Buddhist Scripture)
(HA Jung-woo)
(CHA Tae-hyun)
(JU Ji-hoon)
(KIM Hyang-gi)
(AND LEE Jung-jae)
(WRITTEN AND DIRECTED BY
KIM Yong-hwa)
Kim!
Take my hand!
Give me the kid!
Grab my hand!
Come on!
Reach out your hand!
Hurry!
The rope!
It's on fire!
Take my hand!
No!
Ja-Hong! No!
We made it,
we're alive!
It's okay, sweetie.
Mom!
Hey! Get over here!
That was close!
That could've ended badly!
Little lady,
what's your name?
Kim Ja-Hong!
That's my name, cutie.
How did you know my name?
What's yours?
Your name...
Kim Ja-Hong!
You there!
Get out of there!
It's dangerous!
Get a stretcher!
Hurry the hell up!
Ja-Hong!
Mr. Kim Ja-Hong!
Wow!
How the hell did you think
to jump from there?
You fell from such height,
and honorably saved a girl...
A paragon!
The last honorable death
was 422 years ago.
I am honored,
Mr. Kim Ja-Hong!
The last one was
Nongae in 1592.
He's a paragon?
You passed away on
April 28, 2017 as scheduled.
We are the 3 guardians
of the Afterlife
who will defend you
through 7 trials over 49 days.
I'm a security specialist,
Deputy Guardian Hewonmak.
I am Assistant Guardian
Deok-choon.
It's good to meet you!
It's an honor, sir!
We said 3 guardians,
so why are there only 2?
It's an obvious question.
The last guardian is...
at your funeral home.
It's protocol,
but I think he went for food.
He's a strange one,
don't you think?
Mr. Kim?
What's up?
Everything's fine,
you're a death virgin.
That's why it's confusing
and awkward.
No...
I can't die just yet.
My mother...
I can't leave my mother!
Afterlife Law, Article 3.1!
One cannot wander the living world,
and there's no time for farewells!
If you plead the Fifth,
you'll be at a disadvantage...
He's following the protocol
like a real paragon.
Good, keep going!
Up! Up!
Let me see my mother
one last time, please!
I have something to tell her!
Love for his mother...
Please, I'm begging you!
One last time!
Please!
This is bad even for me.
Casketing for Kim Ja-Hong
will begin shortly.
Once again, casketing for
Kim Ja-Hong will begin shortly.
Mom.
Mom?
Snap out of it, Mom.
He's ready, let's go.
Mom, we should go!
(GATE OF THE AFTERLIFE)
Salute!
That's King Yeomra.
The judge of the Hell of Filial Impiety,
and the king of kings.
And he's Guardian Gang-lim.
The leader and our boss.
He's reincarnated 47 souls
in the past century.
- Paragon Kim, it's nice to meet you.
- Make way for the paragon!
I'm not a paragon.
Over here!
Here! Here!
Let him through.
Make way.
- Mr. Kim, please hurry!
- Make way.
(KIM JA-HONG)
Incredible! He's the one!
Mr. Kim, you really are
an honorable paragon!
It's been 19 years!
Your chance for reincarnation
after 49 days is very high!
An honorable soul!
Paragon Kim Ja-Hong!
(VOLCANO OF THE DAMNED)
Why the hell is
the Hell of Murder our first stop?
The Hell of Murder! The Volcano!
You said he was a paragon.
Did you really kill someone?
What?
I didn't kill anyone.
There are a total
of 7 trials:
betrayal, violence, filial impiety,
murder, indolence, deceit, injustice.
The order of the trials is determined
by King Yeomra himself,
who judges your sins
from lightest to heaviest.
Other than Yeomra,
no one knows the order
of your trials.
Murder? I've never
harmed anyone.
This trial will also
look at indirect murders.
If your past actions
influenced someone's death,
that is enough cause
to be charged.
So don't post mean
comments online hastily!
It's all recorded!
No need to worry,
guess what she's doing.
Our baby has a special power.
She's scanning
a list of all your charges
in order to defend you better.
It may seem like a skill
but it's like karma.
It must be taxing on her.
Who did he kill?
No!
Sir!
(HELL OF MURDER)
Give me your hand!
Just a little more!
I got you!
Climb!
You insolent prick!
How dare you!
(GOD OF MURDER)
This trial is about leaving
a doomed colleague behind.
Despite having enough time,
Kim's desire for his own safety
and his indecisiveness
ultimately caused his colleague's death.
If he'd acted in time,
the victim could've survived,
therefore, this could be
seen as an indirect murder!
This indirect murder was
a direct result of
his willful negligence,
and he must suffer
in the volcano
for 50 years...
5 years!
You can't demand
50 years from a paragon!
He's a paragon!
Be respectful
with your demands!
We demand a punishment
of 5 years that feels like 50!
Because he's a paragon!
Guardians, begin your defense!
I'd first like to question the defendant.
Do you remember your
colleague's last words?
Hello?!
- Listen.
- Help!
Help the injured first.
It'll be safer
if you control the fire.
Puncture the outer wall
and lift this with a pulley.
Got it?
It might cave in,
get going!
Get out!
Go on!
I'll be back shortly.
Stay right here!
That's all I can do.
I'll be right here.
Here, take this.
You'll need it!
Go! Go on!
Kim Ja-Hong,
raise your head.
You're not guilty yet.
Raise your head, Mr. Kim.
One more question.
During the fire that day,
you followed his order
and couldn't save him.
But how many others
did you save?
6...
7?
I'm not sure,
I can't remember...
Please pay attention
to the Mirror of Karma.
May I borrow this?
As you can see,
his memory may be foggy,
but he saved exactly 8 lives
from the vicious inferno.
He was on the nightly news
for his heroism.
Let me ask you this.
The defendant saved
8 total strangers,
but in order to do so,
he couldn't save his colleague.
How, then, are these lives
weighed differently?
I await your answer.
Such nonsense
on the first trial?
How do you weigh lives?
They're not even tangible.
If something invisible
has weight, they're all the same...
Honorable God of Murder,
please take into consideration
the prosecutor's last statement
as you weigh in on
Honorable Kim's charges.
It's too dangerous!
Get back!
Don't go!
No! No!
My daughter...
Ji-yeon, my baby!
Here is my final verdict!
The defendant's decision
to save many lives instead of
his colleague's is paradoxical,
but his death breathed
life to many!
His indirect murder charge
is thus rejected.
This court finds
Honorable Kim innocent,
as his murder charge
is completely without merit.
(RIVER OF INDOLENCE)
Mr. Kim.
The next trial determines
how well you lived your life.
Whether you lived it to the fullest...
Guardian Gang-lim!
It's like we hit a jackpot!
Finished scanning already?
There is no arraignment at all,
and he just has to step in
and say how hard he lived.
We were even assigned
the shittiest prosecutors.
This'll ensure Kim a smooth ride!
Do not underestimate
the prosecutors.
Starting off with a loss,
they'll be armed to the teeth.
If they indict a paragon,
they'll get promoted.
What's in it for you all?
Why are you trying to
save someone like me?
Don't be so cynical.
Reincarnation is good for you.
But I don't want
to be reincarnated.
Mr. Kim, that's for
the Afterlife to decide.
It's a century-old promise.
A promise with King Yeomra.
If we help reincarnate
49 souls over a century,
he'll reincarnate us as well.
As whatever we want!
I've already decided to be
the son of a Fortune 500 CEO.
Anything else is more hellish
than hell in Korea.
However, that's only possible
by defending paragons like you.
For a normal soul to pass
all trials in 49 days
is next to impossible.
Be our 48th reincarnation,
I beg of you.
What if I wasn't a paragon?
What would you do then?
Let me stress again,
that's for the Afterlife to decide.
Don't look at it!
No eye contact!
They see people's eyes
and prey on them.
They come after
souls that look at them.
They'll tear you up.
Mr. Kim.
Think of the Hell of Indolence
as a tourist stop,
but remember one thing.
Do not talk back to
the Goddess of Indolence.
No exceptions.
Your feet.
Grab it!
There, grab it!
Article 2.3
defines Indolence as
(HELL OF INDOLENCE)
wasting away a noble life
given to the subject,
with endless idling
and negligence.
But as you see,
indolence and laziness
are inconceivable
to Kim Ja-Hong.
I present his life to you,
Honorable Goddess.
(GODDESS OF INDOLENCE)
Be careful!
Almost there!
So close!
Good! So close!
Grab it!
Eh? A bee!
A bee!
His passion for saving lives
wasn't limited to just humans!
Amazing! Incredible!
His affectionate gestures
reached out
to even the smallest
and weakest organisms.
Everything he touched
was filled with glimpses of
sacrifice and salvation.
Don't look at me,
look at Navi!
She's over there,
get her, now!
Talk to her,
convince her to come.
Oh gosh!
His vocational ethics
that know no boundaries
often put him into
dangerous situations...
Lamborghini!
You're not at fault,
Kim Ja-Hong!
We understand you,
How could anyone
fault him for anything?
Your Honorable Goddess.
Those guardians,
they're patronizing your court
by turning it into a show and tell.
Hold him in contempt...
Enough!
Forget it,
it's all settled.
Let's erect his statue here.
Raise it!
If not for someone like him,
then for whom? Right?
Let's erect one!
Of course, Your Highness.
While we're at it, make it a big one,
order an extra large statue.
Good, something big.
What compelled you
to throw yourself in the face
of danger to save others?
Or did you want to live
each day to the fullest?
It was all for money.
Say what?
Did I hear you say money?
Cash?
Money?
Yes, I...
had to make money.
Mr. Kim!
Your Highness,
we'll start the lift.
Sure, go on.
Okay.
Was money your god?
You served a terrible god.
I'll make you feel sorry
for choosing the money god.
Hewonmak!
Go save him!
He's gonna fall!
Merciful Goddess!
I beg of you to look at
the Mirror of Karma!
What do you think
you're doing?!
He worshipped the wrong god!
Yes, he did.
And for that reason,
he extinguished fire during the day
and lit one at night.
Get him charcoal fire!
Sure!
Watch out!
Fire coming through.
Due to utter poverty,
Kim delivered veggies
on his off days
and cleaned sauna floors
on the weekends.
And when that was over,
he was forced to work
as a temp driver.
Ja-Hong!
You bastard!
Drive straight!
Even on days off?
Then when did he get any rest?
His true day off
was the day after his death.
He did not rest for a moment
when he was alive.
His ailing mother
required treatment,
and his brother's law school
wasn't cheap!
Without Kim's money,
they wouldn't have survived!
Money was everything to him!
He was only able to sever
the reach of this god by dying!
I beg of you
to embrace this soul,
a soul that only looked after
his poverty-stricken family!
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
My verdict is as follows.
The defendant's reason for
not being indolent
was said to be the accumulation
of money and goods,
which were not for
his own selfish interest,
but to support his ailing mother
and his younger brother.
(BLADE FOREST)
Therefore, I find the defendant not guilty.
The Hell of Deceit judges the lies
one has said in one's life.
The branches are razor sharp,
hence the name Blade Forest.
The reflection of the moon
on the blades...
is quite beautiful, right?
But if you touch anything
out of your curiosity...
If you did
out of curiosity,
the blades will slice you open
and you'll feel incredible pain.
I begged you not to
talk back to the Goddess.
You broke my promise again.
I won't be making
any more of those.
It'll be orders from here on.
Free him!
Why are you so rebellious?
It'd be nice if you'd do
what you're told.
We'd get a 48th paragon,
and you'd get a reincarnation.
And you'd get a dream visitation
before reincarnation.
You could appear
in your mom's dream.
Please hold on,
it'll heal shortly.
What did you say?
Wounds heal faster in the Afterlife...
No, the dream visitation?
You don't know?
Appearing in dreams.
It's a privilege given to those
who receive reincarnation.
Really? I can meet my mother?
I thought we told you.
Before you reincarnate,
you're allowed to see anyone
to say farewell one last time...
People who say they met their
dead father in a dream,
that's what this is.
What's with him?
Mother!
Yes, Ja-Hong,
it's me, your mother.
Mother...
- Should I stay in character?
- Sure, sure.
Mother...
Damn.
This place feels eerie,
even after a century.
We could just walk...
Kiddo, explain this to him
so he doesn't screw us up again.
Think of this as
a special treat for the paragon.
It's a fast transportation system
to pass through this area.
What's he up to?
Let's get going.
A hell ghoul?
What's it doing here?!
Dammit...
Even time is speeding up!
From the living world...
Is it a vengeful spirit?
You got any more immediate family
in the living world?
Drastic changes
in the Afterlife
mean that your family member
has become a vengeful spirit.
I don't understand...
Sir!
The head!
Get rid of it!
Captain! Pull yourself up!
Cap, you okay?
- There!
- What?
Smash it!
Smash the column!
Hurry! Please!
Don't you understand?
It's either your mother or brother!
Somebody has died
with a grudge!
And they've become a vengeful spirit!
With that roaming the living world,
the Afterlife has gone to shit!
Mother...
Mommy!
Deok-choon,
put a blindfold on him.
Mother...
Could something have
happened to her?
We're not sure,
but I doubt that.
Please, I need a firm answer!
Is she alright?
You want a firm answer?
Whether it's your trial or not,
if hell ghouls are wreaking havoc
and time has speed up,
at this rate we'll never reach
the final trial in 49 days.
- Deok-choon!
- Guardian Lee Deok-choon, here!
Deok-choon.
I'm gonna take a detour,
so take over for a bit.
He's a paragon, so there won't
be any victims.
If there's a problem,
stall the trial until I signal.
I'm counting on you.
Don't forget that
you and I are linked.
Don't worry, cap.
I'm here.
No, I don't want you to think.
Do me a favor.
Whenever you get an idea,
make sure to doubt it
before acting on it.
If it's good,
then verify with her.
Correct him instantly.
Easy, eh?
It should be.
So aside from protecting Kim,
I don't want you to think.
It's my sincere hope.
Okay?
Good.
(ITEMS OF THE DECEASED
Accepted by: Kim Su-Hong, brother)
These are Ja-hong's
personal items.
Mom!
Why are you taking that?
It's dead!
Throw it away!
My mother is a mute.
She can't talk.
I've never heard her voice
since I was born.
Just wait 2 weeks.
After my discharge,
I'll always stay with you.
Kim Ja-Hong, that bastard!
(Who are you?)
My deepest condolences, ma'am.
Mr. Kim saved my life,
and I was given a new life
because of him.
I saw the news on TV
and came right away.
I wanted to say farewell...
I haven't had a chance
to say goodbye.
If it's not too much trouble,
may I do so privately?
Thank you, ma'am.
Kim Su-Hong.
Where is the place
of your death?
I must be close to my death.
I can see the Grim Reaper.
Don't say that!
You're not gonna die,
Grandpa!
Look at the sky.
Is this the Afterlife
or a club?
How does time
pass so quickly?
No tickling.
Excuse me.
Any news of my mother?
No tickling.
Excuse me? Wake up!
Don't disturb her,
she's not taking a nap!
She's looking up
the next trial's charges!
You really don't get it.
Are you dumb?
Why did you take that off?
Put it back on!
Forget it,
it's too late.
Get up,
wake her up too.
- Open your eyes!
- Hurry, come on.
Is it over?
Yeah, over for us.
It's King Yeomra!
Bow, bow!
Bow your head!
He's already dead,
but does he wish to die again?
He's the first paragon
in 19 years, Your Majesty!
And why does
our honorable guest
bring forth hell ghouls
and disturb my realm?
Guardian Gang-lim has
gone down to investigate.
He's going as fast as he can,
Your Majesty.
How will he calm the spirit?
The body will be burned
and its soul eliminated,
but without disturbing
the order of the living world.
No!
Hold.
No, you bastards!
- No!
- Stop!
- You can't do that!
- Please stop!
Stop!
Who the hell are you?
Answer me!
Don't you dare
touch my mother!
I'll beat the hell out of you!
- Get him off.
- I'm so sorry!
Who the hell are you?!
How dare you
eliminate my mother!
Get him off of me.
Do you know her?!
- Don't pretend to be cool!
- I'm sorry!
My apologies,
Your Majesty!
Calm down!
Hold still!
Shut up!
Shut the hell up!
Please give us more time,
Honorable King!
Go tell Gang-lim,
that if he eliminates the...
Don't bullshit me!
What's with him?
Go tell Gang-lim!
If he doesn't eliminate
the vengeful spirit soon,
I'll go down to
the living world myself!
Yes, Your Majesty!
My apologies!
What the hell are you?!
I'm so sorry!
Is it true that Sgt. Kim
deserted because of his brother?
I dunno...
Do you know anything?
- He deserted?
- It's been 3 days.
Why'd he desert
just before his discharge?
I feel so bad...
If it were me,
my guts would rot.
And full of fucking maggots.
I'll ask you again,
who was it?
Sorry, sir!
Buddy, look at his face.
I'll do the same to you
and go to military prison.
- I'm sorry!
- Sorry, sir!
He's on suicide watch!
Something over my heart!
Very nice!
A watch badge!
My lyrics are so good!
I wrote it for you, dude!
I love it, sir.
Dong-yeon,
get up, dude.
Sir, I can't walk any further.
Of course you can.
- Get up, come on.
- I'm so exhausted.
You can do this.
It's not that,
I can't sleep at all.
So why can't you?
It feels like someone's
watching me at night,
and I get the chills...
Lieutenant! Salute!
An investigator's here
about Sgt. Kim's desertion.
Is that so?
They sent a Lt. Colonel.
- HQ investigator?
- Yes, sir.
(HELL OF DECEIT)
"Dad will always watch you
from somewhere nearby."
"So study hard and become
a good person.
(GODDESS OF DECEIT)
If you're a good girl, over Christmas..."
What's that?
Kim wrote a letter
to the dead colleague's kid.
As her dad...
"We'll go to
Disney Land together.
I'm so sorry,
and I love you."
The dead man?
Isn't that the will, then?
That's forgery of
a private document!
"Don't get sick
and always be healthy."
This is just a sample
of the defendant's fake letters.
Before this court validates
the nature of his crime,
I'd like you to pay attention
to the sheer number of letters.
How many did he write?
98 letters!
That's the number of letters
this "paragon"
sent under the pretense
of giving hope!
98? That many?
Why didn't he write 2 more
and make it 100?
Are you insane?!
Answer, defendant.
Your legal representative
asked you if you're insane.
My heart ached so much...
They were too young.
Much too young...
That was the only thing...
I could do for them...
- Salute!
- At ease.
I won't mince words,
let's cut to the chase.
Sgt. Kim has deserted,
but his family doesn't know yet?
It's only been a few weeks
since his brother died.
He could be hiding
in the barracks,
but more importantly,
his mother could
go into shock...
Your compassion brings
tears to my eyes.
What's with the bullshit?
Sgt. Kim was like
my own brother.
Unlike others his age,
he looked after his men,
and thanks to him
I received some commendation.
We will be contacting
his mother soon.
Where did you bury him?
Defendant, please answer.
Do you refuse to answer?
Defendant!
Her Majesty is asking you
whether you knew
about their pain and despair
upon discovering the truth!
Please answer!
She knew the letters were fake,
but she still waited every day,
rain or shine,
day or night!
Is the defendant
refusing to testify?
You may think that silence
is the best defense,
but I'll gladly cut off
your useless tongue.
Sir!
Cap! Cap!
Captain!
I'm a busy man.
For the last time,
where did you bury him?
Please!
I'll report you to the MP
for false information!
That's enough.
No need for that.
Is Kim's last duty report correct?
Kim had night guard duty
with Pvt. Won Dong-yeon.
I gave you a chance.
Watch your tongue later.
Assistant Guardian
Lee Deok-choon!
No! Not yet!
Assistant Guardian
Lee Deok-choon!
Lee Deok-choon reporting!
Initiate link.
I'll now begin our final defense.
Hold on for a bit.
- Your Highness.
Defendant Kim Ja-Hong
is indeed a liar.
Is indeed a liar.
What you're seeing now
are not only fake letters
to Ji-yeon, who lost her dad,
but also fake letters to his mother
for the past 15 years.
For the past 15 years.
What the heck?
Shoo! Go away!
Here he comes!
Catch him!
Mother, I injured my arm
while playing with my son.
He lied about a boar injury,
saying it was his son's playful trick.
My wife made scorched rice today.
Fearing that his mother would
give up fighting her illness,
he breathed hope into her
by creating a wife.
Then what happened?
His mother overcame
her incurable illness,
- made a full recovery!
- And now leads a fulfilling life!
Mom, try it.
Is it good?
If she knew how he
braved death
to earn money and pay
for her hospital bills,
I'd like to ask if her recovery
would've been possible.
But if she ever found out!
That all those letters were lies,
imagine her despair,
and would that be treatable?!
I'd like to add that
everyone grew with despair.
One last question.
Do you deny writing
all of these fake letters?
With the anticipation
and hope in those letters,
their sense of loss
would've been equally great.
- But they!
- Those of the living!
They grew up
as much as their loss.
My dear Daddy!
Are you doing well?
Your firefighter friends are
taking good care of us.
I'm doing well in school...
I can do laundry and
make dinner too.
You may be away,
but you're always in my heart.
Watch over me forever.
Your jewel, Ji-yeon.
Prosecution,
were there any
similar cases in the past?
No, well...
The Admiral!
Admiral Yi said
not to announce his death.
To the enemy forces,
of course...
It was a strategic tactic...
The Admiral said that
to his allies.
So that his men would keep
their morale high.
This is why...
I ordered all paragons to
just pass through
without a trial, didn't I?
In the case of defendant
Kim Ja-hong's fake letters,
this court will dismiss
all charges against him.
Any pieces of evidence
presented here today
are removed, and all charges
are dropped immediately,
and he may proceed
to the next trial.
And if you two aren't busy,
come with me.
Outside, now!
I'm getting wrinkles
thanks to you...
Why are you so desperate
to see your mom?
Let's hear why
you're a mama's boy.
Is there something
you want to tell her?
I've been curious too.
Read over the next charges.
Electric rice cooker.
I bought a cooker
that makes scorched rice.
It smells so good!
I always had to
eat it as a kid.
Mother only made rice
with an old tin pot.
But her memory's not
the same as before,
and she burned so many pots.
Come on!
Hot!
So many pots were thrown away...
Mom, do you have dementia?!
Wow! Junk!
But you know what?
Electric cookers nowadays
can make scorched rice.
It's a new model!
So I bought one as a gift
and left it in the storage.
I really want her
to have it.
Really?
Is the cooker the only thing
you want to give to her?
That is so stupid...
Or the letter inside?
You still had one left.
An unsent letter.
Not a fake one,
but a real letter.
Mr. Kim!
Your mother is alive and well.
Guardian Gang-lim, thank you!
Thank you so much!
Su-Hong!
What about my brother?
He's healthy and
doing well in the military.
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Sorry about that.
Listen up.
His brother is dead and
became a vengeful spirit.
I'm looking into where
and how he died,
and I'll incinerate his body.
So long as the spirit is out there,
Kim's trial will be in danger...
You lied...
in front of the Hell of Deceit...
If he knew the truth,
the trial would go to shit.
I understand fully,
why the cap is doing this.
Remove Kim Su-Hong
from your head at once.
It's his fate to be eliminated.
Could you just hurry up?
It's been 3 days since you...
It's alright, dude,
don't worry.
I'll come see you often
even after my discharge.
If the others bother you,
go tell Lt. Park.
It's not about that...
Your brother passed away.
I feel so bad
watching you bear it all.
Dong-yeon.
Private first class,
Won Dong-yeon.
Let's not waste
new tears on the past.
That's what my brother
said to me, dude.
So stop crying like a bitch.
I'm gonna forget him too.
Sergeant...
Hold the rifle properly.
I'm sorry!
Dong-yeon, what's this?
Why is it so hot?
What do I do?
Dong-yeon...
Radio Lt. Park.
Don't let the others find out,
just him, okay?
Just get Lt. Park...
Get Lt. Park!
(GLACIAL CANYON)
Good, very good!
Look how happy you are!
The next round is the Hell of Injustice.
A trial for those
who were unjust.
We're exactly halfway there.
But you said there are 7 trials,
and we've only done 3.
Because you'll walk
right through this one.
It's a hell that punishes
those who were unjust,
so this one is not applicable
for a paragon like you.
My family's okay,
so why is this happening?
Indeed, very curious.
Could we think about that
while we run?
Get in! Hurry!
Hewonmak! Hurry!
Hurry, get in!
Get to the front! Now!
Su-Hong! Su-Hong!
What happened?
Su-Hong! Hey!
Su-Hong!
Wake up!
Su-Hong, please...
Open your eyes, asshole...
Kim Su-Hong!
Sergeant!
Lieutenant...
I held him and...
The gun...
it fired by accident...
I held him,
and it just fired...
Let's clean up.
You bastard!
Clean up the blood!
No...
Let's move him first.
Listen to me, okay?
Dong-yeon, look at me,
you didn't do it on purpose.
It's okay,
I can take care of it.
My promotion
is next month, asshole!
We gotta wipe the floor,
go find a mop.
Clean it here with this,
let's hurry.
Captain!
(THE HELL OF INJUSTICE)
These are cold-hearted souls.
They're being punished for
refusing to help those in need,
so they're locked away in ice.
(GOD OF INJUSTICE)
Whether for a decade, or for a century.
The worst crimes
in the Hell of Injustice
are those that have passed
the statute of limitations.
Where the truth was concealed
for selfish gains.
The statute of limitations
does not exist in hell.
A crime in the living world
will never be erased.
What do we do with him?
I can't do this, sir!
A crime doesn't disappear
even if you keep quiet.
You got me into this mess!
Snap out of it!
You just killed a man!
The longer you hide
your crimes,
the harsher your punishment
in this hell.
Su-Hong cared so much about you!
He'll understand!
Your son deserted
his post last night.
We'll conduct a house search.
Did he ever contact you?
What is cap still doing
in the living world?
When I was young,
Su-Hong pestered mother
to go on a cable car ride.
Cable car? Jeez...
I wanted to scold him
for being so immature.
I envy you.
Pardon?
We don't have any
memories of our past.
Hey!
We don't know how we died.
Not a single memory.
That's what I envy the most
while doing this work.
All 3 of you have
no memories?
Except Gang-lim.
Hewonmak and a petty guardian
like myself have no memories.
I wish I had some...
Is this a confessional?
Stop it already.
There's an interesting truth
when you listen to the souls.
Even the tragic memories
become beautiful ones
when they reach the Afterlife.
Just like this place.
Isn't it beautiful?
Lee Deok-choon!
"Beautiful"?
How does this place
look beautiful to you?
This is hell!
You like this place too?
Your brother'd love it here,
riding a cable car and all.
But he's a vengeful spirit,
he can't reach the Afterlife...
Pardon me?
What do you mean?
Screw it!
Your brother's dead!
He's the vengeful spirit!
The Afterlife's all screwed up
because of him!
This is why the living world
should be left alone!
Hold on!
Hold on tight!
Hold still!
Don't move!
Grab my hand!
My mother is all alone now.
With Su-Hong gone,
I'll have to reincarnate!
I have to meet her!
So please help me!
I'm begging you!
Grab my hand!
How can I?
I only have 2 hands!
Her! Help her!
Grab her!
You sure love to mess
with the living world.
It's your hobby.
He should be incinerated,
so why bother unearthing him?
To give him a funeral?
Or let the world know
where he's buried?
His mother...
She'll never know the truth.
Let's give him
a proper burial.
A proper burial?
We're the ones
about to get buried.
With both brothers dead,
do you feel sorry for her?
Are we in Saving Private Ryan?
Let's burn him.
Afterlife Law, Article 8.2!
A vengeful spirit must be eliminated
and its body incinerated immediately!
Are you breaking the law?
You are disobeying my orders.
Go back.
I'll catch the vengeful spirit.
Alright, I'll sign you off
on a 3-day vacation.
There's some money inside,
so go rest for a few days.
I'm okay, sir.
You're okay?
Look at your face right now.
Why are you shivering?
Still cold?
What if you get interrogated
in this state?
Look at your face.
Look at it!
Dong-yeon.
Go and think about it
for a few days.
We have to be strong.
Do me this favor.
(HEAVENLY PASSAGE)
This is the Heavenly Passage.
We'll reach The Hell of Betrayal
through here.
Souls who betrayed faith
are locked away in a mirror
(HELL OF BETRAYAL)
and get destroyed.
The Goddess of Betrayal is beautiful.
(GODDESS OF BETRAYAL)
And just like her beauty,
she'll only forgive beautiful betrayal.
Isn't that beautiful betrayal?
A beautiful betrayal is
selfless betrayal,
or a righteous one,
or a betrayal of the conscience.
So a righteous man like you
gets a free pass through here.
Shed this futile grudge that is
disrupting the two worlds
and give up your revenge!
If you comply,
I'll defend you till the end
so that you'll be reincarnated.
Screw reincarnation.
And why should I do
what you ask?
Your brother is in danger
because of you.
Brother?
I don't have one.
Why should I care about someone
who left home 15 years ago
and came back
as a dead body?
I understand your rage
and grudge from that day.
So please stop.
How would you know that?
I didn't die that night!
I was buried alive!
How would you understand
the pain of being buried alive
for a whole day?
I was suffocating,
and in that wet shallow grave,
I begged for help!
Begged for help...
A desperate and painful
cry for help.
Just like my father.
Father!
But they didn't hear you,
they thought you were dead.
So you'll calm
my vengeful spirit?
No, I'll decline.
You don't know!
They buried my trust
and hope that day!
They betrayed me!
So you'll betray me?
He was so good to me...
It's too hard...
You got me into this damn mess.
Cap, why are you back already?
Go, keep going!
He didn't visit home even once
for 15 years after high school.
I thought he was a good son.
So he just sent money home
after all that?
Who cares!
Cap, you should go eliminate
the vengeful spirit.
At this rate,
the hell ghouls will get us,
or we'll be eliminated.
What the hell!
I'm begging you.
Please do not eliminate
my brother.
Why not ask us to
raise the dead instead?
If that's possible,
bring him back to life.
Mr. Kim,
we're only capable of
bringing souls here
and eliminating the vengeful spirit.
No way!
Save him!
I know you all can do it!
Please!
Save him!
Please help my brother...
In despair because of me!
On a suicide watch list,
Private Won Dong-yeon!
(VACUUM SINK HOLE)
This is the entrance
to the Hell of Violence.
The depth is depended
on the defendant's crime.
You're a paragon,
so it won't take long.
I saw you saving dogs
and pigs during a flood.
Don't be scared,
this is far easier than that.
She'll go over the charges
as soon as we jump
so let her do her thing,
and just jump!
Begin.
In despair because of me...
On a suicide watch list,
Private Won Dong-yeon.
When you reach your barracks,
don't ask the seniors
their age.
Help that stupid idiot.
I beg of you.
A guardian cannot interfere
with the living world.
I won't flee again.
I won't.
Making any physical changes
is prohibited...
Just save that
pathetic bastard! Please!
I'll do what you ask.
I promise.
Whatever it is.
A figurative question!
What's causing this phenomenon?
The captain has done something
he should never do!
He's meddled with the living world!
Stay back!
No!
He'll live through this.
Yes, thank you.
Let's go.
The ambulance is coming.
Hey buddy, hold on right there.
I've got some last words for him.
I want you to pass it along.
So demanding for a prick
who wants a favor.
So fucking disrespectful.
Respectfully, sir,
please do this for me.
I'm willing to do
whatever you ask of me.
I'll be respectful.
- Dong-yeon.
- It's me, Sgt. Kim.
Arriving at the base,
assigned to a barrack.
Surrounded by
my seniors,
notified of the draft...
Something over my heart!
A watch badge!
Angry faces of
my seniors,
everything is scary.
In despair because of me!
Sergeant?
Sgt. Kim...
Grab Deok-choon!
Grab her!
No! No!
Kim! My hand! Grab it!
Grab my hand! Hurry!
My hand!
So what did you do?
Tell me again.
I didn't do anything wrong.
- Right, you didn't do
- ...anything wrong.
Let's make a promise.
From here on,
from this moment on,
let's
never
ever waste
new tears on the past.
Promise me.
Assistant Guardian?
Wow! Korean firefighters
should join the Avengers!
Are you okay?
Hewonmak!
This trial has a victim.
A victim?
(HELL OF VIOLENCE)
What's going on?
Who did he beat up?
(GOD OF VIOLENCE)
Your Majesty!
This case is about
an indiscriminate beating
of the defendant's own brother
when he was in high school!
You may say that brothers
get into fights often,
but there is something
you must pay attention to!
His brother was suffering from
malnutrition at the time!
This was a time when he required
protection from his brother,
so the nature of Kim's crime
is extremely heinous!
Don't!
Don't hit me!
Don't do that...
No, Ja-Hong,
don't do that...
I knew this'd happen.
Irresponsible bastard...
Let's leave.
What the hell?!
Dammit...
I won't flee,
I promised you!
Shut up and walk.
We must recover
your body first.
What's interesting is that
this case is tied
to the final trial.
Any record of forgiveness
given to the defendant?
No, Your Majesty.
After the incident,
neither the perpetrator nor
the victim ever apologized,
and it all simply ended sloppily,
ambiguously, and fizzled!
That's how it ended
in our records.
But that doesn't make any sense.
They had to live together.
No!
After the incident,
the defendant ran away
and didn't come home for
15 years until his death,
never once stepping his foot
inside this house again.
Your Majesty!
Honorable God of Violence!
May I begin our defense?
I've heard enough!
What's the point?
No forgiveness and
there's a victim.
It's over!
Convict him at once!
Deok-choon.
I'll carry out my idea
without consulting you first.
Get in there.
Go on!
Cap! Cap!
Captain!
Lee Deok-choon.
Assistant Guardian
Lee Deok-choon here!
Request a combined trial.
A combined trial?
It's my brother!
Hey, Ja-Hong!
Kim Ja-Hong!
What're you doing there?
Request it at once!
But cap...
Let's cut our losses here.
- Hold on!
- Lee Deok-choon!
I'll now read
Kim Ja-hong's final verdict.
- We did it!
- Good work!
Deok-choon!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Sir!
Please!
In regards to the defendant's
violent crimes,
I'd like to request a combined
trial at the next trial.
A combined trial?
You hear that?
What say you?
I'd like to know if
the assistant guardian
knows what she's requesting
in her own words.
If he's found guilty
in the next trial,
where the crime is related,
he'll receive a double punishment,
and his guardians will be
stripped of their privileges
in the Afterlife...
Deal!
Do I go to the Afterlife now?
Take the lead.
To the base first.
Sure.
This is it,
(ETERNAL DESERT)
The Hell of Filial Impiety.
A combined trial, Mr. Kim!
Deok-choon, stay alert.
We must visit where you lived
3 times before moving on.
Don't even think about
taking off.
That idiot.
That pussy, I knew
he couldn't go through with it.
Back at that trial,
do you know why
he beat me up?
No, let's go.
We must go up
before the final trial.
That night,
I woke up to find
Ja-Hong hesitating
before Mom.
So I asked him
what he was doing.
What are you doing?
Ja-Hong, what's up?
What are you doing
with the pillow?
Don't do it!
Stop it!
Don't hurt her!
That hurts!
Don't hurt me!
On the night of the incident,
did you try to...
kill your mother?
Is that so?
That's it?
That's why the last
two trials are related.
You attempted murder
on your mother?
So the Hell of Filial Impiety
is the last stop...
I see it now.
Answer me, Mr. Kim.
Were you trying to
kill her that night?
No.
Not just her.
I wanted all 3 of us to die.
We had no hope whatsoever.
I'd kill my terminally ill mother first,
and then,
my brother and I were
going to take sleeping pills.
Is that when you decided?
The day you left home
out of guilt,
you decided to live
for your mother and brother
until your last breath.
Is that it?
No...
Don't look at her.
Can't you read?
Let's hurry up.
Sure thing.
She's back again.
Go stop her.
(PLEASE FIND MY SON, KIM SU-HONG.
I MISS HIM DEARLY.)
Ma'am, you can't
keep coming back.
Sgt. Kim isn't at the base.
Ma'am, you can't come inside!
- Ma'am!
- Please don't do this!
You're making it
difficult for us!
Ma'am!
Huh? Mom?
Why is she here?
Ma'am! Please stop!
Mom, don't cry!
After I left, I couldn't
bear to see her again.
Time simply passed after that.
So whenever you missed her,
you wrote her letters.
You can't be here,
get out of here!
What is he doing?!
Kim Su-Hong!
It's no use.
- There's nothing you can do.
- Get out.
I can empathize.
A terminally ill mother,
a brother with malnutrition,
but no one ever offers a hand.
So you made a decision!
Kill your mother first,
your brother, then yourself!
Hewonmak...
He's the furthest thing
from a paragon.
Where did you get this?
What are you waiting for?!
Throw her out!
Ma'am, I told you,
you can't come in here!
Deok-choon, let's start over,
that'll be faster.
You know that.
Of course you do.
We can start over.
A century flies by fast.
Time flies quickly.
Reincarnation is a pipe dream.
We're better off in the Afterlife.
Please, ma'am!
Don't do this, please...
Your son is a deserter!
Kim Su-Hong, let's go.
Your mother is living her life.
Kim Su-Hong!
Run!
Hewonmak!
No! Please!
No! No!
No!
Take a look, Kim Su-Hong!
The last image of your brother,
as remembered by
you and your mother.
It's the Hell of Filial Impiety...
(ELL OF FILIAL IMPIETY)
Defendant Kim Ja-Hong!
I will now begin
the final verdict for your sins
against your mother!
Your Majesty!
Allow us to defend him!
The final verdict!
Defendant Kim Ja-Hong!
Guilty!
The defendant!
- After that night!
- Attempted to murder...
The defendant did not
yield to his mother,
- After that night,
- despite all the hardships
- he did not rest at all yield to his mother,
- his mother suffered...
to support his family!
How dare you!
This trial is wrong!
She was unconscious!
There is no victim!
You don't know that!
You don't know anything...
Bring up the Mirror of Karma!
Ja-Hong!
Don't do it!
Don't do this!
What are you doing?!
I don't know?
You're the ones,
who don't know anything.
Only your mother,
knew the truth.
The defendant's mother,
wasn't unconscious!
She knew that only her death
would allow her children,
to live comfortably!
She knew all along!
Do you not see?
Your mother lived
her painful life with,
a spike through her heart!
She buried the memory,
of that night in her heart
and waited for her,
pompous son to return!
I deserve to be punished!
I'll accept any punishment,
please let me see her!
I must apologize to her!
You couldn't even do that alive.
I gave you plenty of time!
15 long years!
Read the verdict.
The final verdict!
The defendant Kim Ja-Hong!
It's over, we're done.
Good job, captain.
What do we do with him?
Bury him again?
Or eliminate him?
And the guardians are,
to be stripped of their powers!
The defendant blamed
his life problems
and attempted murder
on his own family.
And as if that's not enough...
As if that's...
not enough,
he wasted 15 years...
Mom...
Mom?
Continue reading!
Despite causing
mental anguish,
he fled home for 15 years,
a filial impiety sin in itself!
Therefore, this court finds Kim...
Mom...
Mom, wake up.
Come on, wake up.
A dream visitation!
He's in her dream!
It's Gang-lim's doing!
Gang-lim, I order you
to halt her dream!
Your Majesty, you must
summon him at once...
Mom, wake up, hurry.
Mom.
Mom!
It's me, Su-Hong.
Look at this.
I'm a Supreme Court Justice,
aren't you happy?
How do I look?
It fits so perfectly.
See? I did it.
Mom.
Why is it so long?
Look, my minions.
Good afternoon.
Mom.
I can't visit you anymore.
Because I'm assigned
to be heaven's judge.
I gotta punish bad guys there.
So don't come to the base
looking for me.
Understand, Mom?
Got it?
Okay, Mom?
Okay?
Do you remember...
A long time ago,
when you were
in the hospital,
I was sick with malnutrition.
You were in pain
and couldn't wake up.
Those were hard times, right?
And Ja-Hong...
that moron...
I heard you knew
he tried to kill us.
You knew all along,
is that true?
And this bastard
of a brother,
he couldn't come home
because he felt bad,
so he worked like crazy
to send us money.
Ja-Hong, that bastard...
Worked all his life...
For you and me...
Su-Hong...
My baby...
You boys didn't do
anything wrong.
It was all me,
it's all because
you had a terrible mom.
Do you understand?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
My baby...
I love you.
Ja-Hong...
Mom!
She can talk?
It's her dream.
Mom, Mom!
Mom...
I love you.
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Mother...
All humans live with sins.
Only a few ever have the courage
to beg for forgiveness.
And only a fraction of them...
are truly forgiven.
Afterlife Law Article 1.1!
A sin that has been forgiven
in the living world
will not be judged
in the Afterlife.
Therefore, this court finds
Kim Ja-Hong innocent
of all charges,
and orders immediate reincarnation!
Thank you.
Bye, Mom!
So what do we do now?
Isn't it obvious?
Take him to the Afterlife.
Who?
Another paragon?
He's a vengeful spirit,
so how could he be honorable?
This is all wrong,
it's an error!
Are you sure?
And a vengeful spirit can't even
enter the Gate of the Afterlife!
Oh yeah?
You didn't know what happened,
and decided to
come for the show
after all was done?
You came down to meddle
when I didn't need you...
What? When did I?
I only came down
because you called me.
You told me not to act
on my instincts!
What?
"Hewonmak!" and you
summoned me.
You sure love to mess
with the living world.
Or let the world know
where he's buried?
Are you breaking the law?
Anyway, he can't
go to the Gate.
There's no need to go there.
Go to the Hell of Filial Impiety,
where Yeomra is.
Am I going to hell?
He didn't mention that.
This is so dumb...
A massive tornado touched down
yesterday in Kangwondo.
Such is not a common sight
in our country.
A tornado can be seen
on an island,
but it was the first time one
touched down on the peninsula.
Parcel delivery.
There weren't any casualties,
but a military base nearby
was heavily damaged.
Experts believe that...
"Cook... scorched... rice...
with... electric rice cooker...
comfortably."
Mother, it's your son Ja-Hong.
I heard that your condition
improved drastically.
Kim's last letter was
delivered to his mother.
I do not know what he wrote
in the letter that contained
the real truth.
I'm not curious either.
He was just another soul,
who tried to do
the right thing after death.
Mother, all the letters I sent you
were lies to make you
feel better.
I lied about having a wife
who made scorched rice,
or a son who looked
exactly like me.
I will come back home
before it's too late.
What I'm really curious about
is why I'm not being punished
for meddling with
the living world,
and why Yeomra tried to test me.
I need to ask him that.
We have an audience
with King Yeomra!
If you do not step aside,
you will perish!
Has he gone
absolutely mad?
I'm sure he has a plan.
He's very considerate.
Yeah, he's too considerate.
He's so considerate that
I can't figure him out.
Kim Su-Hong...
will be our 49th paragon.
The last one needed
for our reincarnation.
Let's go, Hewonmak!
I'll be back.
(ALONG WITH THE GODS
The Two Worlds)
Hur Choon-Sam!
Hur!
You're the troublemaker
household god?
Damn, he's so cute.
Too bad he'll ride
the train to hell.
(A 2017 KIM YONG-HWA FILM)