Are you enjoying yourself, tell me.
Do you like that fish?
I can't get enough.
I love it raw,
fried, in all its forms, in fact.
I don't eat it.
Why?
The trick with the fish,
is that they die with eyes wide open.
I feel they fixate me
and talk bullshit.
I can't stand them.
What about anchovies?
I know you eat it.
Anchovies are OK.
It is also fish,
with eyes.
They have tiny eyes.
Me, I can't look in the eyes.
Jae-ho, he's the opposite.
He kills while looking
right in the eyes.
Besides, he loves fish.
He eats that.
You're like a kid
When you talk about Jae-ho.
You're all excited.
I think he doesn't feel any remorse.
But the guilt,
It's sometimes useful.
Thanks to this,
Our business has evolved.
In the Stone Age,
They were killing with pebbles.
In the Bronze Age and Iron Age,
With knives and axes.
Now, it's with guns.
Guns reduce guilt.
Probably because they kill at a distance.
Fuck, What's this bullshit?
I can't look at him.
Nice work, Nicolai.
MERCILESS
1st day after release from prison
That's really corny.
The hurdle of honor,
The color of the car.
And the worst, the tradition of tofu.
It's mine.
What about me?
You?
Natasha!
The only woman I respect,
It's you, Inspector Cheon.
I love your tenacity.
My lawyers want to ask you
of the damages and interests
But I quickly calmed them down.
"First of all you need respect,
To be respected. "
So many CEOs for such a small country.
Personally,
I have nothing against you.
My job,
is to put the smugglers behind bars.
It's just like that,
which gives me an advancement.
Give me a hand.
A helping hand, my ass.
Do you have any evidence?
It's Russian beluga.
It costs a month of your salary.
Want to taste?
Do you do it with your fingers?
You don't get it up for a long time?
Shit, I can not believe it.
Say thank you and chow.
That makes a lease, inspector!
Still beautiful !
A beginner ?
Who are you ?
We know each other ?
Why do you talk to me?
I can't believe it.
Very good !
Make a good chow-down
And have fun with girls.
You will end up in jail
and jerk off in front of the wall.
Isn't that right, Mr. Han?
Three years ago
Gyeonggi Penitentiary
1, 2, 3!
Next ! No one ?
Come on, you do not deflate!
There, a candidate!
I hesitate. A breath would knock him out.
Ready!
1, 2, 3!
Kid,
Put your teeth together,
not to cut your tongue.
Son of a bitch!
It was a punch!
You want to give me a punch!
Calm down.
It's a shame.
It was a punch,
Dirty cheater.
It was a slap,
bald ass-fucker.
Bitch!
Ass-fucker!
Catch him!
Sorry !
Motherfucker !
Son of a bitch!
I slapped like that!
Like that!
That's a punch!
He's a big tart, this guy!
Why are you here?
There are two kinds of guys
Which are locked up here.
Those with whom you can mess
And the real bastards.
The ones you fucked
Are among the latter.
And you ?
In your opinion ?
I believe that you belong to
the real bastards.
No.
I am the referee.
I advise you to keep a low profile.
Say...
you have beautiful eyes you know.
Pan!
You've been given a pardon.
These are not the kind of guys
to let it pass.
Looks like they've decided
To close their eyes.
Between the blessed children of God,
lets be friends.
I'm not a believer.
If I am with you,
These demons will give me peace.
After the dueling of slaps,
You made a name for yourself.
He manages the tax on cigarettes.
The cigarettes?
Do not hawk all, off the bat
like the last time.
You will receive the cash
For three boxes tomorrow.
To control the traffic of cigarettes,
It pays big here.
It's the war
To have the monopoly.
That's Han Jae-ho.
Hallelujah!
Han's been dealing with meth
Since he is a teenager.
He's not a real leader,
But even the bosses
Move away from him
Like the Red Sea.
Everyone knows
That he has a handheld.
That's Jesus Christ in prison.
He dines every night in the kitchen
With his disciples.
Fill your glasses!
Let's have a toast.
We are...
a family !
Boss ! We love you !
13th day after release from prison
Han told me
The greatest good of you...
A good brain
And a nice punch.
The brains, I don't know,
But the punch ...
Want to check?
What do you mean ?
He wants to rub himself on you.
I do not want dishonored cum.
Stop.
Jae-ho.
It's me you should remember!
No it's me.
Cocky little upstart.
If you win,
I will sing the national anthem
By sucking your cock.
You're not my type.
Fucker!
It's a real gun?
Shit!
Come here.
My dear nephew,
you should
Separate work and pleasure.
Don't be an idiot like your father.
Go.
Bitch...
Shit !
Are you okay ?
Why did you leave so early?
You cried ?
I've cried?
Sorry ?
I've cried, asshole?
Yes sir.
Jerk! Tell me when I cried?
Get down!
It was like Jae-ho, in jail?
Without me,
He ought to behave like a king.
Rather like a president.
What is the difference ?
A president has a mandate.
When it's over,
It can be replaced.
Good Lord!
the time has come.
What?
Kim Sung-han.
You surely
Heard of him.
That's a big fish.
We'll see.
This is the election campaign.
I know of your reputation.
It is an honor.
I'm Han Jae-ho.
You're the boss here, it seems.
I don't about the bush.
I will be brief. Let's share
The business of the cigarettes, 50-50.
No change
Neither the price nor the quality ...
Listening.
I'm Kim Sung-han.
I am a small clerk
in your eyes ?
It seems you were making a living
By dealing meth.
If war is declared,
who will win ?
If not, do we start right away?
Boss, the guards took Ho-yeol.
Well, can we talk?
Chief Warden!
There will be a general inspection.
Is this a joke?
What?
Is that Kim Sung-han?
He poured more water on you, that's it!
He gives you more than me?
Son of a bitch!
Repeat what you just said!
You bloody stinker!
Bitch.
What riffraff ...
Stop. That's enough !
Stop. You're gonna kill him.
Take him.
- Send him to the hole.
- Yes sir.
The elections are over.
Kim and the Chief Warden
Come from the same corner.
631, outside.
Han Jae-ho is coming, chief.
The director disperse the crowd
So he's isolated for the moment.
He is a hard one
But he will not survive on his own.
- Let's drink.
- Everybody !
Guardian!
He has a knife!
It's yours !
Not at all !
He took it out of his sleeve.
I saw him.
Can you prove it?
How?
I didn't take a picture!
Just a cartridge,
For your life?
The investigation begins tomorrow.
It is useless.
Kim and the Chief Warden
Must already masturbate together.
There's something I do not get.
The war is completely lost
for me.
Why would they want to kill me?
Why did they do that ?
My mother always told me
The once who fail to help are
Those who suffer.
Come on, we'll see you tomorrow.
Yes.
You always have your handheld?
Do you have something to report?
I found it on the floor.
You should take a look at it.
It has photos on it,
Rather interesting.
I would like to request this
guy for cigarette smuggle.
This guy?
"Sir", please.
This "Sir".
Are you threatening me?
How can we dare to threaten
The chief guard?
With the photos,
Your report will be easy to establish.
Fuck!
Motherfuckers!
Son of a bitch, I fuck you.
Motherfucker, you shitting me?
Not at all.
I also see
The illegal possession of a telephone.
Son of a bitch!
You shit!
Didn't you catch it?
We have already sent these photos
To the gentleman's friends.
If they can not contact us
Or visit us,
Photos will be transmitted
To the prosecutor.
Warden.
I risk another year,
that's all.
In your opinion,
Whom will I denounce first?
When I was a kid,
I have devoured your memories:
"Every night my fists are crying."
You say you demolished
Thirty guys at once.
That is true ?
I thought you had
Super-powers.
Boss, it's ready.
Just a second.
Ouch, it's hot!
You can go out.
Fuck!
You're a real gangster,
it shows.
There's something eles intriguing me.
There is no chance
That we meet outside.
So why did you want to kill me?
I have difficulties to connect the dots.
I apologize.
Stop it now.
Wrong answer !
Ko Byung-chul!
This is Mr. Ko!
Shut your mouth !
It was your boss who gave it to you!
Do you realize
what you say?
And the delivery of the 5 Kg?
Your boss promised 30% to our gang
If we killed you!
Son of a bitch!
That's enough !
This time...
That's a good answer.
Isn't it ?
I'm Kim Sung-han.
What happened today ...
Tomorrow does not exist for us.
It's useless to threaten me.
There are so many accidents here ...
Here.
Look at me.
Come on, look at me.
If you do not look at me,
It will never end.
Very good.
Ball.
32nd day after release from prison
Strike!
Out!
You are sure that Kim Sung-han
Had a heart attack?
And Jae-ho, he has no suspicions?
You start again.
My uncle, I've already checked.
Kim had some tension.
The older you get,
The more one becomes paranoid.
And more sensitive too ...
Thank you.
My uncle.
Jae-ho, what are you going to do with him?
He is still useful to us.
The friendship of two orphans,
it's for life.
Not necessarily.
You and I are the same blood.
It's a family affair.
Good.
I have a question to ask you.
You pick up a stray dog
in the street
And you feed him well.
It becomes fat
And its hair is shiny.
But as we grew older,
He no longer stirs his tail.
He barks
And sometimes shows his fangs.
The funny thing is, it takes time
For a human being.
This dog...
Byung-gab.
What must his master do?
If you were in my place ...
You are idiots or what?
You stupid!
You almost injured Mr. Ko!
It has been a long time,
I have more control of my strength.
Sorry, boss!
Be soft !
What assholes.
If I do nothing,
He will eventually bite me.
You have to prick it then.
Indeed.
We finish the deal with the Russians
And they take care of him.
Ocean Import
The home of fresh fish
700 delights of the sea
You just wait for us
Ocean Import
Home delivery!
A phone call. And here we are!
3 years and 4 months ago
General direction. Busan Police
Why are we looking at this?
This is our main target.
Ko Byung-chul, 52 years old.
CEO of Ocean import
And head of the fishermen's union.
Mr. Ko, the CEO?
He delivered strippers to
A Russian nightclub.
That's how he knew
Gegard of Vladivostok.
Vitaly Gegard controls more than 80 cargo ships
Which dock at the port of Busan.
Continue.
In 2008, Ko moved to Busan
And founded the company Ocean import.
It's a cover
For smuggling operations.
Meth hashish cocaine
Transit through coolers.
More than 15 kg have been imported
last year.
You should have stopped him!
No use crying over
spilled milk.
File this case.
Find a deal
Which is of interest to the press.
A celebrity who is drugged,
for example.
Why not legalize the cam
for that matter ?
It seems we are on a very high level!
Let's make the people happy
for once.
- Shut up !
- What?
Chief ?
Explain me !
It is an economic problem.
The Russian import quota
Decreases each year.
If the Mafia ships are also banned,
It will be a disaster.
So we drop the drug
Because of the fish?
Calm down
And do as I ask.
It's not by sitting idle
That you will be awarded a medal!
Han Jae-ho out of jail
In 2 or 3 years.
We can kill two birds with one stone.
What is your plan?
Infiltrate our men.
That's okay ?
It's a three-year mission.
It's long.
- With whom ?
- No one.
The police, the customs ...
No one knows.
We infiltrate North Korea?
A rookie and a thief.
The rookie is me!
Lower your arm, you idiot.
You are still single.
I have a wife and a son.
Inspector.
My son just spoke his first word.
You know what he said?
Guess !
We're selling the family now?
My mother is very sick.
You know, don't you?
His first word was "daddy".
In his mother's womb, he already
listened to songs in English.
It's not the time
To send his father to jail!
Jo Hyun-su,
I count on you.
For such a mission,
Why take a rookie like me?
Modesty does not suit you at all.
You were the first of your class.
I can't.
I do not want to.
I would have warned you!
Take him.
He always has hidden missions.
I did a lot of shit!
It's me who always has to do the shit!
You really make me do shit, there!
Inspector, the jail for him
And the gang for me, okay?
I'll find a kidney for your mother.
Dialysis costs will be covered
Before the operation.
It's up to you to decide.
The freighter came from Hong Kong
And went to Incheon.
It carried 20,000 bamboos
And Chinese Ephedra ...
Of ephedrine.
But the docking time has leaked.
Do you have a presentation?
You tell your exploits.
I am better in the situation.
Isn't it good, that?
Guy.
We're working here!
Your language will be more precious
Than your fists.
Be more convincing.
We disembarked at Incheon
At 2 o'clock in the morning.
But there was a leak.
The port swarmed with cops.
What should we do?
Unload the bamboo, hide for
One week in the bunkers.
We're fucked
like dead rats.
False Chinese viagra was found.
The Sino-Koreans said to themselves:
"We'll see if it works."
Result, they all got a hard on
Like deer.
It was effective, then!
Yes quite.
They eventually got off the boat
And got caught.
The trucks were called,
All discharged in one second
And spun.
And the Sino-Koreans?
Everything was unloaded.
Without evidence,
The cops released them.
Hallelujah!
Viagra has saved everyone.
Viagra saves all that is dead.
No, not that !
Make a wish.
Me...
I want a new cell.
The biggest !
It's mine.
Han is not easy to fool ...
So ? He died on the hook?
Yeah, a little ...
We'll see. No more news?
Congratulations. We have a kidney.
Your mother will soon be operated.
That is true ?
Yes !
Good news ?
Yes mom. I'll call you soon.
Tell me.
At your age, you're still
In your mother's skirts?
You exaggerate.
Family love, don't you know?
I don't have a family.
I can't know.
But your gang's out,
It's your family.
And if I joined your gang
At my release?
What do you think ?
It was just a joke.
Don't worry yourself!
Kim Sung-han is here, right?
Nothing to report?
He had a heart attack
upon arrival.
A heart attack ?
It's good news !
According to my sources,
This idiot was here
Only for you.
You know who sent him?
It is this fucker of Ko.
That's it!
A heart attack.
What are you going to do ?
We take care of Ko,
when you leave ?
I'll fix that.
You have no mercy.
You're talking about killing
Your own family, there!
Family, my ass!
When my father died,
He stuck me to the orphanage.
Look!
Look at that!
I ordered spicy noodles
Instead of natural noodles
And he hit me with an ashtray.
You deserved it then.
That is true.
Natural noodles are better.
If war is declared,
The guys will stay on the money side.
Let's wait for the right moment.
I can't take it anymore.
To make the lackey for this old fuck
makes me sick.
BTW,
You inquired?
About Jo Hyun-su?
He did good with the gang
Of the Golden Crane.
Get out!
They have balls ...
Before sending him to the lawyer,
Clean his file.
And Hyun-su, will it work?
He is still alive.
Where he is, that's difficult
to expose.
Better not inform him.
He could fuck up the plan.
This is when his mother's operation?
Yes, I go to the hospital today.
Thanks a lot Madam.
Yes.
And Hyun-su, is he okay?
You tan?
It is so beautiful ...
Yes, what light.
Are you kidding me, fucker!
- Calm down !
- Bastard!
Why is she dead?
Calm down.
She can not be dead!
Liar !
I want to see my mother ...
I want to see her.
Sit down, Jo!
I want to see her, fuck!
Take a seat !
Masked number
Let me out,
Just one day.
Apart from me, she will not have anyone
At her funeral.
You are not an exemplary prisoner.
It will be hard.
And because of who I am here?
I beg you.
I did everything
What you asked me.
I can not help you right now.
Undercover agent
Do something else,
please.
I've been languishing here for two years,
And I can not bury my mother?
If you do not get me out,
I unveil everything.
If I destroy your file,
You're just a bitch.
Is that what you want?
How can you ...
Do this to me...
Hyun-su.
It's not the time to make a child.
Do not touch me.
Yes...
I understand.
What?
You understand what?
Hey?
You'll never understand me, asshole!
Stop, or you'll regret it.
What are you playing at ?
Motherfucker !
Stop it now.
Bastard!
- Stop !
- Leave me !
Stop.
It's curious.
It seems to me that it was yesterday
That you and Han were threatening me.
Drink.
You have an exit permit.
You will be escorted and handcuffed.
This is the address of the funeral home.
Han Jae-ho paid the funeral.
He threatened me
To give you a few days.
But this is the work
of the Director.
A few hours,
It's not so bad.
I don't even remember
The face of my father.
She was everything to me.
I feel completely abandoned.
Let it go.
You can not understand.
You know who wanted to kill me
the first time ?
The woman I called Mom.
When he was drunk, my father beat us,
my mother and I.
When he was sober, it's OK,
But he drank every day.
When I was 12 years old,
One day during the meal,
I felt something weird.
The taste of the rice was bizarre.
My mother avoided my gaze.
So I ran to the toilet
And made myself vomit
with my fingers.
When I came back,
My parents were on the ground,
with foam around their mouth.
I am sorry...
I, too, know what it is.
To be abandoned.
In any case, the moral of the story:
Never believe anyone,
Always believe the circumstances.
When you get out of here,
You really want to work
with me ?
Fuck, if you say yes,
let's do it. Okay ?
Two solitaries must unite
To be strong.
You know,
It would be cool to work with you.
It does not mean
That you will be my lackey.
Would you like to ? Do you agree?
- On the other hand...
- Jae-ho ...
I'm a cop.
127th day after release from prison
What is happening ?
- We lost the signal.
- What?
He got grilled?
I do not think so.
His watch must be broken.
Go ahead.
I do not know what you said
But I only unloaded 200 cartons
Of royal crabs.
Even though I still agree
With Ko,
I'd never do something like that.
Can I call?
Go ahead.
We are in a free country.
Who is it?
Choi Dae-hyun, 45,
12 violent crimes and ...
Captain Choi?
Then ...
He's a professional criminal.
It's too many big fish
For Hyun-su.
What is their story?
Ko tampered with official stamps
For his export documents
But Choi intercepted them.
What stamps?
Those of the customs of Busan
And port government.
Customs officers are going to start a crisis.
Should we not intervene?
And spoil 3 years of undercover?
This is Mr. Ko's last offer.
Stop your delusions.
I have never seen these stamps.
Look at the numbers,
You will love it.
So that.
You're a clown, you,
With your pretty face.
Do I seem to joke?
Let's go.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Looks like you want to piss.
We have to kill them all at once.
Are you afraid for your little protege?
Not here!
Do not come here.
What are you waiting for?
Kill him!
They're coming.
What do you have ?
You want to go there ?
I'll unwind my muscles.
Jae-ho!
Is everyone going?
Good luck.
Honey, it's me!
Come here.
What? Don't do that !
Bitch !
I almost got hurt.
Me, I almost died.
Get rid of that.
Help me to get up.
Get it off first ...
If you do not help me,
I can not move.
Stop...
Stay here ! Do not come near me!
Do not hurt me.
Stamps were found
And we took care of Choi.
Nice work, Hyun-su.
It was fun for me too.
Fun?
Did you hear what he said?
He said it was fun!
It's been a long time.
Is that fun here?
Hello.
Mr. Gegard is waiting for you.
Cheers.
Stay here.
It's been a long time, Mr. Gegard.
Nice to see you again, Han.
You're crazy !
What are you doing here?
You're smart.
Watch this time.
I'm fed up, fucker.
I'm under surveillance or what?
Because of you,
Choi is still unconscious.
We had to be covered!
Send me back to jail, then.
Son of a bitch!
Jo Hyun-su!
Crazy guy !
What are you doing here ?
The toilet was broken,
so I went out to piss.
But this pervert checked me out
My God...
The company has evolved
But there are limits.
It's a misunderstanding.
You are wrong.
Dirty pervert.
You're wrong ...
For playing peeping tom.
Stop !
That's enough now.
Look at your cock.
Okay ? Son of a bitch!
Did you see the cop's mouth?
He pissed on it.
The hit of the pervert,
It was exaggerated.
Why did he emerge like that?
Because of the watch.
- What do you have ?
- Do not move !
Do not move !
Raise your arms!
Are you happy now?
Shit!
At your age, I was already on the field.
You can not imagine
The number of guys who betrayed me.
Even Ko
To whom I dedicated 20 years of my life
In my place,
Whom would you trust?
OK I understand.
I will never force you
To trust me.
But I trust you.
It's really cheesy here.
But you know,
You're somebody right now.
Somebody ?
This is a new sample.
An improved formula,
90% pure and half price.
If it was not illegal,
It would deserve the Nobel Prize.
There is more to choose the day J,
my uncle.
Let's do a big job this time.
How many ?
We think of 50 kg.
50?
We expand our network
And we cover the whole country.
It will take a month
To find the money.
Come on, God created the world
In six days.
This jerk-off Cheon
Will come and sniff our ass.
There's a way.
What is your plan?
This cop con,
What are you going to do with it?
Lower your voice.
Girls !
This guy hangs around with a cop!
You still have not told me
How did you do it.
Do what ?
Your cop, how did you shoot him?
Jo Hyun-su?
He was fine with the gang
Of the Golden Crane.
But the trick is that ...
I got pissed for this.
I wanted to fuck
This jerk-off Cheon, you see ...
Look!
So I got this picture.
Inspector Cheon.
I take care of this bastard outside.
And that's for you.
It's that simple.
The cops are still
More cunning than us.
What?
It is too good
To be removed.
He makes you bend?
I'll put it on our side.
He's a cop!
How do you plan to do this?
Don't bother.
First I try,
And if it does not work
I'll kill him.
Jae-ho.
I'm a cop.
I know it's crazy on my part.
You can break my neck
in just one time.
But I do not want to lie to you.
I'm really sorry.
So this idiot confessed
himself ?
How did you do it?
Relate.
He's too nice.
You and me,
We will never understand that.
Jung Kyung-hee
1962 - 2014
Who are you ?
Who are you, dammit?
Hey, pig.
pig?
What are you talking about ?
Han Jae-ho reveiled everything.
What?
In your opinion, who send us?
Bring the gasoline.
Tip over.
Do you have a last will?
I'll give you 5 seconds.
- 5 ...
- Hold on !
4 ... 3 ...
How did he know?
- How did Han Jea-ho learn it?
- 2 ... 1!
What, a test?
Was this a test?
Didn't you put me in jail?
Want to burn me again?
Hey, pervert.
You took your revenge!
You really talk
Like a gangster.
Do 3 years of prison,
we will speak again !
- Son of a bitch.
- Stop.
The D-Day is fixed?
Han tries to convince Ko.
As soon as he agrees,
The Russians set a date.
The amount ?
About 50.
And who killed my mother?
Hit and Run always ends up pin down
We put pressure on the investigators,
Have more patience.
A year ago
The day of the accident
We must tell the truth to Hyun-su.
If we told him,
It will make his mother come back?
Even if we work undercover,
It goes too far.
Bullshit!
Listen to me carefully.
As long as the fault is not revealed,
No one is guilty.
The culprit,
is the one who gets it.
No sentiment for the bloody idiot.
Otherwise you run at your loss.
What are you doing ?
You repeat a role or what?
What happened to you ?
It's a long story.
Let's get out.
Jae-ho.
You're not fed up
To live like that?
How?
Sometimes your way of life
Makes me sorry.
I don't live like that to live
But to survive.
Things that turn your life upside down
Always arrive at your back.
Never before you.
You must...
Always watch your back.
That is true...
I never believed
That my mother would go that way.
If it had not happened,
You would not be by my side.
Given the quantity of dope,
It will go very fast.
You'll only have one chance.
Are you sure about the info?
It has been hard to get downstream.
The police, the sea guard,
Customs, SWAT ...
It's a blockbuster.
Make it a hit at the box office then.
150th day after release from prison
D-DAY
Let's go !
Thank you very much !
Hi guys !
Not bad.
It's been a long time, Mr. Ko!
What are you waiting for?
On your knees, assholes!
Stop them!
Reach the crates!
Mr. Ko, how's your rheumatism?
Open it to me.
I like that.
You want to use it with me?
The sailors had to feel lonely.
With all my respect.
Mr. Gegard!
Shit.
It takes 2 hours for the salt to melt,
that's it ?
It's almost time.
OK.
Hyun-su is really smart.
Maybe because he's young.
What genius transmitted the info
to Cheon ...
By chance...
Curiosity is a bad thing.
Yes it's me.
I confirm the amount.
Now check the merchandise.
Checked.
Very good.
Clink glasses, Mr. Ko.
Of course, thank you!
Beautiful work, Jae-ho.
Let's get out of here tonight.
Cheers
Boss.
I do not drink with a corpse.
What are you doing ?
Han ...
My apologies.
Traitor.
Take care of the dope.
You, take care of your protege.
Look!
This one is not dead.
Good work !
Is he one of us?
It's okay ?
It hurts !
Bitch ! It rocks !
Do we have to go that far?
Again ?
You're really a sick person.
I was hit during the raid
But the inspector does not give a damn.
Bring me Hyun-su.
He took 2 hits.
He can be sewed up again.
And then, it's not in the head!
What is that ?
Do you recognize him?
Why...
Why did not you tell me?
Why ?
So you do not screw up the operation.
It's fucked up anyway.
Why are you doing this to me ?
Calm down.
Bitch!
Why are you doing this to me ?
You know it well.
What are you going to do
With your mother's murderer?
Calm down.
If it had not happened,
You would not be by my side.
Stop!
No !
The moral of the story :
Never believe anyone,
Always believe the circumstances.
Circumstances.
We are...
A family !
It's classified, buddy!
Let's drink !
Thank you boss.
My friend,
Co-directing is not uncommon these days.
But it's not our style.
- We are...
- A family !
There is a problem ?
Jae-ho.
We're going to investigate.
You're in danger.
What are you saying ?
I think they sold me out.
Someone else know
My real identity?
A warrant will be issued tomorrow
For a jacked search.
Shoot us Today
With the dope.
See you later, I'll tell you when.
See you where you know.
Yes, see you later.
Are we asking for reinforcement?
If the hierarchy learns,
We're in deep shit.
Our target is Han Jae-ho.
About how many guys
Can we count on?
About three.
Will they really come?
What is that ?
He calls me and he is not there?
President.
It's nice. Really nice.
Give me that.
Jae-ho!
Jae-ho ...
Jo Hyun-su, that asshole ...
I'm going to kill him ...
Jae-ho ...
Don't do that.
You're blind, man.
My friend...
Wake up !
Shit.
You're not my buddy.
Bitch!
Jae-ho ...
You're fighting ...
Stop, I beg you!
Young-geun.
You're not fed up
To live like that?
You can go.
What the hell is he doing?
Have you been waiting for a long time?
I am a little late.
Hello.
Did you see the rain?
Do not laugh!
It's better ?
You shot me.
You should know.
Yes, you paid dearly.
On the road,
I saw a tank truck
In the middle of the cars.
Shit.
Tank trucks
Have tinted windows now?
Are you still suspicious of me?
Dig me.
I am really fed up...
To live like that.
Hyun-su!
Sell all the dope
And leave the business.
No.
You're cut for this job.
Kill traitors,
Kill competitors,
Kill all people
That you do not like ...
About that,
Byung-gab is still alive?
I was even told
That you had killed my mother.
That is true,
I was really blinded.
Yes.
I should have killed you from the start.
I should have.
Bitch...
I will have...
Well done ...
That you never find it.
You're hesitating ?
Do you feel guilty?
If you want to shoot, hurry.
The cops will soon disembark.
The plan,
was to go down check
the goods,
And there they arrest you.
I blew it.
Bitch.
Where is Han Jae-ho?
Where is he ?
Show yourself !
Give me your gun,
This is the only way out.
Poor cunt, you want to die?
It's too big of a fish
for you.
Are you scared ?
Shut your mouth !
Stop being stupid !
If you do not kill me, you're done.
At your age, I was already on the field.
You can not imagine
the number of guys who betrayed me.
Okay, I understand.
I will never force you
To trust me.
But I trust you.
Jae-ho.
You know, you're somebody now.
Somebody?
Han Jae-ho.
Where is the merchandise?
Its good.
Jo Hyun-su.
Hold on...
Hyun-su ...
You...
Do not do
The same mistakes that I made.