1
00:01:46,560 --> 00:01:47,754
Good evening

2
00:01:47,960 --> 00:01:49,188
Where's Madame?

3
00:01:49,200 --> 00:01:51,668
Our boss is a little sick today.

4
00:01:51,680 --> 00:01:53,750
And the booze just sold out.

5
00:01:53,760 --> 00:01:55,113
Excuse me

6
00:01:55,360 --> 00:01:56,349
Wainscots

7
00:01:56,360 --> 00:01:58,715
There's a pot left.

8
00:02:02,200 --> 00:02:03,952
Is it OK to warm sake?

9
00:02:04,680 --> 00:02:06,398
Great, thanks.

10
00:02:06,400 --> 00:02:08,436
Are you Chinese?

11
00:02:09,000 --> 00:02:10,672
You speak Chinese?

12
00:02:10,680 --> 00:02:12,272
I'm just a little bit

13
00:02:12,280 --> 00:02:14,077
Nothing but a little bit.

14
00:02:14,080 --> 00:02:15,798
A little.

15
00:02:16,000 --> 00:02:17,831
So you'll live a very easy life.

16
00:02:17,840 --> 00:02:19,751
Know too much to be tired

17
00:02:25,720 --> 00:02:27,790
You come here a lot?

18
00:02:30,280 --> 00:02:31,713
So many years.

19
00:02:31,720 --> 00:02:33,392
Nothing's changed here.

20
00:02:33,840 --> 00:02:36,115
The people here are still the same warm

21
00:02:38,000 --> 00:02:40,309
I'll be here at this time of year.

22
00:02:42,400 --> 00:02:44,038
Everything here

23
00:02:44,280 --> 00:02:47,795
It always reminds me of old movies that I remember.

24
00:03:07,720 --> 00:03:11,713
I remember the movie's classic dialogue.

25
00:03:13,720 --> 00:03:15,790
"A man sometimes

26
00:03:15,800 --> 00:03:19,315
is to face death and fly.

27
00:03:20,360 --> 00:03:21,509
"You see"

28
00:03:22,360 --> 00:03:24,669
"What a blue Day."

29
00:03:24,680 --> 00:03:26,318
"Walk over

30
00:03:26,320 --> 00:03:30,074
You can melt in this blue sky

31
00:03:30,080 --> 00:03:32,036
"Go on, go straight ahead.

32
00:03:32,040 --> 00:03:33,678
Don't look both ways.

33
00:03:34,080 --> 00:03:35,832
You saw that movie, too?

34
00:03:43,200 --> 00:03:44,633
What do you want!

35
00:03:44,800 --> 00:03:46,199
I'm a lawyer.

36
00:03:46,200 --> 00:03:47,633
May I help you?

37
00:03:51,600 --> 00:03:52,953
Tell this man to roll.

38
00:03:52,960 --> 00:03:55,633
You guys come in and drink with me.

39
00:03:56,160 --> 00:03:57,354
Is

40
00:03:57,920 --> 00:03:59,751
I'm sorry, few Big Brother

41
00:03:59,760 --> 00:04:01,716
Dinner's ready.

42
00:04:01,720 --> 00:04:02,914
Inside please

43
00:04:03,200 --> 00:04:04,997
What are you looking at?

44
00:04:05,880 --> 00:04:08,269
Hey, move it, you little lady!

45
00:04:11,240 --> 00:04:13,390
Really don't need any help?

46
00:04:13,400 --> 00:04:16,278
You can't control this.

47
00:04:17,280 --> 00:04:20,875
No one's been talking about old movies in ages.

48
00:04:20,880 --> 00:04:23,348
Old movies are too long.

49
00:04:23,600 --> 00:04:24,828
Ah, yes.

50
00:04:24,840 --> 00:04:28,196
I have a CD of classic old movies in my car.

51
00:04:28,200 --> 00:04:29,633
I can give it to you.

52
00:04:29,640 --> 00:04:30,629
Thank you, sir.

53
00:04:30,640 --> 00:04:32,232
Then go get it.

54
00:04:32,680 --> 00:04:33,749
Good

55
00:04:36,280 --> 00:04:39,397
Hey, stinky, get the booze!

56
00:04:39,880 --> 00:04:41,359
We have a handle on the senior officer.

57
00:04:41,360 --> 00:04:43,157
-No worries, no money.

58
00:05:15,680 --> 00:05:17,557
Yes, he is.

59
00:05:24,280 --> 00:05:26,271
Father's done.

60
00:05:27,080 --> 00:05:29,833
Your friend doesn't have to worry about blackmail.

61
00:05:30,240 --> 00:05:32,708
Damn it! That man almost broke our story.

62
00:05:33,000 --> 00:05:34,069
It's kind of fate.

63
00:05:34,080 --> 00:05:36,719
It's rare for someone to talk about old movies.

64
00:05:50,720 --> 00:05:52,153
Be careful

65
00:05:52,720 --> 00:05:54,676
Talk to you about movies

66
00:05:54,920 --> 00:05:56,592
I'm actually trying to get you.

67
00:05:57,240 --> 00:05:58,559
Let's go

68
00:07:09,280 --> 00:07:12,431
Now, Mr. Kingikung, the President's wine.

69
00:07:12,440 --> 00:07:14,715
Message to Guests

70
00:07:16,920 --> 00:07:19,832
Thank you very much for joining us today.

71
00:07:19,840 --> 00:07:21,831
Celebrating the big day together.

72
00:07:21,960 --> 00:07:23,757
This is the Tenjin pharmacy.

73
00:07:23,760 --> 00:07:25,512
The 65 anniversary of the establishment

74
00:07:25,720 --> 00:07:27,836
The spirit of the God pharmaceutical can continue to progress

75
00:07:27,840 --> 00:07:31,594
Thanks to all your support and efforts.

76
00:07:31,880 --> 00:07:33,393
I'm here

77
00:07:33,400 --> 00:07:36,676
Special thanks to Mr. Duchu.

78
00:07:36,680 --> 00:07:39,194
This great international lawyer.

79
00:07:39,640 --> 00:07:41,153
Three years ago

80
00:07:41,160 --> 00:07:44,596
We had a tough lawsuit.

81
00:07:44,880 --> 00:07:48,395
It was Mr. Duchu who won the fight for us.

82
00:07:49,080 --> 00:07:50,559
Without him

83
00:07:51,320 --> 00:07:53,151
The Tenjin pharmacy can't be that smooth.

84
00:07:53,160 --> 00:07:54,912
Listing in New York

85
00:07:57,240 --> 00:07:58,673
Mr. Du

86
00:07:58,680 --> 00:08:00,113
Thank you so much

87
00:08:00,680 --> 00:08:01,715
Congratulations！

88
00:08:01,720 --> 00:08:03,278
Please take care of it!

89
00:08:03,440 --> 00:08:04,634
Thank you

90
00:08:04,640 --> 00:08:07,438
Besides, I'm very relieved to be

91
00:08:07,840 --> 00:08:10,593
My only son, the macro will take over.

92
00:08:10,600 --> 00:08:13,114
Leading the development of new drugs

93
00:08:14,320 --> 00:08:17,392
And he will take over the new president of the pharmaceutical factory.

94
00:08:18,360 --> 00:08:20,032
I'm sure he'll be better than me.

95
00:08:20,880 --> 00:08:23,553
I hope you'll support him.

96
00:08:23,560 --> 00:08:26,279
Just like my support.

97
00:08:26,280 --> 00:08:28,316
I hope we can teach you a lot

98
00:08:30,040 --> 00:08:31,837
Dad, thanks!

99
00:08:31,840 --> 00:08:32,716
President

100
00:08:32,720 --> 00:08:34,073
Congratulations！

101
00:08:53,560 --> 00:08:54,549
Mr. Sakai

102
00:08:54,560 --> 00:08:55,675
Mr. Du

103
00:08:55,680 --> 00:08:56,874
You really decided

104
00:08:56,880 --> 00:08:58,916
Going to the American pharmacy?

105
00:08:58,920 --> 00:08:59,909
I'm sorry

106
00:08:59,920 --> 00:09:01,956
This is our senior arrangement.

107
00:09:02,400 --> 00:09:03,719
I see

108
00:09:04,320 --> 00:09:07,039
Then keep it a secret.

109
00:09:11,320 --> 00:09:12,799
Ah, Mr. Light, you're finally here.

110
00:09:12,800 --> 00:09:14,279
Hello, Green wood.

111
00:09:15,960 --> 00:09:18,235
What happened to the investigation of the disappearance of the population?

112
00:09:18,240 --> 00:09:19,798
It's been solved.

113
00:09:19,800 --> 00:09:20,596
Deputy minister, thank you.

114
00:09:20,600 --> 00:09:22,113
To get him out of the thugs who blackmailed him.

115
00:09:22,120 --> 00:09:23,394
The Deputy minister also said

116
00:09:23,400 --> 00:09:24,674
If you have the time

117
00:09:24,680 --> 00:09:27,672
To play golf.

118
00:09:29,960 --> 00:09:31,837
Sir, Mr. Wilder is here.

119
00:09:31,840 --> 00:09:33,432
Oh, Mr. Wilder.

120
00:09:33,440 --> 00:09:34,316
Congratulations

121
00:09:34,320 --> 00:09:35,435
I've been waiting for you.

122
00:09:35,440 --> 00:09:36,953
Then it's up to you.

123
00:09:37,120 --> 00:09:37,996
No, No.

124
00:09:38,280 --> 00:09:40,589
I know you don't like needles.

125
00:09:41,680 --> 00:09:42,874
I made it for you.

126
00:09:43,360 --> 00:09:44,588
Pills

127
00:09:45,400 --> 00:09:46,719
As exciting

128
00:09:52,240 --> 00:09:56,233
A pharmacy-savvy lawyer is rare.

129
00:09:57,240 --> 00:10:00,676
I hope Duchu can stay and help macros.

130
00:10:14,600 --> 00:10:17,956
Stay, I need you.

131
00:10:20,360 --> 00:10:21,873
Give me some hope.

132
00:10:27,280 --> 00:10:28,998
Meet

133
00:10:51,720 --> 00:10:52,709
Chinese?

134
00:10:56,320 --> 00:10:57,639
How do you know that?

135
00:10:57,640 --> 00:11:00,154
Cheongsam or Chinese women look good

136
00:11:01,080 --> 00:11:02,274
Thank you

137
00:11:02,840 --> 00:11:04,353
My mother is Chinese

138
00:11:11,680 --> 00:11:13,750
Don't you think it's boring here?

139
00:11:13,760 --> 00:11:14,954
Let's talk somewhere else.

140
00:11:21,080 --> 00:11:22,513
Are you familiar with the Sakai?

141
00:11:22,960 --> 00:11:23,870
Don't know

142
00:11:23,880 --> 00:11:25,598
I don't want to mention this guy's name.

143
00:11:28,000 --> 00:11:29,433
I'm here to find you.

144
00:11:30,720 --> 00:11:32,039
But I didn't know you before.

145
00:11:32,040 --> 00:11:33,109
What can I do for you?

146
00:11:36,320 --> 00:11:38,959
You won so many lawsuits for Tenjin.

147
00:11:40,320 --> 00:11:42,436
How much do you know about them?

148
00:11:42,600 --> 00:11:44,670
Shouldn't they be as innocent as they seem?

149
00:11:45,120 --> 00:11:46,917
As a professional lawyer

150
00:11:47,000 --> 00:11:48,592
After the guest's lawsuit.

151
00:11:48,600 --> 00:11:49,794
I'm in charge.

152
00:11:49,800 --> 00:11:51,756
I'm not asking about anything else.

153
00:11:52,400 --> 00:11:53,913
You never doubted.

154
00:11:53,920 --> 00:11:55,319
Did you ever fight a lawsuit?

155
00:11:55,720 --> 00:11:57,551
What kind of lawsuit are you referring to?

156
00:11:57,640 --> 00:11:58,629
Three years ago

157
00:11:58,640 --> 00:12:00,312
The one that the Sakai just said

158
00:12:46,920 --> 00:12:47,989
Thank you

159
00:12:49,240 --> 00:12:51,071
See you sometime.

160
00:12:51,600 --> 00:12:53,238
The case you just mentioned

161
00:12:54,000 --> 00:12:55,911
I want to hear more about it.

162
00:12:56,560 --> 00:12:57,629
Good

163
00:12:58,920 --> 00:13:00,433
The day after three o'clock in the afternoon

164
00:13:00,440 --> 00:13:02,317
Time Square of Osaka Station

165
00:13:03,400 --> 00:13:05,072
Don't know how to call you?

166
00:13:05,840 --> 00:13:07,273
The far wave is really made by beauty

167
00:13:07,360 --> 00:13:09,749
You can call me really by the beauty

168
00:13:10,960 --> 00:13:11,995
Good

169
00:14:35,400 --> 00:14:36,719
Is it a police station?

170
00:14:37,160 --> 00:14:38,878
I'll transfer you to the English conversation.

171
00:14:38,880 --> 00:14:40,313
Please wait.

172
00:15:01,920 --> 00:15:03,194
It's him!

173
00:15:03,400 --> 00:15:05,595
That's the guy!

174
00:15:06,120 --> 00:15:07,519
Who are you?

175
00:15:07,520 --> 00:15:08,748
I've never seen you before.

176
00:15:10,240 --> 00:15:11,434
I'm not breathing.

177
00:15:11,760 --> 00:15:12,875
The body is stiff.

178
00:15:13,160 --> 00:15:15,276
According to intelligence, the police found a homicide.

179
00:15:15,280 --> 00:15:16,998
Police are currently conducting on-site search warrants

180
00:15:17,000 --> 00:15:17,955
A young woman died in bed in the bedroom.

181
00:15:17,960 --> 00:15:19,188
I'm Dabanfu.

182
00:15:19,200 --> 00:15:22,556
Search a lesson of shallow Noshing two

183
00:15:22,680 --> 00:15:24,238
What happened last night?

184
00:15:24,240 --> 00:15:25,878
Do you know the victim?

185
00:15:25,880 --> 00:15:29,429
What's your special relationship to the deceased?

186
00:15:30,560 --> 00:15:31,913
I need to contact my lawyer.

187
00:15:36,640 --> 00:15:39,871
The suspect was arrested on the spot.

188
00:15:39,880 --> 00:15:41,836
28-year-old woman was found on the bed of the dead body.

189
00:15:41,840 --> 00:15:43,876
There's a lot of media outside the police department.

190
00:15:44,360 --> 00:15:47,272
You go out the front door and distract the press.

191
00:15:47,280 --> 00:15:50,397
We took the suspect out the back door.

192
00:15:50,520 --> 00:15:53,114
Police are preparing to take the suspect away from the crime scene.

193
00:16:09,400 --> 00:16:12,915
You killed someone, and now you're assaulting guns.

194
00:16:13,760 --> 00:16:14,715
Run away.

195
00:16:15,160 --> 00:16:17,310
You're dead

196
00:16:25,240 --> 00:16:26,958
Suspect resisting arrest and escaping!

197
00:16:26,960 --> 00:16:27,790
Over there!

198
00:16:27,800 --> 00:16:30,155
Suspect escaped!

199
00:16:54,720 --> 00:16:56,870
-See him! Stop！

200
00:16:56,880 --> 00:16:59,269
Step aside, stop! Don't run!

201
00:17:30,040 --> 00:17:31,917
Platform Two

202
00:17:31,920 --> 00:17:34,957
The urgent train to Nara will stop

203
00:17:35,080 --> 00:17:36,149
Pay attention to safety

204
00:17:36,160 --> 00:17:39,197
Passengers are requested to stand in the Yellow line and wait.

205
00:18:01,400 --> 00:18:03,072
Damn！ -Police Department!

206
00:18:07,080 --> 00:18:08,195
Tsujitani！ Is！

207
00:18:08,200 --> 00:18:10,350
Close the entrances and exits immediately along the subway.

208
00:18:10,840 --> 00:18:12,193
Call reinforcements.

209
00:18:12,200 --> 00:18:13,269
Is

210
00:18:14,920 --> 00:18:18,356
Two men of unknown origin

211
00:18:18,360 --> 00:18:20,112
is holding a pupil hostage.

212
00:18:20,120 --> 00:18:22,156
They asked for 20 million dollars and helicopters

213
00:18:22,160 --> 00:18:23,354
Everybody stay calm.

214
00:18:23,360 --> 00:18:25,590
The scene is in critical condition.

215
00:18:25,800 --> 00:18:27,791
The above is the reporter live report

216
00:18:33,960 --> 00:18:36,030
Do not do as soon as we ask!

217
00:18:36,360 --> 00:18:38,191
The petrol truck will explode soon!

218
00:18:38,280 --> 00:18:39,952
Blow up the kid.

219
00:18:40,240 --> 00:18:41,434
The whole area.

220
00:18:42,120 --> 00:18:44,429
We need time to prepare your request.

221
00:18:44,880 --> 00:18:47,314
Let's hear the hostage first and make sure he's safe.

222
00:18:47,600 --> 00:18:49,318
You bastards are stalling for time.

223
00:18:51,280 --> 00:18:52,554
Call the TV reporter in.

224
00:18:52,560 --> 00:18:53,709
Hurry up!

225
00:18:57,160 --> 00:18:59,628
Open Guns!

226
00:19:08,280 --> 00:19:09,429
Who are you?

227
00:19:10,680 --> 00:19:12,272
I'm a freelance journalist.

228
00:19:13,040 --> 00:19:14,268
Shi Cun

229
00:19:14,280 --> 00:19:16,157
Come any closer, I'll open guns.

230
00:19:18,400 --> 00:19:21,392
I'll broadcast your statements online.

231
00:19:21,760 --> 00:19:23,671
-Let the whole world see-don't come any closer

232
00:19:24,560 --> 00:19:27,393
Then open guns and hit me.

233
00:19:27,600 --> 00:19:28,919
But at the same time

234
00:19:30,080 --> 00:19:32,640
The moment I guns

235
00:19:33,720 --> 00:19:36,359
It's going to be broadcast.

236
00:19:36,880 --> 00:19:38,916
I'm here.

237
00:19:39,800 --> 00:19:41,438
It's a mental preparation.

238
00:19:47,520 --> 00:19:48,999
Is it live?

239
00:19:49,360 --> 00:19:50,588
Yes

240
00:19:51,840 --> 00:19:53,432
Two-bit name

241
00:19:53,560 --> 00:19:55,551
Will spread all over the world.

242
00:19:55,640 --> 00:19:56,709
Hi, I ...

243
00:20:08,160 --> 00:20:12,438
How do you do it like you do?

244
00:20:12,440 --> 00:20:14,032
No matter what you do

245
00:20:14,280 --> 00:20:15,759
Or something you don't want to do.

246
00:20:16,800 --> 00:20:18,392
Do it all.

247
00:20:19,280 --> 00:20:22,716
I'm going to be like a police uncle.

248
00:20:26,440 --> 00:20:28,112
No matter what job you do,

249
00:20:28,200 --> 00:20:30,794
The most important thing is not to run away.

250
00:20:30,880 --> 00:20:32,074
Well

251
00:20:35,440 --> 00:20:36,873
-It's all yours.

252
00:20:38,920 --> 00:20:39,989
The length of the vector village

253
00:20:40,600 --> 00:20:42,955
I'm from the precinct.

254
00:20:45,600 --> 00:20:47,556
It was assigned to a DABANFU police search.

255
00:20:47,560 --> 00:20:49,915
Follow the chief of the village to assist you in your work

256
00:20:50,560 --> 00:20:51,788
Itochu Instruction

257
00:20:51,800 --> 00:20:53,438
Get back to the shallow wild line long.

258
00:20:53,440 --> 00:20:54,509
Key！

259
00:20:59,320 --> 00:21:01,390
The suspect's name is Duchu, 40 years old.

260
00:21:01,400 --> 00:21:02,753
Chinese male

261
00:21:03,280 --> 00:21:04,793
It's a god-pharma lawyer.

262
00:21:04,800 --> 00:21:06,791
Working between China and Osaka

263
00:21:06,800 --> 00:21:08,153
Shallow Wild line length

264
00:21:08,160 --> 00:21:09,718
All entrances to the subway station have been

265
00:21:09,720 --> 00:21:11,278
We have a police officer stationed.

266
00:21:22,000 --> 00:21:23,797
Department of the long Yi-Teng class instructions

267
00:21:23,800 --> 00:21:26,155
We're going to rendezvous with the shallow wild line.

268
00:21:26,160 --> 00:21:27,798
Now that the subway station is surrounded,

269
00:21:27,920 --> 00:21:29,592
What do we mean by going?

270
00:21:30,680 --> 00:21:31,954
How do you do that?

271
00:21:32,920 --> 00:21:34,194
Open map

272
00:21:34,640 --> 00:21:35,709
Is

273
00:21:36,560 --> 00:21:38,312
The police searched the suspects from the platform.

274
00:21:38,320 --> 00:21:39,958
Jump down the tunnel route

275
00:21:40,080 --> 00:21:41,672
I didn't find anything.

276
00:21:41,920 --> 00:21:43,797
The first mobile team is here.

277
00:21:45,800 --> 00:21:47,631
The suspect is an extremely dangerous man.

278
00:21:47,960 --> 00:21:51,032
He must be arrested before the new victim appears.

279
00:21:51,040 --> 00:21:54,077
Can open guns if necessary

280
00:22:28,200 --> 00:22:29,519
It's safe.

281
00:22:36,000 --> 00:22:38,389
There's no indication of this place on the map.

282
00:22:38,560 --> 00:22:39,788
It's still under construction.

283
00:22:40,400 --> 00:22:43,119
But this is a connection to the station.

284
00:23:39,440 --> 00:23:40,668
Are you okay?

285
00:23:41,000 --> 00:23:42,115
Excuse me

286
00:23:43,200 --> 00:23:45,350
I'll take care of it for you.

287
00:24:16,240 --> 00:24:17,355
Let her go!

288
00:24:17,560 --> 00:24:19,312
Let her go! What are you doing!

289
00:24:19,320 --> 00:24:20,389
Feed！

290
00:24:20,640 --> 00:24:21,868
Everybody back up!

291
00:24:22,360 --> 00:24:23,634
Back up!

292
00:24:26,240 --> 00:24:27,229
Feed

293
00:24:27,720 --> 00:24:28,994
Put down the nail gun.

294
00:24:30,160 --> 00:24:32,549
I said put the nail gun down!

295
00:24:35,960 --> 00:24:37,075
Feed

296
00:24:37,840 --> 00:24:39,239
Put the nail gun down.

297
00:24:40,080 --> 00:24:41,832
Put it down!

298
00:24:41,920 --> 00:24:42,955
No

299
00:24:43,080 --> 00:24:44,672
It's your turn to put guns down.

300
00:24:44,840 --> 00:24:47,559
Do you really have the heart to make a hole in her face?

301
00:24:57,080 --> 00:25:00,117
You can't escape with this fool.

302
00:25:02,000 --> 00:25:03,353
Her first day at work today.

303
00:25:04,240 --> 00:25:05,719
Let her go.

304
00:25:06,360 --> 00:25:08,396
I'll take her place.

305
00:25:26,040 --> 00:25:27,678
It's dangerous.

306
00:25:27,880 --> 00:25:29,950
What, you're an idiot.

307
00:25:30,600 --> 00:25:32,352
I just want her to know

308
00:25:32,680 --> 00:25:34,398
Lawyers can't be trusted.

309
00:25:34,560 --> 00:25:36,073
You don't know anything about me.

310
00:25:36,720 --> 00:25:38,199
I know you.

311
00:25:38,440 --> 00:25:40,954
I remember the case three years ago.

312
00:25:42,600 --> 00:25:43,953
I was framed.

313
00:25:44,680 --> 00:25:46,033
Then follow me.

314
00:25:46,320 --> 00:25:47,878
Tell me the truth.

315
00:25:48,960 --> 00:25:50,598
I don't trust the police.

316
00:25:51,320 --> 00:25:53,117
Go！ Give me a car!

317
00:25:54,080 --> 00:25:55,638
Open the cuffs.

318
00:25:58,760 --> 00:26:00,591
You're not getting away with this.

319
00:26:01,800 --> 00:26:02,676
Drive！

320
00:26:10,080 --> 00:26:12,275
You haven't told me where to go.

321
00:26:12,280 --> 00:26:14,271
Shut up! Keep driving.

322
00:27:53,040 --> 00:27:54,712
If I go back with you,

323
00:27:55,400 --> 00:27:56,799
I'm dead.

324
00:27:57,240 --> 00:27:59,834
There's only one way to be a fugitive.

325
00:28:00,200 --> 00:28:01,633
Wow Road

326
00:28:02,880 --> 00:28:04,598
You have a choice now.

327
00:28:19,000 --> 00:28:20,797
It's a disgrace!

328
00:28:23,440 --> 00:28:25,078
Fingerprints left on the murder weapon.

329
00:28:25,400 --> 00:28:27,868
And the DNA that sticks to the hairs on the Vic.

330
00:28:28,400 --> 00:28:31,676
Enough to prove he was the murderer.

331
00:28:32,440 --> 00:28:33,793
Just grab him back.

332
00:28:34,120 --> 00:28:35,394
We can close the case.

333
00:28:35,560 --> 00:28:38,154
What was the motive of Duchu's murder?

334
00:28:39,720 --> 00:28:41,392
The crime scene was his place.

335
00:28:42,440 --> 00:28:43,714
Fingerprints and hair.

336
00:28:43,720 --> 00:28:45,756
Cannot be conclusive evidence

337
00:28:45,760 --> 00:28:48,274
Let the suspect go and cover him!

338
00:28:48,880 --> 00:28:51,440
The chief is a hostage to save me.

339
00:28:51,440 --> 00:28:53,874
You were the first to let Duchu run away.

340
00:28:54,120 --> 00:28:55,269
What are you talking about?

341
00:28:55,440 --> 00:28:56,714
Bai Tian

342
00:28:58,000 --> 00:28:59,911
Don't speak without permission.

343
00:29:00,880 --> 00:29:01,949
I am sorry

344
00:29:02,600 --> 00:29:03,749
Shi Cun

345
00:29:03,880 --> 00:29:04,949
Shallow wild

346
00:29:04,960 --> 00:29:09,238
You two must work together.

347
00:29:13,120 --> 00:29:14,519
Talk about

348
00:29:15,960 --> 00:29:17,188
Shi Cun

349
00:29:17,440 --> 00:29:19,431
No matter how good you are

350
00:29:20,560 --> 00:29:22,516
Just as someone misunderstood you.

351
00:29:24,760 --> 00:29:25,954
But

352
00:29:26,640 --> 00:29:28,756
I will always support you.

353
00:29:29,000 --> 00:29:30,513
Don't worry about it.

354
00:29:55,960 --> 00:29:58,155
Homicide suspect Duchu in the course of the hunt.

355
00:29:58,160 --> 00:29:59,798
This morning a Chinese man

356
00:29:59,800 --> 00:30:00,835
Osaka police are trying to hunt for homicide ...

357
00:30:00,840 --> 00:30:02,751
Allegedly in his residence.

358
00:30:02,760 --> 00:30:04,193
The murder of a native woman

359
00:30:04,200 --> 00:30:07,875
The suspect Duchu to flee during the arrest.

360
00:30:07,880 --> 00:30:09,438
Osaka Police are ...

361
00:30:09,440 --> 00:30:11,351
The most contradictory thing is

362
00:30:11,360 --> 00:30:13,157
The evidence is perfect.

363
00:30:13,160 --> 00:30:14,229
Oh, yes

364
00:30:14,360 --> 00:30:17,670
The suspect is a very capable lawyer.

365
00:30:17,680 --> 00:30:18,908
How could such a thing be done?

366
00:30:19,320 --> 00:30:20,878
Are you sympathetic to him?

367
00:30:21,840 --> 00:30:24,513
There's too much to understand.

368
00:30:25,280 --> 00:30:28,158
Yes, I think the Dean has a point.

369
00:30:29,360 --> 00:30:30,554
No laughing.

370
00:30:32,720 --> 00:30:33,835
Is

371
00:30:34,440 --> 00:30:35,919
What about the surveillance footage?

372
00:30:36,320 --> 00:30:38,117
Outside the meeting that night

373
00:30:38,120 --> 00:30:39,758
Surveillance footage has been received.

374
00:30:40,120 --> 00:30:41,678
The Vic Kazoko Tanaka.

375
00:30:41,680 --> 00:30:44,148
Was 10.5 minutes away from the meeting.

376
00:30:44,160 --> 00:30:45,798
And Duchu was at 11:36.

377
00:30:45,800 --> 00:30:47,995
Left with another woman.

378
00:30:48,560 --> 00:30:49,788
Another woman?

379
00:30:51,040 --> 00:30:52,359
Zoom in, let me see.

380
00:30:55,240 --> 00:30:56,878
A little clearer.

381
00:31:02,680 --> 00:31:04,159
Three years ago

382
00:31:04,400 --> 00:31:05,674
Her fiance

383
00:31:05,680 --> 00:31:07,352
was prosecuted for stealing the gods ' trade secrets.

384
00:31:07,440 --> 00:31:09,635
Was convicted of a crime

385
00:31:10,920 --> 00:31:14,071
After losing the lawsuit, he died strangely.

386
00:31:33,760 --> 00:31:34,909
He's a tree.

387
00:31:37,280 --> 00:31:41,876
It wasn't suicide.

388
00:31:43,720 --> 00:31:45,278
It's the lawyer.

389
00:31:46,760 --> 00:31:48,990
He was forced to die.

390
00:32:06,600 --> 00:32:08,670
Hey, wait!

391
00:32:15,920 --> 00:32:17,399
That looks like him on the top.

392
00:32:17,400 --> 00:32:18,913
Hey, stop!

393
00:32:20,400 --> 00:32:21,753
Here, Cheers!

394
00:32:21,760 --> 00:32:22,954
Ah, thank you.

395
00:32:28,640 --> 00:32:29,914
Excuse me

396
00:32:34,920 --> 00:32:36,194
Are you hungry?

397
00:32:37,320 --> 00:32:38,389
To

398
00:32:38,400 --> 00:32:39,674
Eat it.

399
00:32:41,400 --> 00:32:42,276
Thank you

400
00:32:44,160 --> 00:32:45,593
Don't move the police!

401
00:32:45,600 --> 00:32:46,794
Hold it!

402
00:32:49,200 --> 00:32:50,394
Have you seen this man?

403
00:32:50,400 --> 00:32:51,628
No

404
00:32:52,640 --> 00:32:53,675
Don't worry

405
00:32:54,200 --> 00:32:56,191
This is my friend.

406
00:32:57,760 --> 00:32:58,875
Thank you

407
00:32:59,120 --> 00:33:00,599
Do you know who I am?

408
00:33:01,000 --> 00:33:02,718
I've seen TV.

409
00:33:02,840 --> 00:33:06,071
You don't look like a murderer to me.

410
00:33:36,800 --> 00:33:37,789
It's hard.

411
00:33:39,360 --> 00:33:40,793
Please use the towel

412
00:33:44,440 --> 00:33:45,839
It's hot.

413
00:33:46,560 --> 00:33:49,313
What about the stupid guy from the precinct?

414
00:33:49,800 --> 00:33:51,358
I'm not here?

415
00:33:56,120 --> 00:33:57,678
It's still here.

416
00:33:57,800 --> 00:33:59,995
What do you think? For me?

417
00:34:00,080 --> 00:34:01,752
I tried to wear a suit too.

418
00:34:03,880 --> 00:34:05,233
I spent the night

419
00:34:05,240 --> 00:34:07,117
Investigated the background of Duchu

420
00:34:07,120 --> 00:34:09,588
1976 Born in Qingdao, China

421
00:34:09,600 --> 00:34:11,591
Studying law at Columbia University in New York

422
00:34:11,600 --> 00:34:13,511
And I've also studied medicine law.

423
00:34:14,920 --> 00:34:16,069
All right, listen up.

424
00:34:16,440 --> 00:34:18,908
From now on, you're going to be completely Duchu.

425
00:34:20,000 --> 00:34:21,353
Feel the way he feels

426
00:34:21,360 --> 00:34:23,351
Imagine what he imagined.

427
00:34:25,240 --> 00:34:27,151
It's just information.

428
00:34:44,240 --> 00:34:46,515
Stab wounds were stabbed after death.

429
00:34:47,360 --> 00:34:50,193
If the time of death is late at night,

430
00:34:51,280 --> 00:34:52,429
Before daybreak, the murderer should

431
00:34:52,440 --> 00:34:53,919
Have enough time to escape

432
00:34:55,280 --> 00:34:56,679
Murderer is

433
00:34:57,240 --> 00:35:01,279
Sleeping next to the body in the morning?

434
00:35:01,440 --> 00:35:02,873
Still is

435
00:35:03,640 --> 00:35:06,632
This is a carefully designed trap?

436
00:35:07,720 --> 00:35:09,358
I think it's a trap.

437
00:35:10,360 --> 00:35:11,998
Traces left at the scene.

438
00:35:12,520 --> 00:35:14,238
Will lead us to the truth.

439
00:35:17,960 --> 00:35:20,315
Where the victim was first attacked.

440
00:35:20,320 --> 00:35:21,958
Not in bed.

441
00:35:23,000 --> 00:35:26,549
She was moved up after she died.

442
00:35:29,120 --> 00:35:30,678
And the dead that Duchu knew.

443
00:35:30,680 --> 00:35:32,671
Free access to his quarters.

444
00:35:32,920 --> 00:35:34,876
The Zipper and buttons on the Vic's clothes.

445
00:35:34,880 --> 00:35:36,757
Only her own fingerprints.

446
00:35:36,760 --> 00:35:39,718
She took the clothes off herself.

447
00:35:40,360 --> 00:35:42,396
On the turntable and the goblet

448
00:35:42,400 --> 00:35:44,709
and her fingerprints.

449
00:35:44,920 --> 00:35:48,708
She drinks, listens to the music, waits for him.

450
00:35:49,840 --> 00:35:52,229
That's when Duchu's not back.

451
00:35:52,720 --> 00:35:53,835
But

452
00:35:53,960 --> 00:35:55,871
She's very confident.

453
00:35:56,400 --> 00:35:59,437
Must be able to charm this man.

454
00:36:00,000 --> 00:36:02,594
Blood on the rug near the desk.

455
00:36:02,920 --> 00:36:04,956
Consistent with the victim's blood.

456
00:36:05,960 --> 00:36:06,836
She had

457
00:36:07,000 --> 00:36:09,230
There's a fierce entanglement with the killer.

458
00:36:11,040 --> 00:36:13,759
She stood by the window and looked out of the window

459
00:36:14,040 --> 00:36:16,508
Waiting for the killer to come back.

460
00:36:25,080 --> 00:36:26,991
And then the killer showed up.

461
00:36:27,240 --> 00:36:29,595
The atmosphere has become different.

462
00:36:29,680 --> 00:36:31,272
No longer the original romantic night

463
00:36:32,080 --> 00:36:33,559
For some reason

464
00:36:33,560 --> 00:36:35,710
The murderer suddenly killed her.

465
00:36:36,840 --> 00:36:38,910
The first attack was at the desk.

466
00:36:39,440 --> 00:36:41,317
Strangled her with a tie.

467
00:36:41,400 --> 00:36:43,356
The ligature marks from the Vic's neck can prove

468
00:36:43,720 --> 00:36:44,709
But we

469
00:36:44,720 --> 00:36:47,154
Didn't find this tie at the scene.

470
00:36:50,240 --> 00:36:51,798
She desperately grabbed the curtains behind the desk.

471
00:36:51,800 --> 00:36:53,233
Trying to escape from the murderer's palm.

472
00:36:53,520 --> 00:36:54,396
This

473
00:36:54,560 --> 00:36:56,790
Found it between her nails.

474
00:36:56,800 --> 00:36:59,075
The same fiber as the curtains can prove

475
00:37:22,280 --> 00:37:24,157
Hey, calm down!

476
00:37:24,680 --> 00:37:25,829
Calm down!

477
00:37:26,120 --> 00:37:27,155
Feed！

478
00:37:31,560 --> 00:37:32,834
Don't cry

479
00:37:34,840 --> 00:37:36,353
It's not over yet.

480
00:38:13,800 --> 00:38:15,916
The murderer was left-handed.

481
00:38:18,400 --> 00:38:20,834
Maybe there's someone else on the scene.

482
00:38:22,120 --> 00:38:25,669
Duchu could be innocent, right?

483
00:38:31,320 --> 00:38:34,153
Hey, who's looking for a job?

484
00:38:35,320 --> 00:38:37,311
Only 10 places

485
00:38:37,920 --> 00:38:39,797
You want to work, line up first.

486
00:38:39,800 --> 00:38:42,155
One for the first check.

487
00:38:42,960 --> 00:38:44,359
This black car

488
00:38:44,440 --> 00:38:45,998
Every two days

489
00:38:46,000 --> 00:38:47,558
To recruit workers.

490
00:38:47,560 --> 00:38:49,391
It's pretty popular.

491
00:38:49,720 --> 00:38:51,312
What kind of work are they going to do?

492
00:38:51,560 --> 00:38:54,279
I heard it was for a pharmaceutical company.

493
00:38:55,160 --> 00:38:57,390
What Institute work?

494
00:38:57,760 --> 00:38:59,591
Looks like the money's good.

495
00:39:00,040 --> 00:39:01,393
When they got there,

496
00:39:01,640 --> 00:39:04,108
No one's ever come back.

497
00:39:07,360 --> 00:39:08,588
I have to go

498
00:39:08,600 --> 00:39:10,079
There are important things to do.

499
00:39:10,520 --> 00:39:11,953
Send you an old saying

500
00:39:12,320 --> 00:39:14,038
You can lose anything.

501
00:39:14,240 --> 00:39:17,312
Don't lose your mind.

502
00:39:19,680 --> 00:39:21,113
We'll start the search now.

503
00:39:21,120 --> 00:39:22,553
Please cooperate.

504
00:39:26,840 --> 00:39:27,795
Hey, you!

505
00:39:27,920 --> 00:39:28,796
Hey, stop!

506
00:39:29,080 --> 00:39:30,274
Come on, don't go!

507
00:39:30,880 --> 00:39:33,997
Red dress!

508
00:39:34,720 --> 00:39:37,359
Hey, stop! Don't go!

509
00:39:46,960 --> 00:39:49,076
Let go of me!

510
00:40:01,400 --> 00:40:02,992
This case can't be delayed.

511
00:40:03,080 --> 00:40:05,310
Otherwise, the damage to the image of the pharmaceutical factory can not be estimated

512
00:40:06,160 --> 00:40:08,151
Put pressure on the police

513
00:40:08,240 --> 00:40:10,037
Let them solve the case soon.

514
00:40:12,120 --> 00:40:13,599
We're paying you so much.

515
00:40:13,720 --> 00:40:15,233
Not even a little bit of it.

516
00:40:15,760 --> 00:40:16,749
President

517
00:40:18,040 --> 00:40:19,359
Your phone

518
00:40:21,720 --> 00:40:22,869
Hey, hello.

519
00:40:22,880 --> 00:40:24,074
President

520
00:40:24,920 --> 00:40:26,114
Mr. Du?

521
00:40:26,440 --> 00:40:29,034
You're probably waiting for my call, too.

522
00:40:29,040 --> 00:40:30,758
Looks like we need to meet.

523
00:40:31,080 --> 00:40:32,957
That 12 o'clock noon.

524
00:40:33,560 --> 00:40:35,198
See you in La Melodie.

525
00:40:41,200 --> 00:40:44,078
You go on a test Duchu know how much

526
00:40:44,640 --> 00:40:45,993
Whatever it takes, let him speak.

527
00:40:46,000 --> 00:40:47,797
Never let him fall into the hands of the police.

528
00:40:48,160 --> 00:40:51,357
Well, that's the way to get rid of Duchu.

529
00:40:51,960 --> 00:40:53,234
The case is over.

530
00:41:00,440 --> 00:41:01,839
"La Melodie"

531
00:41:03,400 --> 00:41:04,879
That's him

532
00:41:17,240 --> 00:41:19,879
I don't want to rely on these pills anymore.

533
00:41:19,880 --> 00:41:21,233
It's so painful to live!

534
00:41:21,240 --> 00:41:22,673
I don't want to see you upset.

535
00:41:22,760 --> 00:41:24,591
I promise this is the last time

536
00:41:41,960 --> 00:41:42,836
Look at that.

537
00:41:43,800 --> 00:41:44,949
Our next goal

538
00:41:50,560 --> 00:41:52,118
If you can't do it.

539
00:41:52,400 --> 00:41:54,197
I can handle it myself.

540
00:42:14,200 --> 00:42:15,553
What's the point?

541
00:42:17,520 --> 00:42:18,396
is something wrong?

542
00:42:18,680 --> 00:42:20,079
New clue

543
00:42:20,080 --> 00:42:22,116
A Aoki lawyer who works with Duchu.

544
00:42:22,120 --> 00:42:23,792
Left the Tenjin headquarters.

545
00:42:23,800 --> 00:42:24,915
That means.

546
00:42:24,920 --> 00:42:26,797
Is Aoki related to the case?

547
00:42:27,080 --> 00:42:27,876
Yes

548
00:42:27,880 --> 00:42:29,677
The shallow wild chief had ordered

549
00:42:29,680 --> 00:42:32,752
Track all people associated with Duchu.

550
00:42:36,320 --> 00:42:38,675
Welcome！ -Beef and chicken rolls, one for each.

551
00:42:38,680 --> 00:42:40,033
May I have your order?

552
00:42:42,160 --> 00:42:43,434
Give me a cup of coffee

553
00:42:43,720 --> 00:42:45,711
Would you like the ice or the heat?

554
00:42:45,920 --> 00:42:46,909
Come on, ice.

555
00:42:46,920 --> 00:42:48,194
Good

556
00:42:55,240 --> 00:42:56,514
Why are you here by yourself?

557
00:42:57,080 --> 00:42:57,956
Where's the president?

558
00:43:15,320 --> 00:43:16,514
Stop the car! Stop the car!

559
00:43:18,080 --> 00:43:19,991
-Back up! Back up! -It's backwards.

560
00:43:21,720 --> 00:43:24,029
A group of people with long shallow wild lines

561
00:43:24,040 --> 00:43:25,917
is also near La Melodie restaurant.

562
00:43:26,320 --> 00:43:27,230
As good friends

563
00:43:27,320 --> 00:43:28,639
I have to tell you.

564
00:43:28,640 --> 00:43:30,870
The more you know the truth, the more dangerous

565
00:43:31,040 --> 00:43:33,998
I'm sure you'll never kill Shizi.

566
00:43:34,640 --> 00:43:37,234
Do you ever wonder who's going to set you up?

567
00:43:37,720 --> 00:43:38,630
No

568
00:43:38,800 --> 00:43:40,950
I'm guessing your current situation.

569
00:43:40,960 --> 00:43:43,633
It's a lot to do with you leaving the drug factory.

570
00:43:44,520 --> 00:43:47,080
They're colluding with an illegal private equity aether.

571
00:43:47,200 --> 00:43:49,031
To develop a very inhumane new drug.

572
00:43:50,080 --> 00:43:51,115
Do you remember?

573
00:43:51,360 --> 00:43:53,032
Your involvement in the Beichuan robbery.

574
00:43:53,240 --> 00:43:55,674
Didn't he steal the anesthetic equation?

575
00:43:55,680 --> 00:43:58,194
That's the key ingredient in the new drug.

576
00:43:58,800 --> 00:44:00,836
I heard it was military-specific drugs.

577
00:44:03,760 --> 00:44:04,829
What are you hesitating about?

578
00:44:05,520 --> 00:44:06,714
Come on.

579
00:44:08,640 --> 00:44:09,675
I'm a lawyer.

580
00:44:09,840 --> 00:44:11,114
May I help you?

581
00:44:12,320 --> 00:44:13,912
Target clarity is almost there.

582
00:44:14,440 --> 00:44:15,668
This can be a violation

583
00:44:15,760 --> 00:44:17,193
International Convention on Psychotropic Substances

584
00:44:17,680 --> 00:44:18,829
Open Guns!

585
00:44:19,600 --> 00:44:21,909
The important person who used to leave the pharmaceutical factory ...

586
00:44:25,520 --> 00:44:26,555
Open Guns!

587
00:44:35,240 --> 00:44:37,629
Always let me clean up the mess!

588
00:44:42,920 --> 00:44:44,433
Not！ Away！

589
00:44:55,920 --> 00:44:57,239
No way?

590
00:45:03,720 --> 00:45:04,596
The police are here!

591
00:45:14,760 --> 00:45:15,875
Damn it!

592
00:45:33,320 --> 00:45:34,309
Tie Chang

593
00:45:34,880 --> 00:45:35,995
-What's wrong?

594
00:45:36,080 --> 00:45:37,149
Aoki's dead.

595
00:46:03,680 --> 00:46:04,430
Be careful!

596
00:46:04,840 --> 00:46:06,353
Step aside!

597
00:46:06,560 --> 00:46:07,709
What are you doing?

598
00:47:29,960 --> 00:47:31,075
Damn it!

599
00:47:34,800 --> 00:47:37,075
You said you didn't kill anyone.

600
00:47:38,120 --> 00:47:39,269
Then you must cooperate with me.

601
00:47:39,280 --> 00:47:41,236
You cops can't be trusted.

602
00:47:41,240 --> 00:47:43,151
That shallow-goose is going to kill me.

603
00:47:43,400 --> 00:47:45,595
You have no reason not to believe me.

604
00:47:46,120 --> 00:47:47,519
-Believe you? -To

605
00:47:49,320 --> 00:47:50,389
Joke!

606
00:48:20,640 --> 00:48:23,916
Feed！ Wait, don't run!

607
00:48:25,520 --> 00:48:27,431
Doing？ Let me go!

608
00:48:35,160 --> 00:48:36,434
I am sorry!

609
00:48:37,720 --> 00:48:39,676
Feed！ That one! Stop！ Hold it

610
00:48:41,680 --> 00:48:43,750
We prepared for the summer

611
00:48:43,760 --> 00:48:46,320
Cool water vapor Spray cools everyone

612
00:48:46,440 --> 00:48:47,998
Let's play together!

613
00:49:21,120 --> 00:49:22,439
I really didn't kill anyone.

614
00:49:26,240 --> 00:49:28,151
I'd like to ask you to be my time witness.

615
00:49:29,720 --> 00:49:30,914
You can prove it.

616
00:49:31,280 --> 00:49:32,952
The night the woman was murdered.

617
00:49:33,400 --> 00:49:34,879
I'm with you.

618
00:49:50,520 --> 00:49:52,272
In our line of work.

619
00:49:52,280 --> 00:49:53,872
Not eligible to fall in love

620
00:49:53,880 --> 00:49:56,758
The first time a man has protected me like this ...

621
00:49:59,960 --> 00:50:01,313
You think you're five years old?

622
00:50:01,840 --> 00:50:04,035
Why don't you go back to the orphanage?

623
00:50:05,880 --> 00:50:07,871
I just want to be a normal person.

624
00:50:09,200 --> 00:50:10,997
But it's too late.

625
00:50:18,040 --> 00:50:18,790
Wainscots

626
00:50:19,760 --> 00:50:22,035
Since we don't know what day we're going to live

627
00:50:22,560 --> 00:50:25,358
Why do you have to live with a bad mood?

628
00:50:28,720 --> 00:50:30,631
Is the soup good?

629
00:50:39,800 --> 00:50:40,949
We have a new target.

630
00:50:41,520 --> 00:50:42,999
I'll do it alone this time.

631
00:50:43,240 --> 00:50:45,515
Before you get sentimental.

632
00:50:47,400 --> 00:50:49,197
The guy's in our search network.

633
00:50:49,200 --> 00:50:51,316
Risk appearing in broad daylight

634
00:50:52,520 --> 00:50:55,034
He's challenging us.

635
00:50:55,040 --> 00:50:56,029
Still is

636
00:50:56,560 --> 00:50:58,516
Just a simple fool

637
00:50:59,360 --> 00:51:00,509
Shi Cun

638
00:51:00,920 --> 00:51:03,115
There's been an incident of guns killings.

639
00:51:03,200 --> 00:51:06,510
The whole of Osaka is in a panic.

640
00:51:06,520 --> 00:51:08,317
There should be something else in this case.

641
00:51:09,360 --> 00:51:12,158
There must be some kind of force behind it.

642
00:51:12,560 --> 00:51:15,552
Let the little fish bait the big fish.

643
00:51:18,560 --> 00:51:19,754
Got it

644
00:51:22,720 --> 00:51:24,119
Find Duchu

645
00:51:28,520 --> 00:51:30,033
Let me see what this woman looks like.

646
00:51:30,280 --> 00:51:31,998
What's going on?

647
00:51:32,720 --> 00:51:34,790
With this woman again.

648
00:51:36,680 --> 00:51:38,591
Two people meet at the station

649
00:51:40,360 --> 00:51:41,554
Not by chance.

650
00:51:59,520 --> 00:52:00,953
-Get back to work.

651
00:52:02,400 --> 00:52:03,276
Miss

652
00:52:03,800 --> 00:52:04,755
How could this man ...

653
00:52:05,080 --> 00:52:06,069
Sister Choi

654
00:52:06,080 --> 00:52:08,640
Get him a room and a suit.

655
00:52:08,960 --> 00:52:10,712
Guess he's hungry, too.

656
00:52:10,720 --> 00:52:11,550
But...

657
00:52:11,760 --> 00:52:14,115
Go on, do as I say.

658
00:52:14,200 --> 00:52:15,110
Yes

659
00:52:15,120 --> 00:52:17,350
Let's talk about it tomorrow morning.

660
00:52:17,640 --> 00:52:19,119
You're going to have a night off here today.

661
00:52:25,200 --> 00:52:27,111
Your rest room is upstairs.

662
00:52:27,120 --> 00:52:28,394
Miss, don't want anyone.

663
00:52:28,400 --> 00:52:29,799
Close to this room.

664
00:52:47,520 --> 00:52:49,112
Don't push me.

665
00:52:50,120 --> 00:52:51,997
What am I going to do?

666
00:52:56,280 --> 00:52:58,350
You haven't slept in days.

667
00:52:58,920 --> 00:53:00,638
It hasn't happened yet.

668
00:53:00,640 --> 00:53:01,993
Don't think too much.

669
00:53:02,400 --> 00:53:05,278
I've been developing new drugs to save lives.

670
00:53:06,320 --> 00:53:10,598
I don't want the bad guys taking my recipe.

671
00:53:10,600 --> 00:53:12,158
To do something illegal.

672
00:53:30,640 --> 00:53:32,278
I'm going to take you somewhere.

673
00:53:34,040 --> 00:53:35,792
You'll remember it all your life.

674
00:53:44,040 --> 00:53:45,439
Remember you were robbed of your crime?

675
00:53:45,440 --> 00:53:47,192
The Beichuan of the accusation?

676
00:53:48,200 --> 00:53:49,269
My fiance.

677
00:53:51,680 --> 00:53:52,635
Used to be

678
00:54:03,400 --> 00:54:05,675
This is Dabanfu.

679
00:54:06,120 --> 00:54:08,315
We're investigating a homicide.

680
00:54:08,320 --> 00:54:11,153
I want to see your hostess.

681
00:54:20,320 --> 00:54:23,232
Please two to hold each other's right hand

682
00:54:23,720 --> 00:54:24,994
Three years ago

683
00:54:25,400 --> 00:54:27,152
I could have been like them.

684
00:54:33,760 --> 00:54:35,239
That year, April 3.

685
00:54:36,400 --> 00:54:38,755
The day after the court's verdict was defeated.

686
00:54:39,800 --> 00:54:40,994
I'm standing right there.

687
00:54:42,360 --> 00:54:43,679
I'll wait for him.

688
00:54:44,320 --> 00:54:45,753
Waiting for the Blessing

689
00:54:46,600 --> 00:54:48,511
Waiting for my happy life

690
00:54:52,520 --> 00:54:54,431
I thought I could catch

691
00:54:54,440 --> 00:54:57,079
The cherry blossom is the most beautiful time to get married

692
00:54:58,160 --> 00:55:00,355
I didn't expect the flowers of that year

693
00:55:00,360 --> 00:55:01,713
End up very early

694
00:55:42,880 --> 00:55:44,438
The day of the losing

695
00:55:45,760 --> 00:55:47,352
He just said a word.

696
00:55:49,120 --> 00:55:51,156
You'll know that sooner or later.

697
00:55:52,440 --> 00:55:54,715
Maybe I'm dead to prove it.

698
00:55:57,440 --> 00:55:58,668
I am sorry

699
00:56:02,080 --> 00:56:03,559
I am sorry?

700
00:56:06,160 --> 00:56:07,559
The tree told me.

701
00:56:08,760 --> 00:56:09,909
It's you

702
00:56:11,000 --> 00:56:13,116
You said he stole the new drug recipe.

703
00:56:13,760 --> 00:56:15,716
Do you know why he stole it?

704
00:56:16,640 --> 00:56:19,632
He didn't want the Sakai to take these things to harm others!

705
00:56:20,360 --> 00:56:21,873
You really think

706
00:56:21,880 --> 00:56:23,711
Everything you know.

707
00:56:23,720 --> 00:56:25,438
Is that the truth?

708
00:57:10,840 --> 00:57:11,829
Are you hurt?

709
00:57:12,560 --> 00:57:13,629
Leg hurt.

710
00:57:14,400 --> 00:57:16,516
Yes, I have a new drug.

711
00:57:17,320 --> 00:57:19,038
Do you have a chance to catch up with them?

712
00:57:19,120 --> 00:57:20,109
Yes!

713
00:57:22,320 --> 00:57:23,833
Let me run into that cop again.

714
00:57:24,120 --> 00:57:25,235
Must have killed him.

715
00:57:25,320 --> 00:57:26,639
I've called them over.

716
00:57:26,640 --> 00:57:27,789
Case

717
00:57:30,880 --> 00:57:31,835
It's him

718
00:57:32,160 --> 00:57:33,878
He's been chasing me from Osaka.

719
00:58:30,960 --> 00:58:32,109
You all right?

720
00:58:49,120 --> 00:58:50,189
You okay?

721
00:58:53,120 --> 00:58:54,109
Feed！

722
00:58:54,120 --> 00:58:55,109
What the!

723
00:58:55,440 --> 00:58:56,395
No!

724
00:59:03,240 --> 00:59:04,036
Son of a bitch!

725
00:59:05,120 --> 00:59:07,190
You know who he is!

726
00:59:07,320 --> 00:59:08,639
Why are you still with him?

727
00:59:08,640 --> 00:59:09,675
I'm not going to let him go!

728
00:59:09,800 --> 00:59:10,869
Get down!

729
00:59:43,800 --> 00:59:46,268
How many people did you provoke?

730
00:59:47,640 --> 00:59:49,119
Are you happy now?

731
00:59:50,360 --> 00:59:51,839
Before I met you,

732
00:59:52,640 --> 00:59:54,631
I'm living a very comfortable life.

733
00:59:54,640 --> 00:59:56,392
Before I unlocked the cuffs.

734
00:59:56,920 --> 00:59:58,114
We'd better get along peacefully.

735
00:59:59,440 --> 01:00:00,759
I hope so.

736
01:00:02,440 --> 01:00:04,590
Hey！ Slow down!

737
01:00:05,080 --> 01:00:07,310
Sorry, Granny.

738
01:00:07,320 --> 01:00:08,992
I'm going to take you with me.

739
01:00:09,000 --> 01:00:11,309
You look like a fugitive.

740
01:00:11,320 --> 01:00:14,551
Even if you die, I'll take you

741
01:00:14,960 --> 01:00:16,154
Drag it back to the station.

742
01:00:22,720 --> 01:00:23,869
You tell him.

743
01:00:23,880 --> 01:00:25,438
The night that Shizi was killed.

744
01:00:25,440 --> 01:00:27,112
I was with you.

745
01:00:28,320 --> 01:00:29,594
You tell her

746
01:00:29,600 --> 01:00:31,318
Evidence of the Beichuan case.

747
01:00:31,320 --> 01:00:32,799
It's from your police.

748
01:00:32,800 --> 01:00:34,836
She always said I killed her fiance.

749
01:00:39,920 --> 01:00:41,194
You're with him?

750
01:00:41,880 --> 01:00:43,598
The night Shizi was killed?

751
01:00:48,120 --> 01:00:49,235
This guy

752
01:00:49,760 --> 01:00:52,149
Are you telling the truth?

753
01:00:53,120 --> 01:00:55,350
If I'm going to jail, I'll see you.

754
01:01:00,560 --> 01:01:01,629
That night

755
01:01:02,920 --> 01:01:06,595
I was with him.

756
01:01:06,600 --> 01:01:09,433
About 0 in the morning.

757
01:01:11,680 --> 01:01:14,035
Can you be his time witness?

758
01:01:14,040 --> 01:01:15,234
OK

759
01:01:18,240 --> 01:01:19,673
Thank you for clarifying me.

760
01:01:20,400 --> 01:01:21,799
Don't come with me.

761
01:01:22,320 --> 01:01:23,878
Wait till you get out of here.

762
01:01:32,120 --> 01:01:33,439
Miss, what's going on?

763
01:01:33,440 --> 01:01:34,953
Just come with me.

764
01:01:36,120 --> 01:01:37,394
-The police, sir? -Go inside.

765
01:01:38,680 --> 01:01:39,908
What happened?

766
01:01:39,920 --> 01:01:41,148
Away from the window!

767
01:01:42,000 --> 01:01:43,399
All down on the second floor.

768
01:01:43,400 --> 01:01:45,038
Never close to the window!

769
01:01:50,120 --> 01:01:51,314
Strange

770
01:01:52,520 --> 01:01:56,513
Cops and killers always come together.

771
01:01:59,880 --> 01:02:02,838
I don't want to die with you.

772
01:02:03,560 --> 01:02:05,312
I don't want to.

773
01:02:10,640 --> 01:02:13,598
Can you use it?

774
01:02:14,120 --> 01:02:15,314
Of course

775
01:02:15,320 --> 01:02:17,880
I've been hunting with my father since I was six years old.

776
01:02:31,840 --> 01:02:33,239
Back off!

777
01:02:58,960 --> 01:03:00,029
Go！

778
01:03:21,360 --> 01:03:22,429
This way!

779
01:04:13,720 --> 01:04:15,278
You should do it for him.

780
01:04:16,880 --> 01:04:18,199
Cheer up.

781
01:04:31,800 --> 01:04:32,949
It's your turn.

782
01:04:33,240 --> 01:04:34,150
I can't

783
01:04:35,280 --> 01:04:36,679
I'm used to the right hand

784
01:04:36,960 --> 01:04:39,394
Today you have to use your left hand

785
01:04:39,880 --> 01:04:41,154
I can't kill people.

786
01:04:41,160 --> 01:04:42,354
Can you kick?

787
01:04:46,160 --> 01:04:47,388
I'll take care of it.

788
01:05:07,520 --> 01:05:08,555
Go！

789
01:05:35,960 --> 01:05:37,109
Sister Choi!

790
01:06:36,920 --> 01:06:37,989
Fast！

791
01:07:00,720 --> 01:07:01,550
Get down!

792
01:07:03,440 --> 01:07:04,190
Mr Murakami

793
01:07:05,400 --> 01:07:06,628
Get the hospital!

794
01:07:07,960 --> 01:07:09,154
The length of the tie!

795
01:07:12,080 --> 01:07:13,229
Wainscots！

796
01:07:13,560 --> 01:07:15,915
Wake up! You wake up and blush!

797
01:07:16,560 --> 01:07:17,675
Wainscots！

798
01:07:18,240 --> 01:07:20,993
The new drug My father gave me was too strong.

799
01:07:22,200 --> 01:07:23,918
I don't feel anything.

800
01:07:24,600 --> 01:07:26,272
You'll be fine, rosy.

801
01:07:48,440 --> 01:07:49,555
You okay?

802
01:07:51,040 --> 01:07:52,678
-Hundred fields-yes

803
01:07:53,400 --> 01:07:54,435
Untie

804
01:07:58,200 --> 01:07:59,269
Untie

805
01:08:02,160 --> 01:08:03,229
Is

806
01:08:07,640 --> 01:08:09,551
-Get the Doctor.

807
01:08:10,680 --> 01:08:12,796
You're not with me today.

808
01:08:14,360 --> 01:08:15,270
Is it?

809
01:08:16,080 --> 01:08:17,195
No

810
01:08:21,280 --> 01:08:22,918
You're free.

811
01:08:25,320 --> 01:08:26,435
Come on!

812
01:08:32,640 --> 01:08:33,550
Don't worry

813
01:08:33,800 --> 01:08:35,279
I'm not going to die.

814
01:08:35,280 --> 01:08:36,235
You okay?

815
01:08:36,720 --> 01:08:37,914
We'll take care of it.

816
01:08:38,840 --> 01:08:39,750
Okay, lift your feet.

817
01:08:48,880 --> 01:08:50,359
The bullet went through his body.

818
01:08:50,720 --> 01:08:51,709
Not in the body.

819
01:08:52,040 --> 01:08:53,109
To get through the dangerous moment

820
01:08:53,120 --> 01:08:54,519
I'll let you know when the anesthetic's back.

821
01:08:54,920 --> 01:08:56,273
Thank you

822
01:09:11,880 --> 01:09:13,154
Where did Duchu escape?

823
01:09:13,360 --> 01:09:14,349
What happened?

824
01:09:14,360 --> 01:09:15,315
Roller！

825
01:09:16,080 --> 01:09:17,798
I'm your boss, too.

826
01:09:19,320 --> 01:09:21,151
You have an obligation to report to me!

827
01:09:24,440 --> 01:09:26,431
My boss is the chief of the village.

828
01:09:28,040 --> 01:09:29,996
I'm not obligated to follow your orders.

829
01:09:30,600 --> 01:09:34,354
Vector Village deliberately let go of suspect

830
01:09:34,800 --> 01:09:37,758
I'm the commander in the case.

831
01:09:38,400 --> 01:09:40,277
Don't you know you're in trouble?

832
01:09:41,600 --> 01:09:43,272
The medicine you took has already betrayed you.

833
01:09:45,400 --> 01:09:46,913
Soon

834
01:09:48,040 --> 01:09:49,268
You're no longer a dean.

835
01:09:49,360 --> 01:09:50,634
Son of a bitch!

836
01:09:52,040 --> 01:09:53,439
What do you mean?

837
01:09:56,360 --> 01:09:58,078
Are you going to kill me?

838
01:09:59,240 --> 01:10:01,196
The man searching for a lesson is almost there.

839
01:10:02,000 --> 01:10:03,672
Just to catch you, the current criminal.

840
01:10:06,160 --> 01:10:09,277
It's the guy in the way!

841
01:10:17,160 --> 01:10:20,311
You never wanted to leak the drug factory's secrets.

842
01:10:20,640 --> 01:10:22,392
This is Duchu's computer.

843
01:10:22,600 --> 01:10:23,828
And also

844
01:10:26,200 --> 01:10:27,189
This one

845
01:10:28,840 --> 01:10:31,070
Hey, come on.

846
01:10:31,400 --> 01:10:33,038
I killed Shizi.

847
01:10:33,320 --> 01:10:34,719
Where are you now?

848
01:10:34,720 --> 01:10:36,153
Apartments in Duchu

849
01:10:36,160 --> 01:10:37,149
You don't touch anything.

850
01:10:37,320 --> 01:10:38,878
I'll take care of it.

851
01:10:55,400 --> 01:10:57,789
Dad, don't listen to that bastard.

852
01:11:03,280 --> 01:11:05,635
Vector village is investigating me.

853
01:11:07,040 --> 01:11:08,951
I have no choice but to flee overseas.

854
01:11:10,240 --> 01:11:12,834
Why didn't you drop the Duchugan at the scene?

855
01:11:16,280 --> 01:11:17,838
If you kill him,

856
01:11:18,520 --> 01:11:20,431
No, it's all settled?

857
01:11:23,520 --> 01:11:25,351
Are you blaming me?

858
01:11:28,960 --> 01:11:30,234
Think clearly

859
01:11:31,680 --> 01:11:33,318
I'm doing this for your son.

860
01:11:33,880 --> 01:11:35,518
To preserve

861
01:11:35,520 --> 01:11:37,829
The reputation and innocence of the new president

862
01:11:38,400 --> 01:11:39,310
And also

863
01:11:39,800 --> 01:11:41,313
I don't have a fallback anymore.

864
01:11:43,400 --> 01:11:44,674
So

865
01:11:45,160 --> 01:11:47,037
How much are you going to pay me?

866
01:11:54,360 --> 01:11:56,920
Kicked by his own dog.

867
01:12:06,640 --> 01:12:07,959
Look me in the eye

868
01:12:08,920 --> 01:12:10,751
Do you think I'm blind?

869
01:12:13,240 --> 01:12:14,514
Cheer up.

870
01:12:15,720 --> 01:12:19,030
You're the next president of the gods Pharmacy.

871
01:12:20,880 --> 01:12:21,835
Is

872
01:12:31,240 --> 01:12:33,356
I found some information from the tree in the room.

873
01:12:34,720 --> 01:12:36,676
But I've never seen it before.

874
01:12:37,400 --> 01:12:38,435
Come on, help me out.

875
01:12:39,120 --> 01:12:40,951
There's one more thing I still don't understand.

876
01:12:43,200 --> 01:12:45,270
What kind of drug research

877
01:12:45,680 --> 01:12:47,033
Can make a fund

878
01:12:47,200 --> 01:12:50,112
Spend so much money on a pharmaceutical factory

879
01:12:51,080 --> 01:12:52,195
"Aether"

880
01:12:52,960 --> 01:12:54,029
What the?

881
01:12:54,040 --> 01:12:55,758
A fund in Bermuda

882
01:12:56,200 --> 01:12:58,668
They continue to sponsor drug companies to develop new drugs

883
01:12:59,520 --> 01:13:01,829
The president of Sakai didn't let me in on this project.

884
01:13:03,000 --> 01:13:04,115
That's what I am.

885
01:13:05,160 --> 01:13:06,718
They're in the dark.

886
01:13:14,960 --> 01:13:16,359
This is a tree candid.

887
01:13:17,400 --> 01:13:18,389
This one

888
01:13:18,600 --> 01:13:19,828
What do you mean?

889
01:13:20,560 --> 01:13:23,279
This is the code for the pharmaceutical formulations of the Tenjin pharmaceutical Factory.

890
01:13:24,080 --> 01:13:25,559
The pharmaceutical companies keep secrets.

891
01:13:25,960 --> 01:13:27,552
It's going to have a code of its own.

892
01:13:28,240 --> 01:13:30,595
This is supposed to be a new drug recipe for a positive tree.

893
01:13:35,960 --> 01:13:37,871
Has Mr. Beichuan finished?

894
01:13:37,880 --> 01:13:39,711
Please give me the formula code.

895
01:13:40,200 --> 01:13:41,633
It's not done yet.

896
01:13:42,280 --> 01:13:45,078
This recipe code is important to us!

897
01:13:46,120 --> 01:13:48,998
It's what the Sakai always wanted.

898
01:13:50,840 --> 01:13:52,910
They're doing human experimentation with the living.

899
01:14:01,640 --> 01:14:02,868
It's beautiful.

900
01:14:02,880 --> 01:14:04,711
When you see this letter,

901
01:14:04,880 --> 01:14:06,950
I should have died.

902
01:14:07,760 --> 01:14:09,716
To give you happiness

903
01:14:09,880 --> 01:14:12,030
I took the money from the Sakai.

904
01:14:13,080 --> 01:14:14,308
I'm not in your heart anymore

905
01:14:14,520 --> 01:14:16,750
The perfect, kind man.

906
01:14:17,760 --> 01:14:19,273
But my conscience tells me

907
01:14:19,920 --> 01:14:21,717
You can't give the recipe to the Sakai and the father.

908
01:14:22,680 --> 01:14:24,591
I hid the recipe here.

909
01:14:25,560 --> 01:14:28,632
Hopefully one day it will play a real role.

910
01:14:28,640 --> 01:14:30,949
For the benefit of mankind

911
01:15:18,960 --> 01:15:20,109
Purple Rain

912
01:15:20,440 --> 01:15:22,237
I'm sorry about the rosy death.

913
01:15:23,960 --> 01:15:27,748
You guys are like my own daughter.

914
01:15:29,360 --> 01:15:32,033
You can't imagine how sorry I am.

915
01:15:35,760 --> 01:15:37,990
Don't let her die in vain.

916
01:15:39,520 --> 01:15:41,397
You know what to do.

917
01:15:42,200 --> 01:15:43,758
Don't let me down.

918
01:15:46,240 --> 01:15:48,435
is Father

919
01:15:59,120 --> 01:16:00,633
Good morning

920
01:16:01,320 --> 01:16:02,719
What?

921
01:16:03,560 --> 01:16:04,879
Crying what?

922
01:16:05,720 --> 01:16:07,119
I'm just happy.

923
01:16:07,120 --> 01:16:09,554
See the length of the line is restored.

924
01:16:10,200 --> 01:16:11,713
That should be a laugh.

925
01:16:12,360 --> 01:16:14,555
Didn't the chief tell me to laugh?

926
01:16:17,880 --> 01:16:19,233
Command undo

927
01:16:21,760 --> 01:16:24,035
Now you want to laugh.

928
01:16:28,800 --> 01:16:29,789
It's just that

929
01:16:30,680 --> 01:16:32,079
Your smile

930
01:16:35,000 --> 01:16:36,399
She looks like her.

931
01:16:38,840 --> 01:16:40,432
Okay, we're not talking about this.

932
01:16:42,040 --> 01:16:43,917
Do you have anything to report to me?

933
01:16:46,120 --> 01:16:47,758
The pill that Duchu home found at the crime scene.

934
01:16:47,760 --> 01:16:49,990
Just like the pill from the shallow wild.

935
01:16:50,240 --> 01:16:53,516
The drug test report also shows that this is a super stimulant.

936
01:16:57,200 --> 01:16:58,519
It's so embarrassing.

937
01:16:59,840 --> 01:17:00,989
Don't get up.

938
01:17:03,360 --> 01:17:04,679
Excuse me

939
01:17:07,520 --> 01:17:08,555
Shi Cun

940
01:17:09,040 --> 01:17:13,238
-You're on suspension.

941
01:17:15,000 --> 01:17:16,433
Wait a minute

942
01:17:18,200 --> 01:17:20,555
I was close to mastering the key evidence.

943
01:17:21,120 --> 01:17:22,633
Catch Tenjin Pharmaceutical

944
01:17:23,080 --> 01:17:24,354
This

945
01:17:25,320 --> 01:17:27,356
I'm confident it'll solve the case.

946
01:17:27,600 --> 01:17:28,919
You've

947
01:17:29,640 --> 01:17:31,995
Released the suspect three consecutive times.

948
01:17:32,160 --> 01:17:33,639
Duchuta

949
01:17:33,640 --> 01:17:35,232
Not the real killer.

950
01:17:37,560 --> 01:17:39,039
I'm asking for an investigation.

951
01:17:40,040 --> 01:17:43,555
The light field is missing.

952
01:17:46,640 --> 01:17:47,914
Missing？

953
01:17:49,200 --> 01:17:50,792
Sakai President

954
01:17:51,840 --> 01:17:54,274
To interfere with a case investigation through officials.

955
01:17:54,280 --> 01:17:56,316
Is that so?

956
01:18:04,040 --> 01:18:06,110
What a Justice!

957
01:18:15,640 --> 01:18:18,757
"Drunken driving kills a policeman's wife."

958
01:18:19,600 --> 01:18:21,511
You haven't put it down yet.

959
01:18:22,680 --> 01:18:24,636
You think about it for me.

960
01:18:25,360 --> 01:18:27,669
There's an investigation.

961
01:18:27,680 --> 01:18:29,159
What will happen to you?

962
01:18:32,880 --> 01:18:35,314
You should move on now.

963
01:18:35,760 --> 01:18:37,159
She must

964
01:18:38,680 --> 01:18:40,352
I hope so.

965
01:18:45,040 --> 01:18:46,314
For three years

966
01:18:46,320 --> 01:18:48,675
I used to watch outside the research center.

967
01:18:49,280 --> 01:18:52,397
I've always seen a black van.

968
01:18:53,080 --> 01:18:55,435
Full of people into the research center.

969
01:18:56,280 --> 01:18:58,635
But every time it comes out, it's empty.

970
01:18:59,440 --> 01:19:00,668
Thank you for your help.

971
01:19:00,680 --> 01:19:01,908
Mr. Sakamoto

972
01:19:03,400 --> 01:19:04,833
What are you talking about?

973
01:19:05,200 --> 01:19:08,556
You can see me.

974
01:19:09,040 --> 01:19:13,636
Actually, I want to see my brother myself.

975
01:19:18,000 --> 01:19:20,195
The homeless man who came to do the experiment.

976
01:19:21,600 --> 01:19:23,591
Miss Tien, I am truly beautiful.

977
01:19:23,960 --> 01:19:28,158
He went alone to the Tenjin Pharmaceutical Research Center.

978
01:19:28,280 --> 01:19:29,998
There's no news yet.

979
01:19:31,240 --> 01:19:33,196
In case of any danger,

980
01:19:34,360 --> 01:19:35,952
You must find a way out.

981
01:19:36,280 --> 01:19:37,429
Last night

982
01:19:37,440 --> 01:19:39,829
We found the data left by the tree.

983
01:19:39,920 --> 01:19:41,399
We found the Tenjin factory.

984
01:19:41,400 --> 01:19:42,879
Always wanted to find the formula code

985
01:19:43,200 --> 01:19:44,315
Duchu said

986
01:19:44,400 --> 01:19:48,678
Make sure the village knows the secret.

987
01:19:48,760 --> 01:19:50,239
Code is

988
01:19:50,320 --> 01:19:56,873
C11h15nzn2

989
01:19:57,200 --> 01:19:58,189
Got it

990
01:19:58,200 --> 01:20:00,270
The doctor is checking for the dean.

991
01:20:00,280 --> 01:20:02,396
Don't worry, I'll tell him later.

992
01:20:12,840 --> 01:20:13,955
Miss Mei?

993
01:20:14,080 --> 01:20:15,832
If that recipe

994
01:20:15,840 --> 01:20:19,515
is used to make a drug ban.

995
01:20:24,600 --> 01:20:26,795
It's going to be us.

996
01:20:26,880 --> 01:20:28,871
The most powerful proof of the gods ' pharmacy.

997
01:20:30,280 --> 01:20:31,759
Open the door!

998
01:20:58,640 --> 01:21:00,596
-Kobayashi! -Banner!

999
01:21:00,600 --> 01:21:02,033
What's wrong?

1000
01:21:02,040 --> 01:21:04,600
I thought I was just trying cold medicine.

1001
01:21:04,600 --> 01:21:06,033
You okay?

1002
01:21:09,840 --> 01:21:12,035
Sakakou, come with me.

1003
01:21:16,920 --> 01:21:20,310
Mr. Sakamoto

1004
01:21:22,960 --> 01:21:24,439
Dr. Dean says you need to stay in the hospital.

1005
01:21:24,640 --> 01:21:25,959
You are not allowed to leave!

1006
01:21:26,960 --> 01:21:29,076
Duchu The Secret of the Gods pharmacy.

1007
01:21:29,080 --> 01:21:30,877
Tell me

1008
01:21:31,160 --> 01:21:33,515
There should be a sacrifice.

1009
01:21:33,520 --> 01:21:35,112
Then I'll go with you!

1010
01:21:36,000 --> 01:21:37,797
Don't follow me.

1011
01:21:38,960 --> 01:21:40,996
I'm already suspended.

1012
01:21:41,520 --> 01:21:42,748
Again

1013
01:21:43,360 --> 01:21:45,316
It's a personal matter.

1014
01:22:01,720 --> 01:22:03,199
Mr. Sakamoto

1015
01:22:07,600 --> 01:22:09,113
How did he become like this?

1016
01:22:09,760 --> 01:22:11,990
-What's going on? -Is everything okay?

1017
01:22:12,000 --> 01:22:14,673
Where are the security guards holding guns?

1018
01:22:14,680 --> 01:22:16,830
Not a simple handyman?

1019
01:22:17,440 --> 01:22:18,555
There must be a problem here.

1020
01:22:18,560 --> 01:22:19,675
Let's just go back.

1021
01:22:19,680 --> 01:22:20,954
Mr. Sakamoto

1022
01:23:02,040 --> 01:23:03,439
Please, you guys.

1023
01:23:04,880 --> 01:23:06,233
Don't come near me.

1024
01:23:25,760 --> 01:23:27,193
Kill me!

1025
01:23:29,840 --> 01:23:31,114
Kill me

1026
01:23:32,040 --> 01:23:33,393
Well, actually.

1027
01:23:33,600 --> 01:23:35,352
I'm a fugitive, too.

1028
01:23:35,760 --> 01:23:38,274
A runaway fugitive.

1029
01:23:39,560 --> 01:23:41,710
For 20 years.

1030
01:23:44,520 --> 01:23:46,033
My wife

1031
01:23:46,920 --> 01:23:49,275
A perfect woman.

1032
01:23:57,520 --> 01:23:59,033
Leave the One you love

1033
01:24:00,320 --> 01:24:01,639
Regret it?

1034
01:24:08,240 --> 01:24:10,674
The only thing I can do for her now

1035
01:24:11,960 --> 01:24:15,157
is not to interfere with her current life.

1036
01:24:41,680 --> 01:24:43,079
Fighting is good.

1037
01:24:43,760 --> 01:24:45,990
But is this madness a little overdone?

1038
01:24:46,600 --> 01:24:49,034
We want a controlled warrior.

1039
01:24:49,120 --> 01:24:51,998
We've been tested in the field since last year.

1040
01:24:52,600 --> 01:24:54,795
You see, with this drug, the super performance.

1041
01:24:55,240 --> 01:24:56,673
We have a new enhanced version.

1042
01:24:57,200 --> 01:25:00,909
The modified formula is exactly what you want.

1043
01:25:02,720 --> 01:25:04,153
Except for the super strength.

1044
01:25:04,160 --> 01:25:06,549
The soldiers ' minds can be completely controlled.

1045
01:25:07,440 --> 01:25:09,032
So long as there is a war

1046
01:25:09,800 --> 01:25:11,711
Whether a military power or a terrorist

1047
01:25:11,720 --> 01:25:14,075
will become our customers!

1048
01:25:27,680 --> 01:25:29,113
President Rest assured

1049
01:25:29,120 --> 01:25:31,588
If there's a mix of Beichuan developed recipes

1050
01:25:31,600 --> 01:25:34,114
The drug can be extended to the limit.

1051
01:25:40,280 --> 01:25:41,395
Why is Duchu here?

1052
01:25:41,640 --> 01:25:43,790
He got in with the homeless.

1053
01:25:44,040 --> 01:25:45,712
Never let him walk away alive.

1054
01:25:50,120 --> 01:25:51,519
Mr. Du

1055
01:25:51,520 --> 01:25:53,238
Long time no see

1056
01:25:54,200 --> 01:25:56,509
What did you do to Sakamoto?

1057
01:25:57,360 --> 01:25:59,954
He volunteered to do some ordinary experiments.

1058
01:26:08,960 --> 01:26:10,188
This one

1059
01:26:10,520 --> 01:26:12,715
It's going to be the Tenjin pharmacy.

1060
01:26:12,720 --> 01:26:14,199
A contribution to changing the world

1061
01:26:14,440 --> 01:26:15,668
One that can be on the battlefield

1062
01:26:15,760 --> 01:26:17,671
A super drug to enhance combat effectiveness

1063
01:26:18,680 --> 01:26:20,636
You murderers!

1064
01:26:26,560 --> 01:26:29,154
Humans can improve their physical fitness for a moment after the drug is injected.

1065
01:26:29,160 --> 01:26:31,151
Feel the pain and fear

1066
01:26:32,920 --> 01:26:34,638
So fighting

1067
01:26:34,920 --> 01:26:36,512
can reach the limit

1068
01:26:38,080 --> 01:26:39,354
Miss Bo.

1069
01:26:40,800 --> 01:26:43,633
But Beichuan a step early.

1070
01:26:45,800 --> 01:26:48,633
He studied the formula three years ago.

1071
01:26:49,960 --> 01:26:52,155
Just to make up for us.

1072
01:26:52,160 --> 01:26:53,798
The shortage of new drugs

1073
01:26:55,120 --> 01:26:57,509
It's Beichuan's dream.

1074
01:26:58,640 --> 01:27:00,232
Do you know where it is?

1075
01:27:03,240 --> 01:27:04,753
I'm not going to tell you.

1076
01:27:06,200 --> 01:27:09,431
The tree was developed to relieve the pain of the patient.

1077
01:27:09,440 --> 01:27:12,671
Medical Anesthesia

1078
01:27:12,680 --> 01:27:14,352
Not for you.

1079
01:27:14,640 --> 01:27:16,437
Used to kill people.

1080
01:27:17,040 --> 01:27:17,916
This experiment

1081
01:27:17,920 --> 01:27:21,515
is a tolerable manifestation of physical pain.

1082
01:27:23,600 --> 01:27:25,033
If she doesn't say it,

1083
01:27:25,760 --> 01:27:28,638
Let her never speak again.

1084
01:27:29,720 --> 01:27:30,789
Is

1085
01:27:34,600 --> 01:27:36,158
Without a weapon.

1086
01:27:38,680 --> 01:27:40,557
I've never been very good at it.

1087
01:27:40,720 --> 01:27:42,153
Dealing with the police

1088
01:27:42,160 --> 01:27:43,388
Is it?

1089
01:27:44,840 --> 01:27:46,910
What are you doing?

1090
01:27:47,600 --> 01:27:49,352
Nothing to do with you.

1091
01:27:49,800 --> 01:27:50,994
Cut the crap.

1092
01:27:52,440 --> 01:27:53,839
What do you think I am?

1093
01:27:53,920 --> 01:27:56,036
Be polite to the guests

1094
01:27:58,760 --> 01:27:59,909
A faux pas.

1095
01:28:00,560 --> 01:28:02,198
It's an honored guest.

1096
01:28:02,920 --> 01:28:04,990
I'm a Dabanfu.

1097
01:28:05,000 --> 01:28:06,228
Shi Cun Cong

1098
01:28:07,320 --> 01:28:08,878
A search for a lesson?

1099
01:28:10,920 --> 01:28:13,150
You're supposed to be suspended.

1100
01:28:18,680 --> 01:28:21,194
I know more about the police inside than you.

1101
01:28:22,120 --> 01:28:24,236
I'm closer to you than you think.

1102
01:28:24,440 --> 01:28:25,953
I'm looking for a fugitive.

1103
01:28:26,240 --> 01:28:27,958
Suspect me of harboring a fugitive?

1104
01:28:28,240 --> 01:28:30,231
His name Duchu.

1105
01:28:31,920 --> 01:28:34,753
I remember.

1106
01:28:34,760 --> 01:28:36,352
But maybe it's been too long.

1107
01:28:37,880 --> 01:28:39,393
It's a little out of whack.

1108
01:28:39,400 --> 01:28:41,152
It's a crazy mess.

1109
01:28:41,240 --> 01:28:42,673
We've locked him up.

1110
01:28:44,640 --> 01:28:46,039
I'm going to take him.

1111
01:28:46,360 --> 01:28:47,952
Do you have an arrest warrant?

1112
01:28:49,440 --> 01:28:51,795
Don't you know you're not related to the case?

1113
01:28:52,520 --> 01:28:53,999
I'll exchange some information with you.

1114
01:28:54,680 --> 01:28:55,715
Intelligence？

1115
01:28:55,720 --> 01:28:58,234
C 11 ...

1116
01:28:58,520 --> 01:29:00,511
H1 ...

1117
01:29:03,160 --> 01:29:07,153
Dad, this is the recipe code Beichuan left.

1118
01:29:07,720 --> 01:29:08,789
Don't worry.

1119
01:29:09,880 --> 01:29:11,393
Complete coding

1120
01:29:12,440 --> 01:29:13,873
Wait till I see Duchu.

1121
01:29:17,880 --> 01:29:19,029
I understand

1122
01:29:20,080 --> 01:29:21,115
I'll show you to him.

1123
01:30:00,640 --> 01:30:02,437
Lost in life

1124
01:30:02,440 --> 01:30:04,590
What kind of feeling is the most important person?

1125
01:30:04,600 --> 01:30:05,919
Pain

1126
01:30:07,400 --> 01:30:10,597
A long and endless pain

1127
01:30:11,600 --> 01:30:12,828
Why do you ask?

1128
01:30:16,000 --> 01:30:17,399
Because

1129
01:30:17,400 --> 01:30:19,197
I know the pain.

1130
01:30:59,720 --> 01:31:01,836
This medicine is so good.

1131
01:31:02,440 --> 01:31:04,715
Lawyers can turn into beasts.

1132
01:31:20,800 --> 01:31:22,756
I'm not your enemy!

1133
01:31:33,960 --> 01:31:35,439
We have to stop them.

1134
01:31:35,920 --> 01:31:37,069
Do you remember?

1135
01:31:38,080 --> 01:31:39,559
Wake Up!

1136
01:31:45,120 --> 01:31:47,156
Don't get beaten by this pill.

1137
01:31:48,040 --> 01:31:49,439
You can beat it!

1138
01:31:51,920 --> 01:31:53,831
There are too many low-level creatures in this world.

1139
01:31:53,920 --> 01:31:55,672
Of course I do.

1140
01:31:56,680 --> 01:31:58,591
You must hold on.

1141
01:31:58,800 --> 01:32:01,155
Hinder the rapid progress of human society

1142
01:32:01,320 --> 01:32:04,630
I tried, but it was really hard.

1143
01:32:05,640 --> 01:32:08,154
We want them to make a contribution to society.

1144
01:32:08,320 --> 01:32:10,311
It's time to fight back.

1145
01:32:42,920 --> 01:32:44,638
-Kill him.

1146
01:32:45,840 --> 01:32:47,068
Father

1147
01:33:09,320 --> 01:33:10,514
What are you doing?

1148
01:33:11,600 --> 01:33:14,273
You forgot who you were.

1149
01:33:14,280 --> 01:33:15,633
And rescued you from the orphanage?

1150
01:33:15,720 --> 01:33:17,517
To be your white mouse?

1151
01:33:18,000 --> 01:33:19,672
Are you out of your mind?

1152
01:33:20,240 --> 01:33:21,275
No

1153
01:33:21,880 --> 01:33:23,836
I just got it back!

1154
01:33:53,040 --> 01:33:53,870
Damn it!

1155
01:33:53,960 --> 01:33:55,188
Damn it! Damn it!

1156
01:34:03,800 --> 01:34:04,835
What a coincidence.

1157
01:34:05,240 --> 01:34:06,389
I bumped into you again.

1158
01:34:06,640 --> 01:34:08,278
Looks like our fates are tied together.

1159
01:34:08,640 --> 01:34:09,709
What the?

1160
01:34:10,160 --> 01:34:12,515
But I've always had a bad luck.

1161
01:34:13,760 --> 01:34:15,830
The people around us always suffer misfortune.

1162
01:34:16,920 --> 01:34:18,831
I'm lucky to be alive.

1163
01:34:24,720 --> 01:34:25,869
Macro！

1164
01:34:34,960 --> 01:34:36,279
Dad

1165
01:34:36,880 --> 01:34:38,950
I'll demonstrate it myself.

1166
01:34:39,640 --> 01:34:42,279
The power of our new drug

1167
01:34:44,520 --> 01:34:45,714
I want to prove

1168
01:34:46,200 --> 01:34:48,555
Everything we did was right.

1169
01:34:49,040 --> 01:34:50,393
Enough with the macros!

1170
01:34:50,400 --> 01:34:52,197
Let's get out of Here!

1171
01:35:05,800 --> 01:35:08,792
Eliminate all new drugs and funds immediately.

1172
01:35:08,800 --> 01:35:10,597
Anyway, to keep the Tenjin pharmaceutical.

1173
01:35:10,600 --> 01:35:11,635
Is

1174
01:36:39,440 --> 01:36:40,589
Open the door!

1175
01:36:57,720 --> 01:36:58,869
Come on, run! Come on, run!

1176
01:37:01,840 --> 01:37:03,512
Up！ -Here we are!

1177
01:37:03,520 --> 01:37:04,669
Father!

1178
01:37:51,800 --> 01:37:53,791
Look at you now.

1179
01:37:53,920 --> 01:37:56,434
Are you a cop?

1180
01:37:56,720 --> 01:37:58,995
You piece of crap.

1181
01:38:03,600 --> 01:38:04,919
Wait, it's dangerous!

1182
01:38:06,840 --> 01:38:08,193
Are you okay?

1183
01:38:08,760 --> 01:38:09,954
Run away!

1184
01:38:10,160 --> 01:38:11,388
You run!

1185
01:38:12,520 --> 01:38:13,794
Oh, Miss Beauty!

1186
01:38:14,600 --> 01:38:15,828
Oh, Miss Beauty!

1187
01:38:39,960 --> 01:38:41,871
Why are you here?

1188
01:38:42,360 --> 01:38:43,918
The president sent me.

1189
01:38:43,920 --> 01:38:45,717
As long as it's dad's orders.

1190
01:38:45,920 --> 01:38:47,273
Can you sleep with anyone?

1191
01:38:47,280 --> 01:38:49,316
I need that medicine.

1192
01:38:50,200 --> 01:38:52,668
You want some medicine? I'll give you the medicine! Say it.

1193
01:39:02,080 --> 01:39:03,433
Oh, Miss Beauty!

1194
01:39:22,000 --> 01:39:23,228
Everything about Dad.

1195
01:39:25,920 --> 01:39:27,592
It's All mine!

1196
01:39:28,000 --> 01:39:29,149
Let go!

1197
01:39:30,360 --> 01:39:32,237
-Let her go! -I dare you to drive guns.

1198
01:39:33,720 --> 01:39:37,110
You're not even a dog!

1199
01:39:38,120 --> 01:39:39,348
Open Guns!

1200
01:39:49,080 --> 01:39:50,832
Why Duchu?

1201
01:39:53,040 --> 01:39:54,792
It's his own bad luck.

1202
01:40:02,600 --> 01:40:06,149
To appear when it shouldn't.

1203
01:40:07,120 --> 01:40:09,588
For that reason?

1204
01:40:31,880 --> 01:40:33,074
Macro！

1205
01:40:55,120 --> 01:40:56,838
Hold on

1206
01:40:58,440 --> 01:41:00,237
The end of the old movie

1207
01:41:02,080 --> 01:41:03,991
It's all like that.

1208
01:41:06,280 --> 01:41:07,759
Isn't it?

1209
01:41:21,520 --> 01:41:22,589
Duchu

1210
01:41:22,680 --> 01:41:23,795
I knew it.

1211
01:41:23,800 --> 01:41:26,792
Your presence will one day be a threat.

1212
01:41:27,040 --> 01:41:29,235
I regret not getting rid of you in the morning.

1213
01:41:30,000 --> 01:41:31,353
Put it down

1214
01:41:37,200 --> 01:41:38,872
I'm going to my son's.

1215
01:41:43,760 --> 01:41:46,354
The medicine could have been ...

1216
01:41:48,320 --> 01:41:50,197
Make people stronger.

1217
01:41:50,200 --> 01:41:52,111
I didn't regret it.

1218
01:41:58,000 --> 01:41:59,399
Stop it!

1219
01:42:23,440 --> 01:42:24,793
The length of the tie!

1220
01:42:27,000 --> 01:42:28,069
Are you all right?

1221
01:42:29,200 --> 01:42:30,758
Can't you see?

1222
01:42:32,120 --> 01:42:33,189
What do you think?

1223
01:42:33,760 --> 01:42:35,034
Can you get up?

1224
01:42:35,760 --> 01:42:37,239
From the Ivy class.

1225
01:42:42,040 --> 01:42:43,075
Are you all right?

1226
01:42:44,000 --> 01:42:45,274
His injury is very serious!

1227
01:42:48,040 --> 01:42:49,917
I'm not that easy to die.

1228
01:42:55,800 --> 01:42:57,233
Future

1229
01:42:57,880 --> 01:42:59,677
I'm busy.

1230
01:43:03,880 --> 01:43:04,995
Is

1231
01:43:09,920 --> 01:43:11,797
Lying in the hospital for so long

1232
01:43:11,800 --> 01:43:13,995
Forgot how blue it is out there.

1233
01:43:14,880 --> 01:43:17,030
Everyone can have a blue sky

1234
01:43:17,520 --> 01:43:19,272
The world is fair.

1235
01:43:19,840 --> 01:43:21,432
I can't believe they're getting so close.

1236
01:43:21,440 --> 01:43:24,159
A couple of months ago, they were running after one.

1237
01:43:25,360 --> 01:43:26,713
Man

1238
01:43:27,000 --> 01:43:29,116
It's a simple creature.

1239
01:43:30,240 --> 01:43:31,070
That's right!

1240
01:43:31,680 --> 01:43:33,989
Can the two of them understand what they say?

1241
01:43:37,320 --> 01:43:38,719
After this

1242
01:43:38,720 --> 01:43:40,278
At least let me know

1243
01:43:40,600 --> 01:43:43,956
You're a man of integrity.

1244
01:43:45,680 --> 01:43:46,954
Going to leave

1245
01:43:47,200 --> 01:43:48,872
Just feel it.

1246
01:43:48,880 --> 01:43:50,108
is so precious

1247
01:43:54,320 --> 01:43:56,197
It's almost time.

1248
01:43:58,120 --> 01:43:59,758
Tomorrow will be better.

1249
01:44:02,240 --> 01:44:03,719
Anyway,

1250
01:44:04,760 --> 01:44:06,637
We haven't officially introduced ourselves.

1251
01:44:08,760 --> 01:44:10,239
Shi Cun Cong

1252
01:44:11,240 --> 01:44:12,832
Please advise

1253
01:44:14,360 --> 01:44:15,588
My name Duchu.

1254
01:44:15,840 --> 01:44:17,193
Please advise

1255
01:44:23,240 --> 01:44:24,559
Strange

1256
01:44:24,560 --> 01:44:28,951
What do you think is missing from this hand?

1257
01:44:31,400 --> 01:44:32,753
Time to get in the car.

1258
01:44:53,880 --> 01:44:55,233
-The length of the line?

1259
01:44:55,440 --> 01:44:56,793
Do you know now popular

1260
01:44:56,800 --> 01:44:58,597
Are you having a wedding on an old-fashioned train?

1261
01:44:58,600 --> 01:44:59,589
Well

1262
01:44:59,800 --> 01:45:01,279
Don't you think it's romantic?

1263
01:45:01,280 --> 01:45:02,508
Don't think