- Dad. Faster.
- I'm pushing eighty, son.
If we get caught,
it's all your fault.
- Was not.
- Was so.
You just had to screw around with
that stupid cat. I'm glad it broke.
- You want me to punch you in the mouth?
- Boys, knock it off.
Do something constructive. Why don't
you practice your football plays?
Ouch! He hit me.
- Breeze.
- Yes, sir.
Here's a good one -
red dog, Omaha, 22.
I know that one.
It's the hook-and-ladder play.
We flank each other...
Watch out!
- You boys OK? You all right?
- Yes, sir.
We are high centered up.
I got to get you inside.
Come on, boys. Come on.
Let's go.
Hello. Hello.
Come on.
I'm sure it's all right.
You boys stay in here.
I've gotta get that truck back
on the road. Y'all understand?
Let us help.
No, you're safer in here.
Breeze, you're in charge.
- Yes, sir.
- You got that, Willie?
- This is all your fault.
- He's... He's going to be OK.
- You know nothing can hurt dad.
- Still all your fault.
- What's happening? Breeze?
- I don't know.
Boys!
- Dad!
- Dad! Dad!
- Daddy.
- Daddy!
- Daddy! Help!
- Somebody, please help!
- Right there.
- We got confirmation, guys.
Looks like our projected course
for Tammy is on the money.
Upgrade it from a tropical storm to
a category-one hurricane.
Hurricane force winds, diameters,
up to 500 miles.
Looks like it is going
to hit Alabama and Florida.
- Get me the latest surface readings.
- They're warm. Way too warm.
The Gulf's at 91 degrees,
200 miles out.
The NHC has 98 on
the coastal buoys,
plus the Azores-Bermuda
high-pressure system
- is exceptionally weak.
- Impressive, Miss Schooler.
Ah, De Molinos, get me Will Rutledge,
and Miss Schooler,
I want you to run some numbers
on the spiral bands,
- and get back to me ASAP.
- I'll have it in five.
Yeah, I need Will Rutledge.
Yes, it's important.
- Is this Dr Rutledge?
- You got him.
Director Frobisher would
like to speak with you.
Sure enough, put him on.
- I got Will.
- Alright. Hey, Will.
Hey, buddy.
Now my central pressure is dropping
like a stone. What you got?
Satellite has got it at
999 millibars now.
So far, your Dominator's
in sync.
- So, I need those drones airborne quick.
- I'm on it.
Trust me, I'm doing it.
I don't want to stay out here
any longer than I have to.
25 years ago, Hurricane Andrew
laid waste to this town.
And now Tammy's here
to do it all over again.
But this time,
no-one's going to die.
- Yes sir!
- That's why I called the mandatory evac.
We got this, Chief.
OK, now once every last car
makes it out of town,
the assigned officers to make sure
their roadblocks are set up.
I don't want any looters heading
back into town. Not on my watch.
- Yes, sir.
- OK, now head out.
Excuse me there, Sheriff Dixon,
this here storm don't look like
it's going to amount to much.
We got to evacuate?
Now, Clayton, best
to evacuate first,
and then double-guess yourself later.
Now, be a good citizen
and get a move on.
- Come on.
- Yes, sir.
'Braveness is the resistance
to concern, mastery of panic,
'not absence of anxiety.'
Mark Twain.
Spare me your poetry today, Connor.
I can't help it,
it's in my Irish soul.
Your Irish soul left Ireland
two generations ago.
No, my parents brought me
over here when I was five.
I didn't know that.
There's a lot of things that you
don't know about me.
Still got two passports.
Gonna retire back there
when all this is over.
And here I've been stuck on
milk runs with you for a year,
and I thought I knew all there
was to know.
What is the hurry?
We do have to bank this load before the
storm hits. So, there's that.
- Move over.
- What?
This is Corbin, buckle up.
You know those bumps in the road
you hear about, here they come.
You know, I think you're
a little psychotic.
I think you are a little bit right.
You're going to ruin
somebody's tobacco crop.
Well, little less
cancer in the world.
Whoa!
- Ask your brother if he's reading it.
- You reading this, Clem?
Hold on, bro, it's checking.
Keep trying, man.
All right, hold on.
All right, that should do it, bro.
Yeah, up link full strength.
Good job, close her up.
Money is honey.
They're underestimating you.
- Morning, ma'am, sir.
- Morning.
- Where are the two other trucks?
- They couldn't keep up.
- I've got a feeling not many can.
- Clear.
Welcome back, you two.
Open it up.
Niles, you still there? I've got
them launched. You get the readings?
Yeah, they're in sync.
Stick around, it's only
going to be a cat two.
Get some new measurements.
You're sitting in a tank, for Christ sakes.
No thanks.
You're underestimating
her, I can smell it.
Yeah, while you're smelling it,
we are reading it
from carefully calibrated
scientific instruments.
Jim was just spiraling inward at
a crazy rate. Millibars 985.
You ever seen
a millibar dive that quick?
- Not consistent with our projections.
- Damn your projections.
I'm telling you, this one's going
to be off the scale. Trust me.
Dinner at the crab shack,
if it gets higher than a two.
Now stop thinking
about your stomach,
and your government expense
account's gonna pay for it.
You should get the National Guard
down here, before it's too late.
I respect you Will, you're a
first-rate meteorologist.
But I can't just traipse into
the President's office,
- and offer up your gut now, can I?
- Well, you'll wish you had.
I've never met anyone so afraid of
the very thing they were fascinated by.
Yeah, I've got a few
contradictions, but so do you.
Like eating candy bars
on a strict diet.
Yeah, now you mention it.
- Wrap it up, and come home, Will.
- Yeah, I am home, buddy.
I am home.
Even after 11 years of this,
I never get used to that sight.
I hate old money. It's greasy,
it smells,
it's been up 1,000 noses,
and buried in too many G-strings.
You say that like
it's a bad thing.
The best part of this lame-ass job
is watching it turn into confetti.
- Sergeant Deary.
- Yes, ma'am.
What's with the backup?
Why haven't these been shredded?
The shredder's been
down since you left.
- All right, let's get them in.
- Copy that.
All right.
It's working absolutely perfect one
second, the next second, stops.
I've got all my
guys looking at it,
and no-one around here
can figure out why.
So, you got here not a minute
too soon, Miss...
Bendietrich.
You can call me Sasha,
Agent Moreno,
because you're the one
paying the bills.
Sasha it is. So, how long's it going to
take to get this thing back online?
We'll run some diagnostics,
and get to the root of it.
We'll have you shredding
your heart out by lunch.
That would be great.
Hundreds of millions,
and a hurricane are not exactly
the best cocktail on the menu.
You know a thing or two
about cocktails, right, Randy.
Excuse me.
Enough of your jokes right now,
Corbin.
Maybe the less you say
to me the better.
All right, I'm in and out. Let's
just keep it professional, right.
- Thanks.
- Right this way.
Morris, Agent Corbin reporting in.
Good time, bad time?
Er, I've got a couple of
bits. Is everything OK?
- Yeah.
- Cargo offloaded?
Yeah. It's all here, with about 300
million of its cousins.
- The shredder's down, though.
- Yeah, I know. Addressed it.
Look, don't forget that 600 million
is your responsibility
- until it is destroyed, OK.
- You've got no problems with that.
Turns out I'm all right at
babysitting old money,
it's not the field, though.
Hey, I went to bat
for you after Utah.
If it wasn't for me, you
wouldn't even have a job right now.
And I appreciate that.
It's not really a job. I think
we both know what this is.
Look, I, I made a bad call.
But no-one can punish me like
I already punish myself.
Casey, don't do this.
Listen, if the money is my
responsibility,
I'd love to get a reset
on the vault code.
Hurricanes give people bad ideas.
OK. Consider it authorized.
- Thanks.
- And Casey...
take care of yourself, OK.
Yeah, this is Breeze,
from Rutledge Tow and Repair.
Leave a message and I probably
won't get back to you.
Hey, Breeze, it's Will.
Look, I'm in town.
Listen, you got to get...
Dammit.
Dialing. This CBC stuff
is so corrupted.
Yeah, that's what made
shutting it down so easy.
Why do they always hire hacks
with so little talent,
when they could have us?
Not enough money in it.
Yes.
Yeah, make yourself at home.
- Better check your backup power.
- Yeah, don't tell me what to do.
Not saying, I'm just saying.
- Oh, boy. It's failed.
- Not good.
I know. The job's outsourced to some local,
Breeze Rutledge, it's 555...
Phone's dead.
Shit, my cell doesn't
have any bars.
Me neither.
Right, where is he?
His shop is off of Baum and Garden.
It's called Rutledge Repairs.
Breeze.
All right Mr, rise and shine.
Come on, Breeze, on your
feet. Get dressed buddy.
Oh, I was dreaming, Will.
Remember Miss Bishop?
10th grade biology teacher.
Never did learn much,
but boy, I was never late.
As I remember it, you had a
keen interest in her biology.
What you doing here, Willie?
There is a hurricane coming,
and it's going to be a mother.
Some breakfast?
Yeah, and I'm a...
What was her name?
- Jaguar.
Well, we are what we are, Willie.
Can't change people.
You sure as shit
can't change hurricanes.
Well, this hurricane can change people
from life to death, so we got to go.
Yeah, I've seen them before,
brother.
Not like this. I'm telling you,
this is worse than...
The one that killed dad?
Yeah.
Red dog, Omaha, 22.
They're good hands.
You always had good hands.
We got to go.
You wasted a trip, baby bro.
I ain't gonna leave.
Look around, man,
because this...
it's my entire life around here.
But you got the cash, and the
airplane tickets I sent, right?
Yeah, I got it all right here.
Take your pity somewhere else,
please.
You need a fresh start, bro.
I make a fresh start
every day, Will.
It's just not so fresh by dark.
And all I got to do is freshen
it right back up again.
Breeze, if this storm
is what I think it is,
they ain't ever seen
anything like it.
OK, I'll buy.
But you're going to help me board up
the windows first, ain't you?
You... You got a hammer?
Heard you got phone trouble?
Got a call from a guy named Moreno.
There is no clearance
for you here, sir.
Corporal, we placed a T20 for
a transponder tower six,
got a lane open, have to shift it
over from the source, which is here.
Sir, we are on lock down,
due to the storm.
You need special clearance,
which you do not have.
Come on, man, we're just doing
our job here. Let us in.
Sir, this is a federal facility,
I need you to turn
this vehicle around,
and I need you to turn around now.
- Are we in any danger?
- There's been a breach.
You are safe in here,
all this glass is bullet-proof.
So I need you to
stay calm, and stay put.
- What's going on?
- We're under attack.
- What should we do, Connor?
- Take a nap.
Come on!
- We got a situation?
- What's going on, Mr Perkins?
What are you doing?
And you said we couldn't do
this with zero casualties?
You may not want to face it now, Connor.
But eventually we may have to kill
some people to get what we want.
- Let's get these guys locked up.
- Yeah, let's break out the P90s.
- Let's get the money.
- Amen.
It's bullet-proof, man,
you're wasting your time.
What if I say...
open sesame?
I have a thing about open sesame,
ever since I read Ali Baba as a kid.
Drop the gun, Moreno.
I should have known there was
something hinky about you two freaks.
We two freaks
hacked your shredder weeks ago,
so that the money would pile up.
Of course, we had
to gamble on the storm,
but all of life has its little risks.
Now, we managed to take this place
without spilling a drop of blood.
I want to keep it that way,
so I need your help.
Now, should you choose
not to help us,
the no blood rule will be revoked.
This is not your money.
The government's not going
to give it to your widow, Brenda,
if you fall on your sword
here now, are they?
This is a federal facility, man.
You know what you're facing
when they catch you.
Oh, I'd rather be facing
that, than us.
The vault, how long?
We have to substitute an I/O device
by loading a hunger striker routine
- into one of the monitor's wormholes.
- English. 30 minutes.
Open sesame in 30.
One of you Breeze Rutledge?
- Yeah. Who's asking?
- Casey Corbin, Treasury.
Our generator's down, I understand
you're responsible for repairs.
- Yeah, I'll go and get my tools.
- Breeze, what about the boards?
My government needs me, Will.
You done this before.
You got swindled into a
bunch of free labor huh?
- Apparently so.
- Yeah, I know that game.
This yours?
You one of those hurricane chasers?
No, I'm one of those meteorologists.
Anybody who chases hurricanes
got a death wish.
OK, let's go and save the world.
Will, buddy,
you going to be here
when I get back?
- No.
- OK.
See you in another five years.
Did real good, kid.
Really proud of you.
Done very well.
But tonight, we're going to
be the richest punk
- to ever come out of Phyllis Point.
- Nice.
So you're a hometown boy?
Uh-huh.
But I took the small detour
to Afghanistan and back,
but that was just to
break up the monotony.
It'll do that.
Now, you see that?
That right there was my
last official glory zone.
Yeah. You're looking at the starting
quarterback in the Gulf port Gators.
'99 to 2001.
All winning seasons, mind you.
I had six brothers, they ate,
slept and drank football.
- Six brothers?
- Yeah.
Shit, lady, I got just one,
and it's a damn minefield.
Open it.
It's all yours.
- What the f...
- Maybe we ran into her bots. Try it again.
- Tell me what is going on.
- The code, it's not working.
- You told us you hacked it solid.
- We did. We ran it this morning.
Then why can't you open it?
This was your only job.
Somebody changed the code.
It wasn't me.
That can only come
from Washington.
Or the Washington liaison.
Casey Corbin.
We can work through our dedicated
cell, do the hack all over.
Let's work on two fronts, Connor.
Frears and I will do the
hack all over again,
while you find Miss Corbin.
- Time frame?
- Three hours, minimum.
- You can do it in two.
- Yes, my love. Two will be fine.
All right. Get to it.
Where is she?
If you tell me anything other
than the truth, so help me,
your brains are going
to spill all over this stainless.
Where is she?
The gen...
The backup generator failed.
She went to get the repair guy,
she should have been back by now.
This is not good.
Listen, if you want help,
just say the word.
Keep low, and keep it running.
This is how it's done.
Agent Corbin, we got you scoped.
Drop the gun, give yourself up.
We don't want to hurt you,
we just want to talk.
Give yourself up.
Don't be stupid.
Let's go.
Not so fast, Corbin.
Go, go, go. Get her.
Don't you move.
Easy. I'm just a repair man,
doing a house job.
Go get the girl.
You got a tail!
Easy. Hell of a day, ain't it?
Hell of a day!
Got her pinned.
War monument.
Get in.
Thank you.
What the hell was that about?
- The Treasury's being robbed.
- You left with my brother,
- I didn't see him. Where is he?
- I think they have him.
- Think who has him?
- The crew that somehow managed
to knock over a
maximum security facility.
We got to go back.
Wait. These guys must be pretty
heavy hitters to pull this off.
They're not just going to hand him
over because we ask. They need him.
Need him for what?
The backup generator's down,
he's the only one that can fix it.
They're going to need
power to get in the vault.
So once he's through that,
they're through with him.
- I've got to call DC.
- You have sat?
- Damn, he's shot my satellite link.
- Shit! Shit!
Hey, hey, hey, we got to stay
focused, OK?
We are going to get help.
Just... Let's stay calm.
Listen, lady, we are
about to be crushed
by the biggest storm
of the century.
I don't think you know
what that means.
It means no-one is going to come here
and volunteer to help until it's over,
and at that point it's going
to be too late for my brother.
Look, I'm with you.
You know any local cops?
Yeah, I guess. It's not like
anything changes round here.
OK!
Best play we got.
He's the generator guy.
Yeah, Breeze Rutledge, that's him.
How's it going, Randy?
Well, you know where it
is, get to it.
- Try a zigamorph.
- I already called the dummy procedure,
there to force a flash of the
optimizers as registered coloring,
that's getting us somewhere.
Eyes front. Eyes front!
Hello.
What are you people doing here?
The town's under
mandatory evacuation.
I'm sure glad you don't listen to
your own orders. Jimmy, it's me.
Willie? Willie Rutledge, is that you?
Jimmy, listen, they got my brother
tied up in the Treasury.
- Who's got him?
- The Treasury's being robbed.
Casey Corbin, ATF.
How many men can you roundup?
I knew today was going
to be a shit-show.
Come on into my office,
tell me all about it.
How many of them are there?
I only had eyes on two,
but they took out 14
guards, high-tech security,
there's bound to be more.
So they're highly organized.
I can't confirm casualties,
but there was no blood, so hoping
there's more than one hostage.
We're going to
have to do something about that.
You, Missy, throw down
your weapon, now.
- Oh, no, Jimmy, you ain't in on it?
- Well, I'm afraid so, Willie.
You watch those semis rolling through
this shithole day after day,
filled with money.
You know it's just going
to the shredder.
Kind of gets you thinking, Willie.
You know?
Gives a man ideas.
Gun down, now.
Very good. I like a gal
who follows orders.
- Dixon here, you read me?
- You got her?
Yeah, pretty little thing,
all wrapped up in a red ribbon.
We need her alive.
Do what you want with
the good Samaritan.
Zander is on his way.
Yeah, well, you tell him not
to dawdle, you hear? Over.
Connor Perkins is the inside man.
Not bad, huh? For two old guys they
were going to put out to pasture.
600 million sure puts
a whole different complexion
on retirement, I'd say.
Go, go, go, go!
Red ribbon, my ass!
Shut up and drive.
They are on our tail.
Come on, can't you go any faster?
I've got my foot to the floor, man.
She's going as fast as she can.
Give me your gun.
That thing's built like a tank.
Oh, shit!
I'm tapped. What?
I'm out of bullets.
How did that happen?
I shot them all.
How far back are they?
100 yards, and closing.
Help me with my harness.
OK, now you.
Do you trust me?
I need you to trust me.
- What? Do you trust me?
- Yeah, what the hell, Will?
Because this is going to be harsh.
Here comes the harsh part.
You OK?
Never do that to me again.
I had to do something.
I guess it worked.
Wait, wait, wait.
Aren't you out of bullets?
They don't know that.
Jackpot.
Uh... Drink?
I'm not naturally a violent man, but
if this thing is not working soon,
I'm going to show you
another side of me.
Well, I'm not naturally
a worried man,
but how do I know when I do, fix
this thing, you won't just kill me?
You don't!
But I would not make me think
about ultimatums, just fix it.
Just do it. I am sick of
waiting for people.
Well, we can't keep running like
this, which 11's going to kill us.
Well, we can't leave,
and we can't call for help,
lines are down,
cell phones are dead.
When I left, all the
cell phones were down,
but those hackers
were still working.
How's that?
Maybe they got a dedicated line,
one with a satellite up link,
like I used to have.
If they were smart, they'd have
installed it ahead of time.
The only way they can
get the new code
is to hack back into
the DC mainframe.
If they had a dedicated
line, we could find it,
we could cut it, hole up,
and wait for help.
Anything on here that
could pick that up?
You know what, this one, this
reads non-ion identity,
which is basically radio.
Really? Great.
So we just search Gulf port.
This town just woke up
from the 1940s,
there can't be but three cell phone
towers in this whole place.
This one will tell us which
one of those is active.
Mr Rutledge, you are my...
Dr Rutledge.
I have a PhD in
synoptic meteorology.
- Dr Rutledge, you are my kind of expert.
- Why thank you.
Zander, come in. Do you copy?
Zander, pick up the walkie.
Where are you?
There was an accident,
our car is totaled.
Are you all right?
Oh, boy.
My arm's busted.
We're pretty shook up, man,
but I'm fine.
The sheriff has broken his
arm, it looks pretty bad.
Cut the shit. Where's the girl?
Have you got the girl?
She got away, Connor.
You screwed up the
easiest chance we had.
We're outside the
Atlantic Hotel.
It's getting savage out here.
You've got to come get us.
Hey, Zander, they're
coming to get you.
I don't understand, if you've always
been afraid of these storms,
how the hell you ended
up with this job?
You could always be in some
nice, dry TV studio.
Up next, we have Weatherman Willie,
bringing you news of a big
storm across the Gulf.
Right, thank you, Casey.
Yeah, that's right,
we've got 500 miles of Armageddon
on its way to crush your house
and destroy your life.
All joking aside,
that is case number one
for a man-made climate change.
The ocean's warming,
it just gives
more and more
energy to these hurricanes.
Right now, the limit's cat five,
pretty soon it's going
to be cat six,
and seven, and so on, and so forth.
By that time you're killing
hundreds and thousands of people.
If we could just figure out
their secrets, you know,
me and my colleagues,
people like us,
we could mitigate
how these storms occur.
Maybe even stop them altogether.
Seems...
seems real personal for you.
I just hope you never have
to watch someone you love
die right in front of your eyes.
I have.
Back in Utah...
I made a bad decision,
got someone killed.
I'm sorry to hear that, Casey.
It's like a weight you never
really put down, do you?
No, you do not.
Come on.
Oh, God.
Come on. Come on.
That tower's definitely active.
Has to be them.
Probably, but we got winds 143,
that's a cat four.
No way we could work
on it up there.
What if we bring it down to us?
There's a pretty serious
winch on this thing.
- You think you could do the job?
- That's one idea.
OK. Hey, where you going?
I can handle a cable,
but I can't handle
that peashooter,
in case we get company.
I need you to stay here
and watch my back for me.
All right.
- This is the winch. Out. In.
- Copy.
- Be careful.
- You, too.
Jesus!
Will!
Casey, tow the line!
- What?
- Tow the line!
Oh, no! Tow the line!
Wait, go back.
Somebody is up there.
Shit!
Jackie, stay back.
- Numbers are coming in.
- How many numbers to the code?
33. Here they come. Six.
OK, this will take a little
bit of time, just be patient.
I can be patient for 600 million.
Jackie. Connor, wait.
She's gone, man. She's gone!
We got to move. Now!
Go get that woman.
I'll cover you.
- Can't you make it go any faster?
- It's a computer...
it's working at
the speed of light, thank you, Rice.
The spikes!
- What?
- Shoot the spikes.
- 36, 16!
- 4 more. OK, we've got 3 more to go.
We've got 1 more. What?
Yes, yes! Hell yeah!
I'm out of ammo, we've got to go.
We are still tethered to the tower.
- We are sitting ducks.
- Watch out!
You work here, get us unhooked.
I'll hold them off.
With what?
- It froze.
- I can see that, shithead.
The line's been cut.
- Way to go, Casey.
- What did you say?
I said, 'Way to go, Casey.'
Let him go! Stop it!
All right, stop!
Oh, geez!
Got it!
Perkins, let's get out of
here, or we are all going to die!
We are unhooked.
God damn that hick.
Lucky timing, I guess.
It's here in my notes,
The volterpolic AJAX.
One wrong entry, and
it shuts down for 48 hours.
Yep, that's what I thought
now rock this...
it's a two integer number.
So after the initialization,
I analyzed the previous numbers,
it's a Marshall-Fibonacci
sequence, see.
Apply it forward, and it will narrow
the probability of the 33rd number.
All right, we got two civilians,
possibly armed.
We got at least three hostiles,
all with P90s,
and they got Moreno.
- Get us out of here, we'll take them.
- Yes, sir.
Holy shit, he's trying to
free the soldiers.
Had to go for two hours.
- All this water.
- Good idea.
Let me get this straight,
you're the only one with the code,
and that's why they need you?
Right.
Why don't you do it?
Why don't I do what?
Open the safe.
It's not your money.
I can't.
Can't is not an answer. I just can't.
That's the job right now,
as shitty as it is.
You don't understand. You can't just
walk into a hostage negotiation...
You want to beat them at their
own game, they need you alive,
so it's a safe game for you.
I can't say the same
for me and Breeze.
He could lose his life because
you want your old job back.
No.
- I'd say that's right on the money.
- Will, listen,
as long as I have the code,
they don't have the money.
As long as they don't have
the money, the hostages live.
If they get it,
they kill all the witnesses.
Follow me.
- What?
- Come on.
- I'm following a damned weatherman.
- You'll learn to love it.
- You OK, boss?
- No, I'm not OK.
- My arm's busted.
- Get me some Vicodin.
Get him in. Get him in.
You all right?
What happened?
Where's the Fed?
We couldn't bring her in. The
storm's the other side of hell.
Where's Zander?
Where's my brother?
He didn't make it.
- What do you mean?
- He's dead.
Jackie, too. Both of them.
Who did it?
The Fed? That bitch.
No, no, don't, listen,
listen to me, Rice...
We don't get the money,
they both died for nothing,
and we are left with nothing.
That's all we got left, me
and you. The money, OK.
You know, there is
a strange irony in all this.
It was us who planned to
use the hurricane,
and by some crazy twist of fate,
we collide with somebody who
knows it better than us.
Boys. What the hell?
Simple, the sheriff had a
plan within a plan all along.
It's like I said,
fate works in crazy ways.
Like when I was sitting in a bar,
on my own,
bitching about my lot in life,
and right next to me was
another man doing the same thing.
What are you telling me this for?
- I was there, you idiot.
- Well, not such an idiot.
Obviously.
Everything was planned perfectly.
All we needed was
one little hurricane,
but you screwed it up,
because you didn't have the balls
to pull this off in the right way.
So everything went sideways.
Well, I'm taking over now.
Boys, we are going
to get that gal,
and cattle prod her privates,
until she gives us the code.
And after that...
the money's all mine.
You hear? You hear me loud
and clear, boy?
No, hold your fire.
Well, that was loud,
and very clear.
- I have a proposal.
- Speak your piece.
Stick with me, and I promise you
all 20 million apiece.
I don't mind partners,
but I do hate witnesses.
What's it going to be?
Well, I think
we can work with that.
But there will be
no money to split,
unless we can get that woman
in here to open the vault.
It sounds insane. You really think
this could work? This...
- Pressure inversion.
- Right.
It's risky, but it's the
best chance we've got.
Those are some slim odds.
Make the call.
Come in. This is Agent Corbin.
Do you read me? Over.
Casey.
Nice of you to check in.
I didn't peg you for
a traitor, Connor.
Guess you can forget about that
retirement in Ireland,
just a nice Super-max for you.
I doubt that's why you called.
I'm tired of running, I'm ready
to make a deal, a trade.
What kind of trade?
You release all the hostages, and
I will come in and open the vault.
You can have it all.
That sounds too good to be true,
coming from an
ambitious girl like you.
I don't want anyone else to die.
Money or garbage, it's not mine.
I will give you one hostage,
one for one.
- No deal.
- Then people start to die.
- Starting with your friend Moreno here.
- Two hostages.
Release Moreno and the repair guy,
and I will come in. After you get the
money, release all of the army guys.
- Do we have a deal?
- Deal. Where are you?
Get proof of life?
Casey, where are you?
Not so fast. First you have
to prove they're still alive.
Gonna need to talk
to Breeze Rutledge.
Get the repair guy out.
And put Agent Moreno on.
Let me talk to him.
It's me, Casey.
Thank you.
No need to thank me, Randy,
we are on the same team.
Will. Here.
Someone wants to talk to you.
Breeze, red dog, Omaha, 22.
- Hey, kid.
- Breeze, you in one piece?
I'm still breathing.
I thought you left.
Nah, I got to missing you too much.
Good old Willie.
Listen, brother,
save yourself, man.
They're gonna kill me anyway.
Just be cool.
All right?
Everything is going
to be OK. You'll see.
I love you.
I love you, too. In fact, everybody
loves everybody around here.
Now, where are you?
- We are at the mall.
- Which mall?
There is only one mall in Gulf port.
Figure it out.
Course there is.
Put this on.
It's a safety harness.
I tried everything, there's no word.
He's just gone.
You got to hand it to him,
he was right.
Tammy is going off the chart.
I used to shop here with my daddy.
We had a small Catalina,
16-and-a-half footer,
used to take it out on the Gulf
in the summertime. It was fun.
Now you're armed.
Come on!
Get in there.
Show yourselves.
We got the place surrounded.
Come on out.
Come out, wherever you are.
Move. OK, hold it.
Show yourselves.
That's far enough.
We don't want no trouble, man.
We're in for the
Treasury woman, right.
This is the deal.
Now, where is she?
She right here somewhere,
she just loves shopping.
Next joke will cost you, asshole.
The girl, or he dies.
How you doing down there, Breeze?
Well, I'm just waiting for my
quarterback to call the play.
This play just a little flea flicker,
I might signal go long.
Shut your yap up,
and send her out now.
OK, OK. Casey.
Where's Moreno?
Oh, he's safe and sound.
You can trust us,
we're the police.
Now.
Look out.
Breeze. Breeze, come out,
it's me and Casey.
Guess he figured this would be
the first place they'd look.
Got you a gift.
It was my daddy's.
Beauty. Browning.
Well, eight rounds
is better than nothing.
Thank you.
How long do you think
we have before it passes?
I mean, it's moving real quick.
I think the eye of the storm is
going to be over us real soon.
It's confusing how in songs,
they always say
into the eye of the storm,
and that's the calm part.
Yeah, it can be the
most beautiful place,
20-40 miles wide, like a
warm summer's day,
but the eye wall, that's a different
story. That's the real killer.
You know, it's the layer
around the ring,
that's fueled by thunderstorms
on an atomic bomb level.
I mean, you get trapped in that,
sure enough, it's death.
Great.
Ain't nothing in there but poison.
I got what you want. What you want is
peanut butter and jelly sandwiches.
Yes, really.
Cool.
Yes. Fricking love Monday,
you weirdo.
Is this Jif?
No, I'm a Skippy guy, so Skip.
Really. It's Smucker's strawberry
though.
Correctamundo.
They're going to use the eye
to escape, aren't they?
It's what I'd do.
Roll-out in the middle,
let it dissipate,
which it's going to do
when it gets inland.
We should take the fight to them.
- How do you mean?
- Car bomb.
We detonate it at a safe
distance, but car bomb.
We just need ammonia,
fertilizer, diesel,
things we can get at a
garden supply store.
How the hell do you know that?
When you are a Fed they
teach you this shit.
Timothy McVeigh took
out the Federal Building with that.
You just load up a car,
plant it at the gate, when
they convoy out, blow it.
OK, so we are going to need a car.
One that's not on its roof.
Would need to be watertight,
have a decent electrical system.
Yeah, where we going to find
a car like that?
The Dominator?
No. No. Are you kidding?
This is a federal vehicle.
Federal property?
So is the $600 million,
they would buy you a fleet
of these things for that, Will.
No.
I need your help.
Found it.
She's got enough gas to get
more bang for your buck.
They must have seen The Dominator.
I'll look for a way out the back.
No shit today, Casey.
I know you're in here.
There's four of us,
all with automatics,
against whatever you got.
You need me, I'm the only
one with the code.
The protection is only for you.
It doesn't apply to your boyfriend.
I'll tell you what.
You let him drive away unharmed,
and I will come in and open
the safe. No, no, no.
Call him out.
Call him out!
Go!
Somebody here. Help!
Will.
Willie. Will.
Hey, Will.
Here. Come here, buddy.
Get on. Come on.
- I got you. I got you.
- I lost Casey.
- I saw her, they got her.
- First things first, buddy.
First things first.
Moreno. You're alive.
No, no, no, no, the money.
We had a deal. You let
him go, and I'll open it.
You are in a piss poor position
to negotiate, lady.
No.
Frears, turn the shredder on.
What? Are you going to shred me?
Oh, not you. Him.
No, no. Hey!
- Wait, you win.
- Stop.
You win.
It was here all the time.
Boy, come to papa.
A priest once said to me, 'Money
won't get you to heaven, Connor.'
Clearly he never saw this.
Randy.
That is what you get for
causing us so much trouble.
That is for Zander,
that is for Jackie.
I will kill you for this.
Everybody else has tried.
Why not you?
Let's load up. Bring her.
I'm not done with her just yet.
Put that around you, Willie.
All right, let's suit up, man.
This your vitamins.
Something warm.
- Definitely need some of this.
- What in the hell?
Well, I am a citizen of Alabama.
Here, man.
Come on, Willie, take your pick.
No, I'd only wind up
shooting you or me.
That's the eye of the storm.
About 40 miles wide,
it could be like a bright,
sunny day in the middle of hell.
Well, dude, it's time for the
Rutledge boys to go to work.
They sure as shit got the money.
And they sure as shit got her, too.
Let me ask you a question, Willie,
we could just let the whole pack
of them go, money and all.
What do they teach you in the army?
Leave no man behind.
- Did you forget that?
- I was just testing.
Nice to see you grow a
pair since this morning.
Let's take the shortcut.
Pick them up at
Shelley's farm, right?
I need to tell you something.
No, you don't.
Everything's fine.
Just leave it.
No, I want to apologise for
some of the things I said.
Well, we all say
things we don't mean.
Forget it.
I can't.
Look, I know you know
I was just a little kid,
but I said some stuff,
to try and hurt you.
I get it. I get it.
And I'm well and truly sorry.
Well, shit, I'm sorry, too.
I haven't been the best older
brother I could have been either.
Lord knows I've tried, man.
Just not hard enough.
All right, now that we've
put all that shit out there,
- you've got to promise me something.
- Name it.
I gave you this once, once, Willie,
but you've got to promise me
this is the last time
we ever share our deep,
personal feelings again.
Hell, yes, sir, you've
got yourself a deal.
Jesus, Perkins, speed up. That thing
wants to swallow us whole.
Now you know why I put you last.
Dick.
You can't drive this thing for shit.
You want to try?
It ain't easy. My brother-in-law
drove one long haul,
and he was an angry son of a gun.
Now I know why.
Just keep it on the road.
And you, nobody asked
to hear from you.
Keep it zipped, hear me?
You are so... So,
- All right. You ready?
- No.
Get your ass out of here.
Send it, Willie.
Whoa, come on, come on.
Jump. It's too far.
Come on, jump.
Grab my leg.
Grab my hand.
That wasn't too far.
We did it.
We're on the top of a truck,
we haven't done shit.
Hey, one thing I learned
in the war, man,
you got to take your victories
where you find them.
Let's do this.
Oh, my God!
Hey!
Oh, my God, you shot him!
Shut up! Get in the back,
before you get one in the head.
I'm going to kill you.
Don't even think about it,
sweet cheeks.
Ready? Oh, yeah.
Here goes nothing.
Well, you'd better hope not.
It's OK.
Yeah.
It's OK, baby.
You killed my brother.
I'm going to kill you,
no matter what Perkins says.
And I'm gonna make it hurt.
I know I'm not the first one
to tell you this, Rice...
you got anger issues with women.
See what I mean.
Get her off of me!
I can't keep it straight.
Get off of me.
You got to get off.
I can't have it straight.
My God.
God dammit, lady, don't make me.
I'm in, Casey.
Oh, shit.
Get ready, Casey.
Take a look outside, tell me
how far back the eye wall is.
Half a mile, at most.
Damn you to hell.
OK, get down low, lovers.
It's gonna get hot.
- Breeze is in trouble.
- Let's go give him some help.
Son of a...
- You see what's behind us?
- Yeah, it's nothing good.
Red dog, Omaha, 22.
- What?
- Red dog, Omaha, 22, hut-hut.
You got it.
Get ready.
Ah, you...
Red dog, Omaha, 22, hut-hut.
One more.
That's the Alabama Slam, baby.
Oh, no.
No, no.
You're blocking the runner,
but forcing him backwards
at the eye wall?
He must have figured it out by now,
but I sure wish
I could have seen
his face when he did.
What? No, no, no, no!
No!
My money! Damn you!
Damn you!
We are not going to make it.
We're not gonna make it.
I'm gonna drop back.
Give me your hand.
All right, we're going
to transfer over.
Come here. I want
you to take the wheel.
Now put your foot on the gas,
right there. Can we get closer?
You're going to come
over next, OK.
Come on, Breeze.
Get me closer.
Let's go.
- Stay!
- Come on.
Now.
- Now punch it, Willie.
- I'm going.
Well, Breeze, you were right.
Come again.
Take your victories where you
can get them. That was a mouthful.
Yes, sir.
We earned 200 million,
that's some kind of victory.
And our lives.
That's some kind of victory.
Yeah. Yeah.
Listen, I've got you two partners,
200 million in cash,
no-one knows shit.
What do you say we turn this
truck around, head to Mexico?
Mexico.
Hell, I like the sound of that.
Yeah, we could get into
a shit load of...
Dangerous.
But, you know...
I was messing with you,
you degenerates.
Oh, mercy.
Red sky at night.
They teach you that in PhD school?
Yes, ma'am.
Subtitles by Deluxe
E-mail sky. subtitles@sky. uk