- Extracted from retail.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
(ENGINE ZOOMS PAST)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(PARKING BRAKE SETS)
(CLICKS)
(ELECTRIC GUITAR CHORD PLAYS)
(LOWER GUITAR CHORD PLAYS
OVER RISING STRINGS)
(BELLBOTTOMS BY
THE JON SPENCER BLUES EXPLOSION PLAYS)
♪ ♪
(SILENCE)
(SONG KICKS BACK IN)
♪ Yeah, ah
♪ Go, go, go, go
♪ Yeah!
♪ Go, go, go
♪ Yeah
♪ Yeah!
To catch the whole
♪ Go, go, go, go
♪ New York City, hey
(MUSICAL INSTRUMENTS PAUSE)
♪ Blues Explosion
(INSTRUMENTS RESUME PLAYING)
(WIPERS SQUEAK IN RHYTHM)
♪ ♪
(SIREN APPROACHING)
(MUSIC PAUSES)
(SIREN FADING)
WOMAN 1: (MUFFLED)
Put your hands in the air!
MAN: Get on the ground now!
I need you on the ground!
Stay there!
(WOMAN 2 SHRIEKING)
Don't you move!
WOMAN 1: Get down!
Don't fucking move!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTS)
(RIFLE BLASTING)
MAN: Let's go!
(WOMAN 3 SCREAMS)
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
MAN: Nobody move!
WOMAN 1: Nobody move!
MAN: Everybody, stay down!
(MOUTHING)
JON SPENCER: Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
Right now, I got to tell you about...
(ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYING)
...the fabulous,
most groovy...
Bellbottoms!
(ALARM WAILING)
♪ Uh! Bellbottoms! Uh! Yeah!
♪ Uh!
(DRUM BEATING)
(ENGINE REVVING RHYTHMICALLY)
♪ Bellbottoms
♪ Bellbottoms, bellbottoms
truly make me wanna dance
♪ ♪
♪ I wanna dance
(SIREN WAILING)
♪ Tell 'em! ♪
(HORN HONKS)
♪ Sit back
♪ Just watch 'em
She gotta have bell
♪ Bellbottoms
♪ She's gotta gun
Way on the list
♪ Oh!
♪ Down on her hips, oh
♪ She's gotta
♪ She's gotta, she's gotta
Blues Explosion
Oh!
♪ She's got 'em
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Whoa!
(TRUCK BEEPING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
♪ I wanna dance
(SIREN CONTINUES WAILING)
♪ ♪
♪ Bellbottoms
♪ Bellbottoms, bellbottoms
♪ I'm gonna break
(HORN BLARES)
♪ I'm gonna break, come on!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
♪ ♪
(HORNS HONKING)
♪ I wanna dance
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(HORNS HONKING)
♪ ♪
♪ I remember
(HORN HONKING)
(WOMAN WHOOPING)
♪ ♪
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
Driving a red Subaru WRX.
♪ Bellbottoms
♪ Yeah!
♪ Bellbottoms, bellbottoms
♪ Bellbottoms
♪ Bellbottoms ♪
(TIRES SCREECH
IN THE DISTANCE)
(INTRO TO HARLEM SHUFFLE
PLAYING)
MAN: (IN DISTANCE) No, no, no.
♪ You move it to the left
♪ Yeah
♪ And you go for yourself...
MAN: I'm here. You're late.
I'm waiting on you again.
♪ To the right
MAN: Hurry up.
♪ If it takes all night
(HORN HONKS)
MAN 2: Asshole!
Hey! Taxi!
♪ Now, take it kinda slow
Yeah.
You go, girl.
♪ With a whole lot of soul
GIRL: You know it, honey.
♪ Don't move too fast
♪ Just make it last
WOMAN: Hey! Jerk.
♪ You know, you scratch
♪ Just like a monkey
♪ Yeah, you do
♪ You're real
♪ Yeah
♪ You slide it
♪ To the limbo
(MAN LAUGHING)
♪ Yeah
♪ How low can you go?
(HORNS PLAYING)
♪ Oh, come on, baby
♪ I don't want you
to scuffle now
♪ You just groove it
♪ Right here
♪ To the Harlem Shuffle
(BELL JINGLES)
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Next customer.
Oh, uh...
Can I take your order?
Uh...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll have, uh,
four black coffees, medium.
Name?
Baby.
"Baby"?
B-A-B-Y, Baby.
(SCOFFS)
WOMAN: Could you pass that?
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
♪ Oh, oh...
BARISTA: Baby.
♪ ♪
DISPATCHER: Subaru WRX believed
to be connected
to the robbery...
♪ Hitchhike, baby
♪ Across the floor
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa
♪ I can't stand it no more
(OVER MEGAPHONE) The river of sin.
Sin is your enemy.
Sin can be washed away
if you just find God.
Don't walk away
from your sin.
♪ Now, get into your slide
(BICYCLE BELL RINGING)
(SIREN CHIRPING)
♪ We're gonna ride, ride, ride
(HORN HONKS)
♪ Little pony, ride...
WOMAN: Is she in there?
MAN: I told you, no.
WOMAN: I can't deal
with you right now.
♪ Shake, shake, shake
♪ Shake a tail feather, baby
MAN 2: Be on time.
♪ Whoo!
♪ Shake, shake, shake
a tail feather, baby... ♪
NEWSCASTER: It is believed
that the robbers
have escaped with
upwards of $200,000.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
♪ ♪
(CHAIR CREAKS)
What's his deal?
Baby?
Full cut, same as everyone.
No, Doc,
I mean is he, uh, retarded?
"Retarded" means slow.
Was he slow?
No.
Then he don't sound
that retarded to me.
He's a good kid and
a devil behind the wheel.
What the hell else more
do you need to know?
So you don't think that there's
something wrong with him
just not saying anything?
There's nothing wrong
with a little quiet.
BUDDY: You know why
they call him Baby, right?
Still waiting on
his first words.
(MUSIC PLAYING INDISTINCTLY
OVER EARBUDS)
(IMITATES ROARING ENGINE)
(IMITATES TIRES SCREECHING,
GRUNTS)
So, you're a mute, Baby?
Is that what it is?
DARLING: (GROANS) God.
Are you a mute?
No.
(BOTH LAUGH)
So, um,
what are you listening to?
Uh, music.
That's right.
You tell him, Baby.
(WHISPERS) Shh, shh, shh.
It's okay.
(IMITATES SOFT EXPLOSION)
For God's sakes, Griff,
leave the kid alone.
You can't just be
in crime, right?
Not without being
a little criminal.
I just want to find out what's
going on between those ears,
aside, of course, from, uh...
Egyptian Reggae.
What's it matter to you?
Just think that he thinks
he's better than us.
He wants to sit there
in his car
and keep his white shirt
clean while the rest of us,
we roll in the dirt.
One of these days, Baby,
you're gonna get
blood on your hands,
and you're gonna
find out that that shit
don't wash off
in the fucking sink.
Relax. The kid did
his job, all right?
I ever say that the kid
wasn't great at his job? No.
I think he's a star.
Would I vouch for him
if he wasn't?
(SHOE SQUEAKS)
(PATS)
Got to hand it to you,
totem pole,
you're either hard as
nails or scared as shit.
(SHOUTS) Which one is it?
♪ ♪
(ENNIO MORRICONE'S SECONDO
INTERMEZZINO POP PLAYING)
(DARLING AND BUDDY CHUCKLE)
What do you think
about that, Baby?
Mommy and Daddy
are getting it on.
Enough.
Yeah, where do you get off?
Right...
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Here.
Okay, folks,
if you don't see me again,
it's 'cause I'm dead.
DARLING: Tell me about tonight, Buddy.
Tonight, Darling, we will have
post-heist revelry at Bacchanalia.
DARLING: Why, that is
the finest winin' and dinin'
of all the wines
and dines in town.
(BELL DINGS)
Ah, that's us.
Bye.
Well, sir,
expect the lady and myself
to darken your door
once the nose bag is empty.
And, Baby, you did good, kid.
Do me a favor.
Next time Doc calls,
don't pick up.
(DARLING GIGGLES)
Don't listen to him.
Now, I get absolutely no pleasure
in taking candy from Baby,
but we're fast approaching
the day when you...
Will be all paid up.
One more job and I'm done?
One more job and
we're straight.
Sound good?
(PATS BABY'S ARM)
Oh...
I was gonna wait until we were
square, but what the hell.
These are for you.
Now give me your burner.
I'm gonna need you behind
the wheel again real soon.
You call, I'm there.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
(GOOGIE RENE COMBO'S
SMOKEY JOE'S LA LA PLAYING)
NEWSCASTER: Here's what we know.
Two men and a woman
came into the bank branch
clad in black
business clothing,
trench coats,
bandanas and sunglasses.
They pulled guns and ordered
everybody to the floor,
and then cleaned out
the registers.
And hear this, they even swiped
jewelry from some of the customers.
You awake?
They ran out of the bank
to a waiting getaway car.
A driver was there to take them away.
It was a red...
You hungry?
Always.
You got it.
♪ ♪
Spread to the edges!
NEWSCASTER: ...is a young Caucasian male.
His identity
remains as yet unknown,
and police are
appealing to anyone
who might recognize him
to come forward.
The search for
the suspect is ongoing.
Police pursued
the getaway vehicle
across downtown Atlanta
and I-85 by helicopter.
♪ ♪
Where is that cash from?
Work.
One more job.
Then I'm done.
(JOE GRUNTS SOFTLY)
You don't
belong
in that world.
Sorry, couldn't hear you.
I have a banana in my ear.
You heard me.
(GENTLE POP INTRO PLAYS)
♪ You are so beautiful... ♪
They grow up so freaking
fast, don't they?
You and I are a team.
Nothing is more important
than our friendship.
How's that
working out for you?
NARRATOR: And still the bull stands,
bloodied but unrelenting.
Gaston is
running out of time.
He's had his tries
from horseback.
Now he must try to
end this on foot.
DOC: (OVER RECORDER) "Retarded" means slow.
Was he slow?
GRIFF: No.
(REWINDS)
DOC: Was he slow?
GRIFF: No.
(REWINDS)
DOC: Was he slow?
GRIFF: No.
(CLICKS)
DOC: "Retarded" means slow.
Was he slow?
GRIFF: No.
DOC: "Retarded" means slow.
Was he slow?
GRIFF: No.
(RHYTHMIC RECORD SCRATCHING)
...slow? ...slow? ...slow?
♪ ♪
(PERCUSSION ACCOMPANYING
DESCENDING MELODY)
DOC: ♪ Was... Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Was he slow?
♪ De...
Devil behind the wheel
(REWINDS)
♪ Was he slow?
♪ No... N-N-No
♪ Good... Good kid and a
devil-devil-devil behind the wheel
♪ Was he slow? ♪
(TAPE RECORDER REWINDS,
CLICKS)
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
(LOW, DISTORTED ARGUING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
♪ ♪
WOMAN: ♪ Temperature goes sky-high
♪ You know I really
don't want to help it
♪ B-A-B-Y, baby
♪ Whenever
the sun don't shine ♪
(TAPE REWINDING)
(OVER RECORDER)
♪ B-A-B-Y, baby ♪
So, what can I get
you this fine morning?
(TURNS OFF RECORDER)
Uh...
Oh, don't worry
if you need a second.
I have all
the time in the world.
Whoa, are you recording this?
Oh, uh...
Am I being monitored
for quality assurance?
No. I... I...
No.
Um, hello? Hello, testing.
What can I get you
this fine morning, sir?
(TURNS OFF RECORDER)
Um...
Oh, um, you know
that's a kid's menu, right?
Yeah, oh.
I get it. It's early.
So you just starting your day
or did you just get off?
Oh, I don't know if I ever get off.
They call, I go, you know?
(PHONE VIBRATES LOUDLY)
So, what is it you do?
I'm a driver.
Oh, like a...
Like a chauffeur.
You drive around
important people?
I guess I do.
Anyone I'd know?
I hope not.
Well, aren't you mysterious.
Maybe.
(LAUGHS) Maybe?
So, when was the last time
you hit the road just for fun?
Yesterday.
Oh, then I'm jealous.
Sometimes all I want to do
is head west on 20
in a car I can't afford
with a plan I don't have.
Just me,
my music and the road.
I'd like that, too.
(COOK CLEARS THROAT LOUDLY)
(CLEARS THROAT) Oh.
Uh, so,
you decide on anything yet?
You are so beautiful.
(LAUGHS)
You just decided that.
Oh, well, thank you.
I'm sure you don't mean it.
I do mean it.
Jonathan?
Oh, sorry.
You know,
this isn't my badge.
I've only just
started here, so...
As a Jonathan?
Yeah. (LAUGHS) As a Jonathan.
Well, um, if you have any
more questions, just holler.
♪ B-A-B-Y, baby ♪
I have a question.
What's that song
you're singing?
(B-A-B-Y BY
CARLA THOMAS PLAYING)
(MOUTHING TO RECORD)
WOMAN: ♪ Baby, oh, baby
♪ I love to call you baby
♪ Baby, oh, baby
♪ I love for
you to call me baby
♪ When you squeeze me
real tight...
I approve.
Of the song?
Of the girl.
♪ And I can't stop loving you
♪ And I won't
stop calling you
(BUZZING)
♪ Baby, oh, baby
♪ You look so
good to me, baby ♪
DOC: Oh, there you are.
I've been calling, Baby.
You have?
I have.
My chicken just
laid a very big egg.
You in?
Am I in?
It was
a rhetorical question, Baby.
You're in.
I'll be there.
(KASHMERE BY
THE KASHMERE STAGE BAND PLAYS)
Meet your new crew.
Over here is Eddie No Nose,
formerly Eddie The Nose.
Why, what happened?
Don't ask me that.
That's a No Nose no-no,
page one.
And right here is JD.
He put the "Asian"
in home invasion.
And over there is
the one and the only Bats.
No need for intros, Doc.
Everybody from the jungle
to the trap know Bats.
This your boy, right?
This the one you say listens
to the music all the time?
The driver's supposed
to be the eyes and the ears,
not just the eyes.
Why does he listen to music
all the time, Doc?
He's got mental problems?
BATS: No, no, no, no.
I'm the one got the mental
problems in the crew.
Position taken.
DOC: He's got tinnitus.
Tinna-what?
He had an accident
when he was a kid.
He's still got a hum in the drum.
Plays music to drown it out.
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING IN EARS)
Yeah, but you feel me.
BABY: Hat?
Huh?
Your tattoo says, "Hat."
Yeah. It used to say "Hate."
But to increase my chances of
employment, I got the "E" removed.
How's that
working out for you?
Who doesn't like hats?
BATS: So, Doc,
how many jobs
you done with the kid?
If you can't take
my word for him,
then get back in
that fucking elevator.
You never heard of
the Spirit of 85?
The joyrider?
Yeah.
The ghost that baited
cops doing 130 on 85.
Headlights off,
brake lights disconnected.
He drove 'em around in circles
on Spaghetti Junction.
Left 'em in the dust every time.
That was our boy there.
Wasn't that, like, 10 years ago?
Yeah.
Well, like I said,
that was our boy.
He's been boosting cars
since he was old enough
to see over the dash.
He stole my Mercedes.
Had a lot of merch in it.
I watched him do it, too.
I didn't stop him, though,
'cause I was just blinded
by the balls on that kid.
'Course he didn't know
who I was,
or the worth of the junk in
the trunk once he dumped it,
but once I tracked him down,
I made sure to tell him who I was,
what I was capable of,
and how much he owed me.
And since he's
been paying me back,
he's also shown me
what he's capable of.
Wow.
I just drew a whole
goddamn map in chalk
while we've been
standing here squawking.
That's pretty
fucking impressive, right?
Shop, let's talk it.
Baby, you with us?
(UNSQUARE DANCE BY THE DAVE
BRUBECK QUARTET PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(JAZZ PIANO PLAYING,
RHYTHMIC CLAPPING)
♪ ♪
(FAINT, DISTORTED SPEECH)
Bank robbers. Whatever.
It's got to be ready for
an 8:30 start in the a.m.
(CLEARLY) Questions?
I got a question, Doc.
Why would I believe Phones over
here heard a goddamn word you said?
You laid down your whole play.
He ain't even listening.
Baby?
The target is an armored truck
at Perimeter Trust in Dunwoody,
10:00 a.m. sharp.
We have
the details of the route
because someone at the depot
has a nasal problem.
The bank itself is right
near the Buford Highway,
so we should be able
to hit the ramp
within 60 seconds
of getting out.
We also have a diversion crew.
They're gonna blow up
a bread truck a ways away,
keep the fuzz busy.
The dress code is the Michael
Myers Halloween mask,
but don't all buy your masks at the
same time. It looks suspicious.
The switch car is ready,
but you want me to hit the
long-stay parking structure
at Hartsfield-Jackson
to get a heist vehicle
that stays colder longer.
Boost a commuter car,
a family car,
something that blends in well
with morning traffic.
Something on the heavy side in case
we need to ram the cops off the road.
A Escalade, Yukon,
Avalanche, whatever.
It needs to be ready
for an 8:30 start in the a.m.
Questions?
Well, ain't y'all cute.
That's my Baby.
Fuck your Baby.
BATS: What's in there
is ours.
It belongs to us.
They took our money,
our hard-earned paper.
They snuck in when we
were asleep last night
and took the pants off the
chair and emptied our wallets.
They got what's
rightfully ours.
Let's go get it back,
what's rightfully ours.
(NEAT NEAT NEAT BY
THE DAMNED PLAYS)
What the fuck is this mask?
Austin Powers.
Doc said Michael Myers!
This is Mike Myers!
It should be
the Halloween mask.
This is a Halloween mask!
No, the killer dude
from Halloween.
Oh, you mean Jason.
No!
EDDIE: No! God! Fuck!
BATS: Let's go.
Wait, wait.
I got to start the song over.
(NEAT NEAT NEAT BEGINS AGAIN)
BATS: The fuck?
EDDIE: What?
Okay, go.
(NEAT NEAT NEAT
INSTRUMENTAL INTRO PLAYS)
BATS: Move!
Go!
(SINGING ALONG)
MAN: ♪ I be a doll, be a baby doll
♪ It can't be fun, not anyway
♪ It can't be found
No way at all
♪ A distant man
can't sympathize
♪ He can't
uphold his distant laws
♪ Due to form
on that today... ♪
(ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL)
EDDIE: Go!
Yeah, we out! Let's go!
BATS: Let's move!
JD: I got this.
EDDIE: Come on! Let's go!
BATS: Man up!
It's a tough business.
EDDIE: Go! Hit it!
Yeah, Baby!
(ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL)
BATS: Look out! Fuck!
What the fuck?
We got a hero!
EDDIE: Go!
♪ No more sight to
bring you down... ♪
(JD SCREAMS)
(ENGINES REVVING)
EDDIE: God damn!
Fuck! Get him!
BATS: Do your job, Baby.
Let's go!
Shit!
Watch out,
watch out, watch out!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(ALL YELLING AND GROANING)
(JD WHOOPING)
JD: Yeah!
(JD LAUGHING)
BATS: That's how you do it, Baby!
(ENGINE REVVING)
EDDIE: Come on!
Yes!
(JD WHOOPING)
Ha!
BATS: What the fuck?
Soldier Boy.
He ain't giving up, huh?
♪ I be a man,
kinda mystery man... ♪
Come on, Soldier Boy.
(YELLING)
Shit!
Ah! No, no, no, no! No!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
No!
(BATS YELLING)
(TRUCK HORN BLARES)
Got your ass now.
(YELLS)
(WHOOPING)
(HORN BLARES)
♪ She can't afford
no gun at all...
Damn it! I had that G.I. Joe
motherfucker dead to rights!
God damn!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
BATS: New ride. Let's go.
(HORNS HONKING)
BATS: Come on, boys, let's rock!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Huh? Sweetheart.
Oh, my love.
(BABY COOS QUIETLY)
BATS: Get out the car!
I have a child!
I got one, too.
Get the fuck out!
(SCREAMS)
(CRYING) No!
Come on!
Get in! Let's move.
(BABY CRYING)
BABY: Here, it's okay.
BATS: Bring your sorry ass over!
JD: God damn it! Shit!
BATS: Baby, what are you doing?
BABY: Here, take him.
Leave the baby in the car.
Leave the baby in the car!
Get your damn weird ass
over here now!
(STATIC)
(NEAT NEAT NEAT PLAYS)
BATS: Come on! Let's go!
JD: I'm coming!
♪ Be a doll,
be a baby doll... ♪
BATS: Let's rock!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(BABY CRYING)
Let's go!
Oh, shit! No! Fuck!
I left my shotgun behind.
What?
Not groovy, JD.
Not groovy at all.
EDDIE: Cops! Cops! Cops!
(SIREN WAILING)
Shit. Get down.
EDDIE: Stay down. Stay down.
♪ Neat neat neat
♪ She ain't got no name
to call Neat neat neat
♪ She can't afford no cannon
(TIRES SQUEAL)
♪ Neat neat neat ♪
(CAR DOOR BELL DINGING)
(DISTANT SIRENS WAILING)
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
All units be on the lookout
for a red Saturn Aura,
license plate...
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
You see JD over there?
Now, JD's a idiot.
But you a bright boy, though.
So I got a question for you.
You make me miss that shot?
Come on, now.
You can tell me.
No.
You're a good driver.
You're a bad liar, though.
In this business, the moment
you catch feelings...
Is the moment
you catch a bullet.
Now, pick up your purse
and go get the coffee.
(THE HARLEM SHUFFLE
BY THE FOUNDATIONS PLAYS)
MAN: ♪ Come on, everybody
♪ Hey!
♪ Ugh, all right, hit it
♪ You move to the left
♪ Then you go for yourself
(QUIET CHATTER)
♪ You move to the right...
EDDIE: About goddamn time.
♪ If it takes all night
♪ Oh, come on, baby... ♪
BATS: Oh, you looking for JD?
International Man of Mystery?
(LAUGHTER)
(IMITATING AUSTIN POWERS)
'Cause he's long gone, Baby.
(LAUGHTER)
EDDIE: You got that right.
Just put it down.
We'll drink it.
(SETS CUP DOWN)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
So, this is it.
I'm a man of my word.
(DOC SIGHS)
And you're all straight,
Baby.
That's it?
Sure is.
You're all paid up. Cause for celebration.
(TRUNK CLOSES)
Yeah, sure is.
DOC: Oh.
Yeah, well, before you
go completely crazy...
You need to
sunset that ride.
Drive safe, Baby.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
(DISTORTED, ECHOING,
INDISTINCT SINGING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(DISTORTED SINGING CONTINUES)
(EARS RINGING)
(RHYTHMIC BEEPING)
(EASY BY
THE COMMODORES PLAYING)
(RHYTHMIC BEEPING CONTINUES)
MAN: ♪ Know it sounds funny,
but I just can't stand the pain
♪ Girl,
I'm leaving you tomorrow
♪ Seems to me, girl,
you know I've done all I can
♪ You see I begged,
stole and I borrowed
♪ Yeah
♪ Ooh, that's why I'm easy
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ I'm easy like Sunday morning
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
(BABY, I'M YOURS
BY BARBARA LEWIS PLAYING)
You're back.
(BABY SIGHS)
I sure am.
Well, then, you, sir,
are gonna be
my very last customer,
because I am walking out that
door in precisely 30 seconds.
You're leaving?
Yes, sir.
Can I come with you?
(CHUCKLES) You don't
have work or nothing?
Uh, I don't.
I am done with work.
Wow. You seem real
happy about that.
Yeah, I sure am.
(POTS CLATTERING)
COOK: God damn it!
I don't blame you. Well,
you're welcome to come with,
but I don't know how exciting
you're gonna find the laundromat.
Huh?
I got to run some errands.
Oh.
But think about what you want,
and I will stick around just for you.
Coffee?
Please. Uh, cream and sugar.
So, how you
two getting along?
Oh, good.
He's sweet, isn't he?
That kid? He's been coming
here since before me.
Think maybe his mom
used to work here.
Huh.
Know what you want?
(MUFFLED MUSIC
PLAYING OVER EARBUDS)
Your name?
Well,
you can get that for free.
(RECORDER CLICKS ON)
It's Debbie. Debora.
(RECORDER CLICKS OFF)
Oh, like the song.
The Beck one? Yeah.
Well, except I'm D-E-B-O-R-A,
and I think that's just D-E-B-R-A.
I don't know that one.
Oh, it goes, um...
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SINGING SOFTLY)
♪ I met you at JCPenney
(CLEARS THROAT)
♪ I think your
nametag said Jenny ♪
Jenny?
The song's about him wanting
to get with Jenny
and her sister, too,
whose name is Debra.
So it's not even really about me.
It's about the sister.
My sister's name is Mary.
She has got all the songs.
"Mary, Mary,
where you goin' to?"
"Proud Mary keep on burnin'."
"The Wind Cries Mary."
She's got me beat. Again.
She's got endless songs.
I got one.
No, you got two.
What's the other one?
Debora,
the song I'm talking about.
(LAUGHS) Who by?
Trex.
T.Rex?
Uh, yeah.
(CHUCKLES) I've heard of them,
but don't know that one.
How's it go?
(RECORDER CLICKS ON)
Oh. (LAUGHS)
♪ Oh, oh, Debora
♪ Always look like a zeb-ora ♪
"A zeb-ora"?
Like a zebra, I guess.
(LAUGHS)
Yeah. Well, I'm wearing
black and white,
so you can call me Deebra.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Actually, I actually
got Debora on here.
Okay, what? How many
of those do you have?
Oh, I got different iPods
for different days and moods.
Oh. And you're in
a pink and glittery mood.
I am now.
(DEBORA GIGGLES)
What is your name?
Baby.
Wait, what?
Your name's Baby?
B-A-B-Y, Baby?
Yeah.
Well, then,
you have us all beat.
(CHUCKLES)
Every damn song is about you.
We could drive back and forth
across the States forever
and never run out
of "Baby" songs.
We might run out
of gas, though.
(DEBORA LAUGHS)
Did your mom call
you "Baby" as a kid?
Sometimes.
She used to work here?
Sometimes, but,
uh, she was a singer, too.
What does she do now?
Nothing.
Uh, I could find
Debora if you want.
COOK: Debbie!
(SIGHS) For crying out loud.
Well, uh, play it
for me sometime
I don't have to
get out of here.
Deal?
Yeah, deal.
Now,
you know what you want yet?
To get out of here.
(DEBORA BY T.REX PLAYS)
(DOOR BELL CHIMES)
MAN: ♪ Dug-a-re-dug,
dug-a-re-dug-a-da
♪ Dug-a-re-dug,
♪ Dug-a-re-dug, dug-a-re-dug
♪ Oh, Debora,
always look like a zeb-ora
(LAUGHS)
♪ Your sunken face... ♪
You're right. I do like it.
Good.
So, what's your story, Baby?
You from here?
I am.
Keep going. Keep going.
You're from here.
Uh-huh.
You're a driver. You like music.
You don't talk much.
No.
I've, uh, spoken more
to you today
than I have to
anyone all year.
Whoa.
Okay.
Not a motor-mouth. Noted.
Yeah, yeah. I have...
I have this,
uh, hearing thing.
I was in an accident
when I was little.
Is that what
happened to your mom?
Yeah. Yeah, and my dad.
I miss her.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
I live with my foster dad,
but now he's getting old,
so it's more like
I'm looking after him.
Yeah. I know how that feels.
I had to look after my mom
when she got sick.
It might seem tough now,
but once they're gone,
you'll miss having
someone to care for.
I don't have much to
keep me here anymore.
You don't?
(DOOR BELL CHIMES)
You know,
mmm, we could get together some
other time, some other place?
Oh, you mean, uh, somewhere that's
not a diner or a laundromat?
(GIGGLES) Yeah, well, it's not
that this isn't nice but...
Oh, well,
we could go to, uh... Um...
Oh, Bacchanalia.
I've never been.
I... I hear it's nice.
Oh, it's... It's the
finest winin' and dinin'
of all the wines
and dines in town.
(CHUCKLES) That is nice.
Um, but they got me pulling
doubles this week, though.
What about next week?
What's your schedule like?
I don't know.
Oh, I forgot.
They call, you go.
No, I mean, I'm...
I'm not working.
You're not driving anymore?
No.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
It's my choice.
Well,
aren't you the lucky one.
MAN: ♪ I want to get with you
♪ Only you, girl
♪ And your sister
(MOUTHING)
♪ I think her name's Debra
♪ Oh, oh... ♪
So who's Debora?
The girl.
(SIGHS)
NEWSCASTER: (ON TV) His name,
Malik Kelly, a local veteran.
You saw what these folks were doing.
You took action. Why?
I'm done.
MALIK: I saw these guys go marching
in the bank with Halloween masks,
weapons drawn.
They were attacking...
Is this the place?
♪ ♪
Here.
Pizza?
Are we celebrating?
Celebrating you getting
a real job.
What kind of job?
Wouldn't it be good
to bring joy to people
when you drive?
Pizza?
♪ ♪
(BELL CHIMES)
MAN: Order's up!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BUZZING)
Whoa.
That was fast.
I know.
FRAT BOY: Pizza!
(PEOPLE WHOOPING)
Look...
You only have to
wash your hands once
after counting that.
I know.
And not put
other lives
in danger.
I won't let anything bad
happen to you.
I'm not talking
about me.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(HORN HONKING)
(ENGINE IDLING)
♪ ♪
MAN: ♪ Baby, let me take you
♪ Let me take you in my arms
♪ Let me take you in
my arms and hold you
♪ Show you I love you
♪ Baby, I love you
♪ Baby, baby, I love you
♪ Don't love nobody else
♪ You got my love
just for yourself... ♪
You're all good. A gentleman
picked this up already.
A gentleman?
Who is that?
BABY: It's my old boss.
Uh...
Excuse me one second.
VALET: Here you are, madam.
WOMAN: Thank you very much.
VALET: Have a good night.
Good meal, Baby?
That foie gras terrine
is something, huh?
Yeah.
You don't look
happy to see me. Why?
I said we were straight,
but did you think we were done?
That that was it?
Uh, I guess I did.
Well, I could give you the
good news and the bad news,
except there is no bad news.
The good news is you're about
to make a lot of money.
And the good news is you're
about to make a lot of money.
I got... I got a job, Doc.
Yeah, but why slave away
delivering GoodFellas pizzas
just to afford
a night out here,
when you could make all that
dough with a great fella? Me.
And then take your gal here for fucking
dinner every night of the week?
You paid off your debt.
Now it's time to profit.
This is the fun bit, Baby.
By the time this job is over,
you'll be rolling in money,
buying Maseratis and feeding
your gal catfish dipped in gold.
So, what do you say?
You in?
Am I in?
No, don't answer my question
with another question.
You give me one of
two replies. Yes or no.
No, Doc.
You know I never do a job with the
exact same crew twice, right?
Yes.
And you also know
you've been my driver
for every job since we met.
Yes.
So, I'm of the thinking
that you are my lucky charm
and that I'm not doing
this job without you.
Now, I don't think I need
to give you the speech
about what happens
when you say no,
how I could break your legs
and kill everyone you love,
because you already
know that, don't you?
Yeah.
So, what's it gonna be,
behind the wheel
or in a wheelchair?
The first one.
I'll pick you up
in the morning.
Don't stay out
too late, now.
Oh.
And your, uh, waitress
girlfriend, she's cute.
Let's keep it that way.
VALET: Good night, sir.
DEBORA: Well, that was some
pretty fine winin' and dinin'.
Must have friends in high
places to get a table there.
BABY: Oh, I don't know
about that.
Is everything okay, Baby?
It will be.
You want to talk about it?
I make a mean cup of coffee.
I mean, I... I don't.
I make terrible coffee.
I want to, but I...
I can't right now.
You know, you...
You don't have
to worry about me.
You can tell me anything.
I'm not worried about you.
I mean, I...
You're the best thing that's
happened to me in a long time.
And I just worry that
I'm not good enough for you.
Oh, well, don't.
I can see you're kind
and you're different.
And I'm here for you
when you're ready.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Uh, you tell me.
(EARS RINGING)
(SIGHS)
♪ ♪
(HORN HONKS)
Good morning.
These places never
get rolled.
People don't realize that there's
gold in them there hills.
And those that do,
don't have the stones
to pull off a job so
public in the hub of it.
This place'll be ripe
around this time tomorrow,
but I need you to do
something for me today.
I can't be seen in there,
but you can.
So go inside.
Take note of the number
of cameras and positions,
the number of registers open,
the number of employees
and the number of customers.
Is there a guard?
Is he armed?
Do they have bandit glass?
And get in line,
buy some stamps.
Take your buds out,
pull your shades off.
Oh, and, uh, take the nephew.
Less suspicious.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CHIMES)
RECORDED VOICE: (OVER PA)
The United States Postal Service.
We're here, working for you,
seven days a week.
We do a lot more
than just stamps these days.
You'd be surprised at
what we have to offer.
MAN: (OVER RADIO) Yeah, Jack,
all looks fine back here. Over.
(EARS RINGING)
(BOY CLEARS THROAT)
(WHISPERS) No bandit glass,
one armed guard,
10 cameras,
eight registers, two open,
11 customers and
four employees.
Thank you.
(BELL CHIMES)
Uh...
Uh, stamps.
That your boy?
Sure.
Yeah, he sure is.
How old is he?
Four.
Eight.
They grow up so
freaking fast, don't they?
(LAUGHS)
Does he have a name?
You have a name, don't you?
Samm.
Well, Samm, I got a mint
with your name on it.
You have a mint
that says "Samm"?
Aw.
Sweet. (CHUCKLES)
Are you here tomorrow?
Sure am. Working 9:00
to 5:00, just like Dolly.
Oh, Dolly Parton. Yeah.
I like her.
Mmm, who doesn't?
"Everybody wants happiness,
nobody wants pain.
"But you can't have a rainbow
without a little rain."
(CLICKS TONGUE) Wise lady.
Yeah, she sure is.
Hmm.
(BELL CHIMES)
Bye.
♪ ♪
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hit me.
No bandit glass,
one armed guard,
10 cameras,
eight registers, three open.
And, uh, 11 customers.
(SAMM CLEARS THROAT)
And, uh, four employees.
Anything else?
The teller seemed nice.
She gave me a mint.
Did she?
Yeah.
You probably wouldn't even
need to use a gun with her.
Just say "boo," and she'll
give you the big bills first.
Chip's off the old block.
(ENGINE STARTING)
♪ ♪
What floor are you on?
Third.
DOC: Those stairs must be a
real bitch for Joe, huh?
It's my business
to know everything.
So, are they a bitch?
There's an elevator.
Ooh, fancy.
(ELEVATOR WHIRRING)
So, am I gonna
see you tonight?
Yes, you will.
You're not just saying what you
think I want to hear, right?
You consider me a friend,
don't you?
You and I are a team.
Nothing is more important
than our friendship.
Good to know.
You'll be out of
this shithole soon.
You're going up in the world!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS)
(PHONE RINGING)
Bo's Diner,
what'll you have?
BABY: Is Debora there?
Debbie, phone.
Keep it short.
Hello?
It's Baby.
Hey. To what do
I owe this honor?
I just wanted to
hear your voice.
Am I still seeing you later?
I have to drive again.
Oh, okay. Thought
y'all were done with that.
So did I.
It's not what I want.
And what do you want, Baby?
I want us to head west on 20,
in a car we can't afford,
with a plan we don't have.
Keep driving and never stop.
Are you serious?
I am, Debora.
You in?
I'm in, Baby.
See you soon.
(DIAL TONE DRONES)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
MAN: ♪ Holy calamity,
scream insanity
♪ All you ever gonna be's
another great fan of me
♪ Break
♪ Bear witness
♪ Bear witness, bear witness ♪
There he is.
Hey, Baby.
Hear-No-Evil's back, huh?
Have you seen this kid move?
Yeah, I've seen him.
Think Doc likes
having him around
because he can park in the
disabled spots by the bank.
Disabled spot?
BATS: Yeah.
He got some shit wrong with his ears.
Tinnitus or something.
Anyway, he gotta listen
to music 24 hours a day
to drown out
the whining in his ears.
DARLING: Oh, shit!
You know who else has
the exact same thing
and does that
exact same thing?
Barbra Streisand.
Darling, do I look like
I know a fucking thing
about Barbra
fucking Streisand?
Hey! Watch your mouth.
That's my lady you're talking to.
DARLING: Yeah.
Watch your mouth.
I'll watch what
I want to watch.
(BATS SIGHS)
BUDDY: Is that true?
Is that why you have music
in your head all the time?
Drown out the noise?
Yeah.
It keeps me moving.
It's an escape. I get it.
Hey, Buddy, you seen a violin?
I had a violin here.
Shut up.
I used to fool around with
cars when I was a kid.
Drive around all night like a speed
freak listening to the radio.
I used to have
my special tape
that had my killer
track on it. Get me flying.
You got one of those?
Sure.
Well, what is it?
Brighton Rock.
What?
Queen?
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
It's got that
crazy big guitar solo.
Yeah, I know that song.
My brother used to
play Sheer Heart Attack
right through the wall.
(SNIFFS)
You got it on here?
Uh, I got it on this one.
Play it.
Let's hear that killer track.
(BRIGHTON ROCK INTRO PLAYS)
Yeah.
(ROCK INTRO PLAYS)
BATS: What you ladies
listening to?
Queen.
Queen!
Queen? Streisand, now Queen.
What the fuck? What y'all gonna do?
Y'all gonna belt out show
tunes on the way to the job?
You don't need
a score for a score.
You just...
(IMITATES ENGINE REVVING)
Put your fucking foot on the
gas and drive the goddamn car.
That's all
the music you need, folks.
Come on, now.
You never been a wheelman?
You never had a lucky song?
Well, a cigarette song.
Apres-heist, glass of scotch.
Absolutely.
But not before a job.
I got enough demons right here
playing music all the time.
Yeah, well, that I believe.
Had a buddy once walk away from a job.
You know why?
Because something was playing
on the radio he didn't like.
We about to go in, he won't
get out the fucking car. Why?
'Cause Knock, Knock,
Knockin' on Heaven's Door
is playing on the FM.
He called it a hex song.
That, End of the Road
by Boyz II Men,
Hotel California
by the Eagles.
He called 'em all hex songs.
Then come talking about some crazy
shit like we all gonna die.
So what?
You bail on the job?
Fuck no,
I didn't bail on the job.
I went and got that money.
And we didn't die, either.
Now, he bought it
a little later,
but it had nothing
to do with the heist.
Do all your stories end up
with somebody dying?
(CHUCKLES)
I guess you just
got to find out, huh?
(BOX THUDS)
I need four pairs of eyes
and three sets of ears.
Gather round.
♪ ♪
(ENGINE REVS)
The postal service is dying.
People don't care
about their mail anymore.
Lucky for us,
their loss is our gain.
Money orders.
For I happen to know a guy
who has a machine
that can turn
blank ones into green.
Each box contains
250 slips per box,
each slip worth
up to a grand.
That's quarter
a mil per box.
Dot, dot, dot.
You do the math.
Darling goes in the front.
Buddy takes a five-alligator
count and follows her inside.
You put on these privacy glasses
to blind the CCTV camera.
Another five-alligator count.
Darling gets in line,
Buddy takes her hostage,
shotgun to her head.
That gets you guys
in the back office.
We role-play that a lot.
Uh-huh.
Baby drives Bats
around the loading dock.
Bats uses this security card supplied
by an insider with a nasal problem
to get in the staff entrance
and cover the rear.
You guys grab all the boxes
and then sneak out the back
to Baby and the waiting car.
Did you get all that, Baby?
Yeah.
Okay, one more thing.
We need some fresh hardware,
not traceable to us or any previous jobs.
Now, I've got some contacts who
can get us some clean firepower,
so the pickup is tonight.
But after the pickup,
you come straight back here.
You all have an early start in the morning,
and there's eyes everywhere.
So, you're staying
the night here.
Oh, we in bed together now.
(INTRO TO
NOWHERE TO RUN PLAYING)
WOMAN: ♪ Nowhere to run to, baby
(SINGING ALONG)
♪ Nowhere to hide
♪ Got nowhere to run to, baby
♪ It's not love
I'm a-running from... ♪
Pull over there.
I got to take a leak.
BATS: Want some gum?
Want some gum, Buddy?
BUDDY: Yeah, I'll take some gum.
(SONG CONTINUES FAINTLY)
DARLING: Tell me what we're
gonna do with all that money.
We're gonna go to Vegas.
We'll put it all on red.
We'll get married again.
It'll be real romantic.
Mmm.
You know what was real,
real romantic?
What was real,
When you stabbed that guy.
(CHUCKLES)
Which guy?
The guy that robbed you,
the guy that called you a whore,
or the guy that
looked at you funny?
(CHUCKLES) The last one.
Yeah. I do remember that.
Bats just looked at me funny.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
BUDDY: You want me to kill Bats?
Not before the job, silly.
Hmm?
You think we should talk
about this in front of Baby?
(DOOR OPENS, BELL CHIMES)
He won't say a thing.
Will you, Baby? Hmm?
Jesus Christ.
What,
did you steal all this?
You said
you wanted some gum.
Fuck I'm supposed to do, pay for it?
Let's go.
(REVVING ENGINE)
♪ I can't around it, no
♪ Nowhere to run
♪ Nowhere to hide
from you, baby... ♪
BATS: Looks like
the farmers' market is open.
DARLING: Farmers' market?
BUDDY: Yeah. Doc says
we got to go see The Butcher.
(WHISTLING A MELODY)
Come on,
you're going in with us.
We might not be
leaving in this.
And, uh, find
something funky on there.
Just in case we got
to rip this joint up.
Take this.
Act like you
know how to use it.
Why would he need it?
Got to swagger in
like you got one,
so we don't all look
like a bunch of pussies.
Darling excluded.
(PERCUSSIVE INTRO TO TEQUILA
BY THE BUTTON DOWN BRASS PLAYS)
What's with the earbuds?
Recording this or something?
It's just his music.
Yeah, he's loony.
He's just like his tunes.
What's he listening to?
BATS: How the fuck I know?
Let me check.
(TEQUILA PLAYING)
Tequila!
Which reminds me,
why'd the Mexican dude
throw his wife off the cliff?
Ah! Ruined it.
Didn't I ruin it?
We met before, right?
I don't know.
You still alive, right?
Uh-huh.
Then I guess
we ain't never met.
(OTHERS LAUGHING)
Shut the fuck up!
I've got it.
Voila!
Welcome to la charcuterie.
(DARLING WHISTLES)
Tonight, gentlemen, madame,
we have only
the finest cuts of pork,
direct from
the local smokehouse.
You're all experienced
butchers yourself.
I assume you are aware that
the humble pig can be cooked
from nose to tail,
everything but the squeal.
I can offer you nine cuts
at the best prices
in all of Christendom.
So let's dive in
head-first.
From the jowl comes the godsent
Roman bacon that is guanciale.
From the shoulder
of the hog comes
the Boston butt,
a tough but tasty cut.
The picnic shoulder
is a favorite
of those who enjoy
the smoking of pigs.
The center-cut loin,
the double-cut pork chops,
baby back ribs,
and the Serrano ham,
on the back leg, of course.
All delicious.
Delicious.
And, of course, we have a
fine selection of sausages.
BATS: Well, I'm hungry.
Fantastique.
And your choice is...
Well, I'm gonna go
with the picnic shoulder,
'cause, um, I just
love smoking pigs.
(GRUNTS)
(GUNS FIRING)
BATS: Done deal.
BUDDY: Dumb son of a bitch.
Whoa! Oh, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fuck, Bats!
You got my wife shot!
I don't like that!
Relax, Buddy.
You handled it!
DARLING: What the fuck, you piece of shit?
You shot the gunsmiths.
Weren't they
fucking Doc's contacts?
They were Doc's contacts!
Guess what, they was pigs.
Look at the box.
It says "APD."
I clocked that
tall strip of bacon
with that fake-ass Louis
Vuitton hat right off the bat.
He busted me in '98.
Now, I don't know about you
lovebirds fucking without a condom,
but when somebody getting
ready to barbecue me,
I go full-metal
batshit on...
DARLING: Shit!
BUDDY: Get him!
Baby, don't let him get away!
Get him! Get him!
Do something!
Get him!
BATS: Oh, shit!
(ENGINE STARTS)
MAN: ♪ Tequila... ♪
Get us out of here, Baby.
Let's move.
Come on, let's go. Move.
♪ ♪
(SCREECHING)
(EXPLOSION)
♪ Tequila ♪
(RADIO STATIC,
STATIONS CHANGING)
♪ Run, run, run...
BATS: ♪ Whoo! ♪
BUDDY: Bats,
you are fucking crazy.
BATS: When your folks name you Bats,
you gonna end up crazy.
I don't doubt you're crazy,
but your real name
is not Bats.
So says you.
You think my real
name's Darling?
Yeah, or Buddy?
No, they're nicknames.
Code names, monikers.
So, what's your
real name, Darling?
Monica.
Hey, I thought we weren't
allowed to discuss names.
We're not.
Baby, what's your real name?
Huh?
Hey, stop, stop,
stop up here.
Stop up here.
I said stop. I'm hungry.
No.
Stop the car!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
No?
You're telling me no?
I don't want to go in there.
"I don't want to
go in there."
Well, hello, Baby.
Bodies hit the floor back there,
you don't say shit.
Now all of a sudden,
you getting...
You getting riled up
about stopping at a diner?
I don't want to go in there.
It sucks.
Well, with that recommendation,
we gots to go in now.
(WHEN SOMETHING IS WRONG WITH
MY BABY BY SAM & DAVE PLAYING)
MAN: ♪ When something is wrong
♪ With my baby
♪ Something is
wrong with me... ♪
BATS: Now, why y'all so mad?
You should be thanking ol' Bats.
For being a walking
fucking death wish?
Well, I treat all of my
jobs like it's my last.
Yeah, but what you do within
this group affects all of us.
Fine, cowboy. You're gonna get
your money tomorrow. Plus, uh...
(SNIFFS)
I know you guys
got noses to feed.
What, yeah,
like you're Mr. Clean.
I'm Mr. Whatever
the Fuck I Wanna Be.
(DEBORA CLEARS THROAT)
Can I get you
anything to drink?
BATS: Uh, yeah, I think it'll be,
uh, Coke all around, right?
How... How you say it
in your language? Coca?
So let me get three
Cokes and one Coca.
Four Cokes?
Yeah.
Look, here's the deal.
You rob to
support a drug habit.
I do drugs to
support a robbery habit.
That's clever.
That's my job, see.
It's you two
who's on vacation.
So you doubt
our credentials?
Wall Street, right?
Doc tell you that?
Doc ain't tell me shit.
(SIGHS)
Just a educated guess
from an uneducated man.
Well, Bats, I would be fascinated to
hear your thoughts on the matter.
Tell me if I'm way off,
Buddy.
You were a stockbroker.
Maybe a different wife, maybe kids.
You stack your paper,
but you say shit like,
"Work hard, play harder," but
you play a little too hard.
You rack up debt, the type of debt
that'd make a white man blush.
Maybe you get into
a little trouble.
Maybe you get your hand caught
in the corporate cookie jar.
Maybe you leave and
run off to the desert.
Maybe with your
favorite lap dancer in tow.
Maybe you disappear into a world
consisting of three things,
money, sex, drugs and action.
Oh, shit, that's four.
Am I close?
This how I look at it.
You guys just think
this is a trip.
Either way,
if you are Wall Street,
you're a bigger fucking crook
than I could ever be.
I'm gonna go right ahead
and speak for the two of us.
You think you know us?
You don't.
Mmm.
DARLING: You think you're
the last word in crazy?
You're not.
And believe me
when I tell you,
you don't want to
see my Buddy mad.
You haven't seen
how relentless he is.
Because when he sees red,
(WHISPERS) you will
see nothing but black.
(CHUCKLES)
You hear that, Speedy?
That's some Oscar shit right there.
That was nice.
Did you rehearse that?
You see this shit, Baby?
See, now this is a prime example
of a man who loves a woman.
You guys are
perfect for each other.
I mean that.
(DEBORA CLEARS THROAT)
DEBORA: Well,
what can I get you to eat?
Get these cats
some Happy Meals,
and, uh, I'm gonna
take care of the bill,
uh, "Debora."
Yo, my friend here, he, uh...
He doesn't like this place,
but I think this place
kind of nice, you know?
So let me ask you something,
Debora.
(EVERY LITTLE BIT HURTS
BY BRENDA HOLLOWAY PLAYING)
WOMAN: ♪ Every little bit hurts... ♪
What's his problem?
Uh, maybe your friend would like
to fill out a suggestion slip.
Tell us how to
improve our service.
♪ Why you treat me cold
♪ Yet you won't let me go... ♪
Baby, you know that bitch?
No.
BATS: Okay.
Let's bounce.
I got this.
What the fuck
is your problem?
Hmm?
♪ My love is strong for you
♪ I'd do wrong for you...
Okay.
Well, make sure you
tip the nice lady.
♪ I can't go on
(SLAPS TABLE)
♪ Giving my life away
♪ Oh, come back to me
♪ Darling, you'll see
♪ I can give you
all the things
♪ That you wanted before
♪ If you will stay with me
♪ Yeah
(ENGINE REVS OUTSIDE)
♪ Every little bit hurts
♪ Every little bit hurts ♪
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS, ECHOES)
(CLICKS, ECHOES)
Bananas.
"Bananas" is a code word.
Whenever a deal is done
with one of my clients,
they call me on the phone and
they say the word "bananas,"
and then they hang up.
(BAGS THUD ON FLOOR)
I did not hear
the word "bananas" tonight.
So you tell me who died.
Well, your contacts
was cops, Doc.
I know. They were my cops.
Yeah, well,
they fired first.
And I'm not gonna
take a bullet for you
or nobody else
in this motherfucker.
Is that true?
They fired first?
Yeah.
Baby?
Ask somebody on
the planet Earth.
I will ask
whoever the fuck I want.
Go home, job's off.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
No. What the fuck?
We are 24 hours from being descended
upon by this entire city.
Those pigs are in hog heaven.
The only way they can ID us is
with a Ouija board or some shit.
Well, your name only takes
four letters to spell out.
Doc, Bats ain't
my real fucking name.
It's over, Leon.
Get out of town.
Wow.
Well, I ain't running, Doc.
I say we drive into the storm.
Ride the hurricane.
We could be on
a non-extradition beach,
drinking
non-extradition cocktails,
counting our non-extradition
cash in 23 hours.
DOC: And who do we get
to fence those money orders
since you shot the fence?
BATS: Buddy got a guy.
I mean, I'm just taking a wild
guess here, but Buddy got a guy.
Ain't that right,
Wall Street?
(BAGS THUD ON FLOOR)
Yeah, I got a guy.
So let's fucking do this.
I only hear three voices,
and the last time I checked,
there's four in a car.
Baby? Your call.
Time to make
a big-boy decision.
Do we do this thing or not?
He's outvoted.
We doing it.
Let him speak.
I say we all get some sleep.
Get ready for
this fucking thing.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(RECORDER REWINDING)
DOC: Baby? Your call.
Time to make
a big-boy decision.
Do we do this thing or not?
(RECORDER REWINDS)
(DEBORA SINGING
B-A-B-Y FAINTLY)
DEBORA: (ECHOING)
♪ B-A-B-Y
♪ Oh, baby
♪ Baby ♪
(CLOCK TICKING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Where you going, Baby?
Uh, coffee.
At 2:00 a.m.?
That doesn't sound smart.
You fucking kidding me?
I got enough on my plate,
worrying about Bats, I got to
worry about you, too, now?
You know what?
Do me a favor.
If you're gonna mail it in
at the post office tomorrow,
then go on your little caffeine
run and don't come back.
If you're just in
this for the buzz,
if driving is just some kind
of escape for you, then go.
(DOOR OPENS) What y'all
doing in here? Huh?
Just making sure everything's
ready for tomorrow.
Oh, yeah.
Well, uh, look like he's going
somewhere at 2:00 in the morning.
Are you?
No.
Good. That's good.
'Cause we got
to discuss this.
No, no, it's the same one.
DOC: (OVER SPEAKER)
Baby? Your call.
Time to make
a big-boy decision.
Do we do this thing or not?
BATS: Now, why you
want to go and do that?
It's just me fooling around.
I like to record stuff.
Why you like to record stuff?
You the police?
Supposed to squeal on the road,
not to the cops.
Speak up, Baby.
I... I like to listen
back to conversations.
I make music out of the words,
songs, mixes. It's just something I do.
(CHUCKLES) That's one
fucking dumbass excuse.
To be fair, even the cops
couldn't come up with an excuse
that fucking dumbass.
Now can you play us
one of your mixes?
I can't, they're... They're just...
They're at home.
Well, it looks like we're all going
somewhere at 2:00 in the morning, then.
Come on.
I live really far away.
No, you don't.
(EARS RINGING)
Wake up, Baby.
(PANTING)
Time to explain.
Joe.
Where is he?
What did you do to him?
BATS: Oh, the cripple?
Oh, don't worry about him.
He's good.
He ain't going nowhere.
Why don't you play us
something, Baby?
(HIP-HOP BEAT PLAYING)
DOC: ♪ Was... Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Good... Good kid
♪ And a devil-devil-devil
behind the wheel
♪ Was he slow?
♪ "Retarded" means slow
Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Then... Then what the hell
♪ Else more do you
need to know? ♪
(LAUGHING) This shit is bananas, Doc.
(RECORDING STOPS)
B-A-N-A-N-A-S.
DEBORA: (OVER SPEAKER)
Hello? Hello, testing.
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKER)
It's Debbie. Debora.
Yeah, except I'm D-E-B-O-R-A.
"Debora." Isn't that the
waitress from the diner?
You said you
didn't know that bitch.
BUDDY: Why would you say
you didn't know her?
Have you been
talking to Debora about us?
I don't say nothing.
What about Wheels?
He can't say nothing.
Yeah, but he can read motherfucking
lips, though, can't he?
DOC: Take this fool
back to his shithole.
I'll find another
driver for tomorrow.
Doc, I'm available. I can take
him where he needs to go,
get him home safe.
No, you're not
getting a new driver.
I've been on every job
since we met.
I don't squeal to the cops,
I squeal on the road.
And I'm not slow, I'm fast.
I'm your driver tomorrow.
I'm driving.
(DARLING CHUCKLES)
Well, you heard the kid.
He's driving.
(FAINT CHATTER)
COOK: I'll tell him.
WEATHERMAN 1: The Atlanta region is under
a light, scattered
thunderstorm advisory
through 4:00 p.m.
this afternoon,
with sunny skies
expected to show up around...
TRAFFIC REPORTER: In downtown Atlanta today
due to the ongoing
construction work
at the intersection
of Ted Turner and...
WEATHERMAN 2: Chance of scattered
thunderstorms
throughout most of the day.
Low tonight about 40.
Tomorrow mostly sunny, 66.
(INTERMISSION BY BLUR PLAYING)
BATS: Remember, what's in there is ours.
Belongs to us.
They got our money.
They got our mama's jewels.
So let's go back in there
and take back what's ours.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
♪ ♪
(WIPERS SWISHING RHYTHMICALLY)
(RHYTHMIC SWISHING CONTINUES)
♪ ♪
Vroom, vroom, vroom.
It's go time, Baby.
How the fuck I look?
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(RHYTHMIC BEEPING)
♪ ♪
(WIPERS SPEED UP
TO MUSIC TEMPO)
Mmm-mmm.
(TRUCK HORN BLARING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Drop it!
(SCREAMING)
BUDDY: Okay, Baby, let's go.
BATS: Move!
Let's go! Let's go!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Let's go!
BUDDY: Come on, Baby.
We got to go,
we got to go, we got to go!
Drive the fucking car,
retard!
Baby, move!
Put your fucking
foot on the gas!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on! Go!
You better move this car,
I'm-a blow your fucking head off!
Baby, move!
Three!
Move!
Two!
BUDDY: Move now!
One!
BUDDY: Now!
(BATS SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
(DARLING GASPS)
♪ ♪
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
Fuck! Fuck!
Come on, come on,
give me your hand!
Come on! Come on!
What did you do, Baby?
(YELLS) What
the fuck did you do?
I moved.
You moved.
I'll fucking kill you!
DARLING: Jason!
(SIRENS WAILING)
(HOCUS POCUS BY FOCUS PLAYING)
Drop your weapon!
OFFICER 1: Oh, my God!
(PANTING)
OFFICER 1: Stop!
♪ ♪
(GRUNTING)
OFFICER 1: Put down your weapons!
Get down on the ground!
(CAR HORN BLARES)
OFFICER 2: Get back!
(DOG BARKING)
WOMAN: Hey, Pongo!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Slow down!
(SIRENS WAILING)
(PANTING)
(MALE SINGERS YODELING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
OFFICER 3: Freeze or we'll shoot!
OFFICER 4: Stop where you are!
OFFICER 5: Stop!
Watch it!
Hey!
Get out of the way!
Out of the way! (HORN HONKS)
Move!
Stop!
MAN: Hey!
(WOMAN GASPS)
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
Shot reported at post office downtown...
♪ ♪
OFFICER 6: There he is!
OFFICER 7: Go, go, go, go!
(STORE ALARM BEEPING)
GUARD: Hey!
(GRUNTS)
Stop, or we'll shoot!
CLERK: Hey! You can't...
(GRUNTS)
(ALARM WHOOPING)
Freeze!
(ALARM BELL RINGING)
Stop right there!
WOMAN 1: Hey! Whoa! What?
DISPATCHER: The driver of the
car has escaped on foot.
WOMAN 2: So Laura said...
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
(GRUNTS)
(OFFICERS SHOUTING)
(HELICOPTER PASSES OVERHEAD)
DISPATCHER: ...dangerous.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(WOMAN 3 SCREAMS)
(SIREN WAILING)
No fucking way!
Baby,
you are a fucking jinx!
Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go!
Fuck!
DARLING: Just go!
Baby, fucking get us
out of here!
This is your mess!
Your fault!
Put down your weapon!
OFFICER 1: Get down!
OFFICER 2: Pull back!
(GASPS)
OFFICER 3: Get an EMT here now!
(OFFICERS SHOUTING)
♪ ♪
Drop your weapon! Now!
(OFFICERS GRUNTING)
This is all your fault.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
OFFICER 4: Put your hands
where I can see 'em!
Fuck!
OFFICER 5: Got three officers hit!
Suspect on foot!
You! Stop!
OFFICER 5: We need support over here.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(EARS RINGING)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(HEART BEATING)
MAN: ♪ I woke up again this morning
♪ I'm so tired of
giving up and running... ♪
Get out of the car.
No.
Get out of the car, lady.
Yes. Yeah.
Getting out.
Getting out of the car.
I'm getting... Oh, my God!
Oh, my purse! (WHIMPERS)
NEWSCASTER 1: (OVER CAR RADIO)
Shootout near Peachtree Center.
NEWSCASTER 2: Botched post office robbery.
(WHIMPERING)
(COUNTRY SONG PLAYING)
(CHANNELS CHANGING, STATIC)
(MALE VOICE SINGS)
(SNIPPETS OF SONGS PLAY)
(RADAR LOVE BY
GOLDEN EARRING PLAYS)
MAN: ♪ Don't need no phone at all
♪ We've got a thing
♪ That's called radar love
♪ We've got
a wave in the air ♪
I'm sorry, ma'am.
God.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
What the fuck?
(TIRES SCREECH)
NEWSCASTER: I have breaking news.
This is coming to you live
from the scene of a police
shootout in downtown Atlanta.
Police tell us
that three robbers
entered a US Post Office branch
downtown shortly after 1:00 p.m.
But what started
as a robbery...
Shit. Oh, shit, Joe!
Joe, Joe, Joe!
(JOE GASPS)
You all right?
I'm so sorry. (WHIMPERING)
This is all my fault.
(SIRENS WAILING OUTSIDE)
All right. We got to get out of here.
All right? Things are bad.
I'm not blind!
JOE: No.
No. No.
(GASPS)
I don't want
your dirty money!
I know, I know,
but I can't leave you here!
NEWSCASTER: From the scene of that shooting,
and we want to warn you
that some of that video
is very graphic...
(PHONE RINGING)
Bo's Diner. What'll you have?
Is Debora there?
Debbie?
She's with a customer right now.
You want to hold?
Just tell her Baby's coming.
Baby?
B-A-B-Y. Baby.
NEWSCASTER: (OVER RADIO)
Be on the lookout
for a 1986
purple Chevy Caprice.
The whereabouts of these
felons are unknown.
(ENGINE STARTS, REVS)
Four policemen were wounded
in a downtown shootout.
Police say not to approach
under any circumstances.
Still at large, are considered
extremely dangerous.
(HEART BEATING)
(RECORDER CLICKS)
(BABY EXHALES)
BABY: Hello.
My name is Joseph.
Uh, I like TV.
And I also like to listen,
sometimes, to old records
through the vibrations.
I like frozen peas and
meatloaf and white bread
and peanut butter.
(CHUCKLES)
Spread to the edges.
Please look after me.
Thank you.
(RECORDER CLICKS)
(SNIFFS)
Will you come back?
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
I don't know.
Is everything going
to be OK?
I promised nothing
would happen to you.
And I failed.
But you're safe now.
I'm not talking
about me.
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
OFFICER: (OVER MEGAPHONE)
This is the Atlanta Police Department.
All residents,
remain inside your homes.
There is an armed and dangerous
criminal on the loose.
Good
luck.
Do not go outside until
an all-clear is given.
(NEVER, NEVER GONNA GIVE YOU
UP BY BARRY WHITE PLAYING)
(HEADLIGHT CRACKLES)
♪ ♪
(WHISPERING)
Your buddy's here.
MAN: ♪ Ah
♪ Oh, baby... ♪
Hey, lovebirds.
I was hoping
I would catch you two.
And here you are.
NEWSCASTER: Police have identified
three of the four robbers.
Killed were Monica Castello
and Leon Jefferson III.
BUDDY: Monica.
My darling.
She was a good girl.
I love...
I loved her.
♪ Right on
♪ Keep on doing it...
What about Debora, Baby?
Is she...
Is she a good girl?
You love her?
Yes, I do.
♪ I swear you got it...
That's too bad.
♪ Keep on, keep on
Whatever, whatever
(SIRENS WHOOPING)
♪ Girl
♪ I'll do
♪ Forever and ever,
yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
DISPATCHER: Considered
armed and dangerous.
Got a bathroom key?
Thanks.
♪ I've got to keep you pleased
♪ In every way I can
♪ Gonna give you all of me
♪ As much as you can stand
♪ Make love to you right now
♪ That's all I want to do
♪ I know you need it, girl
♪ And you know I need it, too
♪ 'Cause I found
♪ What the world
is searching for
♪ Here, right here, my dear
♪ I don't have to
look no more...
That's plenty.
Thank you.
♪ For someone just like you
♪ To make me
feel the way you do
♪ Never,
never gonna give you up
♪ I'm never, ever gonna stop
♪ Not the way I feel about you
♪ Girl,
I just can't live without you
(SINGING ALONG)
♪ I'm never, ever gonna quit
♪ Quitting just ain't my stick
♪ I'm gonna stay
right here with you... ♪
Song is over, Baby.
But I'm afraid you still
have to face the music.
(DOOR OPENS)
How you two doing tonight?
We're doing just fine.
Ain't that right, Baby?
(BUDDY GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
BUDDY: Oh, God damn it!
DEBORA: Oh, my gosh!
Come on.
BUDDY: Jesus Christ, man!
Come on. Let's go. Come on!
(GRUNTS) You can't
keep running, Baby!
There's no escape!
BABY: Come on! Let's get out of here!
Okay. Okay.
BUDDY: I will find you!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Oh, fuck.
Oh...
BABY: Fuck!
What's happening, Baby?
I have to go.
No. I'm coming with you.
He just shot a guy!
OFFICER 1: Who?
Him!
OFFICER 2: Atlanta Police Department!
You on the ground,
are you okay?
Can you show me
where you've been shot?
Yeah.
(BODY THUDS)
Right there.
DISPATCHER: Officer down.
Shots fired.
I repeat,
shots fired at Bo's Diner.
Unit 412 currently on scene,
requesting backup.
Possible female hostage.
All units in the vicinity
respond immediately...
(LINE RINGING)
DOC: Who's this?
It's Baby.
Like I said, who's this?
I need your help.
I'm afraid this line is dead.
(LINE CLICKS)
(DIAL TONE HUMS)
Baby, we need
to get out of here.
I just need one thing first.
And then it's just us,
music and the road.
But we don't have a car.
Or music.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Yeah, we do.
BABY: Get out.
Check out
Bonnie and Clyde, yo.
More like
Bonnie and Bonnie.
Get out of the car.
You holding?
You ever shot
a gun before, homie?
I just did.
Literally five minutes ago.
(DOOR ALARM DINGING)
(KNOW HOW BY YOUNG MC PLAYING)
Can I at least get
my goddamn phone?
No.
MAN: ♪ Some of the busiest
rhymes ever made by man
♪ Are goin' into this mic
Written by this hand
♪ Are comin' out of this mouth
Made by this tongue
♪ I'll tell you now, my name
My name is Young
♪ But so you think that it's your
destiny to get the best of me
♪ But I suggest to be quiet,
bro Don't even try it...
(ENGINE REVVING)
(HORN HONKING)
♪ Groovin' it and always movin'
it 'Cause I'm not fakin' it
♪ Pullin' out rhymes
like books off the shelf
♪ Born in England, raised in
Hollis Taught to go for myself
♪ This is stone cold rhymin'
No frills, no fluffs
♪ And it's no accident
that these rhymes sound tough
♪ I'm goin' off, baby,
there's no turnin' back
♪ I'm on your TV,
on your album, cassette and 8-track
♪ And when the show is finally
finished I'll be takin' my bow
♪ My name is Young
And, yo, I got know-how ♪
(MUSIC ENDS)
Not a chauffeur. Noted.
(EXHALES)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS, ECHOES)
It's over, kid.
I ain't open.
I need those tapes.
I'm not giving you
those tapes.
I have the money orders.
I'll trade you for one of those tapes.
I can't help you, Baby.
I shot Buddy.
Congratulations.
Then you only have every clean
and dirty cop after you.
You gonna shoot me, too?
Never.
You and I are a team. I...
Don't feed me any more lines
from Monsters, Inc.
It pisses me off.
It's one of
Samm's favorites.
I thought it sounded familiar,
you little shit.
I'm not your
lucky charm anymore.
But I'm standing here
asking for your help.
There's nothing
I can do for you, kid.
Why should I, after
what you've done to me?
It's okay. Let's go.
Oh, God damn it.
Look at the two of you.
Okay,
go get your fucking tape.
It's going to take more than a
cassette to get you two out of this,
because the news is all bad.
Well, there is
some good news.
The good news is
you like driving,
because you can't take your foot
off the gas for the next 25 years.
This should be enough
to get you across the border.
From there, it's on you.
Don't trust
anyone but each other,
and don't ever look back.
I was in love once.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Bananas.
Run.
I thought... (GROANS)
(SHOTGUN PUMPS)
I thought I told you to run.
(SIREN WHOOPING)
Go. I'll deal with the cops.
That's not the cops.
BUDDY: (OVER MEGAPHONE)
Here it is, Baby.
Your killer track.
(BRIGHTON ROCK BY QUEEN
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Oh, fuck.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
MAN: ♪ Happy little
day Jimmy went away
♪ Met his little... ♪
(MUSIC STOPS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(DEBORA PANTING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(MUSIC RESUMES)
(ENGINE REVS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
BABY: Move!
♪ Jenny, will you stay?
Tarry with me pray
♪ Nothing 'ere
need come between us
♪ Tell me,
love, what do you say?
♪ Oh, no, I must away
to my mum in disarray
♪ If my mother should discover
how I spent my holiday
♪ It would be of small avail
to talk of magic in the air ♪
(BUDDY GRUNTS)
The bag! Get the bag!
Okay.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVS)
♪ ♪
(DEBORA GASPS)
Fuck!
(CAR ALARM WAILING)
We're getting out.
We're getting out?
I have to end this.
(DOOR ALARM DINGING)
(FEEDBACK HUMS, CRACKLES)
Come on out now, Baby.
"Romeo, Romeo!
(OVER MEGAPHONE)
"Wherefore art thou Romeo?"
Now!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS) Motherfucker!
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
Be on the lookout for squad car 3204,
believed to be stolen
by a Jason Van Horn.
Show yourself, Baby!
You fucking child!
GUARD: Hey, you okay, buddy?
DISPATCHER: He is armed
and extremely dangerous.
Fuck! Jesus!
He shot me!
Assistance!
Assistance, please! (ENGINE STARTS)
♪ ♪
(DEBORA GASPS)
♪ Jenny pines away
Writes a letter every day
♪ We must ever be together
Nothing can my love erase
♪ Oh, no, I'm compromised
I must apologize
♪ If my lady should discover
how I spent my holidays ♪
(GUN CLICKING)
Fuck you, Buddy.
(ENGINE REVVING)
BUDDY: Shit, shit, shit!
(MUSIC STOPS)
(DOOR ALARM DINGING)
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
Baby!
You did good, kid.
But you took something
away from me that I love.
You know
I got to do the same.
(BABY GRUNTING)
(EARS RINGING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(HEART BEATING FAINTLY)
(MUFFLED) I really wish
you could hear her scream.
(EARS CONTINUE RINGING)
Guess you'll
just have to watch.
(DEBORA YELLS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(BUDDY GRUNTS)
(GASPS AND SCREAMS)
(HEARTBEAT CONTINUES)
(MUFFLED) Baby.
(HEARTBEAT FADES)
(BABY'S MOM SINGING EASY
OVER STEREO, MUFFLED)
(MUFFLED) What are you doing?
Hitting the road.
Listening to music.
Is this really your mom?
Yeah.
She has a beautiful voice.
I know.
(CLEARLY)
♪ That's why I'm easy
♪ I'm easy like Sunday morning
♪ Why in the world
would anybody
(SIREN WHOOPS)
♪ Put chains on me... ♪
DISPATCHER: (OVER RADIO)
This is an active scene. Hold all positions.
♪ I've paid my dues to make it
(SIREN CHIRPS)
♪ Everybody wants me to be
what they want me to be
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
♪ I'm not happy
when I try to fake it
♪ Oh
♪ That's why I'm easy
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ I'm easy
like Sunday morning... ♪
(WHISPERS) You don't
belong in this world.
(PANTING SOFTLY)
DEBORA: No.
♪ Easy
♪ I'm easy like Sunday morning
♪ I wanna be high
♪ So high
♪ I wanna be free to know
the things I do are right
STATE TROOPER: (DISTORTED)
Hands behind your back!
♪ I wanna be free ♪
(DISTORTED)
Do not move!
(MOUTHING) I'm sorry.
(DISTORTED, ECHOING)
Please, leave him alone!
♪ ♪
LAWYER: How would you describe your
relationship with the defendant?
DEBORA: We were friends.
And I think we both wanted
to be more than that.
He got himself
into a bad spot.
I was just
trying to get him out.
I believe the defendant
is of good character.
He didn't deserve
what happened to him.
CARJACK LADY: Was the strangest thing.
He finally drove off,
and he threw
my purse right at me.
Then he actually said,
"I'm sorry."
LADY TELLER: He looked at
me and he shook his head,
like he was warning me, somehow
telling me not to go inside.
He looked concerned,
like he was, uh, trying to save me.
INTERPRETER: He made a mistake
when he was younger,
and it's haunted him
ever since.
When he tried to get out,
he was pressured even harder.
It was never his fault.
He's got a good heart.
Always had. Always will.
JUDGE: With regard to
counts 1 through 19,
and count 21,
I hereby
sentence the defendant
to 25 years in
the federal penitentiary,
subject to a parole hearing
after five years served.
(GAVEL POUNDS)
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
(TV ANNOUNCER
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
You got a letter, kid.
DEBORA: Hey, Baby.
You know, it's funny.
Even though I heard it so
many times in the court case,
I still can't get used to the fact
that your real name is Miles.
It's a cool name, though.
I can think of a lot
of great Miles songs.
But we still have to get through
all those Baby songs first.
I can't wait until
the day when it's just us,
music and the road.
See you later, Baby.
All my love, Debora.
(INTRO TO BABY DRIVER
BY SIMON & GARFUNKEL PLAYING)
MAN: ♪ My daddy was
the family bassman
♪ My mama was an engineer
♪ And I was born
one dark gray morn
♪ With music coming in my ears
♪ In my ears
♪ They call me Baby Driver
♪ And once upon
a pair of wheels
♪ I hit the road and I'm gone
♪ What's my number?
♪ I wonder how
your engines feel
♪ Mmm, ba, ba-ba, ba
♪ Scoot down the road
♪ What's my number?
♪ I wonder how
your engines feel
♪ Shine the light
♪ Whoo,
ooh, ooh, whoo, ooh, ooh
♪ Whoo, ooh, do-do-do,
do, ooh, do-do, do-ee
♪ Whoo, ooh, ooh, ooh-ee
♪ My daddy was
a prominent frogman
♪ My mama's in
the Naval Reserve
♪ When I was young,
I carried a gun
♪ But I never got
the chance to serve
♪ I did not serve
♪ They call me Baby Driver
♪ And once upon
a pair of wheels
♪ I hit the road and I'm gone
♪ What's my number?
♪ I wonder how
your engines feel
♪ Mmm, ba, ba-ba, ba
♪ Scoot down the road
♪ What's my number?
♪ I wonder how
your engines feel ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
(ENGINE ROARING BY)
♪ Mmm, ba, ba-ba, ba
♪ My daddy got a big promotion
♪ My mama got a raise in pay
♪ There's no one home
We're all alone
♪ Oh,
come into my room and play
♪ Yes, we can play
♪ I'm not talking
about your pigtails
♪ But I'm talking
'bout your sex appeal
♪ I hit the road and I'm gone
♪ What's my number?
♪ I wonder how your engines
♪ Vroom, ba, ba-ba, ba
♪ Scoot down the road
♪ What's my number?
♪ I wonder how
your engines feel
♪ Ooh-ee, ooh, do,
ooh-ee, ooh-ee, ooh-ee, do
♪ Ooh-ee,
do-do-do, do-ah, na, na ♪
(ENGINE ROARING BY)
♪ ♪
(ENGINES ROARING)
(HIP-HOP BEAT PLAYING)
DOC: ♪ Was he slow?
(RHYTHMIC RECORD SCRATCHING)
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Good... Good kid and a
devil-devil-devil behind the wheel
♪ Was he slow?
♪ "Retarded" means slow
Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no ♪
(RHYTHMIC RECORD SCRATCHING
CONTINUES)
DOC: ♪ Then what the hell else
more do you need to know?
♪ Devil-devil-devil
behind the wheel
♪ "Retarded" means slow
Was he... Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Was he slow?
♪ Devil-devil behind the wheel
Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No
DOC: ♪ He's a...
He's a... He's a good kid
He's a...
♪ D-D-Devil behind the wheel
Was... Was he slow?
GRIFF: ♪ No... N-no
DOC: ♪ Then he don't sound
that retarded to me
♪ He's a good kid and
a devil behind the wheel
♪ What the hell else more
do you need to know?
♪ Was he slow?
♪ D-D-Devil behind the wheel
(DISTORTING)
♪ Was he slow? Was he slow? ♪
(RECORDER CLICKS AND REWINDS)
- Extracted from retail.
- Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44