"Corpse"
"1997"
Come, do it now
doing what?
Put your hand next to me
Don't move, otherwise it will draw crooked off
Reserved
My dad has talked to your dad
They will give us a unit
But this layer has only one unit
He never said that he could not choose the penthouse
Ancient confusion
But I like it
Promise me, after completion
We move together to live
it is good
No regret
Wait
Don't forget to use the ring I gave you
So we are like Shuangmei Mark
Don't you remember?
The mall has a new sticker camera
OK, we see the school tomorrow
My business is over when you do this
What do they say?
Banks are going bankrupt
collapse?
You can't do that
All my cash and assets...
What happened?
Thailand becomes Asia's economy
The dream of the fifth largest country has come to nothing
The government announced the Thai baht exchange rate fluctuations
Leading to an unprecedented drop in the Thai economic index
Thailand is about to go bankrupt
Due to the economic collapse, many companies closed their businesses
The government ordered 16 financial institutions to cease operations
At present, the core of Thailand's economy has ceased operation
More than three million people are expected to be unemployed this year
Numbers continue to rise
The company goes bankrupt, so I have to sell something
Thai baht devaluation
From 25 Thai baht to 1 US dollar down to 56 Thai baht
Debts of various industries are high and bankrupt overnight
We lost this battle
"Dilapidated households rich market"
Directly affected is...
The people's life is very difficult
Get out!
Without income, the public can only live and work hard
The real estate market has frozen nearly 200 billion baht
Overhead demand for residential buildings and skyscrapers
Nobody wants to buy now
"No entry"
My dad is a bad guy
How can he do this to you?
Here's what I bought for you
Your dad still want to commit suicide?
He is so poor
What to do will not be successful
When he wants to commit suicide
My mom hid the gun so that he could not find it
But I know where she hides
and so…
Do you want to kill your dad?
No, I can't give up
I am still relatively easy to commit suicide
Are you stupid?
Who are you dead?
Our family will be seized next week
My mom may take us to somewhere else
I'm afraid I can't see you again
Don't worry too much
Here's for you
This is my tuition
Anyway, I don't want to read that rotten school
Without you, am I good?
You less exaggerated
What can I call at any time?
don't Cry
"Happy birthday to you!"
"Now call you Miss."
"I hope we
Can go through this difficulty together
Thai baht currency has been fluctuating since 1996
Stock market investors began to manipulate the market
Spread rumors at the same time
Said that the Thai economy is in crisis
Now it is a daytime shower
As a result, stock is gradually being shorted
Bank of Thailand's stance is firm
Don't reduce the Thai baht, in order to defend the Thai baht
Intervene...
dad
Why don't you talk to Daddy?
Continue to build Sathorn Building?
do you know?
I went back to stock broking for a few days
There is a big passenger to give me money to buy stocks
We will be rich again
Really? Dad?
Really
Not bad right?
"I must move somewhere else."
"I may never see you again."
Where did the money go?
What money, Mom?
The school called you have not paid tuition
Where did the money go?
I have spent it
How can you spend it?
I gave you a lot of money
What did you bought?
Mom!
Let go
Do you know how hard it is to make money?
Even used to buy this meaningless thing
My daughter will not mess like this
Am I still your daughter?
Did you think of me when making your decision?
Help me transfer to school casually
Also forced me to go to the streets to help you sell things
I will be very shameful when I see my friend
If you let me choose
I will not want to be born as your daughter
Since you feel shameful
Get out
Just die to the edge
"Dad hit me again"
"I can't stand it anymore."
Hey?
Ok
Give you
Miss
Pay money
I am sorry
Scream of Life
Wes Kraven directed
You don't have to worry about it
Believe me, you will make big money
It's fun to talk to people who understand things
Those scholars don't know what to say
do you know?
Waiting for the market temperature, those scholars are unemployed
So they want to blindly scared
But I think...
Currently
Those moths that extinguish the fire will die first
That's right
Wen
How did you come?
Only you?
Wait for me, we'll go home together
I'll dump with guests first
Yes
That oil group, as I said
The most stable array
In any case, the government has to subsidize them
That's right
Right, it is time
Trust me
I have inside information
Message Center switchboard, hello
It is meaningless to be alive
I am going to the building waiting for you
I remember with that velvet bag
Are you afraid?
Don't be afraid
If you continue to live, how much will be hurt?
Don't let me die alone
promise me
happy Birthday
Don't want to see anything, don't want to see the sky
My eyes want to rest forever
Other important news
Investigate the project of "Man Yi Hao Life" apartment building
"2017"
It has been found that the blueprints have not been constructed according to the design
Officials have revoked construction licenses
The following is the chief executive of the contractor development company
Interview with Parivian Ryan Vichaya
This is the responsibility of the contractor
We are about to file a complaint against them
If you continue to develop the plan, will be informed
"Monday"
Miss Pa, the car arrived
Belle and the manager are waiting for you in the car
OK, I'll go right away
Sathorn Building Construction Project
Fortunately, you continue to build this building
Otherwise, our company will be declared bankrupt
don't worry
I have also experienced that kind of thing
I know how terrible it feels
I will not repeat history
Mani project is a pity
We have invested a lot of money
Did not expect that kind of thing happen
The structure is 100% safe
The structure of the building was completed before the shutdown
I am sorry
what's up?
You can see the building is still very attractive
Has been idle for 20 years
Because the other half belongs to my dad's partner
It's hard to find land right in the city center
As long as you are willing to give us a loan, I would like to...
Miss Pau, Man Arnold loan you have not paid
We are going to file a bankruptcy application for you
How could you approve another loan to you?
Even if you confiscate all of our assets for resale
Not enough full loan
And you have to sell it all
But if you give me a loan to build this building
We will have enough money
Manui and Sathorn are paid two pen counts to the bank
This is good for you and me, right?
I will give you a week
You clarify with your partner
We have to make sure that the project will be carried out as scheduled
Otherwise, I must file a bankruptcy application for you
Absolutely no problem
Hey
I just stroll
I'll drop right away
OK, Mom
"happy Birthday"
Why did you bring it back?
Dirty and old
I have never seen a real pager
Only seen online
You know old stuff
Open to it!
Scared to death 咩
Can also be used
Do you have a message? tell me
Yes!
Rose is red
Violet is blue
please tell me…
Point solution I will hang you?
Very old fashioned
and also…
1,2,3, shark live
4, 5, 6, lizard bulge Bu
7, 8, 9, friendship is long and long
10, hanging you hung to the eyes wet
Writing is good, but using the map is much simpler
Right
In those days they wanted to say such things to strangers
Will not be awkward?
what happened?
Don't want to see anything, don't want to see the sky
My eyes want to rest forever
Hide in the shadow of the moon
Just want to dream, no longer awake
I feel really sad
As if heard
Should be the lyrics come
wait for me
found it
Passed to you
This is the link
it is good
Don't want to see anything, don't want to see the sky
My eyes want to rest forever
Peach
Last message
It is meaningless to be alive
I am going to the building waiting for you
I remember with that velvet bag
Do you think the same as I thought?
It may be nothing
Maybe just a joke
Oh shit!
Scared you!
Are you scared? I am sorry
Don't open this joke
Tin back to you
Okay
Is it you, Belle?
Belle?
You want to point?
I have the alarm
Belle
Someone broke in
Call the police
Faster!
How many people live here?
Two
My husband passed away long ago
We did not find anyone searching everywhere
I went to see the fire escape
Wait for me here
Okay, police officer
What are you looking for?
My cell phone
It must be in the room
I'll look for it
Wait for me to get it
Sorry, my wife
what's up?
How long was the handprint on the wall?
When the maid's gone, I locked the door
No one came in again later
Try fast turn
What is the problem? Press play
"Tuesday"
I thought Belle was no longer sleepy after age five
This is her first time sleepwalking again?
Yes, doctor
you sure?
Sometimes the patient will sleepwalking for many years
But don't know their sleepwalking
Because they are sleeping alone
Doctors…
Why did Belle begin to draw while dreaming?
in fact…
When the patient is sleepwalking
No matter the way
It is good to see or do anything
They are all done according to subconscious instructions
For example, her current symptoms
Is caused by the imbalance of neurotransmitters
Does she need to be hospitalized again?
Not necessary
I will prescribe medicine to improve her condition
Re-open sleeping pills
If she is still sleepwalking
Don't wake her up immediately
Please take her picture
We can use to analyze symptoms
it is good
# Sick # sleep a lot # declined visit
I heard you want to come, I'll pick up something instrument
This should be done to send you
When I see you reminds me of the instrument
I don't know what she is alive
What will I do now?
Enough, Mom
The instrument has been dead for 20 years
She may have been reborn
Into the wealthy daughter, lived comfortably
More comfortable than me
Mom, only you can't let go
As for this contract...
It's okay
But the number can't
Now the land in this area has risen a lot
Probably tenfold
Have you seen the status of that building?
Construction spending and devaluation must be counted
You know it too
Our dad only finished 60% of the project
I try to give you the highest amount
Since it is so troublesome, don't get up again
Trouble is dead, too hard to do
Ao
Don't be excited
Wen is like family
Price can't be higher anymore
But if you want more
I can give you 10% of the profits
Profit dividend?
What if you don't make money?
I can't get the slightest bit
Right?
How do I know if you will keep your promise?
You know I can't understand the number of discs
Then you are free
and many more
Well, I am out of respect for our father
Not like this
If you can give me your bonus as you said
Then deal it
This contract is good enough
The price can be negotiated
Belle took sleeping pills
9:00 to go to bed
So far no sleepwalking
If you are hungry, there is a salad in the fridge
I will ask you to go later than usual
Until I'm sure Belle no longer sleepwalking
Problems?
I saw a piece of Belle's sleepwalking
Do you think she is just sleepwalking?
of course
Yes, ma'am
Wen and instrument
"happy Birthday"
Are you coming alone?
come in
me too
really?
where is it?
How long have you been there?
Beautiful scenery
Are you lonely?
How long have you known with my mom?
What do you stand there?
Don't want to see anything, don't want to see the sky
My eyes want to rest forever
Belle!
"Wednesday"
Did I sleep around last night?
Have you recorded it?
No
You don't sleep long time
Ugh…
The doctor said sleepwalking symptoms will eventually disappear
I have obediently take medicine, how will still sleepwalking?
mom
I want to cancel Saturday's birthday party
I kind of only a panda 咁, video will be ugly
Ok
Wait for you to fill it up again
Want me to send you a birthday present?
Alright
My phone is broken
Can I send my new cell phone as a birthday present?
Try it if you don't believe it
Lights will always flash when the ring
look
like this
Thank you
instrument…
I'm sorry for leaving you that day
I did not come back to see you later
From now on…
I will do more good deeds and often pray for you
but…
Can you please put my daughter?
1,2,3, shark live
4, 5, 6, lizard bulge Bu
7, 8, 9, friendship is long and long
10, hanging you hung to the eyes wet
What's wrong, Amon?
Wait!
and many more!
what happened?
Why do you run away?
I ask you, what did you see?
She is behind you
Who?
who is it?
Who are you talking about?
I ask you, who are you talking about?
answer me!
What do you mean?
Who?
Sorry
The child into a messing story
Please ignore him
Belle
What are you looking for?
Belle?
big scissors
Right there
your mom
I asked the scissors to close
It's all here
Belle, you scared me
Give you
You run out and ask you to put the scissors back
I am going to go to the market
it is good
I am up now
Is Belle still awake?
Go to the market and go quickly
"Alive is meaningless..."
"Alive is meaningless, I am going to the building waiting for you."
Miss Pa, you have a registered letter
Belle?
Belle!
What happened?
Are you OK?
Inhale, take a deep breath
mom…
Where did you get it from?
I obviously have thrown away
I remember that…
At that time I was almost 15 years old
That is our impulsive decision
We want to commit suicide together
So that everything can end
But after the instrument committed suicide
I'm scared
She left her like this
I did not tell anyone about it
Did not even tell her mother
mom…
This Saturday
I am about 15 years old
As old as you were then
Belle
This matter has nothing to do with you
look at me
Hear me out
You can't do anything
I am here
Belle, look at me
Mom, I'm so scared
Calm down
Can I stay with you?
Don't mess around
Belle
Mom, I really die?
I will not let anyone hurt you
Please help me
Hurts?
do you know?
I'm actually good for you
I caught in this dilemma
Although all this has nothing to do with me
But I think back
You are not suicide right
mom
Can you promise me?
From now on no matter what happens
You can't give up life
Don't have the idea of suicide
it is good
I promise you
Adults are shaking hands
Belle
Belle...
Why do you do this?
I really want to sleep
Nothing, good girl
Go to sleep
I will accompany you
Belle
"Thursday"
The doctor helped her inject the medicine
Let her rest will be better
no matter what happens
Don't let her leave your sight
If you want to go or do other things
You have to find someone to replace you
If she woke up
Call me right away
rest assured
We gave her sleeping pills
She will wake up long after she sleeps
If you don't understand me
I'll look for someone to take care of her
understood
I'll be back soon
What did you tell me yesterday?
Do you really see her?
What does she look like?
I am also not certain
I am scared to see
Only saw one
Girl wearing a red dress
Can you take me to find her?
Please let him go
I beg you!
As long as he helps me
I am willing to give you a reward
Not a question of money
I'm worried he will be short and long
Please don't force him to do it
Please, my wife
How many people in their home work here?
8 people
All will be expelled tomorrow
Miss Pal
Please calm down
Think twice
please
Please don't fire us, we have nowhere to go
it is good
I'll take you
what!
Are you hurt?
I'm not really going to fire your family
But I really have no choice
She is coming to claim my daughter
Please help me this favor
what happened?
Nothing, Amon
who is it?
Natty
There are workers in the building site?
No
As your bidding evacuated everyone
instrument
is it you?
where are you?
instrument
Kind of come out
Amon, wait!
don't go!
Help me pass it to her
please
instrument
is it you?
Is it instrument?
instrument…
Can you put my daughter?
Can you let her daughter?
I beg you, instrument
This thing has nothing to do with Belle
Please stop pestering her again
Do you want to give life to her daughter?
Injustice, debt owners
I'm sorry to you
If you want revenge, find me
Where has she been?
where is she?
I don't know
Amon
Amon!
Are you OK?
Let go!
I'm going, I am so scared!
Amon
Amon!
Amon, it's me
let me go!
Amon!
it's me
I can't do it…
Can not help you anymore
Of course you can
Please help me, I beg you
please
Your daughter is going to die anyway
Don't!
My daughter can't die!
My daughter will not die!
Amon
What do you see, Amon?
What's wrong, Amon?
enough!
I am so scared, I don't want to help you again
Mom saves me!
So scary!
Nothing to be scared of
Amon, calm down
Amon...
All right
Amon
Calm down, don't be afraid
I'll take you back to find your mother
Don't be afraid
Nothing will happen
I am sorry
"Friday"
Wen
What's wrong?
aunt
Can I talk to you?
Miss Pa, what's the problem?
This is a private matter
I think we should...
I have something important to tell you
You have something to say to my mom, I should also be there
aunt…
I am sorry
Wen...
what's up?
tell me
That day…
Instrument suicide...
I asked her out
We made an appointment to commit suicide
But I am scared
I ran away
How do you tell us now?
After 20 years
just now…
Instrument came back to fulfill my promise
My daughter is 15 tomorrow
She wants to fill my daughter's life
aunt…
Please help me please?
I beg you
You want to help me
You can 嬲 me or hate me
But please help me, I beg you
Please look for instrument to talk please?
enough!
Let go!
Mom, let's go home
Wait, wait a minute
What happened to the contract?
Cancel it
The reason to ask your boss
Go away!
and many more
I told you to go away
Speak slowly
Mom, let's go
Miss Pal
Belle disappeared
Missing?
how come?
She locked me up and escaped from the hospital
what? say it again
She locked me up and ran away
I'll be right there
Immediately notify me when I find her
Ok
Mom, save me
I don't know where I am when I wake up
It is not a hospital here
Belle
calm down
Say it slowly
Where are you?
don't know
This is a dark room
Look around you
what did you see?
Belle
Old things are everywhere
Grandpa and grandmother photos
And your childhood photo with them
Belle?
"Parvijan Ryan Vichaya"
mom…
"Thank you, Miss Palin."
"I've been taking care of me since I was a kid."
I wish you peace and health
"Please stay with me until I get married."
"Love your Belle"
mom
I want to pee
Will it hurt?
Will it be too tight?
Belle
Belle!
stop
Belle
I told you to stop
Stop!
Belle
Please stop!
You're back?
Please enter
No, Belle!
No!
I want to go with you
Wait for me
Belle, no
Instrument, don't haunt my daughter again
Let her go!
Please, I beg you
Instrument, don't take her away
1,2,3, shark live
4, 5, 6, lizard bulge Bu
7, 8, 9, friendship is long and long
10, hanging you hung to the eyes wet
1,2,3, shark live
4, 5, 6, lizard bulge Bu
7, 8, 9, friendship is long and long
10, hanging you hung up to your eyes wet
1,2,3, shark live
4, 5, 6, lizard bulge Bu
Please stop
Let go!
I told you to let go!
No, Belle
If I die, it is you harm
Don't move
It's your fault!
stop! I told you to let go of me!
I call you stop!
let me go!
Quiet!
I am sorry
mom
Don't you sleep?
what happened?
Please relax for me
mom
I am Belle ah
Aunt Zhu came soon
Nothing to be scared of
mom…
mom
I beg you to come back
Enough, instrument
In the face of father bankruptcy
Remember how angry we are?
Although we are powerless
Don't you remember?
Why do you hurt my daughter?
mom!
Those who have not kept their promise are me
You should come to me
"Belle, don't forget how much I love you / mom."
Mom, don't leave me
hateful!
I want to fulfill our promise
What do you want?
Although everything is my beginning
But who is not you want to die?
Is this really what you want?
Ok
Wen, don't shoot
Wen
Please don't hurt me
instrument…
Do you really want me to die?
Then I'll send your mom to funeral
This matter has nothing to do with my mom
The meter is dead
Correct
You died a long time!
Don't haunt my daughter!
Don't!
Hand closed okay?
Okay?
Wen, please don't hurt me
Beg you, Wen
I ask you close your hand?
Answer I am so good!
never mind
"on Saturday"
Are you going to commit suicide?
how do you know…
I will be safe after your death?
Her goal is me
If I die
She will give up
Belle
Belle...
Why do you do this?
mom
shell…
Belle...
Please don't do that
Belle
Why do you do this?
You know how much I love you, right?
Please don't bother me
As long as tonight, you may be fine
You may be fine
You are coming, right?
Don't scare me, I hate it
If you want me to die, take me away
Let my mother let it go!
Hey?
Which building?
Abandoned Sathorn Building, is it?
Correct
Sathorn building
Please send an ambulance immediately
Belle
Belle...
Belle!
Belle
Tonight will die!
I want to die because of you!
Belle...
Belle!
Belle
instrument
Instrument, don't do this
I beg you
Don't let me die alone
promise me
instrument!
instrument! Don't!
happy Birthday
Instrument, stop hand!
Don't!
Belle!
stop!
Give me the gun!
Don't!
instrument
I bet you dare not shoot at me
bring it on! Kill me!
shot!
Belle
Belle, can you hear it?
never mind
Someone will come to save you right away
You have to withstand
Help!
Bullet removed
However, the injured brain was seriously injured
Patients must rely on equipment to survive
Even if you choose to continue treatment
The patient can't fully recover
I am sorry
Let you wait so long
Belle
instrument
Really sorry
We will meet again one day
But not like this
anyway…
I will not commit suicide
Belle
I fulfilled my promise
Belle, you can't give up
Miss Pa, everything okay?
I just heard about your daughter
Unfortunately
Conscious
This box was originally placed in the closet
Do you want to take it?
thank you
Hello, Miss Palin, can you hear it?
I'm Belle
I don't know
What happens to my birthday?
But I want to tell you I love you
I love you all over the world
But you must be strong
I hope you feel happy every time I think of it
Even though I may not be with you
I will always guard you far
Sorry for using your cassette to bring recordings
That's it, Mom
Goodbye
Let me help
You come back early
I changed my diaper and fed her twice with a syringe
Trouble you
You're welcome
I'll go first and see you next time
How are you, good girl?
Do you know what I found today?
look
Who allows you to bring this cassette recording?
This is Platinum Edition
I can't find it now
Thank you anyway
I will always be strong
Belle, please get well soon
I'll pour water to you
Why are you holding my hand tight?
Don't want me to go?
Belle?
Belle, can you hear it?
If you can hear it
Just squeeze my hand twice