(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SATELLITES BEEPING)
You know how I came up with the
idea for the Triple-X program?
Skateboards and swimming pools.
Skateboards used to be
stuck on the ground.
Adolescent transportation.
Then 1977 happens.
Big drought hits
Southern California.
Got so bad,
rich suburbanites couldn't afford
to fill their swimming pools.
That's when
the light clicked on.
Some kid figured out he could
skate those empty pools
and get some real nasty air.
Dogtown and Z-Boys. You ever seen it?
It's a movie.
Doesn't matter.
Anyhow, our hero starts
doing things on a board
that no one's ever seen before.
Things the world thought
were impossible.
Now,
that kid needed that drought.
The world needed
those empty pools.
That's why Triple-X.
Do you feel safer today
than you felt yesterday?
I know I don't.
The biggest, most expensive
military in the world,
and we're still scared of shoe and
tighty-whitey bombs at the airport.
Why is that?
Because soldiers are built to
take orders and fight wars.
But we, my friend,
are not at war.
We are at peril.
That's why Triple-X.
What's the matter?
You on a diet?
You ain't hungry?
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
So? It's lunch or dinnertime
somewhere in the world.
Come on, eat up!
You know who does feel safe?
The men in charge.
The world beaters.
The top-shelf, par excellence
ayatollahs with all the "dollahs."
And that's because
those righteous bastards,
somewhere along the way,
made a deal with the devil.
They traded liberty
for safety. And us,
we the people,
ended up losing both.
That's why Triple-X.
While everybody else
is stuck on the ground,
we're doing shit on the board
nobody's ever even seen before.
(SIGHS) Well, that's my pitch.
(GIBBONS CHUCKLES)
I always was a better spy
than a salesman.
So, what do you say?
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
My bad.
So, I'll leave you be, then.
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
Who said there's no
such thing as a free meal?
(CHUCKLES)
Down on the ground, now!
(GUN COCKS)
Give me the money!
Don't move!
Hurry up!
(GROANS)
Goal!
(LAUGHS)
And you say you're no hero.
I got to call bullshit on that!
You're exactly the kind
of hero the world needs.
At the end of the day,
it comes down to the same
question I've been asking my wife
every Friday night
for the last 20 years.
Do you want some of this?
Or are you just gonna...
(SIREN WAILING
IN THE DISTANCE)
(BEEPS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Access granted.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(GRUNTS)
MARKE: Okay, you may sit.
Gentlemen,
this is the device that crashed
the satellite
and killed Gibbons.
Nerds in the lab have
coined it "Pandora's Box."
My team backtracked the satellite's
last signal input to Miami.
Some asshole living the high life
at the Ritz-Carlton penthouse
thought he could
hold the world ransom.
Three flashbangs, two bullets,
and one body bag later,
we took custody of the device.
We must have over 100
redundancies in place
to prevent some punk with a
laptop from hijacking satellites.
And Pandora's Box
can bypass all of them.
(PANTING)
With the push of a button,
it can eavesdrop on
secure communications,
corrupt military software,
transmit false intelligence, or
crash a satellite out of the sky
like a goddamn tactical warhead.
(CONTINUES PANTING)
One of you is behind this.
And I am not leaving here
until I find out who.
(GRUNTS)
(MARKE GASPS)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIM)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(HAWK GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
You fight me with a book?
Here you go, brother.
Chapter one!
Page one!
Shit happens.
(ENGINE REVVING)
You're late!
Just in time, boss.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(TIRE SCREECHING)
(EXCLAIMS)
MI6 CONTROL: They bust
in here, step on our throats,
and take the one device that can
cause a global power shift.
So, how do we get it back?
These assholes just took out
the best of the best
like it was Sunday brunch.
We need someone who can move
like them, fight like them.
We need someone
who can walk into a tornado,
and come out the other side like
it was a damn gentle breeze.
You know someone like that?
No.
But Gibbons did.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(EAGLE SCREECHES)
(MEN SHOUTING)
What you doing?
That's loco, CHICO!
Xander!
(ALL CHEERING)
MAN: Xander! (LAUGHS)
(HONKING)
Whoo! (LAUGHS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(HONKING)
(THANKING IN SPANISH)
(LAUGHS)
(CROWD EXCLAIMS)
(MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
SPORTS ANNOUNCER: And here
we go, we are underway!
(ALL CHEERING)
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(IN ENGLISH)
Go, go, go.
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
LOLA: Of course, Xander Cage
can't pay the satellite company,
just like a regular guy.
(CHUCKLES)
What?
And line the pockets of some
boardroom billionaires?
You know,
these days, a regular guy
can't afford to be regular.
(GRUNTS)
Let's go.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SONG PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
MAN: World getting smaller?
I know the feeling.
Running from your problems
never works out.
You need a new plan.
I need a new map.
(LAUGHS)
Don't say I didn't warn you.
(HORN HONKING)
(BOMB TICKING)
Oh, boy.
Here we go again.
Down! Get down!
Don't move, asshole!
On your knees now,
you son of a bitch!
Okay, okay.
I want to comply.
I really wanna comply.
But you're confusing me.
"Don't move, you asshole."
"On your knees, you son
of a bitch." Which is it?
You have three
seconds to comply!
You're not good at this.
One!
(SIGHS?)
Two!
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
Okay!
Come on out, Frankenstein!
Gibbons! Gibbons?
Olly-Olly-oxen-free.
Wow. You really do look
different, Gibbons.
Did you lose weight?
Augustus always had such, well,
not exactly nice things
to say about you.
When did you
realize it was all fake?
You mean the clown show?
You had a guy over there
wearing $1,000 Beats
when you can buy the
knockoff for half the price.
Or the lady that was running
to catch a bus that doesn't
leave for two hours.
Or the security guard over there
buying a soda with
foreign currency?
Oh, you know
what the kicker was?
Clarence from
It's a Wonderful Life.
The nice old man
that you had sit down
next to me with
the bag of bombs?
Just happened to
know I spoke English.
Go figure.
The bullets could've been real.
Then the body armor
would've been real.
I don't know you, but...
I don't like to be tested.
Gibbons never believed you were dead!
Never stopped looking for you.
Hell of a friend.
Yeah, well, the joke's on him.
'Cause we were never friends.
Oh, trust me, he's not laughing.
Nor will he ever again,
for that matter.
MARKE: I've never seen
anything like it.
This group is lethal,
and they don't care
who or what gets in their way.
I was hoping you'd be interested
in headlining
the next fight card.
XANDER: Seventy feet across,
90 feet down.
Three inches of security glass?
No rope. No line. No chute.
I bet they had a blast.
We ran facial IDs on
every database in the world.
Nothing. Not even a match
on a speeding ticket.
They're ghosts,
in a day and age where
that kind of thing
is almost impossible.
Okay,
you get that I
don't work for suits.
What makes you think I'm gonna
want to ruin all their fun?
Well, if you won't do it for me,
do it for Gibbons.
Your country needs you,
Mr. Cage.
The Triple-X
program needs you.
It's time to be a patriot.
By whose definition?
The last time I was patriotic,
I got three strikes.
And there was only one man
who believed in the underdog.
Patriotism is dead.
There's only
rebels and tyrants now.
So, which are you?
I'm Triple-X.
Well, welcome back, Triple-X.
Uh, where are you going?
London.
Why? What's in London?
A ghost hunter.
And possibly my fur coat.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
I'd forgotten how beautiful
the view is up here.
Oh, I, uh, see
you found your coat.
Well, you promised
to take care of it for me.
And I did.
So, I'm looking for someone.
Since when have we had
a business relationship?
I get caught even touching a
computer, my ass goes away for 20.
XANDER: Name your price.
You know I'm good for it.
Information like this
doesn't have a price.
XANDER: Ainsley,
everything has a price.
Now, if you don't think
you can pull it off,
if you lost your edge, just
tell me and I'll understand.
You wanna know what it is, Cage?
What?
I used to think
you were the man.
But now,
I don't know, maybe I feel
like you're just
working for him.
Come on.
Nobody knows I'm here.
And you know how I am
about keeping secrets.
So you say, but Interpol's
got these new listening bugs.
They're practically invisible.
Real MI6 kind of shit.
Disappear on your skin,
under your arms,
tied around your balls
like a Christmas bow.
Unwrap me, then.
You know,
studies have proven that
sexual consummation
irrevocably ruins
nine out of 10 relationships.
Lucky for me,
you love to gamble.
Of course...
not.
My friends, on the other hand,
adore stiff odds.
Stiff odds?
(WOMEN GIGGLE)
Hmm.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
The things I do for my country.
Like finding needles
in a stack of needles.
Even though you're shackled
by the Queen,
you're still
the best in the world.
Thank you.
Do yourself a favor.
Burn this.
The whispers I hear,
these ghosts of yours
are the real kind of trouble.
They've got training,
they've got funding,
and they've got no
problem running over
anyone who gets in their way.
Okay, so, you're worried
that I might get hurt?
I'm worried you might get dead.
You know, I'm touched
that you can imagine
a world without me in it.
It'll be a little less fun.
That's all I'm saying.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SIGHS)
Your ghosts are hanging out
in the Philippines.
Figures they'd
go to the Pacific.
Some jungle rave
that's off the grid.
How the hell did you
find it so quickly?
Undercover work.
(UPBEAT SONG PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Where is it? What did you
do with Pandora's Box?
It's in a safe place.
That wasn't a part of the plan.
After all these years,
you're still shocked
when I improvise?
No. But the mission
was to destroy it.
Turns out there's a new mission.
I'm not gonna destroy the one thing
I can use to get what we want.
The whole world
is looking for us, Xiang.
Let them come!
You worry about pawn sacrifice.
I got my eye on the king.
That's the problem.
You forgot the queen.
MARKE: After your success
taking down Anarchy 99,
Gibbons was
handed a blank check.
Which is the long way of saying
he got you a new ride.
World went and got an upgrade
since you died, Cage.
Onboard drones,
anti-air countermeasures,
and fuel tanks big enough
to circumnavigate the globe three
times without ever landing.
You can check your coat.
I promise you,
no one would dare steal it.
I can't guarantee
it won't walk off on its own.
Wheels up in 10, boys!
Which means you're already
seven minutes behind.
Is she always this much fun,
or just on special occasions?
Wow.
No wonder our country's
in debt trillions of dollars.
Do you really need all these
gadgets to get the bad guys?
Oh, we don't need any of it.
But it makes the catching
a hell of a lot more fun.
Hmm.
Xander Cage. Holy shit!
Live and in concert, one night only.
This is crazy!
I was at Coachella and Guns
N' Roses got back together,
but this is way cooler.
Well, I wasn't
actually there, but I, like,
heard about it, you know?
I'm still talking. Oh, my God.
I'm sorry,
it's like a bad habit.
I get started and then I can't
stop and then I can't...
Breathe.
Take your time.
I know
mouth-to-mouth if necessary.
(SCOFFS)
(CHUCKLES)
Wow.
Wow! Are you kidding
me with those guns?
You're like
the frickin' Terminator!
And I'm not talking
about the first Terminator,
but the second Terminator
that goes back
to kill the first Terminator.
It was the liquidy metal guy.
Agent Clearidge
worked closely with Gibbons.
She'll handle
support for the operation.
And I bet a guy like you
needs a lot of support.
What are you?
Like 220? 230?
Be honest. 250 is the hard
max for my swing. (LAUGHS)
Oh, come on.
I'm kidding.
It's not like I have a
safe word, or anything.
It's "kumquat."
Never really think about it.
Kumquat.
What about you?
(CHUCKLES)
No. "Safe" isn't
in my vocabulary.
Touche. You are Xander Cage.
(CHUCKLES)
Anything you need, Becky can
source it within the hour.
Except for any
sort of illegal drugs.
Those,
I'll have within 15 minutes.
Kidding.
But if you need
a fifty of Purple Urkle,
I am not the girl to ask.
MARKE: Okay, Cage, follow me.
I'll introduce you
to your ground team.
Thank you, Becky.
Of course.
Kumquat.
Hey, here comes the Red Bull
freak show.
MARKE: Xander Cage,
I want you to meet Paul...
XANDER: Donovan.
Captain Paul Donovan.
I know you. I saw you on TV!
The President gave him a medal.
That must have been
pretty cool, right?
You guys must have some
seriously cool stories to tell.
Must've seen a lot.
I wonder,
how many of you have ever pulled
a freestyle triple backflip
on a BMX bike before?
All of you?
No. We don't play on bikes.
XANDER: Oh,
you don't play on bikes.
Any of you ever carve an R4
on a snowboard
while an avalanche
is on your booty?
We're soldiers, hotshot.
Not slackers.
XANDER: Okay, but you all
have HALO jumped
over Eastern Europe
using a standard-issue armor
deployment parachute system.
Am I right?
No. We're not all jacked up on
Mountain Dew and Red Bull,
you asshole.
(MEN LAUGH)
Where'd you find this guy?
Well, there's a first
time for everything.
(ALARM BLARES)
(ALL SCREAM)
What did you just do?
I can't believe this shit.
I'm not gonna have clowns
watch my back.
I know I'm gonna
regret asking you this,
but who would you trust?
(SONG PLAYING)
(LION ROARS)
(HUNTERS SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
(EXCLAIMING, SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
You know,
no one has this number.
So, what are you
up to these days?
Me?
(LION ROARS)
I'm evening the odds.
(MAN SCREAMS)
(SONG PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LAUGHING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
OFFICER 1: Move in, move in!
OFFICER 2: Show me your hands!
OFFICER 1:
Get on the car, now!
It was like that
when I got here.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Nobody gets in unless you're an
X-Game participant!
You hear me?
That guy got through.
Hey, get back here!
Wassup, Nyjah?
Lightningbolt and Burrito.
Chad, wassup, bro?
Roberta. I'll see you later.
Show him the love!
Give it up for The Hood!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(EDM PLAYING)
The good, the bad, the extreme,
and the completely insane.
Now, this is
a team I can work with.
MARKE:
I'll make this easy for you.
These four assholes,
very bad guys.
Pandora's Box, very bad thing.
We'll land in Manila
and you will requisition
your own transportation
to the island.
Yo, why don't we just nuke this
bitch from orbit and call it a day?
Pandora's Box is one of a kind.
It needs to be recovered intact.
TENNYSON: Why? What's it do?
Brainwave scrambler?
It killed Gibbons.
All you need to know.
The rest is classified.
Brainwave scrambler.
(SNIFFING) You smell that?
Smells like the same shit
in a different suit.
You think a dog knows
how to work a Frisbee?
Master says, "Fetch,"
and the bitch listens.
You would look so sexy
with a Frisbee in that mouth.
MARKE: Oh, sweetheart,
this is not a game.
You are all my soldiers now.
(CHUCKLES) I'm not a
soldier, I'm a baller.
Do we look like soldiers?
Oh, hell, no.
I dropped your soldiers
over Eastern Europe.
So, why did you
leave Lassie behind?
This is my operation!
You will listen to me.
ADELE: Meeting's over.
Well, other than that, Mrs.
Lincoln, how was the play?
(SNICKERING)
Oh, hey, that's
super-cinch body armor.
You've got to
tighten the strap...
over here.
I got this.
What are you, my handler?
(CHUCKLES)
I'm whatever you need.
I can handle anything.
And I've got a tight grip.
And just so you know,
I am not a field agent.
I do not go out in the field.
Ever.
Now,
that's where all the fun is.
Yeah, fun scares me.
People scare me.
Guns scare me.
People with guns
really scare me.
And if I'm scared,
I can't do my job.
And if I can't do my job,
then people die.
And if people die,
then who am I tech-supporting?
Literally no one.
But I will make
sure to keep you safe.
It ain't easy to keep me safe.
NICKS: Whoa.
Yeah, these bad boys
are my favorite, too.
They're called exo-gloves.
DARPA's new ground
combat initiative.
Pneumatic pistons
drive the gears,
quadruple the speed
and power of your punches.
Uh, uh-uh-uh...
Nope, nope.
This is a multistage
signal disruptor.
It's very, very breakable.
Can you tell me the real
reason behind the crash of
Pan Am Flight 103
over Lockerbie?
Yes.
Ah.
You're one of them, aren't you?
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
Easy there, Rocky.
I wasn't kidding when I said
there's enough
force in these bad boys
to probably punch a hole
through the fricking plane.
Keep screwing around.
What could possibly go wrong?
That is my style, though. Yeah, good.
Glad to hear it.
Oh, you know, actually,
I would rather if you didn't...
Oh.
That's refreshing.
You actually know
what you're doing down there.
Yeah.
That's what she said.
(CHUCKLES) Wow.
(MAN SHOUTS IN THE DISTANCE)
(MAN SPEAKING TAGALOG)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You need something, man?
Well, I heard this is a perfect
place to disappear for a few days
for my crew, no questions asked.
Hey, Mi casa es Su casa,
if the price is right.
Perfect. Tennyson!
You're gonna like this.
I just happen to have the best
hardware in the South Pacific.
(GRUNTS)
30% off the top
gets you our finest
hospitality package.
30% off the top?
Do I get the girls for a
weekend and two coconuts?
10%.
(SPEAKS SPANISH) 10%?
You must've been aiming
at the other lawless,
uncharted island down the block.
Happens all the time.
Here's what you do.
You turn around, go get your boat.
You can kiss my ass.
Okay, hang on.
What do you think?
You talked me into it!
18%!
You think this is a flea market?
You think we're in the hood
selling TVs and fake watches,
or something like that?
What's wrong with you, man?
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
All right.
Twenty-two and a half.
How you gonna do "and a half"?
Twenty-two
and a half.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
All right. Enjoy this party.
I like your style, man.
Stay on that boat,
no matter what.
Adele, Nicks!
All right,
guys, keep your earbuds in.
Like always, Adele,
you're my eyes in the sky.
Nicks, you're gonna show 'em
how we do it.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
You got this?
Just watch.
(CHUCKLES)
Can you keep this
behind the bar for me?
BARTENDER: What can I get you?
A cranberry and club soda.
(WHISPERS) Make that two.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Stay focused.
Really? (SNIFFS)
Xander Cage. Back in action.
Did I ever leave?
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
Oh.
Shit.
Spotted our clown.
Easier than expected.
Drinks all around.
That's him.
(GRUNTS)
What do you know?
It's douchebag hunting season.
My favorite.
It's a little early in the
evening to slay someone.
Let me fix it.
ADELE: Oh, Come on.
If Dance Dance Revolution
doesn't deserve a bullet,
I don't know who does.
NICKS: (ON MICROPHONE)
Is this a party or a funeral?
WOMAN: It's a party!
Either way, somebody's
getting turnt up tonight!
(ALL CHEERING)
(SONG PLAYING)
I told you he was
fun to have around.
(CHUCKLES)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
At first,
I thought Special Forces.
But your ink's all wrong.
CIA?
They would send in a drone,
bomb us to hell.
MI6?
You're not the kind
of subtle they prefer.
You know, the men who come to
this island, they're on the run.
Hiding from the world.
But not you.
You're not here to hide.
You're looking for someone.
And who's to say
I haven't already found her?
Was that meant to scare me?
A little tremble would be nice.
Well,
considering you're one tremble
away from limping out of here...
(GUN COCKS)
I'd say I'm close enough.
Does this mean
you're not making me
breakfast in the morning?
I'd say you're
a couple inches off.
Bit of a stalemate.
Not if you drop the gun.
I'm not the bad guy.
I don't believe in good guys.
XIANG: Serena?
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
We just met.
But we were getting along
famously until somebody
decided to interrupt.
Stick to the path.
Here, honey.
XIANG: There's a lot of
unmarked graves on the island.
I'll bet whoever sold you
that shirt is in one of them.
(CHUCKLES)
And how long do you
intend to push your luck?
Until I get what I came for.
Which is what exactly?
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
So, let's be real and talk
about what we all really want.
I'm only here for that.
And in my mind, you guys
could walk away nicely.
Unless you want to
continue our foreplay.
Power like that doesn't belong
in anyone's hands.
Just improvising.
ADELE:
Mate, seriously? A grenade?
What is this? Eastern
Europe in the early '90s?
Next, he's gonna send you a fax.
(SNICKERS)
So, you're willing to kill
just to keep that for yourself?
That's the wrong
question to ask.
What's the right question?
"Are you willing
to die for it?"
One grenade, three people.
I like the odds.
Two grenades, three people.
I'm loving these odds.
(LAUGHS)
You ever bleed so much,
when you open your eyes,
all you see is red?
When you have fought war
on every continent...
ADELE: Come on, X,
just say the word.
Let me put both these assholes
out to pasture.
You expect death.
Our bodies are
such fragile things.
Come on. Let me shoot him.
Death sometimes just
sneaks up on you.
(BOMBS CLICKING)
ADELE: It's been a while
since I played hot potato.
XIANG:
I'm in this hospital bed.
I'm barely conscious.
Delirious.
Drowning in my own blood.
And all I can hear myself
think is, "Today's the day."
"Today's the day you die."
I'm touched.
Can I have my jacket,
when you get a sec?
Then a man comes along,
tells me a story
about a drought in California.
About skateboards
and swimming pools.
About a man named Xander Cage.
Oh, shit. He's Triple-X.
I heard he was dead.
Is he?
We are all Triple-X.
We just have different agendas.
She wants to destroy it.
I'm gonna use it.
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna
let you take it back to the NSA.
(SINGING)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(SCATTING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Now, it's a party.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Everybody, get down!
Move! Move!
Shit's about to go down.
You ready to have some fun?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Stop it!
Everybody, hands up!
Now!
On the floor!
First person to move,
first person to die!
(MIMICS ROBOT WHIRRING)
I moved.
(CHUCKLES) I just moved again.
I'm still alive.
SOLDIER: Shut up, "hero"!
All right.
Let's do this.
Don't move!
(WOMAN SCREAMS) (MAN
SPEAKING IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
Okay, I actually
have what you want.
Pandora's Box?
I got it right here.
But you're wrong, though.
You take it from me,
and you die first.
Then Lieutenant Leningrad,
who thinks he's got your back.
Then the two Ivans by the door.
Moscow Mule by the bar.
And then Igor on the stairs.
See where we're going with this?
But none of that matters.
'Cause like I said,
if you take this
from me, you die first.
I'll take it from
you dead or alive.
And if you hold it too tight,
I cut your arm off.
Suit yourself.
(BOMB TICKING)
(GROANS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Leningrad.
Hi, Ivan.
Other Ivan.
Whoo!
Ooh, bye-bye, Moscow Mule.
(GRUNTING)
Igor. That's another one
you owe me, X.
(OVER EARPIECE)
Read between the lines.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Tennyson!
Some back-up would be nice.
Huh? Some back-up would be nice!
Come on, man!
X said stay on the boat.
That was before the goddamn Russian
invasion touched down, man!
(ENGINE REVVING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(MAN EXCLAIMING)
(GASPING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING,
SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SOLDIER GROANS)
(YELLS)
X said stay on the boat.
You want to play?
(SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(GUNSHOTS)
(ENGINE REVS)
(GASPS)
That doesn't belong
in anyone's hands.
You want it, come and get it.
(GROANS)
Was that necessary?
It's what Gibbons
would have wanted.
ADELE: X!
X.
It happened again.
Another satellite fell.
Us working as a team.
That's what
Gibbons would've wanted.
You in?
NEWSCASTER: An explosion inside
the Olympic Stadium rocks Moscow.
Seven workers are
now confirmed dead,
with at least 25 others injured
in this senseless
act of violence.
A source inside the Pentagon
says a rogue satellite may
have been used as a weapon.
Guess this means Pandora's Box
isn't exactly classified.
NEWSCASTER: In a new video
released just moments ago,
an anonymous group
is claiming to have the ability
to use satellites as weapons.
They claim "that the
violation of civil liberties
"of all
the citizens of the world
"is an atrocity
that must be stopped."
(IN A DISTORTED VOICE) Disable and
dismantle all the world's spy programs
within the next 24 hours,
or I'll do it for you,
one satellite at a time.
There are 30,000 satellites
orbiting the Earth at this moment.
I will drop one satellite every 24
hours until my demands are met.
Eyewitnesses in Moscow...
Was this always part of
your mission, too?
Of course not.
(SCOFFS)
We were a new Triple-X team
Gibbons created.
We discovered a high-level
intelligence officer
was trying to
manipulate satellites.
And even before we
could unmask him,
Gibbons was killed.
XANDER: So, you knew they were
Triple-X all along.
I needed you to retain
a sense of objectivity.
I don't understand.
If I destroyed Pandora's Box,
what happened in Moscow?
If I'm right, which I am,
this box only
ever had the ability
to control one satellite.
What does that mean?
It means we've been
chasing a prototype.
TENNYSON: And these guys
have the real one?
Yeah.
Serena played us for fools.
Betrayed us.
XIANG:
This isn't about Serena.
This is war. And either
we stop it today, or we watch
the world burn tomorrow.
Can't lose focus on that. Yeah.
Where you been?
You stop off for
the old rub-and-tug?
Your mom says hi.
(LAUGHS)
Tracker on board?
Nobody saw you?
Nobody ever sees me, boss. Good.
XANDER: Now, these suits control
every spy satellite in the sky.
But how often do these seven men
all sit in
the same room together?
MARKE: Almost never.
XANDER: And if you
needed retinal scans,
cell phone data dumps,
biometrics of all
the superpowers in the world,
who would you target?
Oh, shit.
XANDER: Who has that kind of power
to actually set that in motion?
Oh, you're pissing up
the wrong tree, Cage.
I came looking
for you, remember?
Yo, asshole.
We gonna have problems?
Oh, no problem.
How was your trip?
(CHUCKLES)
I'm just doing the math.
Oh, yeah?
What math?
Air velocity
divided by distance.
So, when I stuff
you down the toilet,
search and rescue
will know where
to find you between
China and North Korea.
Keep talking shit, little man.
Hold that thought,
G.I. Joe.
Wow.
Roll it back.
A little more.
More.
A little more. Stop.
Okay, when Xiang
broke the window,
he's the only one
that didn't flinch.
I need
the President on the phone...
That's not gonna come off,
you know that, right?
I'll have to replace
the goddamn screen.
I've been saying
the director of the CIA
has been trying to destroy
the world for years.
Okay, we have carte Blanche to
track this son of a bitch down.
Do any of you know how to do it?
The same way Xiang and I found
Pandora's Box in New York.
Pandora's Box needs to
keep reconnecting itself
because the satellites orbit.
Excuse me.
Uh.
All we need to do is
track down the main signal,
and then we can approximate its
location within a 20-mile radius.
ADELE: Of all the places in
the world to lay low,
this fruit loop chooses Detroit?
MALE REPORTER: These blasts
did take place in Moscow,
but they were felt
around the world.
Good morning.
As feared, the death toll
in the Moscow tragedy is rising.
In addition to
the latest deaths...
Let me guess. Everyone's
jumping at the chance
to dismantle their spy programs.
No.
The world's too stupid to realize
that Moscow wasn't a bluff.
MARKE: Okay, Triple-X,
you will base out of
an NSA safe house.
Becky will coordinate
earbud communications
and have the signal disruptor
on standby.
Nicks,
when I crashed the boat up
on shore and saved your life...
Yeah, whatever, bro.
Do you think that counts
as crash 199 for me?
You know, officially?
Officially, you're deranged.
Cool.
MARKE: We'll set up a triangulated
signal tracking system around the city.
And when Becky locks
in his exact location,
we make our move.
XANDER: What about you? How did
you get roped into all this?
SERENA: I tagged a skyscraper
and got a year in jail for it.
Jail?
Seems excessive.
Mmm-hmm.
The tag was 30 stories tall.
Two million hits on YouTube.
And I served only
half the sentence.
Let me guess.
Gibbons to the rescue.
Yup. He said a lion like me
doesn't belong in
any kind of cage.
I got mine after I left the NSA.
What about that
one on your wrist?
SERENA: London.
2009. I climbed
the Millennium Wheel.
Naked.
Naked?
Yeah.
High school.
Oh, no!
We all have our
embarrassing moments.
(LAUGHS)
What about that sexy one?
This?
Phoenix out of the ashes.
Eighteen hours in
a chair in Mexico.
I drank my bodyweight in
tequila to get through it.
It's the most
important one, actually.
It's when I decided to
change the world instead of
rage against it.
BECKY: We found him.
We found Pandora's Box.
Xander, do you copy?
XANDER: We're here.
Okay, send Tennyson.
Uh, looks like East
404 Congress Street.
He's on the top floor.
I'm showing activity in Pandora's Box.
I can jam the signal,
but only for a few minutes,
so hurry.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
BECKY: You've got to get there
fast and take this guy down.
Not if we find him first.
(CHUCKLES)
Whoa! Red light!
Red light! Red light!
(HORN BLARING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Whoo!
Did you know traffic signals
were invented by Big Oil
to waste fuel and
drive up profits?
If I say yes, will you please
just slow down? Look out!
(TENNYSON CACKLES)
Wait.
Is this the part where
you act the basic bitch
and tell me you
got your eye on me
and that you don't trust me?
Welcome to the moment.
NICKS: Whoa, whoa, whoa
Everyone needs backup.
NICKS: Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Tennyson?
XANDER: Gridlocked.
There it is.
If you run into trouble,
dial nine.
It's an old Gibbons fail-safe.
(CHUCKLES)
You crashed my party!
Stole my dance partner.
I'm gonna crash yours.
Have fun.
This ain't a party.
This is a race.
(GRUNTS)
What the hell you
think you're doing?
Building a ramp.
(GRUNTS)
Go, go, go!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Go, go, go, go!
Hey! Out of the car! Get out!
What are you doing?
Let's go!
(MAN YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(HONKING)
(GRUNTING)
Wow.
BECKY: Shit.
He's trying to reconnect it.
Guys, I can only
jam the signal for so long
before he chooses
another satellite.
You have to hurry.
I have a plan.
(GASPS)
Hold on!
"Hold on" ain't no goddamn plan!
(GASPS) No, no, no, no!
(GRUNTS)
(GUN COCKS)
Hi.
You looking for someone?
(GASPING)
That's 200!
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTING)
Ha-ha! Come on.
No, no, no... Xander, you got
to get to the top floor.
He's trying to
engage another satellite.
Hurry.
(GUN FIRING)
Fish in a barrel.
(SHELL CASING CLATTERS)
Forty-five U.S.P.
Twelve round mag.
Five left.
Three.
What the hell's
going on out there?
(GROANS)
(LOUD THUD)
Empty.
(GRUNTS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
(PANTING)
BECKY: Adele, Xander's in.
Find the target, light him up.
XIANG:
Gibbons thought you'd be back.
To be the hero we needed.
You take the box to the NSA,
and we're right back
to where we started.
(GUN COCKS)
Wow.
This is touching.
(LAUGHS)
Gibbons would be proud to
see you two working together.
(GRUNTS)
I'm walking out of here, Xander.
You want to know a secret?
You forgot to put deodorant on?
I killed Gibbons because
he was a self-righteous prick.
BECKY: Do you have a shot?
CIA DIRECTOR: He thought he had
the right to police the world.
BECKY: Adele, do you have
eyes on the target?
(GRUNTS)
I'm switching to thermal.
I was never going to
stop downing satellites
no matter what happened.
You know why?
Because this world has turned...
BECKY: Please, please, please
tell me you have a shot.
Damn it.
He's turned the heat up.
I can't see shit.
ADELE: X, can't see you guys.
Thermal's no good.
Right? ADELE: I've
lost you in the heat.
You don't see what's
going on in this world?
Take it easy.
Huh?
So, what are you
gonna do about it?
Easy.
X, keep Chatty Cathy talking.
I still don't have a shot.
We made it that way.
People like Gibbons and
the two of you. And me.
We made it that way.
I mean, come on.
What's the point of getting up
in the morning
if you're not gonna
reboot the world, right?
XANDER:
Okay. Easy.
CIA DIRECTOR:
There's a war out there.
We're at war for our survival,
you don't see it?
Millions of people
have died for nothing...
It's their right.
Read between the lines.
Isn't it right?
XANDER:
I'm gonna be honest with you.
What's been bugging me
this whole time
is you've got something
stuck in between your teeth.
What the hell are
you talking about?
I'm serious.
CIA DIRECTOR: What the hell's
wrong with you?
Right there.
Ahh!
(THUDS)
Nice shot.
Was there ever a doubt?
Uh, yeah,
I confess, I had my doubts.
That's for talking shit
about my friend, Gibbons.
(DOOR OPENS)
Xiang! Get on your knees!
On your knees!
Hands! Hands!
On your knees, now.
Just in time.
Watch out, Cage.
Keep this up,
people might mistake you
for one of the good guys.
(HANDCUFFS TIGHTENING)
Hey, suit.
(SIGHS)
You got what you wanted.
We both know
he's not the bad guy.
And who do we blame for Moscow?
Better a living terrorist
than a dead company man.
You see what I'm saying?
Let's go.
Back on the plane.
I want wheels up in 20.
Let's go, boys.
XANDER:
We recovered Pandora's Box.
They're gonna send
an extraction team
to pick you guys up.
But they're taking Xiang.
Oh, and, Serena,
if you don't hear from me,
remember, dial nine.
X takes care of its own.
You gave it back to Marke,
didn't you?
Nice place.
Spacious. Expensive.
DONOVAN: Shut up.
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
Thank you, sir.
Yes, minimal casualties.
Triple-X performed
beyond any reasonable
measure of expectation.
Let me guess.
That was my invite
to the Oval Office.
(GUN COCKS)
As of 10 minutes ago,
the Triple-X program
was officially shuttered.
All active agents are to be
erased from record
and considered
enemies of the state.
It's just never a good idea
to point a gun at me.
(TIRES SCREECH)
NICKS:
Hey, are NSA extraction teams
normally armed like
they're invading Fallujah?
No, generally not.
Watch the boys.
ADELE: Shit.
Oh, God,
it's happening, isn't it?
They're gonna start
shooting at us, aren't they?
Come on!
Clear out, let's go!
It's showtime.
SERENA: I guess we're on
the same team now.
TALON: Give me one.
You know me. Wind me up,
point me in the right direction.
ADELE: Come on, let's go!
BECKY: This shit is
getting real, isn't it?
Is this what happens
when shit gets real?
What do we do?
Just be where
the bullets aren't.
Sadly, the terrorist
activated Pandora's Box
one last time
before we could stop him.
You and your
entire team were lost
in the blast along
with the device itself.
If the world thinks
Pandora's Box is gone,
then they won't know
we're using it to spy on them.
You're just another tyrant.
No. Patriot.
Let me educate you
on the difference.
(GROANS)
Xander!
They say it's the last
great adventure, Cage.
Be sure and send a postcard.
Engines hot!
Let's go!
Xander!
Xander Cage!
NICKS: Go, go!
ADELE: Everybody, fan out!
TENNYSON: Find cover! Move!
NICKS: Get behind there!
There, take cover! Okay, okay.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
What a rush.
Damn, Becky,
that's some body armor.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Hey. I told you
you got no manners.
Did your mother ever teach you
how to zip up your pants?
(GRUNTS)
Shh...
Well?
(YELLING)
XANDER: Serena.
We're a bit busy now!
Marke's got Pandora's Box.
She's gonna drop a satellite
on top of you.
(WHIMPERING)
She's gonna drop
a satellite on us!
Not if I jam the signal!
I need a power source!
Go!
(STAMMERS)
Over there? By myself?
Go!
Cover me!
ADELE: Fan out!
Go, go!
Hurry up, over there!
I go low.
I'll go high.
See if I can't find G.I. Joe.
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(POWERS UP)
Are you getting
this interference?
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKES)
(GUNFIRE, SHOUTING CONTINUES)
Shit.
MAN: Take 'em out, now!
Everyone needs backup, right?
Yeah, I guess.
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
Let's do this.
(SCREAMS)
(DONOVAN YELLING)
(GUNS FIRING)
Nicks!
I've got a plan!
No!
(GRUNTING)
No, no, no!
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
Listen! From now on,
I make the plans, you execute!
Ow!
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(DISTANT GUNSHOTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(YELLING)
Oh, shit.
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(MEN GROANING)
Oh, my God,
this is fucking awesome!
(XANDER GRUNTING)
What's wrong, hotshot?
No witty comeback?
I just finally figured out
that math problem.
(GRUNTS)
(DONOVAN SCREAMS)
It's gonna take two flushes.
Go, go, go!
Oh, shit. Way too many.
Let's get out of here.
Get back! Come on!
Oh, shit!
BECKY: Oh, my, God,
I'm gonna die.
NSA AGENT: Move!
Push forward!
ADELE: This is all we've got.
NSA AGENT:
Pin 'em! Pin 'em down!
Damn! I'm out of bullets.
You got any?
No. Nothing.
I'm empty.
We go on three.
Okay.
(NSA AGENTS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(SONG PLAYING)
Wassup?
Rock, paper,
scissor, grenade launcher.
(LAUGHING)
Darius Stone.
Triple-X since 2005.
Thanks for the assist.
X takes care of its own.
(ALARMS BLARING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GUNS CLICKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
You got to be kidding.
(DOOR ALARM BLARES)
We failed.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
SERENA: Xander, Marke activated the
satellite and it's headed right for us.
I'm gonna have to
take it out kamikaze style.
Don't do it. It's suicide.
Nobody could survive that fall.
Tell Nicks to have
that camera ready.
Low-orbit freefall,
no chute and big fireworks.
They say it's
the last great adventure.
(SCREAMS)
Be sure to send a postcard.
(WARNING ALARM BLARING)
I live for this shit.
(YELLS)
Shit.
(GRUNTING LOUDLY)
XANDER: Nicks,
I hope you got that on camera!
If it ain't on video,
it didn't happen!
Oh, yeah. Hall of Fame
shit right here, bro.
(SONG PLAYING)
(LAUGHS)
You know I
could've done that, right?
Bullshit.
Shut up.
What happened to Marke?
The ground broke her fall.
(UPBEAT POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Still don't
believe in good guys?
It's okay if
you're a little bad.
How bad?
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
(MUTTERS)
Now, that right there,
that was a hell of an entrance.
That's a hell of a car.
Yeah. Gibbons told me
to keep an eye on it.
He said I'd know why
when I need to know why.
Now I know why.
It's exactly the way I left it.
I took it on a date or two.
(LAUGHS)
XANDER:
X takes care of its own.
That's why I figured
you'd come through.
To get a chance to work with
the legendary Xander Cage?
Where do I sign up?
(XANDER LAUGHS)
You know, you done pissed
on the wrong damn picnic.
The whole world
gonna be looking for us.
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
(CHORUS SINGING)
(TENNYSON VOCALIZING)
(SINGING)
(SOBBING)
(VOCALIZING)
(TALON HUMMING ALONG)
(SINGING STOPS)
SOLOIST: We thought we'd end
with Augustus' favorite song.
Wow, that's an impressive trick.
What? (WOMAN SINGING
WHAT A WONDERFUL LIFE)
Think you're the only one
who knows how to play dead?
Gotcha.
This is some pretty surreal shit,
being at your own funeral.
(CHORUS SINGING)
I love that song.
And it could be
a wonderful world,
if we just stopped
doing bad shit to it.
If you wanted me
out of retirement,
you could've just asked me.
You always responded to
less subtle motivation.
Now what?
You keep being the rebel the
world doesn't know it needs.
Watch the watchers.
Fight the enemy within.
Damn, that's so complicated.
Really?
Let me simplify it for you.
Kick some ass.
Get the girl.
And try to look dope
while you're doing it.
You can do "dope," can't you?
Sure you can.
(PEOPLE APPLAUDING)
GIBBONS: Junior,
let's bounce!
I'll see you later, X.
I can definitely make that work.
aLDEN @ Symbianize
Let's do this.
(LAUGHING)
You got me.
(YELLS)
(CHUCKLES) Gotcha.
I'm not a soldier, I'm a baller.
(CHUCKLES)
(WHISTLING)
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
(LAUGHING)
(YELLS)
(BELL DINGS)
(LAUGHS)
(MAN SPEAKING IN SPANISH)
I'll see you later, X.
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
(LAUGHS)
(GUN FIRES)
Sure you can.
(LAUGHING)
Bye-bye.
(GUNSHOT)
(SHELL CASING CLATTERING)