ROBIN: Dear God!
Not a chance.
(LAUGHS)
ROBIN: And why not?
COLIN: She's a famous
heartbreaker.
ROBIN: Do you know her?
COLIN: No,
but I know her brothers.
Don't. Just stop it.
I can't look at you.
COLIN: She's gorgeous.
(SPECTATORS CHEERING)
(MAN LAUGHING)
Sorry! My fault. Sorry.
So where are we going?
I thought Maidenhead.
I know a rather
jolly pub by the river.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
DIANA: This doesn't look like
a jolly pub by the river.
ROBIN: No, we seem to have
lost our way.
DIANA: What a surprise.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
BLOGGS: You can't possibly
marry him, Diana.
He's practically a stranger.
Is he stranger than us,
do you think?
Not much in it?
Has he got any money at all?
DIANA: No.
It's not as if you don't
have other options.
What about that Hugh?
Didn't he have a castle in Scotland?
Mind you, who wants
to live in Scotland?
Oh, do shut up.
She's talking about going
to live in Kenya,
for God's sake.
Don't tell me
to shut up.
Diana?
Please stop going round
and round and concentrate.
This is your future life
we're talking about.
It's your future happiness.
The thing is,
I just know this is it.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You all right?
I'm all right, darling.
Are you all right?
That's the Milima Estate.
More subtle fragrance,
but it hasn't got the depth.
Mmm. And what do you drink?
Oh, I drink Nairobi Chai.
But it's too black
for the home market.
Oh.
We don't usually get wives on these
buying trips, Mrs. Cavendish.
Oh, well,
it's Robin's business.
I want to know about it.
Oh!
(BOTH LAUGH)
KATHERINE: What is it you
actually do out here, Robin?
ROBIN: Oh, um...
Well, I'm a tea broker.
Um, yes, I collect tea,
and then I broke it, and...
Well, it's very skilled work.
(KATHERINE LAUGHS)
And what does Diana do
while you're off "broking"?
Well, she comes along.
My God,
that's almost indecent.
(LAUGHING)
I like it. Really.
MARY: God gave men jobs to do
so women could have
a little time to themselves.
(ROBIN LAUGHS)
DIANA: I like being with Robin.
He really is quite bearable.
COLIN: Well,
I can't see it myself.
It's all
a complete mystery to me.
What Colin means is, how on earth
did Robin manage to nab Diana?
Ah! Yes, my God,
we'd all like to know that.
Yes, I don't know.
How did you, darling?
ROBIN: Do you hear that?
(BIRD CHIRPING)
COLIN: What?
I don't hear a thing.
ROBIN: Yes, exactly.
It's like
the dawn of creation.
DON: You need faith to
survive out here.
Oh, how can you
say that, Don?
And you a doctor.
Well, I believe in
the power of the mind.
Did you hear about the
prisoners on Kome Island?
During the Mau Mau rebellion?
There were 60 of them, all
crammed into a small tin hut.
Prison officer
wouldn't let them out.
Mau Mau leader said, "Very well, I
give my men permission to die."
Next morning,
all 60 were dead.
How?
Mind power.
Hmm.
They chose to die.
They turned their faces
to the wall and died.
Well, I think I would have
chosen to live.
Oh, I've got news.
Oh, yeah?
Yes, it's a bit of
a bugger actually.
I'm never going to be
able to have fun again.
Well, what is it?
I'm going to have
a baby.
Somebody's pleased.
Yeah.
Very pleased?
(ROBIN SIGHS)
Best news I ever had.
Well, since I proposed
and you said yes.
Well, you didn't propose,
though, did you?
Didn't I?
No.
You said you had to get married
before going out to Africa.
Otherwise, you'd go native.
Yeah, that's right.
Mmm.
You did say yes,
though, didn't you?
Apparently, I did.
(ROBIN SIGHS)
(ROBIN CHUCKLES)
Oh, dear.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
ROBIN: Never, ever have a baby.
It's a blunder, Col.
Thank you.
ROBIN: Never.
Robin thrashing Colin again?
No.
No?
Come on.
We're going to be late.
(GRUNTS)
(COLIN WHOOPING)
Yes! Game, Robin!
Oh! Well!
Colin!
KATHERINE: Well done.
(WOMAN WHISTLING)
MARY: I never thought
I'd see the day.
KATHERINE: Well. It might be
our time to break a sweat.
Oh, God, here we go.
COLIN: I can't quite
believe it.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I can't quite
believe it, either.
Thank you, Victor.
See you at tea.
Lovely job, Victor.
You've been practicing while
I haven't been looking.
I have. It was the first set I think
I've ever had off you in my entire life.
Come on. Fancy another one?
Absolutely not.
I'm gonna quit while I'm
still vaguely standing.
God, I tell you what,
this feels rather good.
Now I know what it's been like
to be you all these years.
Oh, yeah, no.
It is rather lovely, isn't it?
COLIN: Look at this.
What is going on over here?
ROBIN: Okay,
what are these contraptions?
Mary, you are extraordinary.
ROBIN: Goodness, Katherine.
Oh, Robin will be
a natural, you'll see.
Never seen you like this.
What is this?
What are you doing?
You just imagine
you're jiving.
And what's the purpose
of this?
Just to look foolish?
No, tone up the tummy.
Mary looks rather fantastic.
Move your hips, darling.
That's it.
This is all it is?
Is this the point of it?
You're just kind of
undulating for fun.
You don't want
a flabby tummy.
Without anyone else joining you.
Just solo undulation.
Look at that.
MARY: That's it.
That's it.
(INAUDIBLE)
COLIN: Are you all right?
ROBIN: Yes,
that's too much tennis.
COLIN: You all right?
Just too much tennis. That's all.
You were rather good.
That's your fault.
Now the crown jester's
going to step in.
(OTHERS LAUGHING)
(SHUDDERING)
Need a drink.
COLIN: It's all in the legs.
I'll have another go.
Let's have another go.
Go.
Are you all right?
ROBIN: Me? Yes, fine.
What's the plan?
Oh, um...
I've asked Thomas
to run me home
because Don's coming round
to prod me again.
That's good. He may want to give
me a prod while he's at it.
You sure
you're all right?
Yeah, it's the pregnancy,
isn't it?
It's just making my joints ache.
That's all.
(LAUGHING) Is it?
Oh, poor Robin.
My joints are fine.
It's funny that, isn't it?
That's because I'm bearing most
of the weight in this pregnancy.
Yes, you are. It's true.
Look, will you come with me?
Oh, dear.
No, I have my, well...
I have my meeting tomorrow
first thing in the morning,
so I was going to bunk here.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
Colin.
(DOOR LOCK CLICKING)
Colin. Sorry.
(DOOR OPENS)
Sorry, old chap.
I'm not...
Sorry. I'm not feeling
too good.
Well, you look ghastly.
(SIGHS)
Arm's giving me some gyp.
Let me help you.
DON: Lift your right arm.
Left arm.
Legs.
I can't move. I can't move.
What's going on?
Get ice now.
I can't breathe.
He's losing it! We have to
get him on a respirator!
(WHIMPERING)
Robin? We have to get
oxygen into you somehow.
Looks like we're gonna have
to smash our way in.
Don.
Diana.
How is he?
He's stable.
He's just coming round.
Here we are.
(RESPIRATOR HISSING)
Hello, darling.
(MOUTHING)
DON: The air can't reach
the larynx anymore.
That's why he can't talk.
He says,
"Bit of a bugger."
DON: You inhale the polio virus
from droplets in the air.
The same way
you catch a cold.
It passes into
the blood stream,
into the central
nervous system,
and attacks a big group of
cells in the spinal cord.
The result is
you become like a rag doll.
You can't move anything
from the neck down.
Can't even breathe
for yourself.
Right, and, um, how long
will he be like this?
The paralysis
is irreversible.
A good respiration system will
maintain life for a while.
We're talking
a matter of months.
(RESPIRATOR HISSING)
Tell me what we can do.
Do you want to go home?
After the baby's born.
What about Robin?
Him, too.
You do know...
I have seen enough people
paralyzed by polio before.
The mercy of it is
they don't last long.
GOVERNOR'S WIFE:
It's no kind of life, Diana.
(RESPIRATOR HISSING)
(BABY COOING)
(COOING CONTINUES)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(RESPIRATOR HISSING)
MEDIC: Easy, now.
Careful with the respirators.
That's it. Keep slack in the
tubes at all times, okay?
Good. Very gently.
Very close now. Good.
Let me get round.
Lots of slack, gents.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Diana.
Oh, yes.
Mrs. Cavendish.
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
This isn't a good time.
We've had to medicate
your husband.
So perhaps you could
come back tomorrow.
I don't mind if he's asleep.
I'd just like to see him.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Your husband is going through
a temporary depression.
But I'd still like
to see him.
I'm so sorry. He doesn't
want to see you.
Excuse me.
There we are.
Tid.
I can manage from now on.
(BABY FUSSING)
It's not fair to
ask you to do this.
Well, I don't see why not.
All right.
I looked after you when you
were a baby, didn't I?
The thing is, we're not
very well off, I'm afraid.
We've got some savings,
but there's not a lot coming in.
Oh, you don't need to
worry about that.
Your family's
my family, really.
It's nice to be back.
Come on.
That's it.
Come on, little man.
Off we go. Come on.
DAVID: Ma?
Moo?
Me?
Me. He said "me."
Eh.
"Eh." "Get."
Is the first word "get"?
Or "let"?
"Let me lie"?
Well, he is lying.
Sorry, Robin, you must think
we're awful chumps.
Let me die.
"Let me die."
DAVID: Talking to Robin
was rather like playing one
of those ghastly party games
where you don't know
the rules.
It's very clever of you to get
him to say anything at all.
Well, what he said was...
What he said was,
"Let me die."
Well, we can't, can we?
You mean we can't even
think of such a thing
or we wouldn't know
how to do it?
Both, I suppose.
Well, it makes
no odds, really.
I had a sort of word with the consultant,
and he wouldn't hear of it.
It's not what they do.
It's not a good way
to go, apparently.
It's several minutes
of agony.
No. No, I don't
want that.
No, of course not.
You do have a life,
too, you know.
You are allowed to
think of yourself.
DR. ENTWISTLE: Chin up.
We're doing very well.
Well, Mrs. Cavendish, we do
have some progress to report.
Progress?
We're learning to swallow again.
We are?
It's more significant
than it sounds.
At present, we have an inflated
cuff round our tracheotomy tube
to stop food and drink
going down our windpipe.
If we can swallow again,
the cuff can be removed,
and air can get to the larynx.
Then we'll be able
to talk again.
DIANA: Might there be
other progress, too?
DR. ENTWISTLE: This is about as good
as it's going to get, I'm afraid.
How are we this morning?
We wish we were dead.
Good, good.
Good morning to you, Paddy.
He couldn't go on
having no name,
so I decided to
call him Jonathan.
I hope that's all right.
DIANA: He never
even looks at him.
He can't bear to
even look at him.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do.
I do. I know everything
he's thinking.
Every time I come here,
I hope he'll have changed.
NURSE MARGARET:
Nearly there.
DIANA: But he can't bear to
look at his own son.
Well done.
CHAPLAIN: An old priest
I knew once, a very holy man,
he used to say,
"Those that God loves most,
He allows to suffer most."
We can't know the mind of God,
but we can be sure
that whatever happens to us
is somehow part of His plan.
(MUMBLES)
I'm sorry. I didn't get that.
Move closer.
Closer. Yes, of course.
(SPITS)
(GASPS)
Yes, well...
I'll be on my way.
I'm thinking
you're not a believer.
Believer in what?
God's a joke.
Hmm. No, pal.
God's a joker.
Look at the pig's mickey
he's made of you and me.
(PADDY WHEEZES)
How do you live like this?
Ah... You get used to it.
What if I don't?
Well, there's always
a way out.
Like Pete there got out.
In his own private box.
(RESPIRATOR HISSING)
DIANA: Robin.
Robin. (LAUGHS)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
DIANA: (WHISPERS) Robin.
ROBIN: Why do you
keep on coming here?
I don't really know.
I'm no use to you.
You really must
leave me here to rot now.
Well, it wouldn't look
very good.
And apparently,
I love you.
You don't love this.
You can't love this.
Apparently, I can.
Well, I don't
want you to.
Don't you understand that?
Makes it harder for me.
Yes, I can see that.
You'd rather just
pack it in, I know.
And bloody machine
that keeps on
breathing for me.
So it looks
as if you're going to have to stick
around for a while, doesn't it?
I'm sorry to say.
I'm not sorry.
I want Jonathan
to know you.
And maybe... Maybe I can make
life a little better for you.
Don't want your duty.
Yes, all right.
All right. All right.
We know all about that.
Everything's as bad
as it could possibly be.
But I can't go on
coming in here
and have you say
that you wish you were dead.
Because you're not dead,
and that's that.
Robin.
Come on, there must be
something I can do
to make things
more bearable.
Get me out of here.
I'm afraid it's out of
the question. I'm sorry.
DIANA: Well,
has anyone ever tried?
(SIGHS)
No one with your husband's
degree of disability
anywhere in the world
exists outside a hospital.
(SIGHS)
But I've watched
what the nurses do,
and if we had
a ventilator at home,
I just don't see
why it wouldn't work.
Allow me to explain.
Your husband is only alive because
a machine is breathing for him.
If that machine
should fail,
in under two minutes,
your husband would be dead.
Forgive me
if I speak plainly.
Do I make myself clear?
I'll be sad to go, of course,
after all these years.
But since Muriel died, I can't
seem to get on top of things.
Hmm.
Things can run away
from you, you know.
Yes.
It's a lot of work.
Is the roof sound?
Some of it.
DIANA: Why are so many of
the windows bricked up?
Ah. Oh, yes,
those are my rooms.
Muriel said it saved such a
lot on the heating bills.
Did she?
Well, it's a lot of work,
but it might do.
The thing is,
I haven't got £12,000,
or anywhere
near that, really.
I'd take 11,
or even 10.
All I can manage is seven.
Seven?
Cash.
And then you'd be
rid of the place forever.
And Muriel.
(MAN CHUCKLES)
Yes.
Really?
Yes. Yes.
Oh!
NURSE MARGARET: And how are
you this morning, Robin?
Did you sleep well?
You're looking good.
Good morning, darling.
Morning, Margaret.
Almost done,
Mrs. Cavendish.
Is that something
I could do?
I don't see why not.
It's just like
a Hoover, really.
Could I try?
Here.
Just...
Right.
Good.
Oh, no, sorry.
Let me.
Let me take it.
Once I got used to it,
I think I could manage.
Why would you want
to manage, Mrs. Cavendish?
Dr. Khan. Robin and I,
we wanted to ask you a question.
Didn't we, Robin?
Can machines like that ventilator
only work in hospitals?
DR. KHAN: Well, it's just
a machine, you know.
You plug it in,
and it goes.
Why do you ask?
Robin's going to
leave the hospital.
Do you have any idea
of the risks?
Yes. Yes, I do.
The risk is that
he might die.
Robin.
I either go on living here,
or leave here
and possibly die.
Yes.
Well, what are we
waiting for?
Up, up.
I thought we were going down.
No, lift your end up
so we can get the bed down.
Very heavy.
(DAVID GRUNTING)
Left, left.
I am going left.
Sorry. Your right.
(DAVID CONTINUES GRUNTING)
So, Robin goes in this bed?
Yeah.
And then Diana's bed
goes next to it?
That's what she wants, yeah.
But surely Robin will have
a nurse when he...
No nurse. Just Diana.
I mean, well...
She can't be with him every
minute of the day and night.
She's got to pee,
hasn't she?
She's got me.
PADDY: £5 says
you'll never make it.
ROBIN: And what do I get
if I do?
You get £5, you t'ick.
You're on.
DR. KHAN: Ready?
So long, chaps. So long.
PADDY: Best of luck, Robin.
So long, Paddy.
I'll be back for my fiver.
(SNORING)
I'll miss you, pal.
DR. ENTWISTLE: Where do you
think you're going?
We're taking
my husband home.
You don't have my permission.
Is this a prison?
Am I your prisoner?
What do you think
you're doing?
It is the patient's
own wish, sir.
He's fully apprised
of the risks.
Take him back to
the ward at once.
ROBIN: Diana,
call the police.
Tell them I'm being
held against my will.
I'm sorry?
What did you say?
You have no right to...
To keep me in this place.
Of course. Be my guest.
ROBIN: Let's go.
Do as you please.
You'll be dead in two weeks.
Ready?
Yes.
Right, bag going on.
All right.
How's he coping?
DIANA: So far, so good.
Right, ready to move?
DRIVER: Lift, lift.
COLIN: Got it.
BLOGGS: Are you
all right, Diana?
DIANA: Yes.
Okay, gently put him down.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
And up again.
BLOGGS: Okay. Okay.
TID: Come on. Let's clear the way.
Clear the way.
One, two, three. Lift.
Here we go.
DRIVER: Keep him level.
COLIN: All right, Robin?
DRIVER: Easy.
DIANA: All right, all right. Gently, gently.
TID: You're clear.
DIANA: We need to get him on the
bed over there, so turn him round.
All right, all right.
Yeah, just to the left.
Uh... Right, yes, that goes
on that table there,
and the cable needs to be
to the left-hand side.
Just leave it there.
Sorry, darling.
Harry.
No, no, Bengy.
Could you come here?
Bengy, get down.
Bengy.
Bengy, off the bed.
You need to do
what I'm doing.
He'll tell you.
Hold on to the cable.
Got it, got it, got it.
He'll tell you if
you're going too fast.
All right, Col, we need
to get him on the bed.
One, two, three. Lift.
There we go.
HARRY: Got him.
It's okay. Okay.
(GRUNTS) Right. Right.
TID: Bengy, off you go.
Just take
your shoes off, Robin.
COLIN: Is it on?
Right...
We're going to change your tubes
right now, darling. Ready, Harry?
I've got your hand, Robin.
All right.
(RESPIRATOR STARTING)
DIANA: It's on.
You all right, darling?
Yes, I think I am.
(ALL LAUGH IN RELIEF)
HARRY: Thank God.
(LAUGHS)
Can't believe
it actually works.
Yes, it works.
Could you get Jonathan?
Oh, yes, of course,
my dear.
DIANA: So this is it.
Our new home.
How do you feel?
Much better.
Diana, what happens
if there's a power cut?
You work it
with a hand pump.
It's a nifty bit of kit.
(AIR WHISTLING)
Look who's here.
Hello.
There you go.
Oh...
Look, Jonathan.
It's Daddy.
Hello, Jonathan.
Hello, dear boy.
(BENGY BARKS)
(GASPS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
This is Bengy.
(ROBIN GROWLING)
DIANA: Night, darling.
ROBIN: Good night, my love.
(JONATHAN RUNNING)
(RESPIRATOR STOPS)
Diana.
(CHOKING) Di. Di.
(CONTINUES CHOKING)
(CLICKING TONGUE)
(BARKS)
Had a bit of a bump, darling?
Oh, no.
What's the matter?
Has Mummy not been playing?
Shall we go and find Daddy?
Where's Daddy hiding? (GASPS)
Where's Daddy? He's in there.
Shall we go and find him?
What's that naughty Daddy doing?
Daddy? (GASPS)
Jonathan, Jonathan.
(SHUSHING)
(SUFFOCATING)
Daddy?
Robin?
Oh, my God. Robin?
(RESPIRATOR STARTS)
Robin? Robin? Robin?
Please, please, please.
Robin. Robin.
Oh, my God.
Please. Oh, my God.
(INHALES)
(SIGHS)
That was interesting.
Oh...
Oh, my God.
(UPBEAT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTTLE POPS)
Ah!
I've saved the best
till last.
This one spent the whole of the
war in my air-raid shelter.
Looks like
a good drop, Teddy.
It is a good drop.
And good wine
deserves good glasses.
This one is for
the lovely Diana.
That's me.
TEDDY: Mary. Katherine.
Bloggs. David.
Biggles.
There we are, darling.
And Tid?
No, no, not for me.
DIANA: Tid only drinks
Dubonnet.
And only on my birthday.
TEDDY: Oh, I almost forgot.
(SHUSHING) He's sleeping.
To Jonathan.
ALL: Happy birthday,
Jonathan.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
Yes, I had been wondering what it
might be like to... To get drunk.
(CHUCKLES)
Given that
I'm legless already.
What you have to do with mechanical
devices is stress-test them,
find their
breaking point, so...
It's rather good, Ted.
An interesting
experiment, Teddy.
Robin would die,
but you'd probably be able to
improve your machine probably.
(SCATTERED LAUGHING)
All progress has its price.
It's the power supply that's
usually the weak link.
You know, power can fail.
Power frequently fails.
Oh, do stop it.
I'm only hypothesizing.
He's just doing
his job.
He doesn't have a job.
He's an Oxford professor.
There's nothing to worry about
because it can be worked by hand.
MARY: Well, what about
in the night?
Well, I'm here.
But you have to
sleep some time.
No, she doesn't.
She's a machine.
Well, if Robin needs me, he wakes me.
Don't you, darling?
BLOGGS: Robin makes a noise.
(IMITATES ROBIN)
Like a duck.
That's a chicken, Bloggs.
Can you do
a chicken, Robin?
I hate you so much, Bloggs.
(ALL LAUGH)
(CLICKING TONGUE)
Not much.
Hmm.
Much rather have
a bell or something.
What can you move?
Cover your eyes, everybody.
(ALL LAUGHING)
You can move your head.
Can I?
I've seen you do it.
All right, well, let's...
So move your head.
Oh, yes, I think I can have
some fun with that.
DAVID: Teddy.
Yeah.
(JONATHAN GIGGLING)
(BARKING)
(BELL DINGS)
Oh, that's wonderful.
Darling?
Bottle?
Oh, why not? Yes.
Why not?
But listen.
Mmm-hmm?
You know those Marconi
shares that I bought?
Justin's hot tip, yeah?
Mmm-hmm?
They've almost
doubled in price.
Really?
Yeah.
Crikey. Well, I hope Justin
got something out of it.
Oh, yes, well, he gets a
very agreeable sensation of
helping someone far less
fortunate than himself.
Oh.
Poor Robin.
Paralyzed for life.
Oh...
(CHUCKLES)
Yes.
And his poor wife.
I hear she's a saint.
She is a saint.
A gorgeous saint.
Ah!
(BELL DINGS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Darling, call Teddy Hall,
would you?
I've just had an idea.
(OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(CRACKLING)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
(PATRIOTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEN LAUGHING)
BLOGGS: Robin.
DAVID: Oh, bloody hell.
TEDDY: Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls,
may I present
the Cavendish chair!
HARRY: That is amazing.
KATHERINE: Hooray!
TEDDY: Roll up, roll up.
There'll be no
stopping you now, old boy.
TEDDY: Not bad, eh?
It looks terrifying.
What if it breaks?
ROBIN: Unbelievable, Teddy.
HARRY: Left, left, left!
(BARKING)
We've lost the dog. Bengy.
Robin, how does it feel?
Bloody marvelous.
Really?
Is the ventilator
a little fast?
Well, maybe a little.
Yeah? Is that better?
Yeah, that's better.
How long does
the battery last, Teddy?
Up to three hours,
we think.
Isn't this a case
where a little more
certainty would
be appropriate?
Well, there's a mains lead
as well.
Teddy, you're a genius.
Well, to be honest, it all
turned out to be pretty basic.
I used a bicycle chain
and Sturmey-Archer gears.
I don't know why
no one's done it before.
I'll tell you why.
Because you're not a doctor.
There's no one to tell you
it can't be done.
(MATRON CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, hello, Matron.
Hello, Matron.
Oh, we've got an
appointment with Dr. Khan.
DIANA: Dr. Khan.
ROBIN: Ah, hello, Dr. Khan.
Huh?
Paddy.
Oh.
Robin.
This really is
quite something.
Jammy bastard.
What in God's name
is that?
Did you give permission for this
contraption to be brought into my ward?
Well, actually, sir,
Mr. Cavend...
It's hard enough
for our patients
to accept the conditions
of their lives
without raising false hopes that can
only leave them more dissatisfied.
Now, where you come from,
it may be common practice to
play games with people's lives.
Here it is not.
Is that understood?
Good.
It was lovely to see you,
Dr. Entwistle.
Oh... That man's
a pompous idiot.
You must want to
smack him.
Believe me, I'm used to it.
Well...
You'd think he'd want to get chairs
like this for all his patients.
Well, Paddy, looks like
you owe me a fiver.
Not so quick, pal.
You could drop off
your perch tomorrow.
Aww.
Is it safe, Doctor?
I don't know, Paddy.
I've never seen
anything like this before.
Goes five miles an hour
with a strong wind
behind you.
I'd advise waiting a little while longer.
Test its limits.
Yes, quite right. Let me find
the breaking point for it.
No, we're not going to test
Robin until he breaks.
Well, actually, that's
exactly what we're doing.
DIANA: You're doing better
than all his other patients.
That's what he said.
Poor old Paddy, though.
I wish we could
somehow break him out, too.
(GASPS)
(SCOFFS)
It isn't kind to let
them out like that.
On the street,
where everyone can see.
Believe me, ladies, my distress
is far greater than yours.
Bloggs told me
the other day
that all our friends were convinced
that I'd give up on you.
Apparently, they saw me as
some kind of pampered nitwit.
Well, you were
a pampered nitwit.
Oh, was I?
Well, it didn't stop you
running after me, did it?
Well, no, I've got
nothing against nitwits
as long as they're pretty.
Well, you're stuck
with me now.
Yeah, I suppose I am.
Mmm.
Just think, all those
affairs I could have had.
Oh.
And me.
It's not too late
for you.
Isn't it?
What, and come back and find
you've popped off while I was out?
(GROANING)
That would rather spoil
the party, wouldn't it?
Yes, it would.
(SIGHS) Hold on.
Look. I found Daddy.
DIANA: That's Daddy
when he was a soldier.
JONATHAN: Was he a soldier?
DIANA: Yes, he was.
And then (GASPS) this is us
when we were in Africa.
That's where you were born.
(GASPS) And what are those?
JONATHAN: Elephants.
DIANA: They're elephants.
JONATHAN: You saw elephants?
DIANA: Yes, we did.
You're so lucky.
Yes, we were.
JONATHAN: Can we go to
Africa one day, Daddy?
I'm so sorry.
Me, too.
(KETTLE WHISTLING)
Right, I'd better
sort out tea.
Can we go to Africa,
please, Daddy?
Wouldn't that be
an adventure?
I could push you.
Rather a long way
to push, J.
I don't mind.
ROBIN: Are you clever?
JONATHAN: Yes.
ROBIN: Can you prove it?
(KETTLE CONTINUES WHISTLING)
(ROBIN AND JONATHAN LAUGHING)
Okay, maybe you are.
Do you know what?
(SNIFFLES)
(GRUNTING)
Maybe you are strong enough.
Mummy.
Yes?
This chair-pushing business.
Mmm?
Is it quite hard to do
over long distances?
Well, it's harder than a pram,
I can tell you.
Oh...
Jonathan?
We're going to have to do some
thinking about this, aren't we?
Mmm-hmm.
(WHIRRING)
(BELL TINKLING)
MECHANIC: As per your design,
Mr. Cavendish.
Be nice.
MECHANIC:
Takes up to 300 pounds.
(DOORS SLAM)
My God.
Hydraulic lifting mechanism.
You won't see that
in a Bedford anywhere else.
What do you think?
What is it?
It's a little dark
in the back.
I feel rather like
luggage is the only thing.
I just thought...
Being as the wheelchair
has to be got in,
the back seemed...
Yes. Yes.
Have you sat in the back?
Me? Well, no.
But, then I'm not, um...
I'm not...
Uh...
You're not luggage, are you?
(SIGHS IN FRUSTRATION)
Please don't think I'm not grateful.
I truly am.
You want to sit in the front?
I don't think
that's possible, is it?
I suppose if I took out
the front seat...
(DIANA AND ROBIN SINGING)
(LAUGHING)
(BOTH YELL)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
BOY: Wait for me!
Wait for me!
HARRY: Careful!
Hi, there, little one.
Ought to be shot.
Robin's amazing,
isn't he?
It's not a bore.
I feel I can
talk to you, Robin.
Mum, Mum,
I'm going in to bat.
Oh, are you? Brilliant.
You go get them.
Good luck, Jonathan.
Go on. Thanks, Mum.
Lucy walked out
a month ago now.
It's been a long time
coming, I suppose.
ROBIN: Oh...
Rory, I'm so sorry.
That's rather rough on you.
Life's a shitty business,
isn't it?
There you are, trying
to get on with life,
and then,
out of nowhere, crack,
everything comes
tumbling down.
(SIGHS)
Rory, grab my drink.
Let's have a toast.
What are we drinking to?
Hmm?
New dawns.
You've made a real
hash of that ham.
Rubbish, Bloggs. You did that.
I've done this. Beautifully.
Do you want it?
Yes. Thank you.
Look at Robin now.
Look at him.
HARRY: Unbelievable.
DAVID: How does he do that?
Well, he proposed
to me yesterday.
Of course he did.
Yeah. And I'm so fond
of him.
The only girl we've
got is you, Bloggs.
Oh, do shut up.
(LAUGHING)
But he's no beauty.
RORY: It's not
just the pain...
Is he actually ugly?
Um... Well, yes.
ROBIN: No, no, no,
that's wonderful.
PAMELA: Why is that wonderful?
Well, because good-looking
men are bone idle.
Ugly men
will get things done.
RORY: So pointless. How do you
get over something like that?
Yep, you're right.
RORY: Lost in the darkness
and silence, but it hurts...
And I will get over it.
I know I will get over it,
but it's just
going to take time,
and at the moment,
I just need a bit of...
(CHEERING)
MAN: It's a six!
Yes! Yes!
Dad! Dad, did you see that?
HARRY: Well done, Jonathan!
MAN: A six!
So?
Mmm?
Did you enjoy that?
Well...
You were surrounded
by admirers.
Yes, as were you.
Me?
Yeah.
Rory Stewart for one.
Oh, Rory.
Lucy's really
messed him about.
Hmm?
Mmm.
I feel so sorry
for him.
He says he spends his evenings
alone watching television.
I suppose he'd like you
to relieve his loneliness.
Well, I'm not going to.
You can
if you want to, darling.
Oh.
You're giving me
permission, are you?
I do sometimes
worry that, um,
you don't have enough fun.
Don't worry about me.
No?
Mmm-mmm.
I'm all right.
Are you sure?
I think so.
Mmm...
We manage, don't we?
That's easy for me.
I just sit here while
you do all the work.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
DIANA: Good old
selfish Robin.
Oh, I say, Diana.
Run away with me.
Where?
ROBIN: Spain.
(LAUGHS)
DIANA: Spain?
We can't. Robin.
(ROBIN WHINES)
DIANA: Robin. Oh, you really
mean it, don't you?
Now how on Earth
do we go to Spain?
ROBIN: Well, by plane,
of course.
DIANA: Darling, how do
we get you on a plane?
(SCREAMING)
(WHOOPING)
Oh, my God!
Whoa!
(BLOGGS SCREAMING)
Are you all right, Jonathan?
Bloggs, are you all right?
(ALL SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
(NEIGHS)
BLOGGS: Come on, then,
you start.
JONATHAN: I spy
with my little eye...
DIANA: The house
is on the beach,
and I brought
a long extension lead,
so in theory you can stay
out all day if you like.
Did you remember
to pack my parasol?
Yes, darling, and I also
brought pints of sun cream.
ROBIN: You're just an angel,
aren't you?
Darling, we should charge
the chair battery.
Oh, good idea. Uh...
Bloggs.
BLOGGS: Yes?
Can you see a cable
down there on the floor?
Sorry. I can't take
my eyes off the road.
Yes, I can. London.
There's a plug board on the
side of the wheelchair.
Can you plug that into the
second socket for me?
BLOGGS: Uh, yes, I see it.
Second socket?
DIANA: Second socket.
BLOGGS: Yeah.
(JONATHAN SCREAMS)
Oh, God. Sorry.
Something's...
I don't know.
DIANA: The ventilator.
JONATHAN: It's burning! Mum!
DIANA: What's happened
to the...
Robin. Robin.
BLOGGS: I'm really sorry.
Just pull over. Jonathan,
are you all right?
JONATHAN: Yes, Mum.
DIANA: Get the hand pump.
BLOGGS: We need to open
the door.
DIANA: All right,
all right, all right.
Bloggs, get Robin's door.
BLOGGS: Stop here.
DIANA: I'm stopping.
I'm stopping. I'm stopping...
(ALL COUGHING)
DIANA: Robin.
Bloggs, the bag.
Jonathan, are you all right?
JONATHAN: Yes, Mum.
BLOGGS: Sorry, Robin.
Oh, God, I knew something like
this would happen. I just knew it.
What did I do?
I don't know.
The ventilator's broken.
Robin, are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
(COUGHING)
Jonathan. (COUGHING)
Do you know
how to fix it?
No.
No, I don't.
Sorry, Diana. I just
don't know what I did.
Neither do I.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Oh, God.
Do you speak English?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Just a little.
We need a mechanic.
No, no, we don't. No, no.
What we need is a telephone.
A telephone.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Yes.
Uh...
I take for you to Torredembarra
to find for telephone.
Yes. Yes.
Is okay?
Yes, yes, yes. Jonathan, could
you get my handbag, darling?
Thank you, yes.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Yes, yes.
Bloggs, Bloggs, Bloggs, Bloggs.
It's rather fast.
You don't have to go so fast.
Sorry.
Don't go so fast.
I'm not a balloon.
DIANA: Bloggs.
BLOGGS: Yeah.
Can you go with this man,
find a telephone and call Teddy Hall?
He'll either be at home
or at the workshop.
That's the Littlemore number.
In England?
Yes. Just tell him
what's happened,
and that we'll
wait for him here.
Yeah. We'll wait for him to
fly out from England?
Yes. Can you just go, please?
Yeah.
Bloggs, just while
you're out, grab us a...
Pick up some sausage
and a nice bit of bread.
And a bottle of red wine.
Corkscrew.
Good luck.
Hola.
I'm not saying it.
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)
I hope you can hear me.
BLOGGS: Sorry!
DIANA: Mmm-hmm?
A rather pleasant
temperature.
Reminds me of Nairobi.
You all right there,
Jonathan?
Yes, I'm fine.
It's quite easy, really.
Oh?
You really are doing
brilliantly, darling.
Truly.
You really are.
I'll take over in a moment.
I'm okay.
Really.
Oh, God. I wonder what it
is they think we're doing.
Why, we've just gone
on holiday in a lay-by.
It's perfectly normal.
Cheers.
Cheers, darling.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
He say God makes a joke.
So we have party.
Sí. Sí.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah... Well, that's quite
all right, isn't it?
(ALL TOAST IN SPANISH)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(PLAYING SOFT LATIN MUSIC)
Do you know
who'd love this?
Paddy.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(RHYTHMIC CLAPPING)
TEDDY: For heaven's sake.
DIANA: Teddy!
BLOGGS: Teddy!
Hello, darling.
Oh, God.
You could at least have the decency
to be on the point of death.
What...
What the hell is this?
There. Now,
let's fire her up.
(RESPIRATOR STARTING)
(ALL CHEERING)
I'm glad someone's happy.
(CHUCKLES)
God knows how you managed to
make such a balls-up of this.
My fault, I'm afraid.
What are you all doing gallivanting
in Spain in the first place?
It's my fault,
I'm afraid.
Well, this isn't built for
trans-continental voyages.
I know, Ted. I'm sorry.
I wanted to see the sun
rise over the Med.
It rises over Drayton
St. Leonard's, too, you know.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL CHEERING)
ROBIN: Teddy?
Absolutely rather good
you're here.
I'm planning
an even greater escape.
TEDDY: Well, I'm not rescuing
you from anywhere else.
ROBIN: Oh, it's not
just me this time.
There's a good few more
that need rescuing.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Let's get this show
on the road!
Is that chair breathing?
Like a sleeping lion.
Glorious.
Is that Dr. Clement Aitken?
The same.
Very good, very good.
Teddy! Mind.
Hello.
This is Teddy Hall.
TEDDY: Oh, dear, dear, dear.
DR. AITKEN: I have never, in all my career,
seen anything like this.
You just made this up?
Well, pretty much, yes.
DR. AITKEN: Only way to get
anything done.
I like this man.
Is he a doctor?
Yes, and he's the Director of the
Disability Research Foundation.
Which he invented.
Yes, and made
himself director.
Well, if nobody else will do it,
you have to do it yourself.
Hello. What's this?
Oh, I'm having a go
at a Mark II version.
The trouble with the Mark I is
the battery is pretty poor,
and the pump's very noisy,
so I'm having a go
at using a solenoid.
Fascinating. So what is
the battery life?
On the Mark II,
about six hours.
How long have you been living
with this condition?
Eleven years so far.
Incredible.
Well, if these chairs
of yours really work,
I'm gonna need
a lot of them.
How many?
Hundreds.
Oh, well, I've been financing
the work myself up to now.
It hasn't set me back
too much,
but if we're to go into production,
we'll need proper funding.
The Department has
to take into consideration
the question of
cost-effectiveness.
The life expectancy
of polio patients
is less than average,
shall we say.
I'm sorry. I can't see how
I can, in all fairness,
make a case for funding.
I have to follow
the rules.
(ROBIN GROANING)
Rules are so paralyzing,
aren't they?
(DIANA CLEARS THROAT)
Of course, I do sympathize
with your condition.
Oh, yes. Likewise.
DIANA: Name?
ROBIN: Lady Jane Neville.
And good for?
Uh...
A thousand at least,
if she's in the mood.
Right. So are we
"plucky" or "pitiful"?
I think
definitely "plucky."
These old dowagers
are tough as nails.
Why does he make
that funny noise?
Well, that's
the wheelchair.
It does his breathing
for him.
Are you quite sure it's
safe for you to be out?
Seems to have worked
so far.
And what exactly is it
you want from me?
Well, we want more
of these chairs.
Yes, for people
like Robin.
At £200 a chair.
DIANA: Yes, which really
is excellent value.
Isn't it?
ROBIN: Well...
It would be five
for £1,000.
£1,000?
Well, 10 for £2,000.
£2,000?
You see, we knew
we could count on you.
Because you're
so generous.
Yes.
I don't usually find it difficult
to say no to spongers.
But with you there,
wheezing away in front of me,
(SIGHS) I suppose
I shall have to pay up.
So very kind of you.
So very kind.
So kind.
This is bloody marvelous.
ROBIN: Aww.
Do you feel safe?
I feel bloody terrified.
Ah...
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
Hello, everyone.
My name is
Dr. Clement Aitken.
I'm the Director of the
Disability Research Foundation.
In this country,
there are hundreds of
severely disabled patients
currently living their entire
lives in hospital beds.
Worldwide,
there are thousands.
Do you think they like that?
If you want to get out,
give me a shout!
(PATIENTS SHOUTING)
ROBIN: How many
thousands worldwide?
Oh, tens of thousands,
maybe more.
No one's ever believed it's
possible to live as you do.
Well, we should show them.
What do you want now,
Robin, a world tour?
Well, there is a European
conference coming up in Germany
for severely disabled living.
All the so-called
key experts will be there.
Oh my giddy aunt!
If only they could see you...
I think he should be
in hospital. No?
You're quite right. No.
COLIN: You did check
we'd be able to fit
the wheelchair in,
didn't you, Bloggs?
Yes, of course, I did.
What do you take me for?
Thank God for that.
I know.
I never thought we'd actually make it...
Oh, sorry.
No, it was probably my fault.
Pull out, pull out.
Let's pull out, that's it.
Straight,
straight, straight...
Straighten it up. In you go.
ALL: Oh!
DR. AITKEN: You're not gonna do it.
That's not gonna go through.
DIANA: Right.
Whose fault's this, then?
ROBIN: I think we're
going to struggle here.
Sorry, I didn't know I was
supposed to measure the doors.
It's the wheels
that are the problem.
COLIN: Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Good idea.
HARRY: Drag him back.
Listen, listen, listen.
DIANA: What?
We're gonna have to take
the inner door frame off.
Oh, well done, Clem.
Clem's done it,
Clem's done it.
(WOOD CRACKS)
(ALL GASP)
Clem's bloody done it.
HARRY: Clem,
that is looking good.
(PEOPLE SHUSHING)
Quick. Go, go.
DR. AITKEN: Get him in,
get him in, get him in.
Sorry.
HARRY: Go on.
(DIANA SHUSHING)
BLOGGS: Brilliant.
(DR. AITKEN SPEAKING GERMAN)
(IN ENGLISH) I want you
to see this, Robin.
Let me go in first.
You may give them
something of a shock.
Dr. Aitken?
Yes.
It's an honor.
Erik Langdorf.
I'm the Director.
Aha! My associates.
I have heard so much about your
care for the severely disabled.
This hospital is famous.
Please.
Such excellent
modern machinery.
And everything so clean.
The chair has a respirator?
Mmm-hmm.
(BOTH SPEAKING GERMAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Sorry,
but he must leave.
Of course.
How stupid of me.
Please understand.
We are Department of the
Bundesministerium des Innern.
If anything were to happen...
The Ministry of
the Interior?
Yes.
Like our Home Office?
Don't they run
the prisons, too?
I believe so, yes.
Thank you so much,
Dr. Langdorf,
for giving us so much
of your time.
May I begin by noting
an interesting fact.
At this conference
on Managing The Lives
Of The Severely Disabled,
there are no
disabled people present.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Dr. Aitken, forgive me,
but the severely disabled
are on life-support machines.
So how could
they be present?
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
Well, allow me to introduce
Mr. Robin Cavendish.
All right...
If I put that there, is it going to work?
Yeah, well done.
Robin, you have a question
to ask our hosts.
ROBIN: Yes, I do.
Why do you keep your
disabled people in prisons?
In prisons?
No. No.
We have some of
the finest facilities
in the world for
the severely disabled.
I know, but they're
run by prison guards.
No, not at all.
Well, patients are kept
out of sight.
Not treated as part
of healthy society.
I must ask
that you withdraw that.
Mr. Cavendish doesn't mean
to cause offense.
He's merely suggesting
that the severely disabled
can be better integrated
into society.
Absolutely. I can see
that you all care
very deeply about your disabled people.
I see that.
But let me ask you,
when you look at me,
what is it that you see?
Do you see a creature
that's barely alive?
Or do you see a man
that's escaped the confines
of the hospital walls?
Now, I have a machine
under this very seat
that breathes for me.
And at home, I have a
ventilator right by my bed.
I also have a remarkable
group of friends.
And, most vitally,
I have my wife.
But, as you see,
I can do nothing for myself.
And yet here I am.
Now, when I first became
paralyzed, I wanted to die.
Yeah, I wanted to die.
I did.
But my wife wouldn't let me.
She told me I had to live.
To see our son grow up.
So I went on living
because she told me to.
Because of her, really,
and with her and for her.
And every day since then,
I've accepted
the risk of dying
because I don't want
to just survive.
I want to truly live.
So I implore you,
go back to your hospitals,
and you tell
your disabled patients
that they too
can truly live.
You all have this power
to open the gates
and set them free.
(CHEERING)
DIANA: Jonathan!
Jonathan!
Help me turn him
on his side.
Jonathan. Help me turn him
(GRUNTING)
That's it.
All right, love.
All right, darling.
It's all right.
All right, we can put him
on his back now. That's it.
All right, darling.
Robin?
Do what you can to clean
up the mess, darling.
ROBIN: It's all right.
It's all right.
It's all right, dear boy.
I'm afraid this is
what happens
after a number of years
on a respirator.
The lining of the lungs
becomes irritated.
You get small abrasions.
You get bleeding.
The fact is,
it's gonna get worse.
More bleeds.
Bigger bleeds.
And... Well, the risk is
you drown in your own blood.
(PEELING APPLES)
ROBIN: Remember that story
in Kenya about
Mau Mau prisoners?
Yes.
Ah...
Their leader said,
"I give my men
permission to die."
And then by morning,
they just all passed away.
And I have decided
it's time for me, too.
I'm going to let myself go.
And what about me?
You're going to be free
at last.
I don't want...
No.
God, you're a stupid,
stupid man.
What do you think I've been
doing all these years?
Hmm?
Your life is my life.
And...
I'm sorry, Jonathan.
ROBIN: Jonathan.
You should let her be.
(DIANA YELLS)
All right. Fine.
Fine, have it your way.
You always do.
But don't you ever, ever say
that you did it for me.
You do know
that it's against the law.
Well, yes, but who's
going to know?
Well, if Diana or Jonathan
were to get involved,
could end up in prison.
They're not
going to be involved.
And what about you?
(SCOFFS) Me.
I've been breaking the rules
my whole life. (CHUCKLES)
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SIGHS)
So promise me you know
what you're asking.
Oh, yes, I know
what I'm asking.
We must buck him up.
You know, get him out
of this morbid frame of mind.
(SPOONS CLATTERING)
(WATER RUNNING)
Make him see how much
his friends need him.
Colin. We're not going to keep Robin
alive for the sake of his friends.
(SIGHS)
No, of course not.
But I expect they'd
like to say goodbye.
Oh...
Hi.
Toby.
He's telling everyone
it's his leaving party.
What, even the girls?
Trevor.
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(APPLAUSE)
JONATHAN: Watch the steps.
Drop coming up.
(ALL CHEERING)
You're planning
another great escape.
Uh... It's time to go.
For me, anyway.
PADDY: Just like
the last time.
Not waiting for your friends.
No, you're too slow
for me, Paddy.
(SIGHS)
You owe me £5.
Ah...
(CHUCKLES)
(GLASS CLINKS)
Well, this is
a Saint-Émilion '59.
My last bottle of one of the
greatest wines ever made.
Jonathan, glasses, hmm?
Teddy.
Robin.
Harry.
We've been friends
for many, many years.
I'd just like to say...
(GRUNTING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Harry.
I broke a chair.
No, you didn't. You didn't.
You didn't.
Give him a drop of that.
COLIN: This'll sort you out.
This'll put hairs
on your chest.
Robin, old man,
here's to you.
I'm drinking to each
and every one of you.
MAN: Cheers, Robin.
HARRY: Cheers, old boy.
BLOGGS AND DAVID: (SINGING)
Goodbye-ee
Wipe the tear,
baby dear, from your eye-ee
Though it's hard to part,
I know
I'll be tickled to death
to go
Don't cry-ee
(SINGING ALONG) Don't sigh-ee
There's a silver lining
in the sky-ee
Bonsoir, old thing
Cheerio, chin-chin
Napoo, toodle-oo, goodbye-ee
(ALL CH EERING)
(BLOGGS CH UCKLING)
(DAVID CHUCKLES TEARFULLY)
There's something
I have to say.
(CHUCKLES)
I want you to know what a
difference you've made to my life.
It's not always been
easy for me.
Every time I come here,
I go away stronger.
And it's not because
you're worse off than me.
No, no, no.
It's who you are, Robin.
Or who you've turned yourself into.
God knows how.
Thank you, Col.
I'm gonna miss you.
Robin.
I'm sorry.
Darling.
That's enough.
Yes.
I expect
you know this, but,
just in case...
No one could have loved you
as much as I've loved you.
I know.
My love.
And my life.
Me, too, Robin.
My love.
My life.
(LINE RINGING)
(RECEIVER CLICKS)
Clem.
DR. AITKEN: Hello, Robin.
It's time.
All right.
When?
Today.
Now.
I'll be with you at 11:30.
(LAUGHS)
It's like a military op, eh?
You can count on me.
Synchronize watches.
I'll be there.
Thank you, Clem.
See you soon.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
Get Jonathan.
Jonathan.
I need you both to listen
very, very carefully.
Just before 11:30,
you're to leave the house.
And you're to come back
at 12:00 on the button.
DIANA: Okay.
Promise me
I'll have time to say goodbye.
ROBIN: Yes, there'll be time.
Hello. I haven't
seen you in a while.
So what can I get you all today?
JONATHAN:
I'm fine, thanks. Mum?
I'm still here.
You go first, Jonathan.
Bye, Dad.
I love you.
My own son.
My boy.
You have given me
more than you can ever know.
Now, I don't have
a farewell speech.
You don't mind, do you?
No.
You've given me
a wonderful life.
It wasn't quite
what you expected.
(CHUCKLES) No.
No, nor me.
Thank you.
For choosing to live.
(INAUDIBLE)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)