Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
Coney Island, 1950s.
The beach, the boardwalk.
Once a luminous jewel, but
growing relentlessly seedier
as the tides roll in and out.
Summers, I work here
on Bay Seven.
Comes the fall, I'm a student
at New York University,
going for my master's
in European Drama.
I'm Mickey Ruben.
Poetic by nature.
I harbor dreams
of being a writer,
a writer of truly great plays,
so I can one day
surprise everyone
and turn out
a profound masterpiece.
Anyhow...
...let me get to the story.
In which I am a character,
so be warned,
as a poet, I use symbols,
and as a budding dramatist,
I relish melodrama
and larger-than-life characters.
Enter Carolina.
Okay, have fun.
Yep.
Excuse me.
Where's Humpty Jablon?
Does he work here?
Uh, Humpty works the carousel,
but today he's working nights.
Do you know
where he lives?
Um, ah, it's around here.
- You can ask Ginny.
- Ginny?
Yeah, his... his wife.
Um, she works
at Ruby's Clam House.
Uh, you just keep
going down that way there.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah, you have a good one.
- Hey, Charlie.
- Oh, hey.
Excuse me.
Do you know if Ginny's here?
- Yeah, I'm Ginny.
- I'm Carolina.
- Who?
- Carolina, Humpty's daughter.
Jesus.
Is he gonna be surprised.
I know he's gonna be upset,
but I had to come here.
I didn't want to,
but I don't have a choice.
I'll tell you the truth.
I don't think
he ever expected this.
You're his wife?
Why are you looking at me?
You're much younger
than I would have imagined.
- Really?
- Mm.
Oh, I don't feel
much younger.
I was thinking
of my mother.
When she died,
she was practically...
...all gray.
I look like her.
Humpty should be back
in half an hour.
He went fishing off the pier
at Sheepshead Bay.
I'd always heard that
he moved to New Jersey.
No, we got thrown out
of our place there.
- Oh.
- Well, I'm not telling you
anything new
about your father.
He fell off the wagon
and busted up the lobby.
I guess you're used
to all this noise.
You never
get used to it.
I hate it.
This whole honkytonk fairyland.
We live up here.
Over here, folks!
Place used to house
a freak show.
Humpty had to do
a lot of fixing up.
Oh, God.
I hope when he sees me
- he doesn't fly off the handle.
- No, I don't think it's...
I hope he doesn't throw me out.
I-I don't know what I'll do.
I don't have
a dime to my name.
I literally
don't have ten pennies.
Come on up
and play Skin the Wire.
Hottest game on the boardwalk.
This, this, this goddamn noise.
I tell you.
You never get used to it.
Ugh, my head's throbbing.
And my, my kid, my kid had
some trouble in school today...
You and my father
have a child?
No, from my first husband.
Don't ever have kids.
Now my head's cracking open.
I get migraines.
If you don't like Coney Island,
why don't you move?
From your mouth to God's ears.
Money, honey.
Mazuma.
The wherewithal.
Ginny!
Ginny, big score.
Fluke, flounder,
some, uh, blue claws.
No.
No. What the hell
you doin' here?
I told you never to step foot
in my home again.
I'm in serious trouble.
I couldn't help it.
You let her in here?
Christ!
I don't believe this.
Can you just go?
Come on, go.
I can't.
If they find me,
they're gonna kill me.
You better hear her out, Humpty.
Mind your own business.
I got a bad headache
and Richie did it again.
You were supposed
to talk to him.
I talked to him.
Frank's gonna kill me.
I ran away and I-I took nothing.
I-I have no clothes,
I've been sleeping in the rain,
and I'm marked.
They're gonna kill me.
Well, that's what you get
when you marry a gangster.
Jesus, they're not gonna
come after you here, are they?
I don't like trouble.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
- They're gonna kill me.
- There's a young kid here.
- This is not our problem.
- All right, all right,
all right, knock it off.
- I-I gotta have a drink.
- No, Humpty, you've been good.
I need one.
Look what's going on here.
No booze.
I'll make you coffee.
Goddamn it.
What the hell
do you expect to happen
when you marry
a cheap hoodlum?
I was 20.
I didn't know better.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you
go to the police?
I told the police too much.
That's the problem.
Why the hell
you open your mouth?
The police told me that
I could be looking at five years
if I didn't cooperate.
Well, what the hell do you know?
Since when do you know
what happens inside the rackets?
How could I not know?
You can't be married
to one of those guys
and not pick up
on what's going on.
Jesus Christ!
I told you not to marry
that racketeer!
I told you he was all mobbed up!
He stank of murder!
She found this,
this greaseball exciting!
He wasn't even good lookin'!
He was a punk!
- I need a drink!
- Forget it, Humpty.
I need one, goddamn it!
Calm down.
Jesus Christ.
Goddamn it, she could have
married a few guys from school,
from the neighborhood.
All of 'em.
Decent kids.
We raised her nice.
Your mother and I,
we broke our backs off working
so you could go to college,
and, you know, you didn't.
You threw it all away.
Well, come on,
you're such a beautiful girl.
You...
You had your pick.
I loved Frank, okay?
And all the guys
you handpicked for me,
they were dull, colorless,
boring guys.
All of 'em honest men.
Every one of 'em.
Christ!
Your mother's
last dying request...
...on her deathbed
was that you didn't run off
with that slime Frankie Adato.
You wouldn't give her that one
bit of satisfaction, would you?
You wouldn't let her
die in peace.
I loved him.
I was 20.
I-I wanted more.
"More."
More.
More what?
Oh, Jesus, Humpty.
There's a world out there.
This does not concern you.
All I know is,
you lost your head.
Your head was in the clouds
over that gutter guinea,
that flashy, cheap,
flashy little wop.
You didn't think
I knew he carried a gun up here?
- Huh?
- He'll know...
He'll know you came here.
No, it's the last place
he'll look.
He knows how you feel about me.
Yeah.
You mean he knows
how much you hated me
for calling it the way I saw it.
Christ.
I counted on you when she died.
I was lost.
You dumped me for that trash.
That's why he wouldn't think
I'd come here.
He knows that we haven't
exchanged words in five years,
that the bad blood between us
ran too deep.
If he shows up here,
I'll kill him.
Oh, God,
don't say that.
- I don't, I don't want trouble.
- All right.
Okay, my nerves are shot
as it is...
- Um...
- ...and you better calm down.
All right.
Just don't tell me
what I should or shouldn't do.
She's my daughter.
Christ.
You were a light, baby.
You were a light in my life.
Do you know
how much I missed you?
Huh?
Jesus!
Suddenly I'm starvin'.
Clean the fish, Ginny.
Yeah, yeah,
I'll make everybody stew.
Yeah, you know,
eh, cooking relaxes my nerves.
Clean the fish?
I got a headache.
Clean the fish, Ginny,
two or three at least,
and put paper down this time.
Last time you got guts
all over the floor.
Hey, you remember, Carolina?
Remember I used to bake?
I used to make you
those chocolate chip cookies?
Mm.
And I'd put
a little salt on it.
You're late.
And you're in real trouble.
You know, you could
kill somebody starting fires.
What kind of craziness is that?
Hey, listen to me.
You could hurt someone.
Well, where'd you get
this idea to make fires?
Jesus, Humpty.
You sound so happy tonight.
What happened?
Your number come in?
Better than
my number came in.
My ship came home.
All right, well, have a good
night at the merry-go-round.
All right, you too, man.
- Smile!
- Oh, that's it.
- Hi, honey.
- Hold on there.
Okay, son, smile.
Oh!
How long's she gonna stay here?
I don't know.
Hey, maybe you can get her a job
at that clam joint
you're working at.
You think that's a good idea?
You said they were
looking for a second waitress.
But they're after her.
Shouldn't she move on?
Move where?
I don't know,
maybe out of the country.
Mexico?
What, are you nuts?
What the hell's
she gonna do in Mexico?
Ah, they're not
coming back here.
She's right.
He knows how we feel
about each other.
Well, we did.
Different now.
Cloud's been lifted.
I don't want guys comin' around
causing trouble.
- There's a kid here.
- Ah, it's okay,
as long as he doesn't
burn himself or kill somebody
with those goddamn fires of his.
He's a moody kid.
He's got a moody mother.
What's that supposed to mean?
Jesus Christ,
I can't believe Carolina's
gonna wind up a waitress.
Thank God Shirley's
in her grave.
What about me
winding up a waitress?
It's not what I had
in mind either.
Hey...
you wanna go fishin'
Friday night?
The boys are bringing the wives.
I don't go fishin', Humpty.
How many times
we have to go over this?
You, you don't like fishin',
you don't like boatin',
you don't like, bowlin'.
What the hell do you like?
You like the radio
and the movie stars, right?
Readin' those goddamn
movie magazines all the time.
I'm worried about Richie.
Yeah, well, let me tell you
something about your son.
He's gonna burn down somethin'.
There you are.
Knew I'd find you here.
- Why aren't you in school?
- I wanna see this picture.
- It's the last day.
- You can't not go to school.
Jesus, Richie, that's why
you're in summer school.
'Cause you missed so many days.
They called again and asked,
- "Is he sick?"
- I don't like school.
It doesn't matter
if you don't like it.
You know, I don't like
waiting on tables,
but we need to eat
and pay the rent.
Some things in life
you have to do
- whether you like it or not.
- Let me watch the picture.
Where'd you get the money
for the movies anyhow?
I took 50 cents out of Humpty's
pants when he was asleep.
What?
You steal from your father?
He's not my father
and I hate him.
Don't you dare say that.
You know, he saved my life.
He's... you know, he's...
he's a good person.
Then why does he hit you?
He doesn't hit me.
Hmm.
Yeah, when he gets drunk
he hits everybody,
but he... he hardly drinks
anymore.
Look, I can't sit here
arguing with you.
I have to go to work.
Go to school, okay?
If I catch you
playing with matches...
Yes, it's a problem.
Kid makes fires.
And not such little ones.
He played hooky
from summer school
and even made fires
on the beach
where it's forbidden.
What the hell does the kid see
when he just stares
into the flames.
Is it the eternal power
of the universe?
The conversion
of mass into energy?
The Furies at work?
Whatever his motive,
it is not appreciated.
Hey!
But what's the conditional?
Oh...
Jesus, Richie,
I c... I can't remember.
I went to school years ago.
God, if you,
if you'd pay attention in class.
You hated school.
What?
No, I didn't.
I liked it.
I liked school.
But I had to quit.
We were poor.
You know, I had to work.
I was lucky.
I-I had some talent.
You know, I-I was a...
I was a...
I was a very promising
young actress.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, if you coulda seen me
in some of those shows.
Let me show you
a couple of pieces,
- but this is, this...
- Again?
...this is from Dulcy, okay?
You know, I know
I showed you these pieces,
but I never know
if you're paying any attention.
I wore this in Dulcy.
Look at that.
Though it's not real,
but, you know.
- I've seen it.
- Isn't it beautiful?
God, look at that.
It's...
Let me show you this, uh...
Wait, did I show you the,
uh, the piece from the musical?
- Yes.
- From Oh, Kay?
I don't know if I did.
I had an incredible voice.
You know, I almost got
the lead in that show,
and the, the girl
who got the part...
She was fat.
And I had a much better voice
than her.
Is that where you met Dad?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, your real father
was a drummer.
He played jazz music.
God, he had perfect rhythm.
Ah, it was quite amazing.
And he also had black hair
and he had...
...he had green eyes.
Where is my father?
My real father?
I told you many times.
Gone.
A rainy day at the beach.
Time off for me.
Nobody swims
during a lightning storm.
I guess this is as good a time
as any to tell you,
I'm having an affair with Ginny,
Humpty's wife.
Let me fill you in on that.
It started at the beginning
of the summer.
At that point I didn't know
either Humpty or Ginny.
And then,
at the end of a cloudy day,
it started to rain,
and the last few stragglers
were packing up
and leaving the beach.
And suddenly this
kind of interesting woman
comes walking along
the water's edge,
and the dramatist in me sensed
she was in
some kind of trouble
because her body language
read vulnerable
and desperate.
Miss.
You can't be out here
right now.
Everybody has to go in.
We're expecting
lightning storms.
- What?
- We gotta,
we gotta go in.
We gotta clear the beach.
- Really?
- Yeah, we gotta go in.
Yeah, I-I been
all over the world.
I went to NYU and...
...right when I started,
boom, the Japs hit Pearl Harbor.
So after I got out,
I went back to school,
and now I'm working
to get my master's.
But I-I don't resent
my years in the Navy.
I mean, I really saw the world.
You ever travel?
Not really.
No place magical.
You wanna know the best place
I ever saw?
Where's that?
Bora Bora.
I heard of it.
It's over by Tahiti
where Gauguin ran away to paint.
The water there...
...is so clear and unspoiled.
You can look down and see
all the bright colored fish,
bright red and yellow fish.
And, and the flowers
are amazing.
And at night,
you never saw stars like that
on this planet.
You can actually read
by starlight.
What're you gonna write?
Plays about human life.
Great tragic plays
where the protagonist
gets crushed
because of some fatal weakness.
Like what?
My tragic flaw is
I'm too romantic a character.
You ever hear that song,
"I Fall in Love Too Easily"?
You always...
...think a person's tragedy
is their own fault?
No.
Fate plays a big role.
More stuff in life
is out of our control
than we'd like to admit.
Except...
I brought my troubles on myself.
Yeah.
I guessed that when I saw you.
I thought,
"She's very pretty,
but somewhere
there's a tragic flaw."
Yeah, I made a mistake.
But that was years ago.
I'll never make that
mistake again.
Yes?
I have to go.
Hey...
...you think you'll make it down
to the beach again soon?
Yeah, I might.
I might.
Where'd you go today?
Came home late.
Took a walk
on the beach.
That's unlike you.
I was in a funny mood.
Hey, you wanna go
to Yankee Stadium Sunday?
It's the Red Sox.
It's not me, Humpty.
For the millionth time,
I don't care about baseball.
But you used to go.
Well, I tried to get interested
for your sake.
I couldn't do it.
You wanna go?
I got an extra ticket.
I wanna go to the movies.
You know what?
You're gonna hurt your eyes
in so many movies.
Your just like your mother.
She listens to that crap
on the radio,
she thinks it's real.
I wanna be honest with you,
Mickey.
I'm married.
I'm a married woman.
I wanna be honest with you,
Mickey.
I'm a married woman.
I'm married, Mickey.
I felt strange mentioning it.
Not that you asked.
I got myself
into a bad situation.
I got myself... I got myself
You're right.
I had...
I had notions
about ending everything.
Thought about drowning.
Of course, with a kid,
that's not an option.
Besides...
...you'd have dived in
and ruined my dramatic finale.
I feel trapped.
Ginny did come back
to the beach.
And she looked sexy.
And I knew a spot
on the far end of the boardwalk.
I have something
to tell you.
Two things to tell.
Nothing you could tell me
could put the slightest shadow
on this evening.
I'm not 35.
I'm 38.
I'm 39.
Ah, that's a very hot age
for a woman.
I'm a very lucky guy.
I'm old... older than you.
What's the second thing?
I'm married.
You are?
I have a husband
and a child
from my first marriage.
You thought, uh...
you thought it would
spoil everything, right?
Has it?
It's not the first time I've
found a married woman beautiful.
I ruined my life by...
by being unfaithful once,
and now I'm doing it again.
You brought about
your own downfall
by being unfaithful?
It was someone I loved.
A drummer.
Whose rhythm pulsated with life.
And we married and had a child,
and...
...he adored me.
And yet...
Oh, and yet I c...
...couldn't resist the beautiful
young man in the cast
who played Marchbanks.
God, he wasn't even
the leading man,
but he, but he kissed me onstage
every night
and I started looking forward
to those kisses,
and... and, um...
I wound up in his bed,
and...
and then my husband found out
and it crushed him.
Oh, he deserved
so much better than me.
I-I broke his heart.
Humiliated, he ran away.
I didn't blame him for going
as far from me as he could,
and when he left...
I learned for the first time
what love was.
But I was too late
because he was gone.
And I started coming apart.
Oh, I-I couldn't act anymore.
I couldn't keep my mind
on my role.
I...
I-I'd forget my lines,
miss my cues,
and I drank,
and I lost work.
And Harold...
...Humpty,
who was also a lost soul,
met me at a diner and thought
I was the prettiest thing,
the belle of the ball, and...
...and we helped one another
scramble back onto our feet,
and it's been five years,
and...
...and I owe him a lot.
But just as I learned
from my first husband
what love was...
...I... I learned from Humpty
what it was not.
It's not gratitude.
It's not company.
And it's not going through
the motions of lovemaking
when... you have so much to give.
And no one
you really wanna give it to.
And so it was
a pretty intense summer,
and not just the humidity.
I was involved
in a relationship
with an older, ex-actress,
unhappily married,
and love starved.
She made up
one lie after another
to filch time to see me.
I've never been
to Greenwich Village.
It's got a lot of meaning
for me.
All the artists and writers
I love hung out here,
and it's close to school.
All right.
Remember...
...it's nothing
but a rented hovel.
Wow.
Ah, it's cozy.
That's very tactful.
These beautiful gardens.
How do you find these places?
My fantasy is that...
is that you write a play
with a character in
it I could play.
"Making her triumphant return
to the stage,
Miss Virginia..."
- Virginia DeLorean.
Virginia DeLorean.
Not Ginny Jablon.
- Wow.
- "In tonight's performance,
the part of Juliet will be
played by Virginia DeLorean."
I love it.
That was your maiden name?
My real name was Westlake,
but, but I took DeLorean
as a, as a stage name.
- Hmm.
- God, all that summer stock
and hard work so I could afford
acting lessons
just so I could...
just so I could wind up
playing the part
of a waitress
in a clam house.
I am playing a part.
You know, it's not me.
It's not me.
You think, you think it's me?
- No, I...
- Oh, God.
I-I mean, I act it every day,
but I'm acting.
I'm not a waitress
in a clam house.
- There's more to me than that.
- I...
I mean, I'm just playing
the thankless role
of the waitress.
Hey, hey.
- Ginny, wh...
- I'm sorry.
I'm unraveling.
Promise me we'll come back here.
She had less trouble
slipping away
after Humpty's daughter
showed up
because he was so happy
to see Carolina back.
Guess which number
came in today?
Oh, which?
Mine.
300 bucks.
This is for your night school.
Good because
I have one picked out.
Good 'cause
I don't want you waitressing
all your goddamn life.
Hey, You Humpty?
- Yeah.
- Frank Adato says hello.
He's very upset because
his wife's gone missing,
and we're trying to find her.
Ah.
Since, uh,
she's your daughter,
we thought we'd
check with you.
Well, I haven't seen Carolina
in years.
We're not on good terms.
Frank must have told you that.
I haven't spoken to her
in five years.
I don't know.
I lost track of her
after she ran off
and got married.
- Uh-huh, really?
- Yeah.
Do me a favor.
I'm talking to you.
Stop working, all right?
You try California?
She always talked about living
in San Francisco or Los Angeles.
I don't know.
I wouldn't even recognize her.
We just thought maybe
she'd turn up here.
Yeah, well,
she wouldn't find me.
I moved three or four times
in five years.
I mean, how the hell'd
you find me?
Frank's very worried about her.
Well, she'll never turn up here,
and if she does,
I'll tell her Frank's
looking for her, all right?
Hey, Humpty.
Did you hit him again?
I told you.
I told you next time I catch him
taking money out of my pocket...
And I told you
not to hit him.
All right.
We'll talk about it later.
I'm talking
to these gentlemen here.
Go home.
We'll discuss it later.
How do you do?
This is my wife.
Stepson.
Go on, go on home.
We're looking
for Carolina Adato.
- I told 'em.
- Humpty's daughter.
I told 'em.
I haven't seen her
in five years.
Yeah, yeah, he disowned her.
She'd never show her face
around her.
Let's go.
Is that a gun?
Sharp kid.
They're very dangerous.
You people would never
try to hide her, would you?
Hide her for what?
What'd she do?
You know,
you're a nice family.
I wouldn't like to see you
get into trouble.
Can I see the gun?
No, you can't.
Let's go, Richie.
See you later, Humpty.
Hey, what can I tell you?
She's not here.
Frank says there's bad blood
between 'em.
Maybe California's
a better idea,
and I'm startin' to think
we ain't gonna find her.
No.
I'm gonna find her.
Wanna get some oysters?
They probably got great oysters
in here.
Oh, I love oysters.
Eh, but do we got time?
Vinnie.
Christ, 5:00
we gotta meet him in Hoboken?
You know the way he gets
when we're late.
Come on.
God.
I coulda went for oysters.
Hey, John,
I need two beers.
Hey, what's your name?
Why?
What time do you get off?
I don't get off.
I go right to school.
Oh.
Night school?
- That's right.
- What are you studying?
To be an English teacher.
- Here you go, two beers.
- What time is class over?
- I got a lot of homework.
- Aw, I'm strikin' out here.
When do you graduate?
And so the angel
of death passed over them
and headed out west,
but his shadow was scary.
It took a few days
of summer sun to decompress.
Life on the boardwalk
provided the tourists
with cheap thrills
and great hot dogs.
When she wasn't
breaking dishes
or customer's hearts,
Carolina took
a limited program
at night school.
And when Humpty
wasn't trying to get riders
for those empty horses
on the carousel,
he was off chasing
fluke and flounder.
Your wife don't like to go
fishing anymore, Humpty.
Ah.
She never really liked it.
She made like she liked it...
...to get me on the hook.
I was the fish.
Careful, careful.
I used to hate the rain.
Now I love it
'cause it means
you get time off.
Oh, one of the perks
of being a lifeguard.
Yeah, now I see rain
through your eyes,
and it's beautiful.
You know, you'd go crazy
over Bora Bora.
The sunsets, the sunrises.
Paradise.
I'd go off with you
any place you asked me to.
You say your miserable
at home with Humpty.
W-w-why do you stay
with the guy?
Oh.
Me and Richie?
What a joke.
Waiting on tables,
trying to suck
nickel and dime tips
out of redneck clowns
wearing lobster bibs?
Yeah, I know.
It is pretty sleazy
what's happened
to Coney Island.
Hey, I don't wanna spoil
the rainy day.
Tell me about
the Chekhov play you read.
No, you tell me.
You ever play Chekhov?
I can't remember.
Maybe once in Baltimore.
When an actress got sick.
How's it coming?
Well...
I know he has feelings for me.
I-I know it's not
just a summer thing.
Oh, God, I hope
I'm not misreading it all.
I try to,
I try to push him
without being
one of those pushy women.
You know, I don... don't want
my desperation to show.
Well, there's progress,
but, but it's slow.
You know?
God, if the summer ends
and it fizzles out
and I'm left at square one,
I don't know what I'll do.
Well, you'll survive
like we all do.
No, no, I'm not
a strong person.
I wouldn't have survived
my breakdown
if it wasn't for Humpty.
Now I'm feeling claustrophobic,
- the headaches are back...
- You just have to be realistic.
In case things
don't go your way.
There's nothing realistic
about a Chinese garden
in the middle of Staten Island,
but...
but it's, it's where
I want to be with him.
How's Richie doing?
Richie?
Oh, I never know
what's on his mind.
I love your hair like this.
You look ten years younger.
- You think?
- Uh-huh.
Oh, I wish I had
your kind of hair.
- Hey, Ginny.
- The rainy weather kills me.
Oh.
- Oh, hi, hi.
- Hi.
Hi.
Um, this is Mickey.
- Hello.
- In case you never noticed,
he's the lifeguard
on Bay Seven.
- Oh.
- This is my husband's daughter.
- Carolina.
- I swim at Bay Seven sometimes.
- You do?
- Mm-hmm.
We have to go.
Just don't drown in Bay Seven
or they'll fire me.
- We, we should get going.
- Okay.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Cute.
- Do you like my hair?
Hmm?
Oh, yes, it's lovely.
Beautiful.
Hey,
I saw your daughter last night.
- She was with a soldier.
- Ah, Jesus Christ.
You put a uniform on a guy
and they lose their head.
- It's true.
- I saw her with a sailor.
She's a very patriotic girl.
Ah, well,
she's pretty, Humpty.
You gotta expect some trouble,
you know?
- That's right.
- Her mother was pretty.
And a saint.
This girl's got a high IQ.
Her mother saw the number.
I play the IQ number,
but it never comes in.
You know,
I'm sure she can handle herself.
She's been married.
She knows the score.
Yeah, he's right, you know.
Once a woman's divorced,
she's fair game, you know?
That's right.
I'm glad I got boys though.
She's goin' to night school.
She's gonna be
an English teacher.
Yeah, right,
if some soldier doesn't
- knock her up first.
- What the hell?
Come on, come on,
I'm just kidding!
Look, look how red he gets?
Look over at Humpty.
What kind of thing
is that to say?
She don't look like
any English teacher I in school.
Yeah, yeah,
what school did you go to?
You didn't go to school,
you idiot.
I went to
the school of hard knocks.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Remember me?
- Of course.
We met outside the movie theater
the other night.
- Yes.
- Oh, gosh.
Yes, with Ginny.
You said you sometimes use
Bay Seven.
Yes, I remember.
I was hoping to get some tan,
- but it's gotten so overcast.
- Yeah, storm clouds.
What is it?
- Hamlet and Oedipus...
- Yeah.
By Ernest Jones.
My goodness,
that sounds deep.
It's not that deep when you're
familiar with the total picture.
What total picture is that?
Well, Hamlet, of course.
I haven't read Hamlet
since high school.
But you've seen it performed.
Once.
And not very well.
I love the theater,
but I haven't seen
that many shows.
Ignorance is no sin.
It just means your experience
hasn't brought you into contact
- with certain things.
- Hmm.
Did you finish school?
No, I got sidetracked.
Yeah, me too.
Uncle Sam.
What's your story?
I got married too quickly.
But it's all over.
Wow.
Marriage is a big step,
isn't it?
- Mm.
- Scary.
What'd your husband do?
Shouldn't you be looking out
for drowning people?
No one ever drowns here,
but I should.
Yes.
Listen, I'm actually
through with this book,
so if you want,
you can borrow it,
and then when you're
finished with it
we can discuss it more fully.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I'd like that.
Yes.
You know who I ran into
yesterday at the beach?
The lifeguard, Mickey.
- You did?
- Yeah.
I was leaving and I noticed him,
so I said hello.
He was sitting up there reading
and he dropped down
and we talked.
He's very nice.
Yeah?
And he's well educated.
He's studying at college
to write plays.
- Uh-huh.
- I thought that
would interest you
since you acted.
And he had a book
about Hamlet,
a psychological study.
Uh-huh.
I haven't read Hamlet
for years,
and he tried not
to make me feel so dumb.
He was sweet.
- How long'd you chat?
- Five minutes.
I had to go home and shower
and dress for a date,
a nice guy from night school
took me to the movies.
Not that I'd like
to see him again.
That's, that's all you talked
about with Mickey?
Yeah.
Actually...
I kind of found him attractive.
- Did you?
- I'm probably reading into it,
but I think
he kind of liked me.
He said I could borrow his book
and we could talk about it.
That flounder was great.
You know, that's the beauty
of being able
to catch your supper fresh.
It's not just the money.
It's the flavor.
- Carolina.
- Uh-huh?
Connie Ryan and Leo
think you're a knockout.
Yeah, they kidded me
about seeing you
with that soldier.
- Oh, Rusty Ford.
- Mm-hmm.
No, he's a real hero.
He fought in Okinawa.
Hey, what am I, the hired help?
You ever think
of clearing your own stuff?
I'm sorry, I... every time I try,
you sit me back down.
That's because we can't afford
to have any more dishes broken,
but you could overrule me
and just be careful.
Oh, of course.
No, I'm happy to help.
I'd do the dishes,
but I just did my nails.
Well, I don't feel
like doing them tonight.
She just did her nails.
When you're married
to a man who got rich
putting people's feet in cement,
you probably never
had to do a dish.
I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- I got it.
Starring as the waitress.
- Something's eating her.
- It's my fault.
I should insist
on doing more around here.
- Well...
- No, she's right.
I'm not used to it,
and between work and studying,
I...
Listen, just get home early.
That's all.
Hey, was everything okay?
Yeah.
Why?
Well, you seemed
a little distracted.
Carolina told me you
ran into her at the beach.
Ran into her?
I nearly hit her in the head
with my book.
She said you lent it to her.
- Yeah, she was interested.
- You shouldn't read up there.
People trust you
with their lives.
So what'd you talk
to her about?
Nothing.
My book, Hamlet.
She said she quit school
to get married.
To a gangster.
Really?
- How interesting.
- You find that interesting?
They're after her.
They wanna kill her.
You better be careful.
I get the creeps
living with her.
- I wish she'd move on.
- She never mentioned it.
Well, she wouldn't.
She's embarrassed
by how she screwed up her life.
They want to find her
and kill her?
You, you must be exaggerating.
It's a long story.
She's a canary.
She sings.
That's terrible.
She's young.
She's pretty.
She should go where she's safe.
I asked you the other day
if she was pretty,
and you said, "Okay."
Eh, it was so quick.
I didn't really get a good look.
But at the beach
she had on a bathing suit.
Yeah.
Well, sort of.
You didn't get any ideas,
did you?
- What kind of ideas?
- What do you think?
Hey, will you give me a break?
What're you doing?
She's not for you.
She's hiding out here.
Her life's all topsy-turvy.
I was just chatting with her.
Well, I hope you didn't
say anything about us.
You know,
she'll tell her father.
That's what canaries do.
They sing.
Of course I'm not gonna do that.
What do you think, I'm a dope?
Let's get off this topic.
Hey, you were in my dream
last night.
Yeah?
What, I'm supposed to be
flattered you dream of me?
I rescued you in the dream.
Rescue me.
What can I tell you?
I'm not going to tell Ginny
my real feelings.
How could I?
But I was taken with Carolina.
Something hit me right off.
The more I talked with her,
the more I was intrigued by her.
I felt a buzz all day
after our encounter.
I'd like to see her again,
but, obviously,
I can't be honest with Ginny
about that.
The last thing I wanna do
is hurt Ginny.
Or wreck a good thing.
Ginny's a very emotional woman.
And how could I ever
explain things to Carolina?
That's all I need.
"Hey, I'm having an affair
with your stepmother
who's cheating with me
on your father."
It's best
to forget about Carolina.
A sweet dream,
but a dream.
But, as in a Greek play,
Ananke, or fate,
rules so much of our destinies.
First,
I accidentally drop my book,
just missing her head,
and now look what happens.
Oh.
- Carolina!
- Huh?
- Come on, get in!
- Oh.
Thank you.
God, I was getting soaked.
Let me buy you
a cup of coffee.
I can't.
I'll be late for work.
I'll get you as close
to the boardwalk as I can.
Okay.
I knew what was going on,
but you look the other way
when you're husband's hot stuff
and 6 million women
are after him,
but he wants you,
and it's all jewelry
and furs and Florida
and the racetrack,
and the Copa,
and the roulette wheel in Cuba.
It's...
Wow, you've really lived a life.
It was great.
Until it wasn't.
And then it was a lot of arguing
and getting pushed around.
What'd you,
uh, what'd you argue over?
Just sooner or later,
everything.
It sounds exciting,
but it's an unreal way to live.
I want a family,
and, and I wanted peace.
So eventually,
the whole thing blew up
and we split,
but the FBI got to me
and I...
I was all mixed up and scared
and I said things.
Because I know things.
So they hate me,
and, uh, they're scared.
I know where
all the bodies are buried.
Jesus, what a sheltered life
I have led.
I have book knowledge,
but you've really tasted life.
You've been around the world.
Yeah, but you've been
around the block.
You think you'll always
be looking over your shoulder?
Everybody dies.
You can't walk around
thinking about it.
You're talking to a lifeguard.
And hopefully with time,
things change.
I-I get paid to save people.
You know, you'd be safe
in a place like Venice
or... or Bora Bora.
That's where I'm headed.
I'm gonna be late.
I'm really flattered
you opened up to me.
You have a kind face.
And you have a beautiful face,
especially in this rain light.
Thank you for the lift.
I hope I didn't make you late.
No, it's okay.
I'm glad I took you up
on the ride.
Bye.
- You're late.
- I'm sorry.
I got caught in the storm.
I'll explain it all
to you later.
I want your input.
Well, I can't do
all the work here by myself.
I-I got a migraine,
wouldn't you know it.
Oh, it's the weather.
Well, get... but next time
get here on time.
I don't want to have
to cover for you.
I'm usually very punctual.
"Usually" doesn't do it.
This is a job.
I know you're not
used to schedules.
Lucky Tiny's not here.
Can I talk to you
later when you're not so...
- when you're feeling better?
- About what?
Just some advice
when you're not so stressed.
Would you stop doing that
with your fingers?
- It would... it would help.
- Oh, it's when I get excited.
Look, I'm... my head's throbbing,
I-I had to do six tables alone,
I broke my neck
for two fat ladies,
and don't you know,
they stiffed me.
Hey!
I am very sorry I'm late.
But I was shopping, and when
I came out it was raining,
and you may have forgotten,
but today is a special day,
and I wanted to get it
gift wrapped for you.
God, don't tell me
you got me a present.
How often do you turn 40?
It's a milestone!
It's a tombstone.
You're not getting it
till tonight.
Can we order some clams?
Uh, yeah.
Hey.
Yeah.
Hi.
You can sit wherever you'd like.
I can't believe it's my birthday
and we can't be together.
I know Humpty's
got something planned.
I don't need any present,
but I wouldn't mind dinner
someplace over candlelight.
You've got a birthday
coming up too.
I love that we're both Leos.
Leos are warm, generous,
protective,
beautiful.
Oh, God,
I'm, I'm not beautiful tonight.
- I got this...
- Here you go.
I got this migraine.
Can I get you
anything else?
I gotta go.
I love you, Mickey.
There you go.
I said it.
- I'm coming.
- I gotta go.
And we wish you
a happy birthday.
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Ginny.
And don't be depressed
over turning 40.
Hang onto it
because take it from me,
in a blink of an eye,
you're gonna be 50...
- That's true.
- You're gonna wish you were 40.
Come on, let me do it,
let me do it, let me do it.
Come on,
you already sung into it.
It's a tape recorder.
This is an unbelievable machine.
Yeah, yeah, well, you know,
I thought she'd like it
for her birthday.
I got a great buy
on that tape recorder.
- It's stolen.
- What do you mean "stolen"?
Ah, some bum stole it.
He was trying to sell it
on the boardwalk, you know.
Big spender.
Yeah, those guys will,
you know...
They'll do anything
to make money to buy a drink.
- So will I.
- Yeah.
I paid three bucks for it.
- $3?
- I mean, I couldn't afford
- a new one, right?
- That's a deal.
- I think so.
- That's a lot of fun,
- isn't it, Ginny?
- Oh, sure.
I wish I had
one of these things.
- It's great.
- What kind of birthday party
- is this with no booze?
- Oh, shut up, Ryan.
Hey, come on,
it's a party.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, wait, no, no.
If you're gonna sing, will you
at least get the words right?
Those are the right words.
"She loved the sailor
and he loved her too."
You know what?
I think it's time to go home.
- No, no.
- It's early, come on.
Now, you know what,
you should come out
on the boat on Saturday.
They're going for bluefish.
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Ah, she don't fish.
Well, neither do I,
but she can get a nice tan.
She don't do nothin'.
Come on, don't go.
Stay, stay. Come on.
Oh, look, it lights up
- when he's singing there.
- Isn't that nice?
Yeah, I love that.
Come on, wait.
Keep on going.
That's it.
Come on.
What do you mean, he was three?
Hi, are you okay?
Yeah, my head's cracking open.
I'm glad you liked the scarf.
It looks great on you.
Oh, thanks.
Jesus, are they ever
going home?
Ugh, my sixth aspirin.
Hey, what did you want
to ask me about?
Oh, it can wait.
I just wanted to get your advice
on something concerning Mickey.
- Mickey the lifeguard?
- Uh-huh.
But it can wait.
No, go ahead.
What about Mickey?
I ran into him today in the rain
and he gave me a lift.
He did?
Lucky me.
I would have been soaked.
Well, he just happened
to drive by?
Yeah, and we got
a chance to talk,
and I really think
there's something there.
Like what?
Well, he was very charming
and flirtatious.
And he liked hearing
all about me.
I must say,
I found him very appealing.
Hey.
What're youse doing?
Why don't you come join us?
Y-y-you can sing.
You know "April Showers," right?
- We're just talking, Dad.
- Oh.
Aw, baby, I didn't get a chance
to give you your birthday kiss.
Come on.
You know,
you're just as pretty today
as you were
when I first started dating you.
I'm a lucky guy.
Come on, join us.
We will.
What makes you think
he liked hearing your story?
Did he say anything?
He was clearly flirty.
- Yeah, it was obvious?
- Mm-hmm.
And we were sitting in the car
in the rain.
It was like being
in one of those love pictures.
Well, how far'd it go?
Did he take your hand
or anything?
No, we just talked,
and I told him all about Frank
and my marriage,
and he found the whole story
dramatic.
You opened up
to a guy you just met?
I know.
I...
I found myself
talking and talking.
Oh, it's funny.
I...
I felt very at ease with him.
Even when I first met him.
Well, did he become familiar?
I mean, did he try anything?
Did he take your hand?
He said I had a beautiful face
in the rain light.
Isn't that a nice phrase,
"The rain light"?
He's a poet.
Uh-huh, and did he
take your hand?
Christ, did he do anything?
Did he touch you?
Did, did he kiss you?
Why are you getting so heated?
Well, it's,
it's like pulling teeth.
God, between you and them
and my, my headache.
Well, I told you
that this could wait.
Just continue.
He didn't touch me.
I'm telling you because
I probably over-interpreted it
because I-I wanted him to.
But that's why I'm asking you.
Because you know the guy.
So, so what's he like?
He's a loose talker.
My advice is to watch yourself.
Yeah, he fills your head
full of lies, but he...
and his reputation
is that he's a phony.
Really?
But he, he didn't do anything?
I mean, he didn't kiss you?
- Unless you're not telling me.
- Why wouldn't I tell you?
Then I say forget him.
I happen to know
he's got a girlfriend
who he's in love with,
and maybe even plans to marry.
So my, my advice is,
is to keep away.
That's disappointing.
Well, honey, he'll,
he'll break your heart.
You know, is that what you want?
Are you sure?
Men can't be trusted.
I should talk.
My husband trusted me
and I...
I hurt him.
I wrecked him.
I'm not sure he didn't kill
himself in some hotel room
in, in Philadelphia.
I-I don't wanna know about it.
If he decides
to take 90 sleeping pills
or 85, I'm sup...
I'm supposed to...
supposed to blame myself.
Christ,
can they get the hell out?
Calm down, Ginny.
They're leaving.
I know him,
and I know him
well enough to know
you're not his type,
and he...
honey, he's taken.
He's not free.
Okay.
That's why I asked you.
Come here, Richie.
Come say good-bye.
- See you later, kiddo.
- Bye.
- It was great to see you.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- Ginny, Ginny!
- Bye.
Happy birthday.
I didn't mean
to bother you with this.
Why don't you lie down?
Just because you're
a pretty young girl,
who's been pampered
and chased after,
you think every man
is a pushover.
Why are you saying that?
- What did I do?
- Well, it's true isn't it?
Car and drivers.
You know,
winters in Palm Beach.
God, who you kidding.
Hello?
What?
This is his mother.
Where?
When? Today?
Well, was anybody hurt?
But nobody got burned
or anything?
N-no.
No, I-I work then.
Well, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, there,
there's no, no reason
to involve the police.
Yeah.
Yes.
I'll be there.
9:30, uh-huh.
Thank you.
Put away that goddamn machine!
What I do?
You know what you did!
You made a fire in the basement
of an apartment house!
What the hell were you doing
in the basement
of an apartment house?
Listen to me!
They were gonna call the police.
We have to be see
the principal tomorrow.
What is wrong with you?
Huh?
You wanna,
you wanna kill somebody?
You wanna burn yourself
to death?
Ah, Jesus,
I can't take this close living.
- What...
- Everything's coming apart.
- What, what's wrong?
- What's wrong
is one of these days he's
gonna kill someone with a fire.
- You did it again?
- Oh, God.
Where'd you get the sick habit
to make fires?
- Are you demented?
- You know what?
I swear, I catch you
with matches again,
I'm gonna beat your brains out,
and that goes
for your stealing too.
Okay, we're too crowded here,
and she's no help.
You know, you spoiled her,
her husband pampered her.
She's no good
in the restaurant.
Let her go to Mexico
where she's safe.
Oh, she's right.
I'll get out.
No.
No, you won't.
Where the hell you gonna go?
Business is off all over.
Come on, we're broke.
No, no, you're finally
going to school.
You stay here till you get
your feet on the ground,
and then you can go.
Look at...
She's not happy
waiting on tables,
and she's no good at it.
All right.
Let's do something
about the kid.
You know what
I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna take my strap off
and I'm gonna teach you a lesson
you're never gonna forget.
- Hey, don't you dare.
- He started the fire.
How did this get to be about me?
Why can't she find a job
somewhere else?
Get a room and split the rent
with some girl.
What're you... come on, she's...
she's trying to go to school.
She's trying to make a life,
all right?
She wants
to amount to something.
She's not gonna spend the rest
of her life waiting tables.
She's better than that.
It's 'cause
you're too close to her.
Honey, there's class
in this girl.
She made a mistake, all right?
And I swore
I'd never forgive her,
but it's not in my nature
to stay angry, honey.
And what about me?
Huh?
I don't wanna
be a waitress either!
There's more in me
than shucking oysters.
You're upset, baby.
All right?
Every birthday,
instead of celebrating,
you put on a long face.
Come on, honey.
Ah, God, what I really need
is a drink,
but I can't have it 'cause
you'll fall off the wagon.
Ugh, go to bed!
- Go to bed!
- Hey!
- Ugh.
- What the hell?
All right, here we go.
Hi, is the same time next
Thursday okay for you?
I work.
I'll have to call you.
- He may have to come alone.
- Oh, that's fine.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- How'd you like her?
- She was okay.
- Well, what'd she say?
- Nothing.
Well, I'm sure
she didn't say nothing.
- She asked a few questions.
- Like what?
- I don't know.
- Tell me.
I don't remember.
About my father and you
and Humpty.
And then what'd you say?
I don't remember.
Did you tell her I love you?
Did you tell her
I screwed up your life
by betraying your father?
Huh?
What'd she say to that?
She must have
a pretty low opinion of me.
I told her that it's your fault
my real father's gone.
Where'd you get that from?
You just said it.
You say it all the time.
I told her it makes you cry
and you think you hear drums.
Hey, humpty.
Humpty.
He, he has to see this doctor.
He has to see this doctor
once a week.
We need an extra $10 a week.
Don't look at me.
You see how business is.
Well, don't look
at me either.
- You have some money saved.
- What money?
Oh, God, plenty of money
from when you hit you number,
and since Carolina came,
you put away a few dollars
from your paycheck every week,
and you have some,
some money left
from selling the car.
Uh, listen, that,
that's for her school, okay?
- She earns money.
- What, Ruby's?
She makes peanuts.
Come on.
You, you got plenty
in that tin box,
and I-I need to pay
the psychiatrist.
I don't believe
in any of that crap.
You know, you just gotta
be stricter with him.
I-I've said it a dozen times.
I-I need some extra money, okay?
He, he needs help.
Well, for what?
What about my daughter?
All right, I'm not gonna
throw away her future
to pay for some
phony head doctor.
That's the biggest
goddamn racket.
What with the cigarettes?
I'm smoking.
Ginny, come on.
Coney's on the skids.
We don't raise enough to live.
Honey, honey,
I don't blame you for...
being moody.
I know you're moody.
Okay.
You know, I-I don't get it.
You're happy one minute
and then you get crazy.
You pick fights with Carolina
for no good goddamn reason.
She likes you.
Look at me.
Come on.
What happened to us, huh?
We used to talk
to each other more.
We used to go fishing together.
- What...
- Your problem is
you're wrapped up in Carolina.
I told you that.
You scrimp and save for her.
You take her fishing with you.
You get angry
if she goes on a date.
And face it, Humpty,
you treat her like a girlfriend.
You're gonna be crushed
when she dumps you again,
and she, she will dump you,
and move on.
You know what?
I cannot have
this conversation anymore.
You got a one-track mind,
and you've become insulting!
You remembered I loved it here.
Here.
Here's your present.
Happy birthday.
It's obviously a book.
Open it.
The Plays of Eugene O'Neill.
You'll like them.
They're dark.
And he really knew the score.
You know, human nature
and existence.
I once acted
in a play of his.
Which?
I know them all.
It was just summer stock.
They did, uh,
The Iceman Cometh.
I-I played
one of the whores.
What power.
To write a play
about the human condition,
the tragic human condition.
How we have to lie to ourselves
in order to live.
Anyhow,
happy 40th.
Carolina says
you were flirting with her.
Flirting?
I gave her a lift in the rain.
You don't have to lie.
She said you parked
and had a long talk.
A flirtatious talk.
Did she get the impression
that I was flirting?
Uh, Jesus, I mean, I was
fascinated by her story.
This girl's lived a lifetime
in her 26 years.
Did you make a pass at her?
A pass?
God, no.
I gave her a lift.
Did you tell her she had
a beautiful face
in the rain light?
I don't remember.
I-I may have,
but what's wrong
with a compliment?
You know she's a marked woman.
I-I do.
She told me her story.
It's chilling.
Would you like
to spend more time with her?
Why do you say that?
Well, that's
the impression she got.
Look, this is supposed
to be your birthday celebration,
and it's turning into
the third degree.
Can't you see I'm jealous?
Nothing's happened
to be jealous of.
I was hoping we might have
a future together.
Yes, I know.
I told you we'd talk about it
when the time comes.
If you told her
she had a beautiful face,
what the hell is,
is she supposed to think?
What the hell
am I supposed to think?
Hey, we were sitting in the car
on a rainy day.
That light would have
looked soft on any woman.
You know what?
This conversation
is starting to take
a crazy turn.
I've become consumed
with jealousy.
Can we start the day over?
I really hope you like
your birthday present.
O'Neill was a great one.
Great and terrifying.
Of course I felt terrible.
I needed
to talk the situation over
with someone
a lot sharper than me.
I called my friend Jake Jacoby
who's a graduate student
at City College
in the philosophy department.
It doesn't make sense because
you're not dealing with sense.
You're dealing with feelings.
Feelings, my friend,
it's a whole different
ball game.
The whole thing
is so irrational.
I've been seeing
this married woman all summer,
and she has these fantasies
of leaving her husband
and going away with me.
Her fondest wish would be
to divorce him and marry me.
And at times I see it
and at times I don't.
She's older than me,
and I like that.
Somehow it fits into
the romantic narrative
of the writer's life.
But she's more than that.
So, so, so,
why am I hesitant?
One minute I'm not sure,
the next I'm ready
to take charge of her life,
to rescue her.
Can, can this Carolina
be relied on?
After all, she, she did
run away with gangsters
because she was
a thrill-seeker.
You know, did, did,
did she learn her lesson?
She may give you
a period of bliss,
but will it sustain?
Will this other one be
a more solid fit for you?
When I hear you say it,
I think, "Yes, she would."
And, and Ginny's counting on me.
She's drowning.
And she'd be eternally grateful
for a lifeline.
And after all, you know,
a love so intense
as hers is for you
is a rare gift
to have bestowed on a man.
It's amazing
how lucid things become
when you get
an outside perspective.
At that moment, a fog lifted
and my choice was obvious.
Carolina was a lovely daydream,
but reality with all its pros
and cons belonged to Ginny.
All my silly schemes
to pursue Carolina seemed crazy,
and I made the decision to never
entertain that pipe dream again.
But, as Jake said, the heart
has its own hieroglyphics.
Maybe he was right.
Hi.
I came to tell you something.
- Oh, yeah?
- I thought of you yesterday.
I know you mentioned
that you loved pizza,
and somebody said he knew
the greatest pizza place
in Brooklyn,
and he took me there
and he was right.
I thought you'd want
to know about it.
- Your boyfriend took you?
- It's called Capri.
It's a few blocks from the
boardwalk, not far from here.
Will you let me take you there?
I'm kind of busy
with school all week.
Uh, is Friday night good?
Friday I can do.
And he's not my boyfriend.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
Do you still have it?
Yes, I do.
I've got the money.
- Here.
- Great.
Oh, wonderful.
Can you take it in the back
and engrave it?
Of course.
What do you want it to say?
I'm glad we could steal
these few minutes.
No one'll see us
this end of the boardwalk.
It's, it's so private.
I wanted to talk to you.
First, I wanna talk to you.
Okay.
Don't look so worried,
mine is a nice thing.
What?
Did you miss me?
Well, you've been so busy
with your son and his school.
Oh, God.
That's not what I asked you!
- Did you miss me?
- Jesus, Ginny, take it easy.
Well, you're always so evasive.
You never wanna
talk about anything.
Okay, okay, look, look, I don't
wanna get off to a bad start.
Remember last week
it was my birthday?
- Yes.
- Well, today is yours.
How'd you know?
You mentioned it.
Remember, we're both Leos?
I mentioned it ages ago.
What a memory.
What is that?
- I got you a present.
- No.
Here.
Oh, God.
Y-you, you can't do that.
- Why not?
- It's not right.
- You got me a gift.
- I know, but...
What the hell?
I got you a book.
This is...
It's much too expensive.
I can't accept this.
How would you know
it's so expensive?
I've inquired
about this watch.
- I was with you.
- Ginny...
Okay, this is a $500 watch.
But you always wanted
this watch.
Yes, but it's much
too extravagant.
- You can't afford this.
- That's my business.
And even if you could, it's much
too extravagant given...
Given what?
Given, given what?
It's too much to spend on me.
You shouldn't be
getting me jewelry.
Why not?
Is it too meaningful?
Oh, Christ, you inscribed it.
Yeah, read it.
Look...
we have to have a talk.
I thought you'd be excited.
It's too much,
and I can't accept this watch.
- Stop saying that!
- You can't be buying me
a $500 watch.
Look... why?
You, you're always saying
what a,
what a beautiful,
perfect summer it's been,
and, and...
It's not right
given the circumstances.
What circumstances?
What are the goddamn
circumstances?
Okay, you're ready
to get very serious,
and I'm just not ready.
Something's happened.
Some... something's happened.
Everything was, everything was
going so smoothly.
Something's gone wrong.
I don't want
to disappoint you.
Look, you, you said
you loved me.
Were you insincere?
- It's not that I wasn't trying.
- What?
Oh, Christ,
if you have to try...
- It's, it's not homework.
- I'm not saying
I don't have real feelings
for you.
Is it Carolina?
Jesus Christ,
I hardly know Carolina.
But you wanna get to know her,
and I should wait around
- while you could try her out?
- Hey, I didn't say that.
I didn't say that.
You're losing it.
You know what?
You don't want it...
...forget it.
Huh?
Forget it!
What the hell are you doing,
Ginny?
- Are you crazy?
- Don't talk to me!
All right, you little punk,
Give me back that money
or I'm gonna kill you.
Hey, wh-what's going on?
I didn't take his money.
Don't tell me you little thief,
you're always stealing from me.
He took 400 bucks
out of my tin box.
- I did not!
- You know what?
That's 400 bucks.
That's grand larceny.
You know,
I oughta bang it outta ya.
He didn't take it.
Don't, don't be tellin' me
he didn't take it.
You know, you're always
sticking up for him.
That's why he is the way he is.
Now you give me that money back.
- I took it.
- Don't make up a story.
I took the money,
not him.
You took it?
Yeah, I-I needed it
to pay for a psychiatrist
for him.
- What?
- That's right.
They're, they're a lot of money,
and, and he's been goin'
every few days.
I-I didn't want to tell you.
You took my savings
to pay for a head doctor?
- Look, he needs help.
- Yeah, you know what,
I was saving that money
for Carolina's school.
Well, she'll just have to put
some of her dreams on hold.
I got a call from his doctor
that he started a fire
in her waiting room.
Richie, is that so?
I don't wanna go back there.
You know what, you steal,
what kind of example is that?
- Jesus.
- Oh, God,
I can't handle this now.
Look, I'm, I'm late for work.
I am sick of waiting on tables,
and kicking in my salary
so that you can put away
your extra money for Carolina.
Oh, God,
now my head is pounding.
- So go take an aspirin.
- I don't want an aspirin.
- I want a scotch!
- Take an aspirin!
Je... so that's where
you've been hiding it?
I knew you had a stash,
and when I begged you
for a shot, you...
when I needed it,
you wouldn't give it to me,
- but when you need one, you...
- You're not allowed!
I knew you had a bottle.
I knew it.
Hi.
I'm late.
I'm such a scatterbrain.
I have a date
and I forgot my wallet.
Uh, I'm meeting Mickey
and I found
this great pizza place.
It's his birthday,
so I'm treating.
You're... what?
You're going with Mickey?
Don't look so stunned.
You introduced me to him,
remember?
If he breaks my heart,
you're to blame.
I know you warned me,
but...
...I think he likes me,
and is sincere.
Not that anything's
happened yet,
but I'm hoping
tonight's the night.
Yes.
I've gotta go.
- Bye.
- Don't come home late.
- What're you doing?
- I'm drinking.
What does it look like
I'm doing?
- Tiny?
- Yeah?
Uh, the... those two guys
that were just here...
Yeah, they were looking
for Carolina.
How'd they know she worked here?
- I don't know.
- Well, what'd you tell 'em?
Nothing, I hope.
They said they needed
to find her.
I know she's having dinner
with some guy tonight
at the Capri Pizzeria
up on Beach Walk.
Oh, God,
I hope you didn't say that.
Yeah, I did.
Why, did I do wrong?
- Something wrong?
- Oh, God.
I have to make a phone call
before they get there.
- Uh, phone's not...
- Capri, the Italian restaurant?
Yeah, yeah, it's
not working though, the phone.
What do you mean the phone's
not, not work...
I don't know,
all day long.
Oh, Jesus, I have to make,
make a phone call.
- You need a nickel?
- I have to make a phone call.
I-I have, have to make
an emergency call.
All right, miss.
I-I gotta call you back.
There's an emergency here.
Someone needs
to make a phone call.
All right, yeah.
No, I'll call you back.
Okay, thank you.
Yeah, I need the number
of a-a restaurant in Brooklyn
on Beach Walk
called Capri Pizzeria.
What?
- Capri, John speaking.
- Yeah, Capri?
Yeah, I-I need
to speak with a customer.
She has, she has,
uh, she has blo... blond...
Hello?
Capri.
Isn't it the best pizza
you've ever had in your life?
And I'm taking you.
I have something
I wanna tell you.
If only it wasn't
so fattening.
But, of course, you don't have
to worry about that.
A few things
that I wanna tell you.
Yes?
First...
I'm in love with you.
You'll think I'm very silly,
but I believe firmly
in love at first sight.
Maybe because I'm writer
and we over-romanticize,
but you just rang
some sort of a bell with me
the minute I laid eyes on you.
I don't know what to say.
I don't want you
to say anything.
I don't expect you
to say anything,
but I still wanted you to know.
I'm glad you feel that way.
Now I'm going
to tell you something
that you're going to have
complicated feelings about,
and you may not be so thrilled
to hear it,
but I have to be honest.
Hmm.
Why'd I suddenly get nervous?
I've been having an affair
with Ginny.
That's right.
She's very unhappily married
to your father,
and we met at the beach
and it began,
and while I like her very much,
and I've even tried to
convince myself that I love her,
but I'm just not
in love with her.
And she's looking for someone
to pull her out
of her unhappy marriage,
and it's never going to be me.
So I'm going to break with her
either way.
But I still
wanted you to know
the, the whole story.
This is gonna kill my father.
He's so dependent on her.
How...
...how awful for Ginny.
Oh, God, I...
I told her we were going
for dinner here tonight
and that I...
I hoped that you'd finally
tell me how you felt about me.
And I did.
I don't know
how to take all of this.
I'm sure you don't.
It just seems to go
from one drama to another.
Can we get the check?
- I'll get it.
- No, no, no, no.
No, it's,
uh, it's my treat.
Thank you.
Hey, my car's
just around the corner.
- I'll drop you off.
- I prefer to walk.
Okay, well, I'll walk with you.
No, I have
a lot of thinking to do.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, got it.
Um, I'll call you later.
And I'm, I'm sorry
if I upset you.
It's a lot to take in.
It's nice to know
you love me.
Yes?
You take out my daughter
last night?
Oh, you're Carolina's father.
I'm Mickey Ruben.
I'm happy to meet you.
Yeah, well, where is she?
Now?
Isn't she at work?
No, no, no, she didn't come in.
I already called.
She didn't come home
last night?
She didn't stay with you?
No, she went home.
Listen, you could
tell me the truth.
You know,
I'm kind of worried about her.
We had a pizza
at Capri Pizzeria,
and then we left.
We had a nice time.
I offered to drive her home,
and she said she wanted to walk.
I-I told your daughter
that I cared for her very much,
and she wanted time
to think things over.
- Wait, what do you mean she didn't come home?
- She didn't sleep at your place?
No, I'm telling you.
We split up after dinner.
I told her I'd call her.
You know,
I'm gonna call the police.
They're gonna wanna check
your place out, you know that.
Listen, she wasn't at my place.
I live in Greenwich Village.
They're free to check it out.
Which way did she go
when you split up?
She went over
toward the boardwalk,
and I walked around the block
to get my car.
If you're lying to me...
if you're lying to me,
you're gonna be in
a lot of trouble, you know that?
Take it easy.
I'm as alarmed as you are.
She tell you that these,
these guys are after her?
I know her whole story,
but, but she didn't walk around
as if she was worried about it,
and I didn't see anybody.
Where the hell is she?
What's the matter, Mom?
Nothing.
Then why are you drinking?
- This is my first.
- Third.
Can I go to the movies?
Picture at the Neptune changed.
Oh, yeah?
What's there?
Flying Down to Rio.
Oh, Rio de Janeiro?
That sounds pretty good,
doesn't it?
- Yeah, you wanna come?
- To Rio or to the movies?
I'd like to go to Rio.
And never come back.
They got her.
They got Carolina.
Somehow, they knew
where she was,
- and they snatched her.
- Why, why do you say that?
I knew it.
- Give me that.
- No, no, Humpty, no.
I'm not gonna argue with you.
You give me a hard time,
I'm gonna knock you through
the goddamn window.
- Give it to me.
- No, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, c-calm down.
I... no, no, they meant,
they meant to get her,
they meant to kill her,
and by now, she's probably dead.
No, wh... what are
you talking about?
You don't know anything.
Don't tell me I don't know
what I'm talking about.
I wasn't born yesterday.
They knew exactly where she was,
right down to the pizza joint.
I'm going to the movies.
Can I have 50 cents?
Goddamn it, here, here, here.
Take it! Take it!
Take it all!
Now you don't have to steal it.
I gave it to you.
Okay, okay, okay, well, did,
did you call the police?
- Ah, naturally!
- Well, they'll find her.
What the hell do you care?
You don't even like her.
- So...
- You hated her.
You were the one
who wanted her out.
- Stop it.
- No!
No, you, you were the one
making all the cracks
about how I'm too close to her.
You, you could have tipped 'em.
Well, I didn't,
so don't be crazy!
If you did, I will,
I will kill you.
Stop!
You're scaring me.
- Stop drinking!
- No, no, no.
Somehow, for some reason,
they knew, they knew.
- Why did they come back?
- Well, it wasn't me!
I'd never do that.
It's...
I wouldn't know who or how
if I w-wanted to.
What, what do you,
what do you mean?
What do you mean,
"if you wanted to"?
- I wa...
- Did you?
I'd never do such a thing.
Oh, God.
Leave me alone.
You're hurting me.
Ah, you're hurting me.
Ginny, I'm sorry.
I-I can't believe this.
- I'm going nuts.
- I-I...
She finally comes back
and now this.
God, I don't want
to be around you...
around you
when you're like this.
Ginny, no, no, don't...
stay here!
I don't wanna be alone.
I can't handle this without you.
I gotta get some air.
God, I'm choking.
Ginny, Ginny,
I can't believe this.
I can't believe she's gone.
W-well, do...
well, don't look at me.
Don't, don't,
don't stare at me.
You look funny.
- You're imagining it.
- Goddamn it!
I need another drink!
What're you doing here?
I came to speak to you.
Oh, well, yes,
but do you think it was wise
to show up at my door?
I mean, I do have a husband,
you know.
My God...
...I was not expecting anyone.
I must look like
the wreck of the Hesperus.
I thought about it,
but in the end
I decided
to come here.
Oh, if you're,
if you're gonna tell me that
you've made a terrible mistake
and thrown away a relationship
with a woman you now realize
loved you in a way
that you will probably
never experience again,
still...
it was reckless of you
to come to where I live.
It just so happens,
Humpty's out.
He's, uh... he, he got drunk
and he, he accused me
of unspeakable things.
I mean,
he's understandably distraught,
but, but he scares me.
He...
He scares me,
but I will say,
I told him many times.
"You're smothering that girl.
It's not healthy."
I mean, she's,
she's a grown woman.
She's a divorcee.
I-I mean, you'd think
she was 15 years old
the way he fussed over her
and hovered.
But, did she act strange
when you had dinner with her?
Because she is
a strange creature.
I w... I warned you about that.
I mean, for all we know...
you know, maybe she's
gone back to her husband
or decided maybe Mexico
is best for her.
But I did warn you
she was marked.
You cast me aside
for a marked woman,
and now I hope
you're not asking,
"Is it possible to just
take up where we left off?"
I mean, that's,
that's a little opportunistic,
wouldn't you say?
I mean, it kinda reads that way.
But when it comes to love,
we often turn out to be
our own worst enemy.
I suppose one of the advantages
of being a little older is that
we have more tolerance
for mistakes.
Because over the years,
we all have made our share.
That's... that's why forgiveness
is possible.
What a cold world
it would be without it.
I know the whole story, Ginny.
What story?
I know what it is you did.
I-I don't know
what you're referring to.
Oh, you've suddenly adopted
a supercilious tone of voice.
By now she's probably rubbed out
or dumped somewhere.
Oh, my God, this is awful.
"Rubbed out," "dumped."
My goodness.
Well, don't you think you're
being a little melodramatic?
I put it together.
I spoke to Humpty, to Tiny.
The phone at Ruby's
was out of order.
You used a payphone.
I spoke to John from Capri.
A woman called,
and then hung up.
I got it.
It doesn't take Sherlock Holmes
or, or Eugene O'Neill
to plot this one out.
A lifeguard can do it.
I don't know
what you're implying.
I'm not implying.
I'm accusing.
Accusing me?
You certainly don't
seem too concerned
- by her disappearance.
- How would you know?
What, because
I'm not a mass of hysteria?
Like her father who has
an unnatural attachment to her.
Plus, I think I should tell you,
I've had a few drinks.
I know I told you I never drink,
but...
when I'm under
severe emotional strain,
it's, you know,
it's just sometimes
the only thing that
keeps me head from throbbing.
You wanted her gone.
- Oh, please, you're delusional.
- No.
That you think that I could...
no, you know, I will...
I am not going to stand here
and have my character sullied
- by wild and fantastical insinuations.
- I didn't think you had it in you.
- What, that I-I lacked
sufficient stature?
You had time to warn her,
and you hung up the phone.
That I was too mediocre a person
to rise to a tragic action?
Honey, I don't know
what fanciful scenario
you're writing in your own mind,
but I suggest you get a grip
- on your imagination.
- I can't believe this.
You had time to warn her.
You hung up the phone.
Well...
...maybe in the end,
you misread my body language.
I mean, you said it wasn't
an exact science.
You know?
I loved her.
Jesus Christ!
You just met her!
Well, no, I forgot,
you're a dreamer
who believes in
love at first sight.
You know, when I think of it...
when I think of it, I could...
I could...
What?
And you, you,
you could live with this!
Huh?
Oh, God, spare me the bad drama.
Oh, here.
Here.
Why don't you kill me?
And avenge her, huh?
Isn't... isn't that
the way it happened
in the, uh, theater
in Athens?
What good are the police
if that's the job they do?
Police can't protect you.
You look a little crazy to me.
Why are you staring
at me like that?
- I'm fine.
- Staring at you like what?
Where'd you get the dress?
You're nuts.
You know, uh, uh, don't get
on my nerves, Ginny, okay?
I-I swear to God,
I will smash you.
I am not in the mood.
You... and you look
a little crazy to me.
Leave me alone.
G-Ginny, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ginny.
Don't ever leave me.
That's not what
you were thinkin', was it?
I was thinking Richie'll
be home from the movies soon.
He'll be hungry.
I don't believe what happened.
You gotta get me through this
like you did...
Like you did.
Y-y-you know, y-you gotta...
I gotta wash my uniform.
Talked to Connie Ryan.
They're goin' fishin' Labor Day.
You wanna go?
No.
I don't like fishing.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard