^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com
We have six members that were
found last night, in bed,
shot and killed.
NEWSCASTER :
In 1965, Ronald DeFeo moved his family
from Brooklyn into a beautiful three-story
home in Amityville, Long Island.
Envisioning a better life for themselves,
they even put a sign in front
of the house saying "High Hopes."
Then things went terribly wrong.
Rumors have been circulating
that there is something dark
and evil about the house...
that the house somehow drove
Ronny DeFeo to commit this grisly act.
(UPBEAT POP INTRO BEGINS)
Okay.
We're home.
(DOG WHIMPERS)
(FAINT SCRATCHING)
(WHIMPERING)
Larry, you little sneaky bastard.
How'd you even get in here?
(FLOORBOARD CREAKS)
Juliet?
You up here?
Hello?
(FLY BUZZING)
(HORN HONKS IN DISTANCE)
WOMAN  (DISTANT): Joanie. Hey.
Hi! You guys made it.
How was the ride on the way up?
- JOAN : Uh, you know what, it wasn't bad.
- WOMAN : So glad you guys are back in town.
JOAN :
Thank you so much for helping with all this.
WOMAN : What are sisters for?
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Uh, have you told them about...
No.
(CHUCKLES)
No, I just want us
to get settled in first. Okay.
Okay. I have everything set up the way
you wanted, if you want to check it out.
WOMAN : I set up an emergency
backup battery, just in case.
You never know with these old houses.
And...
you know we're only
five minutes down the road,
so you say the word if you need anything.
We'll be there.
JOAN : Thank you.
We've pretty much got
into a routine now, so...
WOMAN : Well, I'm glad you're here.
Everything's gonna be fine.
What did Dr. Milton say?
JOAN : Same as usual.
You know. I'm not gonna give up fighting.
WOMAN : Of course.
(LARRY WHIMPERS)
All right, everybody, dig in.
Aren't we gonna say grace?
You hate saying grace.
Never stopped you before.
(LARRY WHIMPERING)
Well, maybe I'm embracing a change.
I'll do it.
Dear Lord...
thank you for this food and for this house.
(BARKING)
And for keeping James safe and happy.
Amen.
Jules, how do you like your room?
Awesome.
It's got pink, purple, silver and gold.
All my favorite colors.
Did you get all your paperwork
done for tomorrow?
Yep.
How's it look? All right?
Yeah, it, um, it looks great.
Besides the fact that I have to move
to a completely new school and start
all over again in my senior year.
We all have to make sacrifices.
(BARKING)
Quiet, boy!
And what part of sacrifice
does this house fit into?
It's... it's three times
as big as our last one.
I told you, we got a deal.
Save a few bucks?
That's good to know.
JOAN : We moved here to be close
to my family, to Candice.
And St. Alcuin's has the best
neurological department in New York.
I want you to trust me, all right?
This house is gonna be good for James.
And that's all that matters.
Right now, yes, that's all that matters.
(LARRY BARKS)
We all need to rally around him.
That's the only way
he's gonna get through this.
Get through what, Mom?
I know James, okay?
I know him better than you do.
He's my twin... I can feel it.
He's not there.
Then whose fault is that?
James is gone, Mom.
That's enough!
(LARRY BARKING)
Belle?
Larry, come on.
(DOOR OPENS)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(WHIMPERS)
Yeah.
You still love me, don't you, Larry?
Even if you are stuck with that dumb name.
(FLIES BUZZING)
Come on.
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
I miss talking to you.
(WHISPERING): I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(CRYING SOFTLY)
(BUZZING)
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
- MAN : Let's go, people.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Hey, guys, this is Belle.
She just transferred here.
Have a seat and take notes.
We left off yesterday at page 38.
1862, the Civil War.
Battlefield medicine.
Clara Barton.
(WHISPERING):
Check out the lipstick on freaky girl.
She ended up starting the American Red Cross.
What she did was,
she taught mothers and daughters
to come out to the battlefield
- and take care of their sons.
- (WHISPERS): Hey.
- Brothers.
- It's not you.
TEACHER:
What she did was revolutionize medicine...
It's the house.
What house?
You know, 112 Ocean Avenue.
Ew, what are you?
Some kind of stalker?
What? No.
How do you know where I live?
Everyone knows where you live.
- Please, just...
- Hey, hey, hey.
It's your first day.
You might want to listen.
("WHEN THE SUN CAME DOWN"
BY ARTIFICIAL DARKNESS PLAYS)
(FLY BUZZING)
(BUZZING CONTINUES)
(LARRY BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(QUIET, EERIE WHISPERING): Kill... kill...
- (MONITOR BEEPING)
- Kill...
(QUIET, EERIE VOICES): Kill them all...
Kill... kill...
(MONITOR BEEPING)
(RUSTLING)
(WIND WHISTLING LIGHTLY)
(QUIET, EERIE VOICES): Kill... kill...
(GASPS) Oh, my God.
(PANTING) Juliet, you can't just...
...sneak up on people like that.
Sorry.
(DOOR CREAKING, MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
What are you doing up?
I just wanted to talk to James.
Doesn't James talk to you, Belle?
In a way, I guess.
Does he use bad words?
Why would you say that?
Okay, party animal.
It's sleepy time. Come here.
Oh, yes.
Come on.
Belle?
Yes?
How come Mommy doesn't love you anymore?
Who told you that?
(ALARM BEEPING ON MONITOR)
Go back to bed.
Go back to bed, girls.
You heard what Mommy said. Go back to bed.
(KISSES)
(IRREGULAR BEEPING)
- (BEEPING CONTINUES)
- James?
Okay, honey.
It's his heart.
Sweetheart, stay with us, okay?
Belle is here.
Mommy's here.
Good.
All right, sweetheart,
you're doing great.
Who's my brave boy?
(WHISPERING): He gonna be okay.
(BEEPING STEADILY)
All right, baby.
Now, okay, sweetie.
(IRREGULAR BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING INCREASES)
Baby?
I don't understand.
What's happening? Come on.
That's too fast.
(BEEPING INCREASING)
Come on.
Come on, don't do this. Come on, baby.
- (FLATLINE TONE)
- Shit.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, honey.
- (FLATLINE TONE CONTINUES)
- Come on.
Stay with me, James.
James... come on...
Mom.
It's over.
That's what you want, isn't it?
It's what God would want.
(STEADY BEEPING RESUMES)
Honey...
I'm never gonna stop fighting for you.
I'm so proud of you.
Come, sweetie.
Want to give him a kiss?
(KISSES)
- (GASPS)
- (JULIET SCREAMS)
(LARRY BARKING, GROWLING)
I knew you'd come back.
(SIGHS)
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
Juliet?
Who fixed you breakfast?
(GASPS)
BELLE : Shit.
Language, honey.
Do you want some granola?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
NEWSCASTER :
In 1965, Ronald DeFeo moved his family
from Brooklyn into
a beautiful three-story home
in Amityville, Long Island.
Then things went terribly wrong.
REPORTER :
Are you still questioning Ronald DeFeo?
No comment.
REPORTER 2 : Where is Mr. DeFeo?
REPORTER : What kind of a guy was Ron DeFeo?
MAN : Uh, he's a... he's...
Don't worry.
I'm just stalking you.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, um,
sorry about yesterday.
He didn't look for trouble.
You know, he was that type of fella.
You know, you're not
the first girl to mistake
my basic human decency for perviness.
You really didn't know?
(SIGHS) No idea.
BOY : Man, I can't believe
no one told you about that.
Sick shit, right?
Voices told him to do it.
Took out the whole family, six people.
Wait, whoa, where you going?
I already missed the last three periods,
and I don't really want to transfer again.
Hey, wait.
You ever see this?
You recognize that house?
We need to talk.
Good to see you, honey. How was school?
Why didn't you tell me about the house?
I've just been waiting for the right time.
And when would that be?
You know, it's just a ghost story, sweetie.
- It's an urban legend.
- Yeah,
that everyone at my school
seems to know about.
You're right. I'm sorry.
I should've told you.
I just, I really have had a lot on my mind.
Well, it would be nice if Juliet
and I could be on your mind, too.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
That's the, that's the doctor.
Good talk.
JOAN (VOICE-OVER):
But it's an improvement, right?
I mean, it has to be.
I know it may seem that way,
but remember, the last time we checked,
there was no brain activity at all.
But he opened his eyes.
I mean, who's to say
that he won't start speaking
or even sitting up or something?
Joan, you know there are no documented cases
of anyone with James's injuries
ever recovering.
Then James will be the first.
Is there any way to be sure
if there is any recovery?
It's highly unlikely.
But I suppose we could do another fMRI.
BELLE : Great.
How much more shit do you want
to put him through?
Just leave him alone.
Hasn't he suffered enough?
JOAN (WHISPERING): I'm sorry about that.
JULIET :
Yesterday me and Deedee went to the park.
Last night it was broccoli and carrots.
- (JULIET MAKES CHEWING NOISES)
- (DOOR CREAKING)
And Deedee likes to chase
the ducks at the park.
And at dinnertime...
Are you talking to James again?
Yep.
(SIGHS)
What does James have to say this time?
He says he misses talking to you, too.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Jules, your mom's gonna walk Larry.
- You want to go with her?
- Okay.
Come here.
One, two, three.
Ooh, yeah.
(SIGHS): Oh, good.
Uh, Belle.
You know I don't want any more tests, either.
Then why did you suggest it?
Because this test is gonna show your mom
what you and I already know.
Did you know about the house?
Please, just go.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(THUNDER CONTINUES)
- (THUNDER CONTINUES)
- (CLOCK TICKING)
(SLEEPILY):
Juliet, you can't keep doing this.
Scoot over.
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
Happy Monday.
Belle, this is Marissa.
She's my girlfriend.
You wish.
M, uh, this is my friend Belle.
- You wish.
- Wow.
All kinds of love for Terrence today.
See how it is? (GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
See you later, man.
Those guys.
So, yeah, Marissa didn't believe me
when I said I knew you,
so I thought you guys should, uh, meet.
What's up?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
MARISSA : God, I would kill my mom if she did
something like that without telling me.
Yeah, well, talking's not
really big in my house, so...
Yeah, well, thank God
none of this Amityville shit is real.
Whoa, whoa. That all depends
on your definition of real.
You know, if someone's talking
a lot about something,
your mind starts playing tricks on you
to make you think it's real.
(CHUCKLING): According to who?
Science.
Well, I'm really over
this Amityville stuff, anyway.
My family's got enough demons to deal with.
I don't need fictional ones, too.
I don't know, maybe that's
exactly what you need.
Hey, we should watch the movie.
No, thanks.
Come on, that, that's what horror movies
are all about, like, escaping reality
with your friends for a little while.
It's fun.
Okay, fine. Let's watch it at your house.
No. Your house.
Come on. How often do you get to watch
"The Amityville Horror"
at the actual Amityville house?
(CHUCKLES) Okay, sure.
Awesome. Okay.
We have to watch it at 3:15 a.m., though.
Why?
'Cause that's when Ronnie DeFeo
murdered his family.
And that's when the house comes alive.
(MUMBLES SLEEPILY)
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
(BARKING, GROWLING)
Ah, shit. Larry.
(SIGHS)
(LARRY GROWLING)
What?
- (GROWLING CONTINUES)
- What?
Come on, you see something?
- (GROWLING STOPS)
- What do you see?
What do you see?
- (YELLS INDISTINCTLY)
- (GASPS)
(LARRY GROWLING)
(CHUCKLES)
- Oh, that was great.
- (LARRY GROWLING)
- Go, Larry.
- Oh, man.
Look, I told him not to do that.
Oh, you should've seen your face.
You guys seriously have to be quiet.
- You don't want to wake up my mom.
- Sorry.
(WHISPERING):
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
Wow, this place is amazing.
Is that a bounding circle in the backyard?
A... bounding circle?
Yeah, like, hundreds of years ago,
like, colonial times,
there used to be all this weird
occult shit going on around here,
so if they thought an area was evil,
they would do a ring around it
with like, salt or fire,
whatever, to try and keep the evil contained.
Yeah, or maybe the gardener just got
a little carried away with the weed killer.
All right, so, I thought
we were here to watch a movie.
Yes.
Hell, I've seen the movie
a dozen times, but...
Shut up.
(WHISPERING):...I've never
been inside the actual house.
Okay, I'm going to punch you
in the actual mouth if you don't shut up.
Oh, yeah?
Is that a threat or a promise?
Gross.
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
What's in there?
Nothing. Let's go.
Okay, so you've got the original
1979 film starring James...
Shh!
(QUIETLY):
Starring James Brolin and Margot Kidder.
Um, but just in case,
I brought the "Amityville 2,"
which is technically a prequel.
So I don't know if you like that...
Anyway. Um, then, of course,
there's the remake.
- No way.
- No.
Yeah, remakes totally blow.
Agreed. All right.
The original it is.
So how'd you girls like to be
the bread in a Terrence sandwich?
In your dreams.
NARRATOR (OVER TV):
This house is built on special ground.
Satan worship.
Demons.
You cannot destroy this evil.
It will always find a place to dwell,
something or someone to latch onto.
What's going on?
Have you all gone mad?
George!
- (DOOR CREAKING)
- They...
come and go through here.
(CREAKING CONTINUES)
DEMONIC VOICE : Find the well.
It's...
the passage
to Hell!
(TV STOPS)
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
What?
(BEEPING STEADILY)
TERRENCE : Holy shit.
It's 3:15 on the dot.
No, it's not.
I swear. Look.
- What did you do?
- Uh... What?
- Nothing.
- I really hope not.
- I gotta get the lights back on.
- Well...
I mean, it's probably just a fuse.
Right?
No, we need to fix it or else
I'm gonna have to wake up my mom.
Mmm, okay, then where's the fuse box?
(BEEPING, BLIPPING)
I think it's under the stairs.
(SIGHS)
Oh, great, the basement
of the Amityville house.
That's perfect.
I haven't been down there yet.
Hold on.
I got this.
Who wants to go first?
MARISSA : Oh, God, what's that smell?
BELLE : Just try and find the fuse box.
TERRENCE : Wow.
BELLE : What?
Under the stairs.
It's where they discovered the Red Room.
Whatever is in there gets inside your head.
MARISSA : Wouldn't find much in your head.
They say this house makes you see things.
It affects your dreams until you can't tell
what's real and what's a nightmare.
Then boom... blood splatter
and brain matter everywhere.
Can we please just find the fuse box,
so we can get out of here?
Hey, I think I found it.
(BLOWS)
(SIGHS)
BELLE : My phone is dead.
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
- (GASPS)
- (SHRIEKS)
What the hell are you doing down here?
I could've killed you!
MARISSA : Uh...
we'll let ourselves out.
Yeah, nice meeting you.
BELLE : Since when do you carry a shotgun?
Jesus.
It was your father's, for protection.
Well, I really don't think I need protection
from my friends, but thanks.
You are not allowed to have
friends over without asking me.
You know how easy it is
for James to get sick?
What are you talking about?
They weren't anywhere near him.
Someone was in his room.
The door was open when they
came over, but I... shut it.
Then who took his blanket off?
He's not some sideshow attraction.
Go to bed.
DR. MILTON (VOICE-OVER): It's possible
that he has something called LIS...
Locked-In Syndrome.
JOAN : Does that mean he's conscious?
Well, it means he may have
a sort of consciousness,
but he's locked into an inactive body.
So he is getting better?
Well, looking at this fMRI scan
and seeing the return
of some limited eye mobility,
uh, it would appear so.
And this thing will tell us for sure?
The EEG machine measures brain waves.
The more activity on this monitor,
the stronger the emotional response.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
You ready to give it a try?
(CHUCKLES): All right.
Step into his line of sight.
Hi, Jimmy.
Hey.
(MONITOR BEEPING, VENTILATOR HISSING)
Jimmy.
(EEG BEEPS)
DR. MILTON : Whoa.
That's a definite response.
(WHISPERING): Candice.
Belle, come closer.
(EEG BEEPING, INCREASING IN FREQUENCY)
Mom?
(JOAN GROANS)
Are you okay?
Your brother's back.
(EEG SLOWING)
(SIGHS)
- (FLY BUZZING)
- Oh.
It's just a fly, James.
Don't worry about that.
(BUZZING INTENSIFIES)
Jesus Christ!
(MUFFLED SCREAM)
(BUZZING STOPS, DR. MILTON CHOKING)
(GASPS)
What's going on?
I'm sorry, uh, I can't, uh,
I can't really explain it,
but I... I don't think
I can do any more for you.
Dr. Milton?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
Come on, Jimmy.
You're doing great.
You're doing so great.
(WHISPERING): I love you so much.
Come on.
Let's try and just move that thumb up.
Do you want me to rub your feet?
You can blink once for "yes."
That's okay.
When this first happened, Belle said,
"Jimmy will never give up."
(DOOR CREAKS)
(GROWLING)
(BARKING, GROWLING)
Okay, out! Out!
- Go, now!
- (BARKING CONTINUES)
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Out, Larry!
Bad dog!
Don't worry, I'll never let him hurt you.
(WHISPERING):
I love you more than anything in the world.
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
(GRUNTS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(CREAKING)
(WHISPERING): James, is that you?
JAMES : Shh.
What do you want?
Come here.
(LOW, RASPY BREATHING)
Where are you?
James?
(HISSING)
(SCREAMING)
Juliet?
Jules, where are you?
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
(GASPS)
Hey, sis.
(SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING, CRASHING)
CANDICE (VOICE-OVER): Start with just
- yes or no questions.
- Okay.
Dr. Milton said
that would be easiest for him.
JOAN : Okay.
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Jimmy?
Sweetie?
Do you recognize me?
Belle?
James wants to talk to Deedee.
Will you help me find him?
(JOAN LAUGHS)
Belle...
come say hi to your brother.
CANDICE :
He's talking to us through the computer.
It's amazing. Come see.
It's called an AAC.
He can use his eyes to choose letters
so he can communicate.
(JOAN CHUCKLES)
You can talk to your brother again, honey.
- BELLE : Uh...
- JOAN : What do you want to say to him?
I don't know.
JOAN : Just talk to him slowly.
Um...
Is that really you in there?
(BEEP)
(CHUCKLING): Wow, it's so cool.
I miss you.
(ONE BEEP)
(TWO BEEPS)
(LAUGHS)
(SNIFFLES)
He misses me, too.
(SNIFFLING): Um...
(ONE BEEP)
(CONTINUAL, SLOW BEEPING)
(SOBBING)
BELLE (VOICE-OVER):
I just never really told anybody about this.
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
No, um...
I should.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I really think I need to.
I was having a lot of problems
with my family
and with school, um, in and out
of a lot of different programs.
And I just started doing stupid shit.
I sent these pictures to some guy,
and when I woke up the next morning,
they were all over the Internet.
They were everywhere.
Everyone had seen them.
Everyone at school and my mom
and my brother.
So what happened?
James wanted to find the guy who did it.
And he lived in a, um,
three-story apartment building.
There was a really big fight, and...
...he went over the balcony.
Look, you didn't do anything wrong.
You know that, right?
You know, I... I really want to believe that.
And I keep telling myself
it was his choice.
He would do it again in a heartbeat.
I know he would, because...
...that's just who he was.
No, that's who he is.
Belle, he's still alive.
You've just talked to him.
(SIGHS)
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
TERRENCE : You're reading the wrong book.
And you know it.
TERRENCE (VOICE-OVER):
All I'm saying is it's a little weird
that your brother's in a coma for two years,
and the minute you move into this new house,
he miraculously gets better.
(SIGHS): I don't... I don't know.
Unless, of course, it's not...
really him anymore.
What are you talking about?
He's talking about a possession.
Yeah. In 1974, the house drives Ronnie DeFeo
to kill his whole family.
A year later, it nearly drives the next
family to do the exact same thing.
And they blamed it on the Red Room
that they discovered
right there, in the basement.
See? It's right under your brother's bed.
So you're saying...
this evil thing...
- latched onto my brother?
- Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Look, I hate to bring everyone
back down to earth, but...
other families have lived in that house...
nothing scary has happened
there for 40 years.
40 years... that's a very
significant number in the Bible.
"And the land had peace 40 years."
So maybe the evil only latches on
- every 40 years.
- No, that's stupid.
Dude, seriously? The Bible?
(CHUCKLES) Look, Belle, you're not
actually buying this shit, are you?
Well, you said he can talk now, right?
So why don't you just ask him yourself?
Yeah. What's the worst that could happen?
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY,
VENTILATOR HISSING)
I need to ask you a question.
You okay with that?
(BEEP)
Is someone else...
in there with you?
(BEEP)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(VOICE BREAKING): What can I do to stop it?
How can I help you?
(BELLE SHUDDERS)
(BEEPING)
BELLE (TREMBLES): No...
No, I can't do that.
(BEEPING)
(WHISPERS): No.
(SOFT, TREMBLING BREATHS)
(CRYING): I love you so much.
(TREMBLING BREATHS)
(CRYING SOFTLY)
Are you sure you want me to do this?
(BEEP)
I'm gonna take this out.
(CRYING QUIETLY, SNIFFLING)
(DEEP, RASPING GASP)
(SNIFFLES)
(MACHINERY POWERS DOWN)
- (GASPS)
- You're the one who's gonna fucking die!
(BEEPS CONTINUE)
JOAN : Is he all right?
Are you okay, honey? What's going on?
Jimmy, you okay?
What did you do?
- I...
- What did you do?
You have no right to do this!
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
He's breathing.
He's breathing on his own.
(KISSES)
(JOAN LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Jimmy wants to live.
He deserves... to live.
JOAN : Get out.
(SNIFFLES)
If you touch him again, I swear... (SNIFFLES)
BELLE (VOICE-OVER): It's bad enough
that he's trapped in
his own body, and now he's...
what, he's... there's
something in there with him?
Wha... What am I gonna do?
I...
- I have to help him.
- Look, Belle,
you have to help your entire family, okay?
I mean, whatever's in there
with James, if it... if it wins, you know,
it it takes over completely,
it will kill everyone.
Belle, you got to get
your family out of there.
Or we have to prove it to your mom somehow.
Find a way to show her
that your brother is being controlled
by whatever is in that house.
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
Belle?
Why aren't you in school?
I wasn't feeling well.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
No, I'm sorry about last night.
For what?
If you hadn't pulled Jimmy
off the respirator, w...
we wouldn't know that
he could breathe on his own.
I know you...
were doing what you thought was right.
But now you know how wrong it is.
Right?
Jimmy was always going to come back.
You do want us to be a family
again, don't you, Belle?
Of course.
Good.
Get some rest, sweetie.
I love you.
Hey, James. How you doing today?
(WEAK, RASPY BREATHING)
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
"Outside walk."
Those are your biggest words yet.
You're doing so great. Yes, we can!
(INDISTINCT VOICES IN DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT TALKING CONTINUES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
JOAN : Honey! Be careful by the water, okay?
JULIET : Okay!
I don't know why it's so hard
for everyone to believe
- he's getting better.
- Well, he's getting better,
but don't you want to know why?
He's really...
I think a second opinion would be good, too.
CANDICE : We can do that.
A second opinion's okay.
- Have you asked Dr. Milton about this?
- JOAN : Mmm,
I haven't been in contact with him yet.
(INHALES)
Ugh.
(SCREAMS)
Juliet!
What happened? You okay? Come here, baby.
Come on.
- What's wrong? You tell me. What's wrong?
- (CRYING)
JULIET : It's Larry.
CANDICE : Okay. Don't look at it.
TERRENCE (VOICE-OVER):
Is that a bounding circle
- in the backyard?
- BELLE : A bounding circle?
TERRENCE : If they thought
an area was evil, they would do
a ring around it with, like,
salt or fire, whatever,
(ECHOING): to try and keep the evil
contained... the evil contained...
CANDICE : It's gonna be okay.
- (GENTLY): Okay.
- (GRUNTING)
(DISTORTED, ECHOING WHISPERS)
(EERIE WHISPERING): Kill, kill, kill...
kill, kill...
Kill...
- (FADING): kill, kill, kill...
- (MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
CANDICE : Okay.
All right, that's great. Thank you.
So, the vet can be here first thing
tomorrow morning to pick up the body.
JOAN : Thank you for doing this.
- Thanks for everything.
- Of course.
Joan...
- don't worry about it.
- I know.
And Juliet is gonna be okay.
I know.
How about I come by and check
on everybody after my shift tonight?
That sound all right?
(SIGHS) Yeah, that sounds great.
CANDICE : Okay.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
He can't leave the house.
(VOICE-OVER):
Hey, Mom, I need to talk to you.
Mom, stop.
Are you listening to me?
Look, I know you're
gonna think I'm crazy, okay?
But I... I got a really
bad feeling about this house.
I think it's doing something to James.
It's... it's, like, possessing him
or infecting him.
I... I don't know.
There's this room in the basement, okay?
I've been down there. I've seen it myself.
I swear, I think that's what's...
making him all of a sudden better.
Please say something.
I don't think you're crazy, sweetheart.
I know about the Red Room.
Come here.
Wait, wh... what did you just say?
You know I always believed in God.
And then your father got sick.
And we had to watch him
rot away from the inside from cancer.
Every day I prayed.
And then James got sick.
But still I prayed.
Two years.
The doctors are giving up on him, right?
They said he'd never come out.
- I won't accept that.
- What are...
what are you talking about?
God gave up on us, sweetheart.
So I gave up on God.
And I moved us here.
Because if...
if there is some...
power...
that can make your brother better...
Better? No, Mom, no, you don't understand.
James isn't better.
(WHISPERING): This house is evil.
This house is really bad.
It's gonna drive James to kill
our whole family, just like the DeFeos.
You, me,
- Juliet...
- Shh. Stop. Stop.
Come here. No, no, no, no, no.
James would never do that.
Okay?
He would never do that. He's getting better.
- (WHISPERING): Hi, baby. Hi. Hi. Get up.
- Belle?
Yes. I need you to put this on, okay?
I want you to hurry. Just stay quiet, okay?
- Where are we going?
- I'll be right back. Shh.
(JOAN YELLS)
(GROANING SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
(SOFT POP SONG PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(JULIET SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Hi, honey. Come sit down.
We're just about to start dinner.
- Hey, guess what, Belle?
- Chicken smells great, Mom.
Oh, hey, Belle.
How'd you sleep?
I hope you're hungry.
Mom made all this great food.
Juliet, pass the chicken, please.
JOAN (QUIETLY): So strong.
JULIET : There you are.
Where's your bed?
JOAN : In his room.
It's about time we had a proper dining room.
Jimmy.
Of course.
JAMES :
Dad would be so happy to see us all here...
together.
Don't you think, Mom?
Yes, I do.
(SONG GROWING LOUDER)
(SONG STOPS ABRUPTLY)
(SCRAPING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(CRACKLING)
(CREAKING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(RATTLING DOORKNOB)
(EERIE WHISPERING VOICES)
- (AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT)
- (CRACKLING)
(RATTLING DOORKNOB)
(GASPING BREATHS)
Oh, fuck.
- (AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT)
- (LOW, RASPY BREATHING)
- (PANTING)
- (RATTLING DOORKNOB)
- (AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT)
- (LOW, RASPY BREATHING)
Candice?
- (THUMPING)
- Candice?
- (AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT)
- (RASPY BREATHING)
(QUIET, PAINED GASP)
- (PAINED GROANING)
- (CRACKLING)
Don't come in!
- Call the police!
- (POUNDING ON WALL)
(AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT,
EERIE SCREAMS, CRACKLING)
(RASPY BREATHING, GROANING, CRACKLING)
(AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT GROWING LOUDER)
(DISTORTED, ECHOING BREATH)
(ECHOING BREATH FADES)
- (PANTING)
- (DOOR CREAKS)
Joan?
CANDICE (IN DISTANCE): Joan? You awake?
Belle?
(GUNSHOT, BODY THUDS)
(GASPS)
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
Belle?
- (TREMBLING BREATHS)
- JOAN (CALLS): Belle?
JOAN (IN DISTANCE):
What are you doing, Belle?
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
Juliet? Belle?
JOAN (IN DISTANCE):
I can't get out of my room!
(RATTLES DOORKNOB)
- (SLAMMING)
- (GASPS)
JOAN (CALLS): Belle?
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- Belle, I can't get out of my room!
- (QUIETLY): Juliet?
- Belle!
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- Shh! Mom...
- Belle, what's going on?
- Be quiet.
JULIET : Belle?
What's wrong with Mommy?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
JOAN : Hello?
(SHELL CLATTERS ON FLOOR)
(WHISPERS): Juliet?
(DOORKNOB SQUEAKS)
(CREAKING)
- (GUNSHOT BOOMS)
- (JOAN SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(ERRATIC, TREMBLING BREATHS)
- (PANTING)
- (JULIET WHIMPERING)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKS)
(PANTS QUIETLY)
(DOOR CREAKING)
Hi, Mom.
Hi, baby.
What are you doing with that?
(SHELL CLATTERS ON FLOOR)
Don't you recognize me, baby?
Oh, God, no.
God has nothing to do with this.
Damn you to hell!
(GASPING)
Too late.
(GASPS)
(GROANING IN PAIN)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT BOOMS)
- I left Deedee upstairs.
- Shh, shh.
Shh, shh.
(DOOR CREAKING)
(WHISPERS): Where are you going?
(GROWLING)
(WHISPERS): Is that Larry?
(PANTING): No, baby.
I want you to go to the next-door
neighbor's house and wait for me, okay?
- (VICIOUS GROWL)
- (JULIET SCREAMS)
- (GROWLING)
- (CRIES OUT)
(GASPS)
- (GROWLING)
- (GASPING)
There you are, sweetie.
- (BELLE SCREAMING)
- (STABBING)
(BREATHING SLOWS)
James, I'm scared.
(WHISPERS): Shh. Don't be scared.
Deedee.
We're gonna play a little game, okay, Jules?
I don't want to.
Turn over and go to sleep.
Do it.
(JULIET SHUDDERS)
Stop!
Don't hurt her.
You wouldn't hurt your brother, would you?
You're not my brother.
My brother died two years ago,
and you know it.
Because of what you did.
(SCREAMS)
(THUD)
(GASPS)
(COUGHING, PANTING)
(GASPING BREATHS)
(WHIMPERS)
(WEAK, GASPING BREATHS)
(BOTH GASPING)
(TREMBLING): Belle...
it hurts so bad.
(GASPING, GRUNTING)
I can't move. (GRUNTS)
That wasn't me, Belle.
You have to believe me.
I swear.
Please... (GRUNTS)
...help me.
(GASPING): Help. I miss you.
Please.
(JAMES TREMBLING, GASPING WEAKLY)
I'm so sorry.
(SOBBING): I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry about everything.
I love you.
Help me.
Take me back inside.
Ah... It's... it's...
it's what Mom would have wanted.
You don't want to disappoint her... do you?
Mom is dead.
So is Juliet.
All we have is each other now.
(CRACKLING)
Liar.
- No...
- You're not James.
You're a liar.
- JAMES : Belle! Belle! No!
- No! You're not James!
No! (GAGGING, YELLING)
I don't want to die!
(SOBBING)
(JAMES YELLING, GASPING)
(EERIE WHISPERING): Kill... kill... kill...
It's me! Please! Aah!
(YELLING, GRUNTING)
It's me, Belle!
(SOBBING): Oh, why? No!
No! No! No! No!
Belle!
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING): Please...
(GASPING, SCREAMING)
- (JAMES GASPING)
- (BELLE PANTING)
(CRACKLING)
JAMES (WHISPERS): Hey.
Thank...
you.
(SOBBING)
(BELLE CONTINUES SOBBING)
JULIET (CALLS): Belle?
- Belle?
- Juliet?
Belle!
Juliet?
Oh, my God! Oh, my...
Baby.
Hey, hey, let me see you. Are you all right?
Are you hurt? Oh.
What happened to James?
He was gonna hurt us, baby.
But he's in a... he's in a better place now.
I promise.
Okay, now, listen to me, Juliet.
The police are gonna be here really soon,
and I'm gonna tell them
exactly what happened.
But I need you to do the same, okay?
James tried to hurt us, and
I need you to tell them that.
Right, baby?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
(CRYING): Oh...
Do you think they'll believe us?
NEWSCASTER : Tragedy has struck
once again at 112 Ocean Avenue
in Amityville, Long Island,
the infamous house
where Ronnie DeFeo killed his entire family
with a shotgun, more than four decades ago.
Police are questioning
17-year-old Belle Walker
as a person of interest in the
brutal murders of her aunt Candice,
her mother Joan, and the death
of her brother James.
Miss Walker claims that her
brother committed the crimes,
and her story has been corroborated
by her seven-year-old sister Juliet.
A spokesman for the Amityville Police
Department said that forensic evidence
does point to James as the killer.
His fingerprints were found
on the murder weapon.
But Dr. Ken Milton refutes that claim,
stating that James Walker was
too weak to get out of bed,
let alone stalk his
entire family with a shotgun.
For two years prior to the murders,
James was in a coma, a vegetative state.
Is this house a source of evil,
- as legend suggests?
- (AMPLIFIED HEARTBEAT)
Did it awaken and possess
James Walker or his sister Belle?
For now, the police are left with
a horrific unsolved crime,
and Amityville, Long Island,
is once again the center of shock and horror.
(MUSIC ENDS)
^.^.^.^.subtitles by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com