Everyone was warned,
but no one listened.
A rise in temperature...
Ocean patterns changed...
And ice caps melted.
They called it
extreme weather.
They didn't know
what "extreme" was.
In the year of 2019...
Hurricanes...
Tornadoes...
Floods...
And droughts...
Unleashed a wave of destruction
upon our planet.
We didn't just lose towns...
Or beachfronts.
We lost entire cities.
The East River swallowed
Lower Manhattan.
A heat wave killed
two million people in Madrid...
In just one day.
But in that moment...
Facing our own extinction...
It became clear that no single nation
could solve this problem alone.
The world came together as one...
And we fought back.
Scientists from 17 countries...
Led by the U.S. and China...
Worked tirelessly.
Not as representatives
of their nations...
But of humanity.
They found a way
to neutralize the storms...
With a net of
thousands of satellites,
each deploying countermeasures designed
to impact the basic elements of weather,
heat, pressure, and water.
All overseen
by the International Space Station.
They gave the satellite net
a technical name...
But we all came
to call it Dutch Boy...
After the story of the child
who plugged a dam with his finger.
This is what saved us all.
And it was built by a team
led by one man...
My father.
-Thank you.
-Keep the change.
Jake Lawson. I have a Senate--
Senate hearing in room 12.
Yeah.
Lawson?
-You're the Dutch Boy guy, right?
-Yeah.
Man, I need to shake your hand.
Oh. Okay.
Tornado? Zap!
Blizzard? Zap!
Monsoon?
-Zap?
-Zap!
Everybody down here owes you,
Jake Lawson.
If you need anything, you just ask.
The Senate Committee
assigned to oversee Dutch Boy
will now hear from Jacob Lawson...
Climate ISS Chief Operations
Coordinator.
May the record reflect
that he was nearly one hour late.
Yeah, sorry about that.
l literally had to
fly in from outer space.
Oh, here we go.
Mr. Lawson, we find ourselves
heading toward a crossroads.
As you know, as per
UN Resolution 28-14,
the United States will be
handing over control of Dutch Boy
to an International Oversight Committee
in three years.
This in spite of the fact
that we actually built the thing.
Excuse me, Senator.
I don't wanna slow things down.
You said "we" built it?
Yes, indeed, I did.
Because I know what I did. I'm the guy
who led the team that built the station.
I was up there with an international
crew of 600 people, not just Americans.
And I know all of their faces,
but I don't remember yours.
We had a plumber up there.
He looked a little like you.
--Very clever, Mr. Lawson.
Dutch Boy was an international effort
- and, yes, it may, one day, very well...
...belong to the world.
But until it does,
we have authority over its operation
and we have authority over you!
And you have been flouting
that authority.
I have report after report here.
Failure to follow procedures...
Numerous violations
of the chain of command.
Then, there was the incident where you
punched a federal inspector in the face.
Well, your federal inspector
doesn't know
that a capacitor holds a charge
even when it's disconnected.
He was grabbing for the damn thing.
I saved his life!
You can make all the excuses
you want, Mr. Lawson,
but there's one thing you cannot defend.
And that would be the day
you brought Dutch Boy online...
...and operational without our consent!
And what would that have taken, Senator?
There were a series of storms building
in Southeast Asia and the North Atlantic
that would have killed
tens of thousands of people.
Dutch Boy was ready. We went green.
It works. You're welcome.
Mr. Lawson, if you continue
to defy our authority...
Dutch Boy will go on without you!
Am I making myself clear?
Yes.
Good. Oh, and one more thing.
To ensure compliance, this committee
will be sending up new support staff.
Naturally, when they get there, you'll
have to send some of your people home.
We'll leave those choices up to you.
Senator, respectfully,
my crew didn't do anything wrong.
Excuse me,
I'm not asking for your input.
These people left their homes
and their families
and risked their lives
to save this planet.
This hearing is adjourned.
I'm not cutting a single one
of those people loose!
Excuse me?
People like you need people like me.
You know why?
So you can take credit
for everything we accomplish.
So you can go to your constituents
and your cronies...
This meeting is adjourned.
...and your mistresses
and puff out your chest
- and say, "Hey, look at me!"
- Sit down, please!
-Well, I'm looking, Senator.
-Excuse me.
-We're all looking.
-This meeting is adjourned.
This meeting is adjourned! Thank you.
Well, that was going well, huh?
Up to a point.
No, Jake, that didn't go well
at any point.
But, hey, what are you good at,
little brother, huh?
Like working the angles,
smoothing ruffled feathers?
You can fix it. You always do.
It's like a talent.
It is a talent.
Of a sort.
I wish I could help you.
I really do.
But it's not that simple,
not this time.
Why not?
Well, as of last week,
they have put me in charge of Dutch Boy.
Well, that's great!
That's great! You kidding me?
You're kidding me.
Look, what do you want me to do? Huh?
You leave me no choice. I told you
this had to go well, and it didn't.
I'm sorry, Jake.
You're fired.
Jesus. It's over 120 in this mother.
Fan out.
Hi, Agent Wilson.
Assistant Secretary Lawson.
Oh, you look nice today.
I'm wearing the same thing
I always wear.
Not exactly.
Have you seen I, well, got on a new tie?
I observed. We're trained to notice
any disturbing details.
-Sarah, come on.
-Assistant Secretary Lawson...
I'm not permitted to engage in
casual conversation while I'm at a post.
We are being watched.
We're always being watched.
Well, if we're always being watched,
what's the point of hiding anything?
You're interfering with my duties.
I'd rather not shoot you.
Well, it would be an honor
to be the first person that you kill.
Hang on.
What is it?
Uh, the president's called
a security briefing.
It was not on the schedule,
so I guess I'm now on duty.
I like the tie. Home by 7:00. Love you.
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
I didn't say anything.
Move along, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
What the hell happened here?
One of our thermospheric satellites
malfunctioned over Afghanistan.
A UN recon team found it, Mr. President.
And the members of the Climate Council,
they're aware?
Yes, and they've all agreed
to keep the incident discreet.
But with this many people in the loop,
I'm not sure how long it's gonna keep.
And we're sure this was caused
by Dutch Boy?
Absolutely.
Can we assume that this is
an isolated incident? Doctor Quigley?
We're fairly certain, yes.
It's great to know
that you're "fairly certain."
This is a serious malfunction.
So your proposal is what?
Simple. We shut down
all Central Asian satellites
until we know what went wrong.
-Are you serious?
-Yes, I'm serious.
Know how difficult it was to get every
one of these nations online for this?
We have worked extremely hard
to assure these nations that this
system will protect them, and it has.
And let's not forget, people,
it's an election year.
We shut Dutch Boy down,
the press is gonna jump all over this.
Oh, my God!
300 people died in that village.
I mean, who gives a damn
about the politics of it all?
Look, we cost those people their lives.
The only thing we should be concerned
about here is how to fix it
and making sure it never happens again.
And how do you propose we do that?
We can't do anything.
What I mean is, the problem is
not gonna be solved in this room
and, well, certainly not by us.
No, no, we need an international team
on the station itself.
You know, not suits.
Engineers, coders, builders
doing a comprehensive systems check,
no matter the cost,
no matter the politics,
and we need 'em up there now.
We are set to transfer full authority
for Dutch Boy
to the international community
in two weeks.
I will not be the president
that hands over damaged goods.
Not now, not ever.
So we are gonna handle this problem
and its solution in-house,
and we are gonna send up one man.
One of our own, who reports only to us
and that we can control.
Understood?
So find me that someone.
Now.
Yes, sir.
Look, I know you're not gonna like it,
but as I see it,
there's only one person
to go after for this.
Your brother, Jake.
Come on, not Jake.
17 countries, hmm?
17 countries had teams working on
Dutch Boy. They all reported to him.
Nobody knows what's under the hood
better than him.
Come on. Can we weigh other options?
Max, how long have you known me?
Ever since I was transferred
to the State Department.
That's right. I handpicked you.
I believed in you. You're smart.
And I was right about you.
I'm right about Jake.
If this is gonna be a problem...
No, sir.
Good.
Afghan satellite
zero-niner-six inbound.
All crews prepare for incoming
Afghanistan satellite.
Replacement satellite
standing by.
HERNANDEZ". Afghan sat is locked in.
Replacement cleared for launch.
And away on sat 5-A.
Airlock doors secured.
I want a full dissection
of all components.
Priority one.
Afghan satellite dissection
commencing.
I will take care of this.
Make sure they depressurize
the fuel intake.
Yeah, we got it, man.
Makmoud. Oi, Makmoud!
I'm about to obliterate
your top score here, pal.
I have to do some reprogramming.
Oh, come on!
He's got no pride of ownership,
that lad.
Please stand clear of the doors.
Uncle Max?
Hey! What you doing up there?
What is that? A solar generator?
Dual axis sun-tracking solar generator.
Replacing the power converter.
on, God!
You're getting more like your dad
every day.
Hey, where'd he find that?
Are you seriously asking that question?
Oh, of course.
He made it, right? Come here, you.
Ah, it's good to see you!
How you doing? You okay?
I'm really great.
Okay, what's going on here?
All right, this is freaking me out.
You're supposed to be nine years old.
Thirteen.
You were supposed to be
a part of my life,
but shit happens.
Ouch!
So what's going on here?
You living with him now?
He gets me two weekends a month.
Oh, good. Well, how's your mom?
Hmm, justifiably pissed.
| bet.
JAKE". Hannah, it's time.
What's up, Jake?
Hannah, I thought I told you not
to talk to strangers.
Come on. Don't listen to him.
Your dad and I were your age,
we were so close we had
our own secret code.
- That's true.
- Really?
I don't remember that.
Yeah, you do.
No, I don't.
Well, it was nice seeing you.
Hey, look, you take care.
What's with all the car parts?
I build electric motors
for the retirees down in Vero Beach.
Keeps me busy.
Seems hardly worth your talent.
Kidding?
Having the time of my life.
It's a little early, don't you think?
I got fired by my own brother.
Then I lost my family,
my house, my dog,
so happy hour
starts around 11:00 out here.
Okay, saw your niece,
you don't want a beer.
Road's that way.
There's something wrong with Dutch Boy.
No, there isn't.
Well, an entire village of
dead Afghans may disagree with you.
Yeah.
And then yesterday,
an airlock just opened by itself.
We lost one of our crew.
Dutch Boy is not my problem anymore.
That I am calling bullshit on.
'Cause other than your daughter
and your precious soccer club,
Dutch Boy was all
you ever gave a damn about.
Oh, yeah, once.
Yeah, but you took care of that.
You don't care?
No?
Well, then, what are you doing
living out here?
Hmm?
Look, I know you think I'm a weasel,
someone who just moves pieces
around a chessboard for a living.
Well, guess what, yeah. Yeah, I am.
But that is how you get 17 countries
to agree to build a space station.
Now, you build things, right?
And there is something wrong
with the thing that you built,
and people are dying.
If you really think you're the best,
which I know that you do,
then how the hell
can you stand there and say no?
I'll be taking orders from someone,
I suppose.
Yeah.
So what? ls that a yes?
Long as it's not you, yeah.
Hey, this is Max.
Leave a message.
You got any room in there for me?
Whoa!
Okay.
I think this is everything.
I made you a packed lunch as well.
Did you hear about the gas main
explosions in Hong Kong?
Yeah, it just hit the news.
It's terrible.
Was it anything like what happened
in Afghanistan?
No, nothing happened in Afghanistan.
Are you going back up to space?
-No.
-Yes, you are!
You're leaving today to fix Dutch Boy.
What did I tell you
about eavesdropping?
You've never told me anything
about eavesdropping.
You don't really do much parenting.
How do you know it's safe?
Of course it's safe.
I've been up there 100 times.
Don't treat me like I'm a child.
Someone died!
- It was an accident.
- Someone got sucked out!
It was an accident.
See, that's what I'm going up there
to fix, okay? You don't have to worry.
Hey, think of it like I'm going
on a vacation for a week or two.
To a place 250 miles straight up
and -450 degrees?
Some holiday.
Yeah, you got a point.
Why'd Uncle Max fire you?
Unbelievable!
Did you do something wrong?
No, look, your Uncle Max and me...
It's not just about the one job.
You know, sometimes,
younger brothers resent being younger.
So they get bossy.
They think they know everything.
They tell you how to act, how to talk,
and after a couple decades,
you just get tired of listening to it.
Maybe you should listen.
My lift is here.
-Gotta go.
-What?
Wait, I thought I was
taking you to the airport.
You really wanna see Mom? Great!
We can all fly home to Atlanta together.
Got it covered.
Quit acting like you're mad.
Hannah, what do you want from me?
I want you to come back alive.
And you're not exactly
the reliable type.
Hey-
I know I haven't always
kept good on my promises,
but I'm coming back.
_|__
-Promise.
I promise.
Come here.
I'll be back soon, okay?
OV-104 is now at
T minus one hour and ready for boarding.
We're at T minus one minute
and counting.
Have a safe trip, sir.
Booster rocket
separation confirmed.
Hate to interrupt, Major Tom,
but in a few seconds,
you should be able to see the net.
How's it feel to be back home?
Look at you, girl.
Livin‘ and breathin‘.
Mr. Lawson.
Hey-
Ute Fassbinder.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, I remember you.
Yeah, you were the German scientist.
You were here when I was here.
Thermospherics, right?
Yeah.
The containment shell needs
a fresh coat of sealant
where the APT ducts push
through the channel housing.
Not good. That's wrong.
And you hear that?
- I'm sorry.
- Shh. Listen.
That wobbly hum?
That's a bad step-down transformer.
All these things,
they have to be watched, cared for.
- Mr. Lawson.
- No, I know. It's not your fault,
but when I left,
everything here was perfect.
I need to speak to your Chief Scientist
about the art of giving a shit.
I'm the Chief Scientist.
I've been promoted a year ago.
Right, congratulations.
One of our crew died this week,
Mr. Lawson.
Sorry about the transformer.
Let me introduce you to your team.
Oh, of course, an American.
Actually, my brother and I
were born in the UK, but thank you.
Yeah, but you've got the old
Stars and Stripes on your arm there,
and a cowboy look in your eye.
Oh, no offense.
This is just a serious situation,
and the last thing we need is some
Washington stooge to come supervise us.
Do we, lads?
Well, you got one,
so how about we start
with names and positions?
Mmm-hmm.
Adisa, structural.
Duncan Taylor, systems and OS analyst
and loyal British subject.
Hernandez, robotics.
Dussette.
Satcom and security.
And you are?
This is Mr. Jake Lawson.
You're Jake Lawson? The Jake Lawson?
You look much older
than I would've thought.
I mean, you look good---
...but your physical appearance is not,
does not match the amount of time
that has elapsed in your life.
Am I getting fired?
Okay, we don't have
a lot of time.
So we have three situations to examine.
Afghanistan, the scientist that died
here, and the new incident in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong?
No, that was a gas main explosion.
We all watched that on the telly.
All right, okay.
You just keep believing that.
I, on the other hand,
have a mystery that I'd like to solve
and prevent more deaths,
so feel free to join me.
Or not.
MAX". All right, quick question.
Okay, active shooter,
the president and I are both
in the line of fire.
Who do you save first? Me--
The president.
Oh, come on. You could take
a second just to think about that.
Sorry, baby.
Job comes first, same with you.
No, that's not true.
No, I have priorities and you,
you are my priority.
Come on, let's do it.
I kinda want to,
but you just keep talking.
I mean, why do we always
have to be sneaking around?
Come on, let's do it. Let's get married.
We can't.
It's against the rules.
One day, baby.
Um, you're gonna get that.
Because your job comes first.
No...
I'm gonna get it 'cause
I don't want it to interfere with this.
See?
Now I might just not save you.
Yeah, hello?
Max, it's Cheng.
Cheng, God, tell me
you're not in Hong Kong.
-Cheng?
-Last night,
I was right in the middle of it.
It was horrible. That's why I'm calling.
Phone service just came back on.
Yeah, well, you're lucky to be alive.
- I mean, those gas pipes?
- I'm not so sure that was the cause.
What do you mean? I don't follow.
It was abnormally hot
before the pipes blew.
The satellite sensor
should've recorded it, right?
I checked over a dozen times but I can't
access Dutch Boy's Hong Kong satellite.
My access has been blocked.
Check your H0|0Frame.
I don't understand.
We both have clearance.
CHENG". Exactly.
The only people that have authority to
block are in the building you work in.
Wait. What do you mean?
If someone is covering up
a system defect,
there's potential for critical failure
on a global scale.
If Dutch Boy has a catastrophic failure,
it can create something far worse than
the very thing we're trying to prevent,
what we call a geostorm.
What? Slow down, Cheng, all right?
A what?
A geostorm.
Simultaneous catastrophic weather events
triggered all over the globe.
Once they pass a minimum threshold, the
storms will start causing new storms,
like a chain reaction,
until they merge together.
It's gotta be a glitch.
I'll give you a call
when I know something.
All right. Thanks.
These pipes had not been
well maintained or upgraded in years.
Cheng thinks Hong Kong
has something to do with Dutch Boy.
You know, he's implying
some kind of cover-up.
I just got a text and POTUS
called a last-minute press briefing.
What, you can't stay?
Oh, when duty calls, duty calls.
"Neither rain nor snow
nor gloom of night," right?
Honey, that's the Postal Service.
We're the Secret Service.
Secret Service.
Oh, there's a difference?
Really?
I didn't know that.
Grab his laptop. Let's go.
So the satellite that went rogue
over Afghanistan, what type was that?
That's my fave, actually.
I call it a "rock 'n' roller."
Oh, the SR-22.
Uses sonic waves to slow
molecular movement causing cooling,
but, in that case, freezing. Why?
We don't know.
We checked the satellite's hard drives,
but the logs were wiped clean
by the malfunction.
All right. Let's pull up every
"rock 'n' roller" satellite we have
to see if we can find
any corruption in their logs.
Pull up every "rock 'n' roller"
in the net.
There's gotta be more than
1,000 of them.
Ah, 1,270, to be exact.
And we're gonna scan
each and every one of 'em.
Dana. Hey.
Hey. What are you doing here?
What do you mean,
"What am I doing here"?
I work here. I'm your boss.
Yeah, but what are you doing
down from Mount Olympus
and visiting me in Millennial Village?
Well, I have a bit of a favor
to ask you.
You're the best at what you do.
But I need you to keep this between us.
Okay.
I have a problem with my HoloFrame.
Do I look like a Genius Bar to you?
I'm sorry. I'm sitting here
defending the free world
against state operators
and cyberterrorists,
but Grandpa needs help fixing his phone.
I have a problem trying to get through
to satellite G-22 over Hong Kong.
So a satellite has a bad comm.
That happens.
No. No, not a satellite.
All of them.
Oh.
I am mildly intrigued. Stay.
Okay.
It looks like vanilla line disruption,
bad server relay, or trunk failure,
or something.
Are you still dating
that Secret Service chick?
What? No.
No, I'm not dating anyone.
Mmm-hmm.
Wait, look. Oh, my God.
Someone wanted to block your access
without you knowing it was intentional.
But this...
This is very intentional,
and it's very clever.
And I know what you're gonna say.
You're gonna say,
"Tell no one." And I won't.
But I didn't sign up to work here
so I could cubicle-squat 24/7.
So whatever is going on,
I want in on the action.
Well, let's hope there isn't any action.
And yeah,
tell no one.
Miss Fassbinder, we've just been given
a priority communication request.
From Climate Command?
The White House.
All right. So who are the yahoos in
Washington we gotta deal with on this?
I guess I would be the head yahoo.
Hello, guys.
Max tells me you don't have
a high opinion of politicians.
I didn't say that.
Well, neither do I.
We went through hell getting
the world on board for this program.
We've come too far for it to fail.
You and I both understand
why we cannot let that happen.
Yes, sir.
So if I find anything,
I'll report to you right away.
Actually,
you'll be reporting to Max here.
Good luck.
Have at it.
Thank you, sir.
I'll leave you two alone.
And if you need me, I'm in my office.
Thank you.
I'll be reporting to you?
You lied to me.
Again.
No, I just didn't answer
your ridiculous demand.
How do I switch this thing off?
There's something you need to know.
We've been having issues down here
accessing the Dutch Boy satcom.
We have reason to believe that it...
Well, it may not be accidental.
Might not be accidental?
Well, I've been trying to access
the Hong Kong satellite.
I knew it. I knew it!
You think it's possible?
Yeah. It's possible.
But even if you could access
the Hong Kong satellite remotely,
you're not gonna get the logs you need.
No. We gotta pull that information
from the actual satellite up here.
Okay. I can authorize that.
I don't need your authorization
for anything.
I'm sure that's really scary for you,
but how about you just count on me
to do my job, and say thank you?
Oh, count on you.
Remember the first time
I had to bail you out?
Oh, God. Jesus Christ!
Yeah, it was just one week
after Mom and Dad died.
You got arrested for fighting. Hmm?
That's when I realized that
despite everything I was going through,
I was gonna have
to be responsible for you.
All right, you know what?
Fine. It is what it is.
I guess I got no choice
but to count on you.
But if you ever authorize anything
without my approval,
you'll be on the next shuttle home.
Transmission ended.
Hong Kong satellite 022
inbound for examination.
All right.
Let's take this thing apart
and find out what happened in Hong Kong.
Bring it down.
It should have come down by now.
UTE". What is that?
I have no idea.
- All right, shut it down.
- It's not responding.
DUNCAN". Jesus, Hernandez!
Get down!
Get out of here! Go!
Somebody, open this door, now!
Watch out!
Shit!
All right, let's pick up
every single piece of this thing
and get it down to manufacturing.
Do you think we can retrieve
the logs from the hard drives?
Well, the accident created
an electrical short
and fried all the drives.
I mean, look at it. It's toast.
So we've lost all the drives
with possible corruption?
Not all of them.
UTE". What do you mean?
I was reviewing your video
of the accident that killed Makmoud.
Each of the panels that blew
has a drive inside.
And one of them got stuck
in the communication tower.
It looks like
the seal locks are still intact.
If we're lucky, the corrupted drive
will still be inside.
We gotta get that panel back.
Yeah, hello?
I just got into DC. We have to meet.
I figured it all out.
Meet me at 10:00 at the place across
the square where we used to have lunch.
Back in college.
All right. Yeah, I'll be there.
MAN". Ready to decompress.
All right. Door's open, kids.
You're clear to exit.
UTE". Step across the gravity threshold
and follow me.
Let's just get the panel,
see what's on those drives.
Okay.
UTE". There's the panel.
Wait. Hold up.
We designed the tower
to have emergency de-rig ports
so the bars can be moved easily.
Control, the panel is secured.
Roger that.
Come back now, kids. Come back.
UTE". We're on our way back.
UTE". Jake, what's happening?
JAKE". I don't know! I don't know!
UTE". Jake? Jake!
JAKE". I can't control the damn suit!
- What's going on?
- His suit is malfunctioning.
-Jake, do you read me?
-Duncan, tell him to cut it.
Jake, cut off the fuel intake.
JAKE". It's not responding!
Hang on, Jake.
JAKE". I can't hold it.
- Eject the pack- Eject the pack!
Oh, Christ. We're gonna lose him.
We're gonna lose him!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
You got the drive?
I grabbed it when I freed the panel.
You smashed up a dozen comm links,
TCAS sensors...
I'm fine, thank you very much.
What happened out there?
Propulsion throttle locked up.
And you lost the door panel,
which means no drive codes.
Back to square one.
Great.
Why didn't you tell them
about the drive?
Because someone just tried to kill me.
I know my crew. I trust them.
You think you know them.
But someone doesn't want us
to see what's on this drive.
Jake,
there's no corruption here at all.
The doors weren't accidentally
blown off. They were programmed to.
-This wasn't a malfunction.
-No.
Someone intentionally killed Makmoud.
No doubt the same person that tampered
with the Hong Kong satellite.
The user logins have been wiped clean.
We have no digital fingerprints.
No. That's what they think.
Login records are synced back
to the mainframe.
Yeah, but that's the problem.
If they're deleted in one place,
they're deleted everywhere.
No, everywhere they know about.
When we built Dutch Boy,
we put in a locked off library.
Something that would track
and archive everything.
Our saboteur's login info
is gonna be in there.
Nope.
You've been locked out.
But by who?
The virtual conference room.
How many have access
to those transmissions?
Anyone with level three access
and above.
Dozens of people.
Max.
-Max.
-What?
Relax. He'll be here soon.
What, really? I seem nervous?
Just a little.
He's here.
He's here?
No!No!
Cheng! My God!
No!
This is Agent Wilson.
Yes, I need an ambulance right now.
- Dupont Circle.
- Max...
Agent Wilson,
I have dispatched the ambulance.
You got me. You got me.
I'm here. Look at me. Look at me.
Zeus.Zeus.
What?
Virtual conference initiating.
Max? You okay?
They said it was urgent.
What is it?
Yeah. Um...
I wanted to apologize.
Ap0logize?
If you had any idea
what I just walked away from...
You're gonna drag me up here
just to apologize?
All right. Fine.
Apﬂlogy accepted.
Hey, Max, we don't walk out
on each other.
That's the unspoken code
between brothers.
You remember that day
Dad took us fishing?
Yeah, he dropped his cell phone
in Key Biscayne.
Proof the Lawsons aren't fishermen.
Four hours,
the three of us didn't catch a thing.
I tried to sabotage Dad's reel
so we could leave.
That pin
at the highest part of the spool,
pulled it so the level mechanism
would pop out.
Of course, Dad was a government spy
his whole life, caught me red-handed.
"Trust me," he said.
"l get it. No one likes to fail.
"But I'd rather not catch fish
with my family
"than catch 20 fish alone."
I didn't even understand
what he meant back then.
But I do now.
Take care, Max.
End transmission.
Transmission ended.
What was all that?
That was the first decent conversation
we've had in years.
- Hey.
- on, my God!
Would you relax?
What?
Do you have a moment?
Yes! I do. I got your message.
Jesus.
What happened?
Did Secret Service Barbie dump you?
I need to show you something.
Take a look at this.
You remember that day
Dad took us fishing?
He dropped his cell phone
in Key Biscayne.
Our dad never took us fishing.
Oh.
That's sad.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not good at the, like,
"Talk about your daddy issues"
kind of friend thing. I just...
What? No, no, no...
It's a code.
"He dropped his cell phone
in Key Biscayne."
His cell phone number is the key.
Take a look at the digits.
Okay, you got your first number,
that's your first word.
Second number, nine,
you move on nine words.
-That's your second word.
-Mmm-hmm.
Third number, nine again.
Another nine, you move on. Then nine,
then two, then nine, then five,
and so on and so on until you get
an entirely different message.
Oh. So, who came up
with this encryption, a 12-year-old?
No. I was 13.
Okay.
So, one-nine-nine-nine,
two-nine-five-five,
eight-seven-one and go.
Proof of sabotage at
the highest level of government.
Trust no one.
Well, you said
you were looking for action.
Uh, yeah, but I mean, holy shit.
If you don't wanna take this any
further, I totally understand.
No. I do, I do. I just...
I do and I don't.
Kinda like going on a rollercoaster
or eating Chipotle.
What's our next move?
Okay. I need you to find anything
you can on a file named "Project Zeus."
"Project Zeus"?
Yeah.
Okay. Looks like we have ourselves
a bro-spiracy theory.
-Just run the damn search.
-Yeah.
Um...
I am getting a hit.
But it looks like it's double encrypted.
It's a little 0CD.
Can you break it?
Yeah, I could,
but I can't do it from here.
The file's under a White House security
network, and it's just not hackable.
I'd have to log in,
and I don't have the credentials for it.
Shit. Neither do I.
I don't know anyone who does.
Yeah, you do.
Max?
Freeze.
Oh! Holy shit!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Honey, relax!
Who is this girl in our house?
I can explain everything.
Mmm, that sounds really pervy.
-Shut up.
-Okay, I'm sorry. I will.
I broke one of your wine glasses. Um...
ltjust fell and I promise
I'm gonna reimburse you.
I have the money. I'm sorry.
Talk.
This is Dana.
She works with me in State.
Now, I asked her here
because I need her help,
and as it turns out,
I need your help, too.
She's hot!
I know how much
your job means to you.
I took an oath, Max.
We have rules.
Technically, you're not supposed
to be sleeping together either--
Dana.
You're asking me to commit a crime.
You're soliciting a Secret Service agent
to break into the White House server
and illegally obtain files.
And you thought I would say yes!
-I still think you're gonna say yes.
-Why?
Because I'm the one who's asking you.
And if I'm asking you,
well, then it must be important.
And you know that it's bigger
than you and me.
"You and l."
Shut up.
Sarah, please.
One time.
We need to play back the security
cameras without alerting anyone.
Someone killed Makmoud.
We find out why,
we know who's behind this.
But you can't access the cameras
without it being logged in.
That's why we're going to the back-up
server room.
You see? It comes in handy
that I built the place.
Yes, but I live here.
Show off.
Makmoud was prepping diagnostics
on the Afghan sat
while we launched a replacement.
Son of a bitch.
He pulled something off the sat.
Poor bastard figured it out,
and they killed him to make sure
no one else did.
There are no cameras allowed
in the locker rooms.
Then let's go take a look for ourselves.
181.
What's the code?
Seven, six, three, six, three.
What do you think
you're doing?
You know what happened to me out there
wasn't an accident.
Whoever did that
killed Makmoud.
And what makes you think it is not me?
Because if it was you,
I'd be dead already.
Dussette, lower your gun.
Whatever you're looking for,
it is not in this locker.
I was here when Makmoud came in.
He put his stuff in an empty one.
Why didn't you tell me?
You watched the same
security footage as I did.
I was just waiting to see who was
gonna come and look for Makmoud's stuff.
It's in here.
UTE". Two, six, six, five, three.
Bingo.
This is everything he copied
off the satellite onto his HoloFrame.
That's a virus.
That wasn't generated by the satellite's
on board computer.
Because they were planted.
Makmoud found the virus and got killed
before he could tell anyone.
Oh, I got it-
All right, here we go.
Project Zeus.
There are tens of thousands of
storm simulations in here,
and each one is starting
in a different place.
MAX". They all end the same way.
A geostorm.
I mean, unlike anything we've ever seen.
Dana, can you show us just the
simulation that begins in Afghanistan?
Yeah, sure.
Okay, now filter those
so that the second malfunction's
over Hong Kong.
Where are you going with this?
What if Cheng realized that someone
was following one of his scenarios?
You know, making it look like
a predicted pattern of malfunction,
disguising a crime
like a series of accidents.
It might actually be
a series of accidents.
If it were,
they wouldn't have killed him.
Someone has weaponized Dutch Boy.
Virtual conference initiating.
H9)’-
New face?
Yeah. A friend.
Uh, she's keeping things off
the monitor channels,
so we're good.
- So you got my message?
- Yeah, I got your message-.
It's, uh... It's worse than we thought.
Whoever's doing this is using
Dutch Boy to target cities.
Yeah, they're disguising their moves
as malfunctions.
They already killed the man
who found out about this,
and I don't think they're done.
Yeah.
This was my life's work, Max.
You know, they said it was impossible,
but we pulled it off.
And it worked
perfectly, without fail,
day after day, year after year.
So what do people do with it?
Turn it into a gun.
I know.
I know. It's not too late.
We can fix this
before it happens again,
but I can't do it on my own.
I need you. I need you to tell me,
how are they controlling Dutch Boy?
- I know how they're controlling it.
- How?
A virus.
Well, can you stop it?
There's only one way.
We can shut down Dutch Boy temporarily.
The reboot will flush out the system,
kill the virus, and revert back
to the fail-safe OS.
Okay. Let's do it.
I'm authorizing.
Yeah, I think we've established
that I don't really wait for that.
This isn't a Chromebook.
You don't just put your finger
on the power button.
You need the kill codes.
And the only one who has those
is the president.
So let's just go to the president
and tell him what we know.
No. You can't go to Palma.
We need way more proof than I have.
We're talking about shutting down
Dutch Boy.
I mean, even for an hour,
that puts the whole planet at risk.
No, I don't think you understand.
Someone sealed off the backdoor
into the system.
A backdoor almost no one knew existed.
But the president did.
No. Jake, come on. What?
Are you out of your mind?
Not saying it's him. I'm saying,
"What if?"
Who else has the resources
to pull this off?
Murder, cover-up, a virus that can only
be stopped with the codes in his pocket.
Why? Huh? Tell me, why?
Why would he do that?
We're two weeks away from transferring
Dutch Boy to the rest of the world.
Two weeks away from losing
autonomous control.
Now, he talks a good game,
but he's never gonna let it happen.
A series of disasters,
an international crew to take the fall,
and he'll have to cancel the hand off.
And who would blame him?
All right. You stay on top
of your satellites.
Max.
Max, don't do anything stupid.
Let's go.
Okay? They already
tried to kill me once.
Max!
Transmission ended.
President Palma,
a couple questions, please, sir.
REPORTER 2-. Thoughts before you head to
the national convention in Orlando, sir?
Mr. President, do you care
to make a statement?
Mr. President, a moment
before you head to Orlando?
My friends
from Washington, D.C.
I could never get on a plane without
saying hello to you. It's impossible.
What are you doing here?
-Are you insane?
-Sarah, look.
Jake needs us to
steal the kill codes from Palma.
Us?
You're asking me to help you
on the word of your asshole brother,
who you haven't even spoken to
for three years.
Yeah.
Think about it. Afghanistan, Hong Kong,
Cheng, the crazy sim shit,
the death on the space station. Come on.
Look, you gotta trust me on this,
all right? I'm not kidding around here.
-Okay.
-Look.
The codes are on Pa|ma's HoloFrame.
We can't do it on the plane.
Why not?
Too many eyes. He's never alone.
All right, then what's the play?
Palma wants some private time to shower
and make calls before the after-parties.
You follow. I'll get you inside.
I can steal the codes while he's
in the shower.
-That's the idea.
-Yes, it is.
- Warning.
- Out of the way.
- All satellite communication offline.
All satellite communication offline.
All crew report to stations immediately.
Oh, my God.
We have nearly 200 satellites
reporting malfunctions,
most of them nearing critical.
Pull up the satellite closest to
cﬂﬁcaloveﬂoad.
We've lost all control
of the Tokyo satellite.
Max.
I didn't know you were coming
to the convention.
Yeah. You know,
my dad lives in Florida,
so I promised I'd get him
into the convention.
We need every vote, right?
Yeah, well, bring him to the green room.
We'll do a little photo op.
Oh, that's very kind of you, sir.
Thank you.
We've got reports of extreme weather
anomalies building
over Brazil, Mexico, Bucharest,
and Belgrade.
There's over 1,000 storm warnings
issued around the world.
Rio de Janeiro satellite critical.
--Retrieval routine offline.
Chart a new course!
Get us close to the nearest satellites
going critical.
-What are you trying to do?
-We're gonna launch the replacements.
-As many as we can, as fast as we can.
-Wait, wait, wait...
We have to retrieve the other
satellites first.
Or the replacements will crash
into them.
They're programmed to arrive
in the exact same destination.
And they'll knock out
the infected satellites.
-Yeah.
-Of course!
All crews report to stations
for Rio satellite replacement.
G0 for launch.
Away she goes.
Satellite replacement for Rio
on its way.
Warning. Satellite on collision course.
Disable the retro-boosters.
Don't let it slow down.
Load 'em up and keep 'em coming!
Warning. Geostorm alert.
Time to geostorm: one hour, 30 minutes.
Four more years!
Thank you. As you know,
the environment
was my late wife's
great passion and purpose.
And I know that she would be
extremely proud...
Caused by
the worst hailstorm in recorded history.
There has been another extreme weather
event, this time in Rio de Janeiro.
An offshore cold front moved rapidly
across land,
plunging the city into
dangerously low temperatures.
There are reports
of numerous casualties,
but we don't know how many at this time.
We're also hearing that a cargo plane
may have crashed in the city itself,
possibly related to the freezing cold.
Tokyo and Rio are the first catastrophic
events since the launch of Dutch Boy.
Stay tuned after the break, when we'll
be joined by our reporter Sally Jones.
MAXI Oh, God.
DEKKOM". Hey, Max!
Where's your daddy?
Oh. Uh...
You know what? He got so caught up
in all the excitement.
I recruited you for this position.
I know everything about you.
Your brother, and your mother's death,
your father's death, everything.
Why'd you lie to me, hmm?
Why'd you insist on making this trip?
Tell me what's wrong.
Maybe I can help you, maybe I can't.
All right, look.
I gotta tell you something. Come here.
We are 90 minutes away from
a global storm we won't recover from.
And I need the president's kill codes.
Come again?
We gotta shut Dutch Boy down, now.
You're serious.
You say you hired me
because you believe in me, right?
All right, well, I need you
to believe in me now.
Well, we've gotta brief the president.
Get to Cape Canaveral.
No, no, no. We can't do that, sir.
Why not?
I believe he's the one who initiated it.
United we stand.
United we can.
Four more years! Four more years!
You better be goddamn sure of yourself,
making accusations like that.
With all due respect, we don't have time
to argue about this.
Palma and I go way back.
Why would he do that? That's insane.
Yeah, well, he's doing it.
What's your proof?
Yeah, I got proof.
Dozens of files, all right?
In Project Zeus. It's all there.
Well, we can't get the kill codes
from the president.
Why not?
Because the president is the kill codes.
Biometrics. Ten fingerprints,
two retina scans.
Well, what do we do?
I'll have to reason with him.
We'll have to reason with him.
Satellites are
going critical over Florida.
Load a replacement sat, now.
Station
self-destruct sequence initiated.
Phase one commencing now.
Okay. Shut that down!
I can't. I'm locked out.
We built in backdoor overrides.
Yeah, I'm trying them.
If we lose the station, we won't be able
to control the satellites.
Self-destruct?
Why would you build that
into the station?
In case it fell to Earth.
Where's Duncan?
He's the one with enough programming
expertise to override the commands.
Duncan.
JAKE". That's the fuel tanks.
They're the first to go.
Then section by section
until command and retrieval.
Okay, everybody, get to the shuttles!
Evacuate!
Come on, we gotta hurry! Go, go, go!
Jake, what are you still doing here?
That felt good.
Been wanting to do that
since I first met you.
Have you gone mad?
Yeah, pretty much.
The virus.
You're the only one that could have
put it in the system.
You're the only one who could've
sealed off the backdoor.
The only one that could've helped
to pull this off.
I need the overrides for the
self-destruct to the station, now!
I mean, what for?
I'm not gonna be here when it blows.
But you will.
Come on, man. Why'd you do it?
Well, you know what us
lowly scientists get paid?
Take that times 1,000.
What difference is it gonna make?
If you don't stop, there's not gonna be
a planet to spend it on.
Please. We're gonna keep
all the best bits.
Aren't you a little bit curious
to watch the world burn?
No. 'Cause millions of people
are gonna die.
And one of them's my daughter.
Oh, shit.
Holding room for the president
down on the left.
We'll confront him there.
Project Zeus.
Did Cheng tell you anything else?
Cheng?
But this president
knows that hope is not a plan.
This president knows
that despite how far we've come,
there is much more work ahead.
Working to save our planet
is my first priority as vice president.
This is but a stepping stone
to the success
and greatness that can and will be
the future of our society.
Excuse me.
That's why I'm here tonight with
the Speaker of the House,
the Senate pro tempore,
and President Pa|ma's whole cabinet.
We all stand united in support...
Palma doesn't leave the building.
-Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
Where have you been?
Come here.
It's not the president, all right?
It's Dekkom.
Dekkom? How do you know?
Because he just tried to kill me.
That's how I know.
Look, the sim shows Orlando
is the next city to be hit.
Here? Why would he do that?
Because Dekkom wants Palma
trapped here, all right?
And everyone else who's next in line
for the presidency.
Are we still stealing the codes?
The president is the kill codes,
all right? They're biometric.
If Palma dies,
Dutch Boy can't be stopped.
Sure, kidnap the president.
That sounds like the reasonable move.
Yeah, well,
it's the only move we've got.
Unless you wanna steal his fingers
and his eyes.
Huh?
We go now.
You get us a car.
I'll get us a president.
All right, good.
The program did not gain
the immense
international support that it...
Gunman spotted. POTUS is compromised.
Evac to secure location Alpha.
Get him out, get him out!
GO, go:
Secret Service! Get back! Get back!
You got a 20 on the shooters?
Front mezzanine by exit 212!
Two men with automatics!
- I'm on it! You get POTUS!
- You two,
secure this entrance!
No one comes down this hallway!
Nobody gets through! Hard room, Lammy.
- Got it!
- You two,
clear the emergency exit now!
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
You need to come with me.
This eXil‘ is Off limits!
Please remain calm.
Seriously? A self-driving cab?
Dana jacked it remotely.
It was all I could get.
What the hell's going on here, Lawson?
Please, sir. Look, I'll explain
everything in the car.
Please, sir! We don't have much time!
Keep moving! Get to the shuttles!
Keep going!
Quick!
Time to geostorm, 55 minutes.
Sir, I can barely hear you.
The storm is causing too much static.
The Secret Service
will be homing in
on the beacon
on the president's HoloFrame.
You have got to get to him
before they do.
Under no circumstances can he make it
out of Orlando.
Our man on the space station
did his job.
-Now you do yours.
-Copy that. Got it.
- Dekkom?
- It's the perfect weapon, sir.
All right, Dekkom is trying to change
the map of the world.
And what? Blame it on a computer glitch?
Yeah, well, that and a dead president.
He'll take office after wiping out
everyone in the line of succession.
Dear God.
-Get to cover! Under the bridge.
-Sir.
You are implicating
the Secretary of State in this.
Do you realize you're committing--
Treason. Oh, yeah.
I kidnapped the president.
I've stolen state secrets.
Anything I'm forgetting, honey?
Honey?
Guilty.
It took years
for Dekkom to plan this, sir.
A president's schedule
always changes last minute.
This is the one day and date
he could be sure wouldn't move.
Having my brother and I
lead the investigation
was a setup from the start.
Think about it.
He hired us to fail.
Get down!
All right, it's saying
we're back in the clear,
where the four meets the 91!
Just gotta take care
of a little problem first.
Hold on!
MAXI NO!
Marry her.
No. We're fine here.
A lightning storm in Orlando
has caused a horrific explosion
at the DNC.
There is no official word
on the whereabouts of the president...
I don't know. I don't know.
I just can't get in touch
with Jake.
And we have reports now of explosions
on the space station.
Honey, the Orlando storm is getting
really close to your dad's place.
I can't get through to him.
Has he texted you?
He's not there.
He's there.
Of a major issue on the space station.
Attention all crews.
Now loading final shuttle.
Please board your designated
evacuation shuttles immediately.
Shuttle launch sequence initiated.
Jake.
- I'm not coming.
- What?
When my brother gets those kill codes,
someone has to be here
to execute the program.
No. We need to go.
We haven't heard from him in hours.
ltrust him.
You know the reboot
has to be done manually.
Then I stay. I'm the commander.
No.
I'm the only one my brother
will trust with the codes,
so I need your HoloFrame.
You have to insert it manually
at the core of the mainframe.
You can find it, yes?
-Yes.
-Good.
Goodbye, Ute.
Auf Wiedersehen, Jake.
DEKKOM". Pull over here.
The president's beacon shows him
heading right towards us.
You really wanna drive back into that?
Yeah, right after it passes,
I'll be the sole survivor,
ready to be sworn in as
the next President of the United States.
Here they come.
Fire.
You thought the president was the only
one who could be tracked?
-How in hell did you--
-How?
Because I'm the goddamn President
of the United States of America.
You're done, Leonard.
He's all yours.
Wait, wait! Wait a minute.
I've given you an opportunity,
Mr. President.
You should take it.
An opportunity? Let him go!
It's genocide, Leonard!
You say genocide,
I say preemptive strike.
You've lost your mind!
Tomorrow the sun will rise.
All our enemies will be gone.
Wiped away as if by the hand of God.
Why would you do this?
Because no one else would.
I'm turning the clock back to 1945,
when America was a shining city on a
hill, not a bank disguised as a country.
By playing God?
What the hell is Dutch Boy
if not playing God?
Ask Max. He knows.
Science is all about playing God.
Sometimes God doesn't play so nice.
Yeah, well,
you know what my brother would say?
What?
Get him outta here!
Let's go, Lawson!
That's my fiancé.
Get the president to cover! Hurry!
Mr. President.
We got the kill codes.
You'll have to hurry.
The station is in full shutdown.
What about the crew?
Safe.
But Jake decided to stay.
To reboot the satellites.
Your brother is waiting for you.
Come on.
Virtual conference initiating.
Hey-
MAXI Jake.
Jake, it was Dekkom.
Well, I did say I might be wrong.
Mr. President.
How's Hannah?
Oh, she's good. She's safe.
Atlanta wasn't hit.
Thank God.
Identity verified.
Shutdown protocol transfer initiating.
It's gonna take 60 seconds to upload.
How long till the self-destruct?
Eight minutes,
give or take.
Mr. Lawson,
we thank you for your sacrifice.
Wait. What the hell's going on?
You've done your part, Max.
Jake, what is going on?
Now it's time for me to do mine.
No,no,no.
The kill codes don't stop
the self-destruct, do they?
Do they?
No,
only the geostorm.
The station self-destruct
can't be reversed.
Come on, come on.
There must be a way, huh?
Come on. It's all my fault.
I'm the one who put you up there!
Hey, it's okay.
I wanted to go. It was my choice.
God knows,
I haven't always made the right ones.
You know, you were right,
little brother.
I was supposed to look after you.
But you looked after me.
Can you forgive me?
Yeah, always.
Look after my little girl.
Stay in her life.
I will.
We should've done this
a long time ago, huh?
Yeah.
You're a good man, Jake.
I'll see you, kiddo.
Transfer complete.
Time to geostorm: 5 minutes, 51 seconds.
Warning. Core rotation has terminated.
We don't know
what's happening up there.
We just know the station has suffered
a devastating accident of some kind.
We're being told now
it is beyond repair or salvation.
Honey.
He's coming back.
He promised me.
We will keep you updated
with any new developments.
Self-destruct entering phase four.
Code invalid.
UTE". Need a hand?
Wrong door.
What're you doing here?
I told you. I live here.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Time to geostorm: 1 minute, 40 seconds.
Uploading kill codes.
Satellite shutdown in process.
When the last satellite
cycles down, let me know.
I'll manually reboot the entire system.
-That should flush out the virus.
-Okay.
Five to go.
Three.
-Come on, baby.
-Two.
And one.
Manual reboot activated.
Status: rebooting.
The net is back up.
The virus is gone.
Transferring control of the net
back to NASA.
Jake!
We QOt you!
Warning.
Self-destruct entering final stage.
Best seat in the house.
Ute,
do you believe in a Hail Mary?
Follow me. We gotta get
to the satellite.
JAKE". I've got you.
We've gotta get away as far as we can
before the final detonation.
Dock releasing.
And it appears
we have lost the space station.
A tragic ending
for the two heroes still aboard.
Hey, Max, take a look.
I'm picking up exhaust flares,
and they're pulsing in a Mayday pattern.
See if we can turn
one of the shuttles around.
JAKE". Hopefully, someone sees this.
Fingers crossed.
Hernandez, you son of a bitch!
Thank the Mexican.
Yes! Come here. Yes!
NEWSCASTER". A miracle indeed.
The shuttle you see is bringing home
all the ISS crew members
who remained on the station.
Hi, Jake. I'm Sarah, Max's fiancée.
Oh, welcome to the family.
Well done, well done, both of you.
Sorry I doubted you, Mr. President.
Yeah, well, you were wrong, Jake, again.
Well, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Never listen to me.
God, it's good to have you back, man.
Good to be back.
It's a nice place
you got here, Jake.
Thank you.
So when you heading back up?
-In a week.
-Yeah?
Yeah, a lot of work left.
But I'll be back.
I know.
-This sucks.
-Yeah, seriously, this is so boring.
You know what?
I can't do this for another second.
Now, Why'd you make us do this
in the first place?
I don't know.
I was trying to relive a moment.
A moment? What moment?
We never went fishing with Dad.
You made that whole story up.
Yeah, but that was a good story,
though,huh?
I mean, you gotta give me that.
I mean, it had a moral and everything.
Moral? What moral?
HANNAH". You can't undo the past.
All you can do is face what's ahead.
NASA maintained the satellites
while we rebuilt the space station.
We made it safer, made it stronger.
It belongs to all of us now.
One planet, one people.
And as long as we remember that
we share one future, we will survive.