Subs By Asmita
Psagmeno.com
Subtitles/Trailers/Screenshots
In the future, the line between
human and machine is disappearing
Advancments in technology allow humans
to enhance themselves with cyernetic parts
Hanka Robotics,
funded by the government,
is developing a military operative
that will blur the line even further
By transplanting a human brain
into a fully synthetic body,
they will combine the strongest
attributes of Human and Robot
PROJECT 2571
Oxygen levels are dropping
Brain function, normal.
Cerebral salvage, ready to proceed
Robotic skeleton, prepared
and waiting for brain insertion.
Initiate Project 2571.
Now your eyes are gonna open.
You're safe.
It's ok, just breathe.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
Good.
That's good.
Hello Mira.
I'm Dr. Ouelet.
Do you remember anything
about the attack?
What...?
I was... drowning.
There was water.
That's right, you were on a boat.
A refugee boat.
It was sunk by terrorists.
Why can't I feel my body?
Mira, your body was damaged,
we couldn't save it.
Only your brain survived.
We made you a new body.
A synthetic shell.
But your mind, your soul,
your ghost,
it's still in there.
Please.
Sedate her.
Will it work?
Absolutely.
She's a miracle.
A machine can't lead,
it can only follow orders.
A machine can't imagine,
or care, or intuit.
But as a human mind in
a cybernetic frame,
Mira can do all those things
and more.
The first of her kind.
She will join Section 9
as soon as she's operational.
Please don't do that.
You're reducing a complex human
to a machine.
I don't think of her as a machine.
She's a weapon.
And the future of my company.
ONE YEAR LATER
The first artificially created
memory enhancement.
Sirenum training protocol is the
fastest and most efficient way
to develop your ability...
Stronger than ever.
Experience your power.
Cybercrime is a Type 1 offense.
Minimum punishment: 15 years in prison.
Hanka Robotics guarantees
personal safety against...
All patrolling area units,
be advised possible cybercrime
activity in the vicinity.
Airspace in adjoining areas
will be locked down.
Section 9 is currently on site.
Repeat: All patrolling area units,
be advised, possible cyber crime...
This is Major.
I'm on site.
Awaiting instructions.
Analyze and report.
I'm human, I'm flawed,
but I embrace change
and enhancement.
Now, there's nothing I can't do.
Nothing I can't know, nothing I can't be.
I want you to listen to something.
Au clair de la lune,
mon ami Pierrot.
It's my 4 year old daughter.
In the time it took her to sing that
lullaby she learned to speak fluent French.
Do you know that song...?
- Is there an echo box up here?
- Why do you ask?
Someone's scanning data traffic.
Trace where it's transmitting.
Let's see who's worth
this kind of surveillance.
Accessing hotel security network.
What are you seeing, sir?
I've got a lot of hotel to scan.
There is a banquet room reserved for
the President of the African Federation.
Dr. Osmond is invited
on behalf of Hanka Robotics.
Got it. 43rd floor.
Someone's contacted the president's staff.
Someone's watching him.
Dr. Osmond,
what is it you want from us?
I think it's more about what
Hanka Robotics can do for you.
73% of this world has woken up
to the age of cyber enhancement.
Do you really wanna be left behind?
My people embrace cyber enhancement,
as do I.
There's no one who really
understands the risk
to individuality, identity,
messing with the human soul.
Gentlemen, excuse me,
I think you have the wrong...
Hallway. Six men.
Shots fired.
Section 9 ETA?
- Two minutes out, Major.
- Too long.
I'm going in.
Hold!
Mayor, stop!
I've heard this speech before
from your competitors.
- And now Hanka Robotics serves it...
- What are you doing?
Look.
This is what I'm talking about.
Major!
Initiate the hack.
Help me. Please.
Don't let me die.
Who sent you?
Help me. Please.
Answer me!
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics
and be destroyed.
You okay?
You're injured.
You're not the same.
Hey, it's just a robot!
Your skin deserves the best, so do you.
Try our hand cream.
DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE,
CENTRAL OFFICE, SECTION 9
- So what do we have on Osmond?
- So far, very little.
He was the head
of Hanka's Robotics Division.
Human,
but of course cyber enhanced.
So how did they hack him?
Somehow this geisha bot
got past his encryption.
Something's different.
What'd you get?
Why are you always thinking
he's out there enhancing.
Because he is.
Cyber mech liver.
Been saving up for a while.
Now it's last call every night.
You got enhanced
so you can drink more?
Embrace enhancements, Togusa.
We wouldn't be here without it.
I'm all human and happy,
thanks.
Any more information
about the seized geisha bot?
Hanka's running scans.
Dr. Dahlin will have the
reports ready but...
I've been talking to the Prime Minister.
He wants a full report.
Togusa.
Following last night's attack,
3 more Hanka scientists
were murdered,
at the company's central laboratory.
The first two were shot.
And the third was beaten to death
by his own service robot.
All showed signs of cerebral hacking.
The same as the geisha did to Osmond.
And all were senior figures in Hanka.
Just like Osmond.
A message was left
at each of the crime scenes
by someone identifying himself...
as Kuze.
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics
and be destroyed.
Togusa.
You and Ladriya go speak to Mr. Cutter,
the CEO of Hanka.
Major and Batou
take a look at Dahlin report.
Find out what has been
recovered from the geisha.
Major!
I told you not jump off.
I had to, or more would have died.
You're a member of my team,
and my responsibility
I will find him and I will kill him.
It's what I am built for, isn't it?
You are more than just a weapon.
You have a soul, a ghost.
When we see our
uniqueness as a virtue,
only then will we find peace.
Safely reconfiguring the
child's genetic structure.
Families built better.
What was going on with
you at the hotel last night?
- Nothing, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Hey, sweetheart, want an upgrade?
- Move.
- I have anything you want.
- Back off!
- Hey, Ming!
- Hey, Batou!
- Got your bones.
- Thanks man.
- What are they for?
- For the dogs.
For someone who doesn't like people
how come you care about dogs so much?
Don't know. I like just strays
and they like me.
They like you 'cause you feed them.
You got no heart.
Hey, girls!
Hey Gabriel!
Meet Major.
Major, Gabriel.
I used to have a dog.
Seriously?
I had you down, as more of a cat person.
You don't talk about that stuff.
What?
- Your past.
- I don't remember much.
Just fragments, bits and pieces.
What about family?
My parents, they died
bringing us to this country.
Our boat sank in the harbor.
I almost drowned.
It feels like there's always
this thick fog over my memory
and I can't seen through it.
You're lucky.
Every single day,
I get screwed by my memories.
It's better to be pure.
Like you.
HANKA CENTRAL OFFICE OF ROBOTICS
Welcome to Hanka Robotics.
All visitors must display
appropriate credentials at all times.
Opens and close, please.
Your have damaged internal systems.
Maybe next time you can design me better.
- How are you?
- I'm fine. I can't feel anything.
No you, in There.
I've been having glitches.
But they'll pass.
- Have you been taking your medication?
- Yeah.
These ones are still cycling.
I had two this morning.
- Sound or image?
- Both.
I see it.
You made any unencrypted downloads?
- No. Just delete them from me.
- Consent?
My name is Major Mary Killian.
I give my consent to delete this data.
It's done.
- No big deal.
- What are they?
Sensory echoes from your mind, shadows.
I'm not sure.
How do you know what's a glitch
and what's me?
The glitches have a different texture...
to the rest of your code.
I can see everything.
All of your thoughts, your... decisions.
- I guess privacy is just for humans.
- You are human.
People see you as human.
Everyone around me seems to fit.
They seem connected to something.
Something I'm... not.
- It's like I have no past.
- Of course you have a past.
And with time you'll feel more and more
connected to it and to them.
Opens and close, please.
We cling to memories
as if they define us, but...
they really don't.
What we do is what defines us.
You are entering a Hanka secure area.
Authorized personnel only.
Please disable communication enhancement.
I'm busy.
Dr. Dahlin!
Are you finished yet?
If you hadn't riddled
the Geisha with bullets,
this would be much easier.
- I didn't shoot'em.
- I did.
This is gonna take days.
I need to run hundreds
of potential simulations.
We don't have the time.
She was a Hanka companion bot.
But she was reprogrammed
for cerebral hacking.
What was on her drives?
Nothing. The data was destroyed
as it was transmitted.
No sign of what she was after.
Her hardware was vandalized.
They ripped her up.
Then I have to do a deep dive.
You can't encrypt during a deep dive
I know.
They could've left traps in her.
Mag pulses, viruses.
She's right.
You will be exposing your mind to
who ever hacked her. You'll be wide open.
I have to get inside her memory.
It's the fastest way to find Kuze.
It's too dangerous.
And highly irresponsible.
Are you sure?
You see any bad code headed my way,
pull me out.
How come you're the one sweating?
Run it.
Cyber mind connection to the Major,
now active...
and unencrypted
consent required for data download.
My name is Major Mira Killian
and I give my consent.
Disconnect. Get her out.
- Get her out!
- I'm trying, but she's being hacked.
Get her out now!
Now!
Are you okay?
I know this place.
They run black market here.
You tooled up?
- Yep.
- Target is in the basement. I'll lead.
Switching to mind coms.
- Hope you've been practicing.
- That's unfair.
Just text me the moment
you are in.
Get the hang of it.
Two mercs at the door.
Armed and enhanced.
Copy that.
We got it covered.
There's a lot of heat in here
for a nightclub.
It's a Yakuza club. What did you expect?
I quite like the place.
Why doesn't that surprise me?
I'm gonna have to draw some attention.
See if I can access the basement that way.
You're not here
looking for any trouble, are you?
I'm just here for the girls... and beer.
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for someone.
You been here before?
My friend had some mech work done here.
Industry stuff.
We don't do mech work here.
My mistake.
Why don't you come have fun with us?
Have some privacy.
I'm in.
I'll be here when you need me.
- You say your friend worked here?
- I said my friend had work done here.
She's human?
Your friend.
What's that supposed to mean?
Batou.
Can you hear me?
Who did this stunning work on you?
It's divine.
Ladriya... guns.
Here.
Batou, I'm losing signal.
Don't worry sweety.
We have privacy.
Listen.
No signals going in or out.
Major, I'm in position. Do you copy?
Beer.
If you don't answer,
you're gonna hurt my feelings.
Ladriya, do you have Major on Comms?
Got nothing. Signal's still blocked.
I'm afraid I get bored rather easily, so...
You don't wanna talk...
Maybe you wanna dance!
Major, come on. Answer me.
I thought you said no trouble.
Dance!
The truth is...
I wasn't built to dance.
Back on comms.
I'm heading to the back room.
I missed you. I'll meet you there.
Collaborate with Hanka Robotics
and be destroyed.
Major?
Where's Batou?
In enhancement, next door.
He's doing well.
You took most of the blast.
I saw him down there.
It was like...
He waited to see me.
We synaptic scanned you.
Everything you witnessed
went to Section 9 to evaluate.
You know, the scan...
also turned up the number of glitches.
They've been getting worse.
Since when?
Since the deep dive.
Do any of the glitches
mean something to you?
No.
They don't.
You've been inside
the same shell as he has.
That could have very serious consequences.
You were not authorized
to deep dive the geisha.
You're disappointed.
No, I'm worried.
You're not invulnerable.
I can repair your body,
but I can't protect your mind.
Why not?
You can see all my thoughts so...
You should be able to secure them.
Try and understand
your importance Mira.
You're what everyone will become one day.
You don't know how alone
that makes me feel.
I can see you out there, you know.
How many fingers am I holding up?
Funny.
Say something nice.
You chose those?
They're tactical.
- Always for the job.
- What else I got?
- They suit you.
- Yeah?
I got night vision, zoom...
and X-ray.
I guess I see like you now.
Don't worry, you'll get used to it.
Thanks for saving my ass.
Glad to see you're okay.
Major?
Could you feed the dogs for me?
I don't wanna scare them.
Anytime.
Are you insufficiently funded, Mr. Aramaki?
Is section 9 missing some
critical operational resource?
We have everything that we require.
Major is our most sophisticated weapon
only if she's intact.
And Dr. Ouelet informed me that
you let her dive a corrupted geisha.
You realize the supreme importance
that Hanka represents to this government.
Major is the future of my company.
If you compromise
your systems again...
I will burn this section.
Yes sir.
Mr. Cutter.
Be careful who you the threaten.
I'm accountable to the Prime Minister,
not to Hanka.
Create your own beauty.
Beauty enhanced.
You human?
Yeah.
Can you take that off?
So I can see your face?
What does that feel like?
It feels...
different.
What are you?
SECURE PROJECT 2571
HANKA PERSONNEL FILES
Look at me.
Tell me what they took from me.
I'm sorry.
They never told us.
It feels weird driving
with these eyes.
Why do you take that?
Keeps my brain from rejecting
this body.
Major, Batou, you need to get here.
What've you got?
Another Hanka scientist
has been found dead.
It's Dahlin.
Got it.
Major this way.
SECURE - PROJECT 2571
What is that?
She found what Kuze stole from Osmond.
It's a list of everyone
who worked on a project called 2571.
That's who he's targeting.
Is there anyone else on that list?
DR. OUELET
Find Ouelet. Now!
She's in transit. Her comms are down.
I'm looking at her and I'mm thinking:
"You want me to pay for violin too?"
Don't get me wrong.
I love that kid to pieces.
I do. She's amazing.
But when she practices that thing,
it is painful, right?
Why not piano?
I mean, it's the same price,
and doesn't sound so bad.
At least if you can't play that proper,
it sounds...
2-5-7-1!
Tell me everything!
Are you prepare
to die for 2-5-7...?
Go!
Who is Kuze?
- Why does he wanna kill Ouelet?
- I don't know anything.
Enough, enough!
We need him alive.
Please. I have been through this.
You have the wrong guy.
So tell us who we do have.
My name is Lee Cunningham.
- Where'd you get the weapons?
- I don't know.
Who loaded the...?
I don't know anything about the weapons,
alright I told you.
I was picking up my daughter.
She takes violin lessons.
What's her name?
- Is this her?
- Yeah. Isn't she a little angel?
- This is your daughter?
- Right.
Do you have kids?
Where do you live?
I can't remember.
I think it's a tall place.
Is it a tall building?
It's a tall place, right?
You don't have a child.
You don't have a wife.
You live alone, just you.
- What? No.
- We went to your apartment.
- There was nobody there.
- No.
You live there for
10 years by yourself.
No.
- You're just lying.
- I'm not lying.
I didn't kill anyone!
- Why do you keep doing this to me?
- Holocube disconnect.
Please!
I didn't do anything.
Why do you keep
saying this to me?
I don't understand. How can he not know?
The hack must have created a vacuum.
Kuze's wiped his memory...
and somehow installed a new reality.
At least he got to believe he had a kid.
What's the difference huh?
Fantasy, reality...
Dreams, memories...
it's all the same.
Just noise.
It's him.
He's in there.
This cube is secure. He can't be, Major.
The lie detector!
He must've hacked in that way.
We should uplink to the machine,
trace the code, get a lock on his location.
Do it.
Don't go in there.
It's too dangerous.
Major
We don't know what else he can do.
The signal's unstable.
Can you get the lock on him?
We gotta move fast.
We're losing him.
Connecting.
Who are you?
Come here.
I'm shy.
I'm not beautiful...
like you.
Tell me who you are.
I have been born more than once.
So I have more than one name
I'll find you.
Not yet.
I'm not done.
The machine's tracing his location.
We got a fix!
I need to see her.
No Please. I know..what...
We got'im.
Let's go.
P S A G M E N O .com
Weapons armed.
- Go.
- On me.
Stay Down! Stay Down!
Put it down, put it down.
Grenade!
Major!
Come in.
I know why we couldn't find him.
He's using human minds
to create a network of his own.
We're coming to your position.
Tell me who you are.
I'm that which you seek to destroy.
In this life, my name is...
Kuze.
What are you doing to me?
I have, connected you,
to a network of my own creation.
W-w-when I'm finished in this world...
my ghost can survive
there and regenerate.
What do you want from me?
I became...
fascinated with you.
Reading y-y-your code...
when you were inside that geisha.
Like nothing I had felt before,
yet so...
familiar.
We are the same.
We're not the same.
You kill innocent people.
Innocent? Is that what you call them?
I am as they made me.
Who made you?
What have they told you?
That you were the first?
The first cerebral salvage.
You were born of lessons they
took from my failure.
What are you talking about?
I was conscious while they
dismembered my body, and discarded me
like garbage.
I was lying on a table,
listening to doctors talk about how
my mind had not meshed with the shell,
that they had built;
how project t-two, five, seven, one
had failed,
and they had to move on...
to you.
What a beauty you are!
They have improved s-so much,
since they made me.
They thought that we would be
a part of their evolution.
But they have created us,
to evolve alone...
beyond them.
Evolution? That's what you call...
killing everyone who made you?
You're not listening to me.
You're a murderer.
They tried to kill me first.
It is self-defense.
Defense of self!
More will die...
until they tell me what they took.
I won't let that happen.
You want to kill me?
Like everyone else?
Do it, then.
Do what you were programmed to do.
What is that?
I c-c-can't remember,
but I am haunted by it.
Do You see it?
Togusa!
Don't take the medication
that they give you.
They use it to suppress your memories.
Your shell belongs to them,
but not your ghost.
Your ghost is yours.
Remember that.
And maybe you can remember it all.
Get away from her!
Get down on the ground now.
Major!
Oh, Mira!
My got, you are safe!
You have been gone
for hours.
And no one knew where
you were.
You are scaring me.
Calm down.
How many were there
before me?
The integrases of shelling your mind,
it had never been done before.
It was inevitable that we will
be failures.
How many?
...Dozens.
98 unsuccessful attempts,
before you.
You killed 98 innocent people?
No, I didn't kill anyone.
You wouldn't be here.
You wouldn't exist if it
weren't for those experiments.
Experiments?
- Is that what I am to you?
- No!
No, Mira!
Sacrifices were made.
Where did the bodies come from?
Where did I come from?
Mr. Cutter brought them to us.
I didn't ask questions.
The harbor?
My parents?
The way they died?
Did that happen?
No.
We gave you false memories.
Cutter wanted to motivate you.
To fight terrorists.
I didn't approve.
It was cruel, but my work,
that was important, and...
you were born.
You were so beautiful.
Nothing I have is real.
I found him.
I told you to be careful.
You knew who he was the whole time.
You built him.
He had a..
violent unstable mind.
His cerebral connection wouldn't hold!
- I tried to save him!
- No.
You left him to die.
Nothing on Kuze yet, sir.
Checking upper zones next.
Is there any word on Major?
She's gone.
Off-grid. Silent.
Copy that, sir.
I know where to find her.
I didn't ask you to come here.
You never ask.
But I always do.
Did they send you to bring me in?
I'm just here to fish. Did you see any?
You're a company man, you follow orders.
So, if they ordered you to kill me.
Stop saying shit like that.
You're gonna piss me off.
What's it like down there?
It's cold and dark.
Just a million miles away.
No voices.
No data streaming.
Just...
nothing.
- It scares me.
- Then why do you do it?
It feels real.
Why didn't you stop him?
I dunno who to trust anymore.
You trust me, right?
Yeah, I do.
I just don't like it.
I need you to take me back.
There's more I need to find out.
Sure.
Dr. Ouelet...
What have you told her?
She knows.
I'm bringing her in.
Hanka security to Headquarters.
We have the Major.
Why is she sedated?
She's been turned by a terrorist.
But you know that already.
You should have called
the first time she came to see you.
Instead, you gave her information.
What makes you think you have
the right to tell me that?
2571 took us close.
It's time to move on
to the next iteration.
2571 isn not a failure.
I will delete all the data
and reprogram her.
- She won't remember him at all.
- No, no, no...
You download all the data
on the terrorist
and then I order you to terminate.
- What?
- We'll build one that's better.
- I'll delete everything.
- You deleted before.
- She's mine.
- No.
She's a contract with me.
We succeeded.
She's more than human and more than AI.
We changed her entire identity.
But her ghost survived!
Her ghost is what failed us.
We cannot control her.
She's no longer a viable asset.
You should be the one to do it.
What are you doing to me?
I'll run the standard synaptic.
Upload your data on the raid.
Find out exactly what Kuze told you.
You know what he told me.
The truth.
You're deleting everything, aren't you?
No.
Make it so I don't remember...
you.
My name's Major Mira Killian
and I do not consent
to the deletion of this data.
I do not consent.
We never needed your consent;
yours or anyone's.
You're killing me,
aren't you?
Mira?
Can you hear me?
This is your past, your real past. Take it.
- Guards!
- Come on, come on!
Come on, go!
Go!
Security alert on level 25.
Initiating Lockdown procedure.
Please relocate to your
designated safe room.
Thank you for your cooperation.
That's the problem with the human heart.
I want to see her scan.
She killed Dr. Ouelet.
You're to have no further contact with her.
Hanka security will hunt her from here.
- What are the orders?
- To terminate on sight.
You want to kill her? You built her!
Have your sergeant
stand down.
The Major would never
hurt Dr. Ouelet.
She's not the Major anymore!
We have a Section 9 operative
under terrorist programming.
This goes public,
your unit goes down.
You kill her,
you kill us.
I'll take that under advisement.
So what now?
Oh, the poor pumpkin!
Oh, you surprised me.
She likes you.
I was looking for...
No, come in.
Yeah, come come.
- Can I offer you some tea?
- Okay.
That's Motoko's room.
My daughter died a year ago.
I'm sorry.
She ran away.
She was difficult.
And... we fought.
But I guess we all fight
with our parents, right?
Please come and sit, yeah?
What happened to her?
I don't know.
The Ministry sent me her ashes, and...
they told me she took her own life.
But Motoko... No, no, no.
I never believe them.
She was happy living in the
lawless zone with her friends.
She'd write her manifestos about
how technology was
destroying the world.
Then one day...
the police came and they run.
It's strange.
I see her in so many young women.
On the street, in my dreams.
As if she's still here.
She was...
fearless.
And wild.
You remind me of her.
Sorry.
How do I remind you of her?
The way you look at me.
Who are you?
I don't know.
Wait, wait, wait!
Will you come again to visit me?
I will.
Aramaki.
Listen to me.
I was never in a terrorist bombing.
My parents...
Everything was data,
they installed in my mind.
And there were others;
run-aways like me.
Considered disposable.
Kuze was one of them.
That's why he's coming...
for Hanka.
Can you prove this?
Dr. Ouelet can.
Ouelet's dead.
Cutter says you killed her.
Put me on the grid. I need Kuze to find me.
We will be exposed to Cutter.
I know, but I need to do this.
I'm going to meet with the Prime Minister.
He must be stopped.
The virus has spread.
All agents stick to mental comms.
Don't send a rabbit
to kill a fox.
We're burned.
I repeat.
We've located Major on the grid.
She's in the lawless zone.
Air support 5 minutes out.
Is the spider tank within range?
Yes sir. Awaiting your orders sir.
Motoko!
It is real.
This place.
I remember what they did to us.
Cutter and his men.
This is where they took us from.
We used to sleep right here.
We were like a family.
All of us run-aways.
We had nothing...
except each other.
They took that from us.
Your name was Hideo.
Motoko.
That was your name.
Come with me...
into my network.
We will evolve beyond them.
And together we can avenge
what they have done to us.
Come.
With me.
I'll take control from here.
Weapons system manual command.
Spider tank now active
It's Cutter, he found us!
Target acquired
No!
Target eliminated.
You came close...
you freak.
Motor center compromised.
Sniper team on site?
Approaching the target now sir.
Come with me.
There is no place for us here.
No,
I'm not ready to leave.
I belong here.
I'll always be there with you,
in your ghost.
Target is in view.
What are you waiting for?
DO IT!
No!
Keep firing.
Saito, have you found Major? Is she safe?
She will be.
Hey!
Hey.
Say something nice.
What's your name?
Aramaki told me you had a name from before.
Motoko.
Major still in there, right?
I am.
Mr. Cutter.
I talked with the Prime Minister.
You're accused of murder
and crimes against the state.
I thought that it might be you.
It's unwise to resist.
Please.
Major?
I'm with Cutter.
Do you wanna say anything
before I kill him?
Tell him this is justice.
It's what I was built for.
So do you give consent?
My name's Major.
And I give my consent.
You don't have to come here anymore.
I know.
My mind is human.
My body is manufactured.
I'm the first of my kind, but...
I won't be the last.
We cling to memories
as if they define us.
But what we do defines us.
My ghost survived
to remind the next of us
that humanity is our virtue.
I know who I am.
And what I'm here to do.
Major.
Engage targets.
You're authorized.
Subs By Asmita
Psagmeno.com
Subtitles/Trailers/Screenshots