♪ Hey! Hey! Hey! ♪
♪ Hey! Hey! Hey!
♪ See the ponies
trottin' down the street ♪
♪ Equestria is where they wanna meet ♪
♪ They all know where they wanna go ♪
♪ And they're trottin' in time ♪
♪ And they're trottin', yeah,
they got the beat ♪
♪ They got the beat, they got the beat ♪
♪ Yeah, they got the beat ♪
♪ Go-go music really makes us dance ♪
♪ Do the Pony puts us in a trance ♪
♪ Do the Watusijust give us a chance ♪
♪ That's when we fall in line ♪
♪ 'Cause we got the beat ♪
♪ We got the beat, we got the beat ♪
♪ Yeah, we got it ♪
Huh?
Excuse me! Dragon on the move!
Important Princess Documents
coming through!
Wow! Everypony from Manehattan
to Saddle Arabia is here!
I know, filly.
We almost couldn't book a stable!
Princess Twilight must have
her hooves full with this giant festival!
Are you kidding?
She's smart and organized
and cool under pressure.
There's nothing she can't handle!
My goodness! I can't handle this!
Nothing is working!
I just have to get it together.
Just go in there. And ask!
This is your Friendship Festival.
Every pony's happiness
rests in your hooves.
Okay, Twilight.
Got all your charts and graphs!
Oh, thank goodness
you're here, Spike.
I'm just so nervous about this meeting.
What you talkin' about?
I'm about to ask the three
most royal princesses
of Equestria for a huge favor.
What if they reject me?
It'll be fine!
Just remember the most important thing.
Smile?
Uh, no.
You're a princess, too!
Right.
Good morning, Princesses!
Thank you all for seeing me.
I have an idea that I think will make
our Friendship Festival
the most wonderful celebration
Equestria has ever seen.
Yes, Twilight, we are very excited.
Ponies have been arriving
from all over all morning.
I'd like to think it's to see us
but Songbird Serenade might
be the bigger attraction.
Yes, she is the "mane" event.
And to make it extra special,
I could use your help. Spike?
Songbird Serenade's performance
is not scheduled
to start until after you begin the sunset.
And based on my precise calculation
to get the very best lighting
for the stage,
Princess Celestia,
I was hoping you could make sure
the sun stays about 28.1 degrees
to the south.
And Princess Luna,
if you could raise the moon 62 degrees
to the north at the same time,
it would reflect the sunlight
on the other side
and really frame
the entire stage perfectly!
- I...
- But wait, there's more!
Cadance, if you could use
your crystal magic
to create an aurora above the stage
the sun and the moon
will shine through it
and create a truly amazing light show!
Presenting Songbird Serenade!
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
Whoa. Whoa!
Tada!
So, you're saying you want
us to move the sun
and the moon for the party?
Well, I'd do it myself except
I don't have your magic.
Twilight...
Each of us uses our powers
to serve Equestria in our own way.
You are the Princess of Friendship.
You already have all the magic you need.
So that'd be a no?
Yes!
Skies cleared and ready for the festival!
Heads up, Fluttershy!
Out of control balloon!
I don't think it's the balloon
that's out of control, Pinkie Pie.
Hey, y'all!
Anypony up for some free samples
of my family's apple cider?
Ah!
Thank you. Loved it.
Wow, Rarity, that's a fine job
you're doing there.
'Course it might not get done
till after the concert.
Applejack, darling, anypony can do fine.
Twilight asked me.
So clearly, she's going for fabulous.
And fabulous takes time.
Fabulous takes forever. But awesome...
Whoa!
Can get done in four seconds flat.
Faster if I do my Sonic Rainboom.
No, no, no, no!
Don't you dare, Rainbow Dash!
It looks wretched enough already.
Oh, come on, it's fine.
If you were raised in a barn!
No offense, Applejack.
None taken. 'Specially since
I wasn't raised in a barn.
My family just happens to have a barn,
where I was born.
And spent most of my formative years.
Raised in a barn!
Okay, just 218 things left
to do, and we're ready.
Hey, Twilight.
Hello, Spike.
Uh, hi, Rarity.
How'd it go with the other princesses?
They like your idea?
I bet they loved it!
Not exactly.
They think I can make today
perfect without their magic.
And they are absolutely right, darling.
This festival is your brilliant idea,
and we know you're up to the task.
But what if I'm not?
What if Songbird Serenade hates the stage?
Or nopony makes a new friend?
And if I fail at the festival,
then who am I?
Twilight, look at me.
This will be the biggest celebration
Equestria has ever seen!
As the Princess of Friendship,
you cannot fail!
This day will define who you are!
The pressure is intense!
It's almost too much
for any single pony to handle!
But you have us! So stop worrying.
♪ It's time to show 'em
what you've got ♪
♪ It's time to go and get things done ♪
♪ But you don't have to do it
on your own ♪
♪ 'Cause you've got friends
right here to make it fun ♪
♪ We got this
You got this ♪
♪ We got this together
♪ Sometimes the pressure gets you down ♪
♪ And the clouds are dark and gray ♪
♪ Just kick them off
and let the sun shine through ♪
♪ And scary as it seems
more help is on the way ♪
♪ 'Cause friends have friends
that want to help out too ♪
♪ We got this
You got this ♪
♪ We got this together ♪
♪ It's the Festival of Friendship ♪
♪ And we can get it done ♪
♪ A festival that they won't forget ♪
♪ A party to be proud of
A day of games and fun ♪
♪ Just you wait and see
A magic day in perfect harmony ♪
♪ You got this ♪
♪ We got this together ♪
♪ With friends and family
you are never alone ♪
♪ If you need help we've got your back ♪
♪ You can be honest
Let your problems be known ♪
♪ 'Cause you got us
to pick up the slack ♪
♪ We got this ♪
Eyup!
♪ We got this together ♪
♪ Pay attention to the details ♪
♪ Every gem even spaced
make the colors perfect ♪
♪ Taking one or two to taste ♪
♪ Inside and out beautiful throughout ♪
♪ Generosity is what we're all about ♪
♪ We got this ♪
♪ You got this ♪
♪ We got this together ♪
♪ Today needs to be perfect
It all comes down to me ♪
♪ I don't know if I'm ready ♪
♪ For all the things they need me to be ♪
♪ I am the Princess of Friendship ♪
♪ But that is more than just a crown ♪
♪ It's a promise
to bring ponies together ♪
♪ And never let anypony down ♪
♪ We've got an awful lot to bake ♪
♪ Each pony needs a piece of cake ♪
♪ Oh, wait!
There's something better we can do ♪
♪ We're gonna need some more supplies ♪
♪ To make a really big surprise ♪
♪ She'll be so shocked
She's sure to love it too ♪
♪ You got this ♪
♪ We got this together ♪
♪ It's the Festival of Friendship ♪
♪ Together we are one ♪
♪ A day we will never forget ♪
♪ And now everything is ready ♪
♪ So when the day is done ♪
♪ The weather ♪
♪ The banquet ♪
♪ The style ♪
♪ And music ♪
♪ All will be in perfect harmony ♪
Pinkie!
Oopsie!
Guess my easy bake confetti cake cannon
needs a little bit more finetuning.
Songbird Serenade!
Is it really her?
It is, it is!
Hiya! I'm looking for
the pony in charge.
I need to set up for my sound check.
Ms. Songbird Serenade?
Um, I was just going to check on you.
I'm Princess Twilight.
And sorry about the mess.
I'm usually not so...
Oh! How embarrassing!
Caked in cake?
You have visual on buttercream?
Visual confirmed. Go for cleanup.
Storm clouds?
I ordered perfect weather! Rainbow Dash!
Uh...
I don't think those are storm clouds.
Ooh. I bet those
are the clowns I ordered!
You are definitely
not the clowns I ordered.
Brian, no!
Ponies of Equestria!
We come on behalf of the fearsome,
the powerful, the almighty,
Storm King!
This is terrible.
And now,
to deliver the evil, evil message,
put your hooves together
for Commander Tempest!
Is that a unicorn?
I think so,
but what happened to her horn?
Tempest, is it?
How may we help you?
Ah, I'm so glad you asked.
How about we start with your complete
and total surrender?
What? What?
Hi, there, Princess of Friendship.
Not exactly sure what's going on,
but I know we can talk things out.
Oh, goodie. All four princesses.
Here's the deal, ladies.
I need your magic.
Give it up nicely, please,
or we make it difficult.
For everyone.
And why should we cower before you?
There's one of you, and hundreds of us.
I was hoping
you'd choose difficult.
- Cadance!
- Argh! I can't stop it!
Luna, quick! Go south!
Beyond the badlands!
Seek help from the Queen of the Hippo--
Luna!
Twilight!
Easy as pie.
Oh, I love pie.
Oh, you totally got the last princess.
That's not the Princess.
Grubber! Get her now!
Guys, we gotta get the Princess!
Over here, y'all!
Come on!
Which one of you guys
are going down there?
I would, but I just had a hearty meal
and I will sink and I will side cramp.
I'm very big-boned. I sink quick.
Everypony okay?
I think my bottom's on backward.
We just got our cupcakes handed to us
by the worst party crasher ever!
We gotta go back there and fight!
You saw the size of those goons!
Do you seriously wanna go back?
So, now what?
We can't hide here forever
and let's be honest, we can't go back.
Look at what they did to the princesses.
We've got to keep them from Twilight.
The Queen...
Yeah, the Queen!
Uh, what queen?
Celestia told Luna to find
the Queen of the Hippos.
Luna can't, so I have to.
Uh, hippos? Seriously?
I've heard they're surprisingly graceful
for their size.
But they're always hungry.
- Hungry?
- Hippos?
They're somewhere south,
past the badlands.
But that means we'll have
to leave Equestria. Ooh!
I'm not even packed!
I understand you're scared,
and nopony else has to go.
But I have to find this queen.
She might be our only hope.
Well, you're not getting all the glory.
We're in this together.
- We got yer back!
- Indeedy!
I am ready to save Equestria!
Yay.
We're all behind you, Twilight.
Let's go find this hippo!
Uh, south?
Boingy, boingy, boingy, boingy, boingy.
Anypony up for a game of "I Spy?"
No really, come on!
I spy with my little eye
something that is orange.
No takers? It's you, Applejack!
All this power, wasted on parties.
When there are far greater uses.
Well, answer it!
Where am I supposed to be looking?
I never understand how this spell works.
Tempest!
Over here, Your Excellency.
- Where? Huh?
- Over here. No.
No, right. Look right.
- My right?
- Yep.
Oh, there you are.
Here's the deal. I'm in the
middle of a big rebrand here.
"The Storm King" is tracking well,
as "intensely intimidating."
But you know what? I need to back it up.
You know what I need to back it up with?
A storm! That would be great!
You promised me magic that
could control the elements
and right now, I'm holding a what?
A branch, a twig. Blegh.
Uh, that would be The Staff of Sacanas,
Your Excellency
- and it will channel the magic--
- Mm-hmm.
...of the four rulers of this land.
You'll soon have the power
of 100 armies.
So, that would be a "yes"
on you locking down
the four pegacornicuses
or whatever you call them?
Give me three days.
I'll have everything ready
for your arrival.
Remember, Tempest, only I have
the power to make you whole.
Make this twig work,
and you'll get your reward.
Fail me,
and your horn won't be
the only thing that's broken.
It won't be a problem.
Great!
I'm ready to power up, crash and bash,
and be the biggest, baddest bugaloo!
Sorry. Bad spell service.
You want me to call him back?
Do you have the Princess?
Well, uh, funny story.
It kind of seems like she...
She might have, like,
you know, gotten away.
A little bit.
I know you're disappointed,
but I got one word for you.
Spongecake.
I need all four for the staff to work.
Hey, I know.
I want the Storm King to fix
that crazy horn as badly as you do.
It looks like a crackly, chipped tooth
on the top of your head
and you know you don't look
good in hats.
That princess is not gonna keep me
from getting my horn back.
Prepare my ship!
Please. How far can one little
pony get on her own?
Guys, sand's in my everything.
Saving Equestria.
Oh, look! Maybe this guy knows
which way to go!
What's that, friend? We're lost?
We could be going in circles.
Endless sand.
Nothing for miles but sand...
And this rock...
And this cactus...
And this road.
This road.
- Hmm?
- A road?
Where there's a road, there's a...
Whoa!
Cool!
What is that?
Ooh! A city! We are doing it, you guys!
You know what they say,
"Where there's a city, there's a spa!"
Who says that?
In case you forgot,
we're on a mission to save Equestria.
I can multitask.
Don't worry, little one,
we'll let you go.
To the highest bidder!
Nice!
Storm King bobbleheads!
Ooh. Hey. You with the horn.
You selling?
Oh. Ooh!
Hi, there.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here, let me help you with that.
Hey, no magic around my merchandise!
Hmm?
Very interesting.
Okay, we just gotta stick together.
Be careful who you talk to,
and try to blend in.
Can I have your attention, please?
Can anypony take us
to the Queen of the Hippos?
You want something,
you gotta give somethin'.
Well, how about a big warm hug
from a grateful pony friend?
How about this comb
that I've never used?
A picture of my sister Maud?
This breath mint?
Seriously, buddy. Help me help you.
Pinkie, you can't just take off.
And you don't need to announce
to every--
Relax, Twilight, I've totally got this.
How much for the giant gecko?
Who you callin' a gecko?
Uh, Spike isn't for sale.
I want that fancy purple hair!
I'll give you two Storm Bucks for it.
Two Storm Bucks?
It's worth more than that.
Heh?
- Give me that pink one!
- I'll take the blue one!
- No, I want the blue one!
- I need that lizard!
I'll take the picture of your sister!
I want all seven for my collection.
Back up, everyone! Back it up.
Y'all in some serious danger!
Now, you didn't touch any of them,
did you?
Just look at all those colors.
You think that's natural?
They're infected
with pastelus coloritis.
Now you listen here, fella,
there ain't--
Don't worry, don't worry.
As long as you're
not covered in purple splotches,
you'll be fine.
Uh-oh.
What do I do?
Enjoy your last moments.
And don't touch anyone.
Because parts will fall off.
Me parts!
Well, all right.
- You are awesome!
- Mm-hmm.
And quite charming.
Capper's the name. Charming's my game.
So, to the hippos then?
I don't know if we should trust him.
We could definitely use
a friend out here.
You know what?
Little Cotton Candy Hair is right.
And if I do say so myself...
♪ This town is not a nice place ♪
♪ For little fillies all alone ♪
♪ There are lots of twists and corners ♪
♪ That could lead to the unknown ♪
♪ Let me guide your way ♪
♪ And I'll be sure to help you through ♪
♪ You could really use
a friend out here ♪
♪ And luckily for you ♪
♪ I'm the friend that you need ♪
♪ When you're lost
and don't know what to do ♪
♪ I'm your pal, your amigo
Useful and resourceful, too ♪
♪ And my help, you'll concede,
is a plus guaranteed ♪
♪ You can call and I'll come running,
just follow my lead ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the friend you need ♪
- ♪ He's a friend ♪
- ♪ Quite a friend ♪
♪ He's a friend indeed ♪
♪ You need a bud to spot the danger ♪
♪ A pal to stop the creep ♪
♪ A chum and not a stranger to assist ♪
♪ You need a bro who is cunning ♪
♪ That can help you take the leap ♪
♪ A friend who knows what's lying
in the mist ♪
♪ Don't fear these darkened alleys ♪
♪ They're scary, yes, I know ♪
♪ Why you could use a friend
to protect you wherever you go ♪
♪ And such a dazzling beauty
covered in dirt and muck ♪
♪ But now your fate is changing ♪
♪ Now you are in luck ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the friend that you need ♪
♪ When you're lost
and don't know what to do ♪
♪ I'm your pal, your amigo ♪
♪ Looking out for friends like you ♪
♪ And my help, you'll concede,
is a plus guaranteed ♪
♪ Just call and I'll come running,
we'll say it's agreed ♪
Here. Tell Verko, my place, 20 minutes.
I've got something that will
"magically" erase all my debt.
♪ 'Cause I'm the friend you need ♪
♪ He's a friend ♪
♪ Quite a friend ♪
♪ He's a friend indeed ♪
Welcome, my little ponies,
to my little manor.
Ooh, sort of a Rocohobo
Bohemian hodgepodge.
Apologies for the state of
my litter box.
I wasn't expecting guests.
Ooh, so many fun breakables!
Whoa!
Y'all sure y'all want the hippos?
Yessiree!
The Queen of the Hippos.
Not like the queen of the lions,
or tigers, or bears?
- Oh, my!
- Huh?
Please, please, I don't know anything!
You really think
the ponies got this far?
Oh, they're here.
Attention.
A little purple pony passed this way.
Tell me where she is.
Or somethin' real bad's gonna happen.
You think we're gonna fall
for this again?
I don't know what kind of scam
you're workin' with Capper
and the rest of your friends, but--
Friends?
Poison or no poison, you're gonna pay.
Oh! Fishman just got dropped!
Now...
About this Capper...
Stop playin' me. A Sonic Rainboom?
That's not a real thing.
Is that a real thing?
I'll show ya!
No, no, no. I don't need you
Sonic Rainbooming up in my place.
Thank you very much.
Whoa, hey. Hold up now.
Whoa.
Here you go. I do apologize.
If we were back home, I could have
done something truly fabulous.
Okay.
- What's the catch?
- Nothing.
After all that you've done for us?
Consider it a "thank you."
Oh. Don't thank me. Really.
Guys!
We've been looking for the wrong queen!
We don't need the Queen of the Hippos.
We need the Queen of the Hippogriffs!
Part pony, part eagle.
Oh! Oh, the Hippogriffs?
Now the trouble with that is,
no one knows where they are.
Says here they're on the top
of Mount Aris.
You mean the mountain
right outside the window?
Objects in windows may be less
mountainous than they appear.
Let's go, everypony.
Wait! You can't--
you can't make it by yourselves!
You'd need an airship.
And lucky for you, I can get you a ride.
I think we can get there on our own.
Here's Verko!
These ponies better shoot
rainbow lasers out their eyes
if they're gonna settle your debt.
Brought the big cage.
Let's load 'em up!
You were...
You were going to sell us?
I knew it!
We gotta get out of here!
Silly little ponies.
Tempest!
Trusting strangers? Big mistake. Big.
Huge!
My goodness!
Well, look at you!
With your scary broken horn
and scowly eyes.
What tricks do you know,
my little pony wony?
Not bad.
Go, go!
Get her now!
You gonna be scared now, ponies!
I'm gonna...
Be...
Sick!
We have to get there, to the docks!
Hurry!
That's it. Don't look down now.
Yay!
Whoa!
Pinkie!
Best escape plan ever!
What?
Shh.
Did you hear something?
Yeah, probably just the rats.
If we find 'em, we'll eat 'em.
Rats?
Now...
Where are they going?
Okay. No need for violence.
Uh, they're headed...
They're headed east.
Yeah, to Black Skull Island.
So, uh, glad I could be of service
to His Majesty, the Storm King.
I'll just be on my way.
When I get my princess.
Until then, your fate is still
up in the air.
Oh, you're gonna go in the skiff.
Which is a boat, specifically,
a air boat!
We make a great team.
I love it how you said his fate is up
in the air and then I said,
"You're gonna be in the air
in the air boat."
Ugh.
What do you think, Twilight?
Should we just ask 'em to take us?
The last time we trusted somepony,
he tried to sell us.
Hey, guys, come check this out.
Looks like a pack of stowaways.
What are we s'posed to do with them?
I think we tie 'em up.
Nah, we clip their wings!
Nah, we scar 'em...
Emotionally!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What say the book, Captain Celaeno?
Storm King's rulebook says...
"Throw them overboard."
Arr.
All right, that's lunch!
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
So, you were about to toss us overboard,
and you stopped for a lunch break?
Storm King only allows
one break a day for meals
then it's back to hauling goods.
- So, you're delivery guys?
- And gals.
These uniforms aren't exactly
doing us any favors.
Then, can you deliver us to Mount Aris?
Sorry. We do what the Storm King orders,
or we suffer his wrath.
Right, still going overboard.
It's nothing personal. Pudding?
There's pudding?
You weren't always delivery birds,
were you?
What about before the Storm King?
Yeah, we used to be
much more adventurous.
Ooh! I met that guy in the desert!
Whoa! You used to be pirates?
Um, we prefer the term,
"Swashbuckling Treasure Hunters."
So, pirates.
You birds have a choice to make.
You can let some cloven-hoofed Storm
King tell you how to live your lives
or you can be awesome again!
Rainbow Dash, this really
isn't a good time for a--
♪ I know the world can get you down ♪
...song.
♪ Things don't work out
quite the way that you thought ♪
♪ Feeling like all your
best days are done ♪
♪ Your fears and doubts
are all you've got ♪
♪ But there's a light
shining deep inside ♪
♪ Beneath those fears and doubts ♪
♪ So just squash 'em ♪
♪ And let it shine
for all the world to see ♪
♪ That it is time, yeah,
time to be awesome ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, awesome! ♪
♪ It's time to be so awesome ♪
♪ You've no idea how hard it's been ♪
♪ It's time to be awesome ♪
♪ This dull routine
we've been forced to do ♪
♪ Don't let them rob you
of who you are ♪
- ♪ Be awesome, it's all up to you ♪
- ♪ Be awesome ♪
♪ I feel the light
stirring deep inside ♪
♪ It's like a tale
still yet to be told ♪
♪ It's time to be ♪
♪ And now it's time
to break the shackles free ♪
♪ And start living
like the brave and the bold ♪
♪ It's time to be awesome! ♪
- ♪ Let loose, be true ♪
- ♪ So awesome! ♪
♪ It's time to be awesome! ♪
- ♪ Go big, be you ♪
- ♪ So awesome! ♪
♪ We used to soar through
the clouds in the skies ♪
♪ Elaborate schemes we would
love to devise ♪
♪ We rescued our treasure
and stored it away ♪
♪ Saving those gemstones
for a rainy day! ♪
♪ We see that light
filling up our skies ♪
♪ So take the Storm King's orders
and toss 'em ♪
♪ 'Cause it's the time
to let our colors fly ♪
♪ Hey, scallywags,
it's time to be awesome ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
Come on, let's show
these little ponies how it's done!
Ooh.
Awesome!
I knew you had it in you!
And now, for the finishing touch!
Rainboom, rainboom!
- Rainboom, rainboom!
- No, no, no... No!
Ah, yeah!
Wow!
Oh!
Huh?
Look at that rainbow!
Whoa, that's so cool.
Yeah, of them to alert us.
Funny though,
they don't seem to be heading
to Black Skull Island.
Like, "Haha" funny, or...
Whoa!
Yeah!
Nice!
Storm guards!
Looks like they found you.
Tempest!
Secure the rigging! Lock down the cargo!
Everyone, prepare to be boarded!
Oh, goodness!
You think she saw my Sonic Rainboom?
Are you kidding me?
Where is the pony princess?
Princess? Princess, princess...
Nope. All we're hauling
is Storm King merchandise.
You do realize that if you
were to shelter fugitives
the Storm King would be quite...
explosive.
We have to get off this ship
before they tell Tempest we're here!
We helped them get their mojo back.
They're not gonna give us up!
Whoa.
I've got this.
Now, I'm gonna to count to three,
and if you don't tell me where they are,
your ship is going down.
One...
- Hold this.
- What are you doing?
Two...
Oh, this is intense.
Three!
What?
Oh, for Celestia's sake!
Whee!
I can't look!
What in the hay is she up to?
Oh, thank goodness.
Phew!
Quick thinkin', Twilight!
Yahoo!
That was fun! Can we do it again?
Next stop, Mount Aris!
We're home free!
All right!
There's no ponies.
But I found this.
It's a kind of a cupcake,
some sprinkles.
Oh, yeah, and I found this, too.
Wow. This is a real artist.
Looks like they're heading
to Mount Aris.
Really? Mount... Mount Aris? I didn't...
Well, that's my mistake.
I didn't know that they...
Mount Aris, my bad, I didn't...
That's my bad. I'm sorry.
I'm very, very sorry.
Now...
About your betrayal.
We had to crash the balloon
at the bottom of the mountain?
That's it! I simply cannot even!
I have nothing.
The bad guys have won!
I'm so sorry!
We're almost there!
Will you stop saying that?
No, really.
We're actually here!
This is it.
Ooh!
Well, I'll be.
Hippogriffs, here we come!
Ooh. Time to rest my hooves.
Are we sure this is the right place?
Hello? Is anypony home?
No Hippogriffies here.
Or here. Or here.
Or here. Or here. Or here!
Wait...
Nope. This place is empty.
But Celestia...
The map...
They have to be here.
Something bad happened here.
Something that turned this
whole place into a ghost town.
Ghost town?
It's coming from over there.
What was that?
Hey! Wait up!
Cannonball!
Pinkie!
She's gone.
Now what?
- Huh?
- Woah!
Oh, boy.
I hate epic adventures.
Way to leave it till
the last minute, Twilight.
I didn't make these bubbles.
Then who did?
Hello?
We're looking for the Hippogriffs.
How do I know I can trust you?
Please.
The Storm King invaded our land,
and we need their help.
The Storm King?
I'm so glad I saved you guys!
I'm totally taking you to my mom!
Does your mother know
where they are?
She might have an idea.
We're almost there.
Wow!
Mother!
Look what I found!
Is it another shell?
- Mm-mmm.
- Because I am telling you,
if it is another shell, I am--
Princess Skystar, what have you done?
You know surface dwellers
are forbidden here!
Guards!
No, no, no. Mom, please!
It is so not like that!
The Storm King is trying
to destroy their home, too!
We need to find the Hippogriffs.
Do you know what happened to them?
Well, of course I know. I'm the queen.
I know everything.
Oh, oh. It's such a good story.
Don't you dare tell them!
Once upon a time, like, a while ago,
the Hippogriffs did live on Mount Aris.
Did I not say don't tell them?
But, hey, I'm just the queen.
Don't mind me.
Fine! I can't tell you.
But if I could tell you,
I'd say that that horned beast
did show up to steal their magic.
Seriously?
But to keep it out of his clutches
their brave and majestic
leader, Queen Novo,
hid them deep underwater
where he could never go.
We are...
Well, we were the Hippogriffs!
Tada!
But I totally did not tell you that.
Well, I guess the pearl
is out the oyster now.
I am Queen Novo.
Hold on now, let me get this straight.
When the Storm King came,
you just abandoned
your entire city and fled?
We didn't flee, we swam.
You know, in order to flee.
But how?
Oh! Can we show them?
These are the first guests
we've had in, like, forever!
Can we? Can we? Can we...
Well, I suppose I should make
sure it still works.
Careful now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wow.
Haha!
These fins are divine!
Hey, Applejack!
I'll race ya to that coral!
You're on!
Woo-hoo!
Ooh, try it, Fluttershy.
Yay.
Guys...
Guys, what is happening?
Aw, so cute!
This is amazing!
With this, we could transform
everypony at home
into something powerful enough
to face the Storm King's army!
Or it could end up in his greedy claws.
- But...
- Honey...
I'm sorry about your home. I truly am.
But my responsibility
is to protect my subjects.
The pearl...
is not going anywhere.
But we've come all this way.
And you can't just hide down here,
trapped forever.
There's so much you're missing.
We are 100% okay with that.
Yes, Jamal?
Ooh, time for my seaweed wrap.
Yes, a massage, too.
Mama needs her deep tissue.
So that's it?
We left home for nothin'?
Oh, my gosh!
Best idea.
You can stay with us forever!
There are so many things we can do.
We could make friendship
bracelets out of shells,
and picture frames out of shells,
and decorative waste baskets
out of shells.
Oh, I have so many projects
that involve shells.
Now I have someone new
to share them with.
I mean, aside from my friends,
Shelly and Sheldon.
Right, Shelly and Sheldon?
Get it?
Oh, oh!
That sounds lovely, darling,
but you must realize we can't stay.
We've gotta get back to our families.
Oh, no. Of course. Of course.
Of course you have
your own friends back home.
It's fine. It's fine!
Shelly and Sheldon get jealous anyways.
It's probably for the best.
Yeah, I'll just, um...
I'll get Mom to turn you back
so you can go home.
I know we have to go,
but you guys saw how disappointed
Princess Skystar was.
Couldn't we stay for just
a little longer?
Pinkie, we just don't have time--
Oh, no. No, no. Pinkie's right.
Say what now?
Well, we still need to come up
with a plan to get back.
A few minutes won't make
a huge difference.
And if there's anypony who can
cram a lifetime of fun
into a blink of an eye,
it's Pinkie Pie.
So go ahead and show Skystar
the best time ever!
I won't let you down!
I'm counting on it.
It's probably for the best.
♪ Hey, now, don't be sad ♪
♪ I know we cannot stay ♪
♪ But we've got a couple minutes
and a little time to play ♪
♪ I know you have important things ♪
♪ So it's okay, just go ♪
♪ But we can still pick
one small little thing ♪
♪ To do with you, you know! ♪
♪ One small thing
doesn't seem like a lot ♪
♪ One small thing,
work with the time you've got ♪
♪ Soon one small thing becomes two ♪
♪ After two perhaps another few ♪
♪ Then one small thing is not so small ♪
♪ One small thing can be
the biggest thing of all! ♪
♪ All right now since you're here ♪
♪ Let's see what we can do ♪
♪ Swim with the flow until you go ♪
♪ Together me and you ♪
♪ I've got necklaces for every fish! ♪
♪ So what else do you got? ♪
♪ Well, we could play the bubblefish ♪
♪ You'll like this one a lot ♪
♪ One small thing
it's a good place to start ♪
♪ Just one small thing ♪
♪ One small thing
and we don't seem so far apart ♪
♪ Soon one small thing leads to more ♪
♪ It's so much more
than there was before ♪
♪ Just one small thing
and you will see ♪
♪ The start of something big
for you and me ♪
- ♪ One small thing ♪
- ♪ Just one small thing ♪
- ♪ Or a tall thing ♪
- ♪ Just one tall thing ♪
- ♪ Or a sing thing ♪
- ♪ Just one singy thing ♪
- ♪ Or a bling thing ♪
- ♪ Just one blingy thing ♪
- ♪ A conga thing ♪
- ♪ Or a longah thing ♪
- ♪ Just one longah thing ♪
♪ A blue thing, true thing, you thing ♪
♪ A wee thing, sea thing, me thing ♪
♪ So many things and everything
until our time is done ♪
♪ There's one small thing
for each and every one ♪
♪ One small thing
so much we can create ♪
♪ You and me
we started something great ♪
♪ It's so amazing, look around ♪
♪ At all the happy sights and sounds ♪
♪ One small thing is big, it's true ♪
♪ You did this all for us ♪
♪ I just wish there was
one small thing ♪
♪ An extra special kind of thing ♪
♪ That we could do for you ♪
♪ One small thing ♪
Well, I guess there is
one small thing we can do.
The pearl alarm!
Oh, no! The pearl alarm!
Ow.
No! Please!
All of this so you could
sneak in and take the pearl?
This is why we don't bring strangers
into our home!
You don't deserve to be one of us.
What were you thinking?
I mean, stealing their pearl?
It was the only way
to save Equestria!
Except it wasn't!
The queen was going to say yes!
We did what you told us,
and that's what made her realize
we were ponies worth saving.
Unless,
you didn't really want us to
show her the best time ever!
You just wanted us to distract her!
I never would have done it,
but this isn't Equestria!
We can't just dance around
with con artists,
make rainbooms in the sky,
and expect everything to work out!
It's not enough. We are not enough!
No, Twilight. We stuck together.
We were gonna get the help we needed.
The only thing that stopped us was you.
Well, I'm doing the best I can!
It's all on me.
I'm the one Tempest wants.
I'm the last princess!
You're also the only one
who doesn't trust her friends!
Well, maybe I would have been better off
without friends like you!
Pinkie, I...
I just can't talk to you right now.
Twilight...
It's okay.
You'll figure it out.
No.
I can't.
I ruined everything.
There's no chance to save Equestria now.
It's all my fault.
Spike?
Twilight, look out!
No, no, no!
Spike!
Twilight!
Aw, the Princess of Friendship
with no friends.
And no way out.
Why are you doing this?
You're a pony, just like me.
I'm nothing like you.
I'm more than you'll ever be.
♪ It's time you learned a lesson ♪
♪ It's time that you understand ♪
♪ Don't ever count on anybody else ♪
♪ In this or any other land ♪
♪ I once hoped for friendship ♪
♪ To find a place among my kind ♪
♪ But those were the childish wishes ♪
♪ Of someone who was blind ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
♪ See the world from where I stand ♪
♪ Me among the mighty ♪
♪ You caged at my command ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
♪ Give up your sweet fantasy land ♪
♪ It's time to grow up and get wise ♪
♪ Come now, little one ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
♪ We all start out the same
with simple naive trust ♪
♪ Shielded from the many ways
that life's not fair or just ♪
♪ But then there comes a moment ♪
♪ A simple truth that you must face ♪
♪ If you depend on others ♪
♪ You'll never find your place ♪
♪ And as you take that first step ♪
♪ Upon a path that's all your own ♪
♪ You see it all so clearly ♪
♪ The best way to survive is all alone ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
♪ See the world from where I stand ♪
♪ Me among the mighty ♪
♪ You caged at my command ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
♪ And behold the faded light ♪
♪ It's time to grow up and get wise ♪
♪ Come now, little one ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
I'm so sorry you felt so alone.
I saw the truth.
My friends abandoned me
when times got tough.
Looks like I'm not the only one.
Face it, Princess.
Friendship has failed you too.
Friendship didn't fail me.
I failed friendship.
This whole journey was such a mistake.
All we wanted was somepony to help us.
You think maybe it's time
we talk to Twilight?
She's been taken!
What?
Twilight's been taken! Tempest!
She grabbed her and took her
on her ship!
- We gotta get her back!
- How?
We'll never catch up.
And we got no way
to defeat those monsters.
Well, good thing
I happen to know
of a group of mighty heroes
that could handle this easily.
Well, look what the cat dragged in.
Himself!
These heroes have faced
the Storm King's army
and escaped.
I've seen them tackle
the streets of the roughest towns,
break out of the tightest situations,
and inspire others to join their cause.
Ooh!
Now, don't get too excited.
He's just talking about us.
They even escaped certain doom
at the hooves of Commander Tempest.
Yeah, that was pretty great.
Are you kidding me?
That was awesome!
Figured you could use a claw.
We're onboard to help you
fight the Storm King.
Just not on board our actual ship.
That crazy unicorn sunk it,
but you got back our argh.
And we're ready to kick some booty.
Is that what I think it is?
Hello! Me again!
I'm gonna get so grounded.
But I talked things over
with Shelly and Sheldon,
and they pointed out that you were
just trying to help your friends.
So, I wanna help, too.
Because, you know, one small thing...
Can make a really big difference.
That's it, right?
We didn't make friends
with anypony else?
All right, y'all.
I think our course is clear.
Y'all ready to do this thing?
We're coming, Twilight!
Yeah!
As soon as we bake up a plan!
♪ I am here and I see your pain ♪
♪ Through the storm through the clouds,
the rain ♪
♪ I'm telling you, you cannot escape ♪
Tempest, don't do this.
Don't give the Storm King--
Your magic?
Did you think you'd keep it
all to yourself?
Time to share.
I'd love for everybody out there to know
what I can really do.
Ooh, fascinating.
What can you really do?
Your bidding, of course,
your mighty one.
Bidding's good. I like bidding!
Um, what are you supposed to be?
I'm the Princess of Friendship.
Oh!
That's nice.
Why is this one still moving?
She and her friends
put up a bit of a fight,
but she's alone now.
She won't be a problem.
Yeah. So, speaking of problems,
this place, it seems a little too,
oh, I don't know, cute!
I don't like cute.
I never did like cute.
Doesn't really go
with my whole big, bad,
powerful magic guy thing, does it?
Deliver the punch line, Tempest,
because this has gotta be a joke!
Huh?
No!
Check out the light show!
Wow!
Let's get this storm started!
Ooh, hey, that's good,
I should trademark that.
Not bad. Actually, kind of first rate.
What else does it do?
Your Excellency, you promised
to restore my horn, and give--
Uh, uh, uh... Okay, hang on.
You gotta be kidding me!
I can move the sun?
Whoa!
Now this is what I'm talkin' about!
Time to play!
Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday!
Day, night, day, night, day,
night, day, night, day, night,
sunrise, sunset...
Uh, yeah. I got a delivery here
for a "Mr. The Storm King."
I was given explicit instructions
to bring this here cake
to this here castle's throne room.
All right, then.
Look here, could one of y'all
go be a pal, go tell your boss
he's not getting his
"Congratulations on subduing
defenseless pastel ponies" cake?
'Cause I don't want to be
the one responsible
for the big guy missin'
his special dessert...
You know what I'm sayin'?
Thank you kindly, fellas.
I'mma be sure and put in a good word
for the both of y'all.
Pinkie, quit lookin' so happy.
Y'ain't foolin' nopony.
Oh, okay!
Mmm, pie.
Oh, hello, cake.
Ooh, don't mind if I do.
Mmm.
It's some, like, gourmet icing.
Who puts eyeballs in filling?
Guards!
Uh-oh. Plan B?
The jig is up!
Come on!
Gotcha!
Argh!
Lovely.
Surprise!
Double surprise!
Whee!
Oh!
You seem tense.
Do you wanna talk about it?
Yeah!
Head for the castle!
We'll hold them off!
Come on!
Let it all out.
Fluttershy!
Oh, sorry, our time is up, buh-bye!
Buh-bye.
Keep going! Shelly, Sheldon...
I can't see!
Uh-oh.
Hey, ain't you a firebreathin' dragon?
What?
How?
- It's... It's the magic of--
- Yeah, yeah.
Friendship and flowers
and ponies, and blegh!
I'm so totally over the cute pony thing.
This ends now!
Uh-oh.
Yeah!
Move them hooves, ponies!
You'd have to be flying faster than
a speeding Pegasus
to break through that wind!
Excellent idea, Rainbow Dash!
Now, I truly am the Storm King!
And the entire world will bow
to my ba-ba-ba-boom, baby!
Yes, yes you are every bit
as powerful as I promised, sire.
Now, restore my horn and I swear to use
my magic to serve you.
Who cares about
your dinky little unicorn horn?
But we, we had an agreement.
Get with the program!
I used you. It's kind of what I do.
Argh!
Hold on!
Why are you saving me?
Because this is what friends do.
Aw, isn't that just so sweet.
Yeah.
See ya.
You sure about this?
Yes, do it!
Thank you!
I'm excited. Who's excited?
I've never been so excited!
Whee!
Bullseye!
Pinkie! You all came back!
I'm so sorry! I was wrong to--
I'm sorry, too!
Friends mess up sometimes,
but we never should--
Uh, make up later! This isn't over!
I've got to get control of it!
Go! You've got this, Twilight!
No. We've got this.
Together.
Whee!
The staff belongs to me!
No! That's my staff!
Mine! Mine!
No!
- Oh, no, no!
- Whoa!
Twilight!
No!
Yay!
- Yeehaw! All right!
- Yay.
Group hug!
No!
Whoa.
I can't believe she did that.
I can.
Now what?
Now, we fix everything.
Ah! Twilight!
Princesses!
Fillies and gentlecolts!
Get ready for a little...
Songbird Serenade!
And now, to celebrate
the fact that we're all
still here in one piece,
give it up for Princess Twilight
and her friends!
All right! Way to go, guys!
Yeah!
♪ I know you, you're a special one ♪
♪ Some see crazy where I see love ♪
♪ You fall so low ♪
♪ But shoot so high ♪
♪ Big dreamers shoot for open sky ♪
♪ So much life in those open eyes ♪
♪ So much depth
you look forward to life ♪
- Ooh.
- And perfection.
♪ But when your wounds open,
you will cry ♪
Mom!
You are so grounded.
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears
as they're fallin' down ♪
♪ I can see your soul grow ♪
♪ Through the pain
as they hit the ground ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears as the sun comes out ♪
♪ As the sun comes out ♪
Well, that's one thing
that never changes around here.
A party.
Well, I hope you'll stay.
More friends are definitely merrier.
But, um...
My horn?
You know...
your horn is pretty powerful,
just like the pony it belongs to.
I did tell you I wanted to show
everypony in Equestria
what I could do, right?
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears
as they're fallin' down ♪
♪ I can see your soul grow ♪
♪ Through the pain
as they hit the ground ♪
Nice touch, Tempest.
Actually, that's not my real name.
Ooh! What is it?
It's Fizzlepop Berrytwist.
Okay! That is the most awesome
name ever!
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears
as they're fallin' down ♪
♪ I can see your soul grow ♪
♪ Through the pain
as they hit the ground ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears as the sun comes out ♪
♪ As the sun comes out ♪
♪ I am here, and I see your pain ♪
♪ Through the storms
through the clouds, the rain ♪
♪ I'm tellin' you, you cannot escape ♪
♪ You can do it, just feel, baby ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears
as they're fallin' down ♪
♪ I can see your soul grow ♪
♪ Through the pain
as they hit the ground ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears
as they're fallin' down ♪
♪ I can see your soul grow ♪
♪ Through the pain
as they hit the ground ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears as the sun comes out ♪
♪ As the sun comes out ♪
♪ Here comes the sun smiling down ♪
♪ Smiling down ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears
as they're fallin' down ♪
♪ I can see your soul grow ♪
♪ Through the pain
as they hit the ground ♪
♪ I can see a rainbow ♪
♪ In your tears as the sun comes out ♪
♪ So, we wanna stay ♪
♪ But can't find peace
while sitting still ♪
♪ I guess we never will ♪
♪ We run the way,
we won't hurry back again ♪
♪ The journey is the end ♪
♪ I love this very moment
we're speedin' up, not slowin' ♪
♪ We might know we can't win
but we're dumb enough to try ♪
♪ We're going, there's no maybe
That's why they call us crazy ♪
♪ And we'll say if anybody asks us ♪
♪ Hey! Where you gonna go? ♪
♪ We're off to see the world ♪
♪ We don't need to know ♪
♪ Oh! Hey! Where you gonna go? ♪
♪ We're off to see the world ♪
♪ We don't need to know ♪
♪ We never need to know,
seeking boundaries to break ♪
♪ Let's forget the ones we've made ♪
♪ So we carry on ♪
♪ Don't let good things pass us by ♪
♪ The time we're gone will
be the best time of our life ♪
♪ I love this very moment
we're speedin' up, not slowin' ♪
♪ We might know we can't win
but we're dumb enough to try ♪
♪ We're going, there's no maybe
that's why they call us crazy ♪
♪ And we'll say if anybody asks us ♪
♪ Hey! Where you gonna go? ♪
♪ We're off to see the world ♪
♪ We don't need to know ♪
♪ Oh! Hey! Where you gonna go? ♪
♪ We're off to see the world ♪
♪ We don't need to know ♪
♪ So go tell 'em we won't stop,
we know they can't change us ♪
♪ We're gonna go way off the map ♪
♪ To get ourselves back on the track ♪
♪ Go tell 'em we won't stop,
we know they can't change us ♪
♪ No need to worry so much,
we do whatever we want ♪
♪ Oh! Hey! Where you gonna go? ♪
♪ We're off to see the world ♪
♪ We don't need to know ♪
♪ Oh! Hey! Where you gonna go? ♪
♪ We're off to see the world ♪
♪ We don't need to know ♪
♪ Oh! Oh! Oh oh! ♪