Credits & Thanks to miss_p1nky for the sub
This story has been inspired
by true historical events
Hwang Jung-min
So Ji-sub
Song Joong-ki
Lee Jung-hyun Kim Suan
Kim Min-jae Kim Joong-hee
Kim In-woo Shin Seunghwan
Lee Kyoung-young
Get down, quickly.
Get down there.
Move.
Keep in line.
Hey, we can't fit in here.
Someone small, okay?
Kids?
Send the young ones in there.
Get in there.
Gas!
Help! Help!
Help!
Where are you going! Get back here!
Not today.
Get in.
Bastard.
November 1944
Japan Hashima Coal Mine, Korean Quarters
I'm sorry.
You've had to pay for
my generation's sins.
I wish you success.
Grow old and fight for Korea.
We'll come back for you.
Don't you worry about an old man like me.
Just live a good life.
Time is running out.
Let's go.
Won't you come with us?
Then who will care for Mr. Yoon?
Even the weather is helping you out.
It's time. Hurry.
Go on! Be careful.
If one of you is killed on the way.
Leave him or you'll all die.
Care only for yourself until
reaching Nomo Peninsula.
Hide there for a day to
rest up, then go to Nagasaki.
A lot of people get caught
in Nagasaki as well.
So don't rest easy until you reach Korea.
Please survive, and let's
meet in a better world.
Hurry.
Who's there? Don't move!
Stop or we'll shoot!
You want to get killed too?
How much further?
What?
How much further to go?
We're almost there! Keep going!
Yamada-san.
Should we fish them out?
Why bother?
Just report that we found them drowned.
With three catches, we'll get a bonus.
Let's go back, quickly!
1, 2, 3!
Labor Mobilization for
the Japanese Empire
It's not the front line.
Why get so uptight?
It's no joke. I've been drafted.
Oh my, drafted?
Don't you intellectuals know that slogan?
"The people have a duty to the nation."
Then will you send your son to do his duty?
My son has tuberculosis.
If not for that
he could serve in the
rear like you, earn money,
and support the Greater
East Asia Co-Prosperity...
What's with this damned music?
Would you like a drink?
Mister Lee, Mister Lee.
Damn.
Are you going to play this music all night?
We're sending boys off
to war, it's too gloomy.
Don't you have any nice jazz?
Why?
You know that jazz is banned.
You want me arrested?
Who's going to arrest you?
This room is filled with high-ranking,
well-connected people.
We need some fun for once.
You want some fun?
That'll cost you a bit of hazard pay.
Oh gosh... all right.
February 7, 1945 Peninsula Hotel,
Myeongdong Seoul
Where's Gang-ok?
On the stage.
If he wants to stay out of jail,
tell him to come down and find me.
Huh, why? Did he make trouble again?
Damn idiot.
Fooled around with a section chief's wife.
Gang-ok.
♪ The tap dance of love ♪
♪ Until the night is gone ♪
Gang-ok.
Okay.
Give her a hand.
No, come on.
Come on, everyone.
With a glass of champagne.
Let's have ourselves a dance.
Where's my wife?
Stand up!
Spin! Spin, you brat.
Wait, Daddy! Wait!
Are you out of your mind?
The section chief's wife likes my music.
She kept offering to buy dinner,
how can I turn it down?
And offered to introduce
me to the theater owner.
All we did was eat.
If you get drafted for
this, what will she do?
I'm not going to be drafted.
You think you'll get away with
touching a section chief's wife?
Then today you play jazz?
Did you bring it?
Here.
It's nine musicians, including you.
And your daughter makes ten.
There'll be nothing left for me
and my police colleagues
I'm always in your debt, Mr. Sugiyama.
Look.
I'll arrange a bribe for you and your band.
I'm asking around the offices
of Japanese factories.
Explain the situation to your band well.
And bring in some more cash.
You always said you wanted to work in Japan
I heard.
The Philippines The army was
driven out of the Philippines again.
Is Japan going to lose?
That's all just talk. Don't
you read the papers?
There are thousands of U.S.
POWs in Japan now.
It'll be over before the
cherry blossoms fall, trust me.
We're going to see cherry blossoms?
February 12, 1945 Ferry to Shimonoseki
Get off then.
Let's go.
God, what a smell.
You should be sucking
on your mom's breasts.
What's a kid like you doing on this boat?
I was running errands for my father.
And the town clerk said by joining the army
I can earn lots of money
and put me in a truck.
Okay, okay.
Couldn't even tell my
parents before leaving.
Tell me about it. They dragged
me off on my wedding night.
As a newlywed?
I was still hard down there.
And already forgetting her face.
You in the glasses, how'd you end up here?
I go to Keijo University.
Whoa!
You are an intellectual?
No doubt, studying is
better than going to war.
I heard if you work like crazy
for one year, you get a house?
Even still...
How could they drag off
pre-pubescent boys?
Snatching them from the fields
or when they're out wrestling.
Give me the case.
When the boat lands
we'll ditch these guys.
- So bear it until then.
- Okay.
All of you brought cash?
Take it out.
This is our lifeline.
If we lose this, we're dead.
Okay.
Dad, where are we really going?
You'll see later. Stop asking me, go away.
You asshole.
There's a fight.
Is that Choi Chil-sung?
The famous gangster?
Stupid Koreans, making sure
everyone knows we like fighting.
Can't help but fight each other.
Stop fighting! Calm down!
Sohee.
Go away! Go!
Any more trouble, we'll call
it a riot and start shooting.
What the fuck is he saying?
Hey.
Can anyone here speak Jap?
If you freak out again,
they'll start shooting.
So shut the fuck up and calm down.
How'd your mouth get so filthy?
Is it as filthy between your legs?
Did you ever see between my legs?
Did you?
Do you even know who you're talking to?
Sit down!
You look like gangsters
from some Seoul slum.
So if the Japs slap you around.
You take it out on Korean girls?
Quiet, sit down.
All right, just let go.
Sit down, guys.
I said sit.
Not much worth grabbing there anyway.
Are you a man?
I feel bad for your mom...
Wow, she made a fool of him.
Stick out too much and people hate you.
Sometimes you have to keep your head down.
Some people bring on their fate.
Shimonoseki Harbor, Japan
Dear passengers.
The ferry from Busan to
Shimonoseki has arrived
Japanese passengers, please
await separate instructions.
Sohee, listen to me.
If you lose my hand.
Watch my back and follow me.
- You guys, hold those cases tight.
- Okay.
Stay focused.
Hold this.
Sohee! Sohee!
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
This letter is from Detective Sugiyama
of Seoul Central Police Station.
Where can I find Shimura-san?
Shimura-san?
Yes.
Detective Sugiyama from Seoul.
Told me to find Shimura-san.
There are lots of Shimuras here.
This way, please.
Hey, take them.
Wait...
Detective Sugiyama...
Recommendation Letter
Wait, let go.
He told me to find Shimura.
Workers' ferry to Hashima
Sohee, are you okay?
Sohee, are you okay? Are...
I don't need that!
Asshole!
Stop it!
Stop!
Daddy!
Sohee! Sohee!
Sohee, it'll be okay!
Stay with those women!
Please stop!
No!
Next!
Take your bag and go!
Move forward.
Keep going.
Bastard.
It really is nothing, you see.
I just have cigarettes.
What's this?
Give it here.
Go, now!
Don't stare. Eyes forward.
Hey, shut up and put
your head on the ground.
Hands on your head
I said hands on your head.
Nothing
I have nothing.
Foreheads on the ground.
What do we do with these?
It's war here, too.
Get rid of that Korean habit
of depending on everyone.
Sir! Sir! You're Korean?
Just a moment, please.
There's been some kind of mistake
I was supposed to meet someone here.
We haven't been drafted like the others.
This is from Detective Sugiyama
at Seoul Central Police Station.
And this is our performing license
I'm Lee Gang-ok of the Lee Gang-ok Band.
We released a record at
Okay Record Company.
We performed at Government
Hall, Myungdong Theater.
Peninsula Hotel, everywhere!
Musicians?
1, 2, 3, 4.
This kind of shit always
gets mixed up in the crowd.
They said it's a factory.
Why take off our clothes?
Follow me.
Go on.
Are those tattoos?
Here at Hashima Comfort Station.
We've received a special medal for
being free of venereal disease.
To protect our perfect record
please keep yourselves clean.
Next.
Sir, just a minute.
This is a luxury Western
watch called Rolex.
It was a gift from someone
at the Governor-General's office
I'm sure you'll take care of things.
But I came here with my daughter
Lee Sohee. We came off the boat separately.
She's just a little girl.
If you could even tell me where she is...
Can you play "Cherry
Blossoms of the Same Class"?
Yes.
Damned music men are
settling in comfortably.
Son of a bitch.
♪ You and I are ♪
♪ Cherry blossoms of the same class ♪
♪ Blooming in the same ♪
♪ Naval training ground ♪
♪ Any flower ♪
♪ Is destined to fall ♪
♪ So let us fall brilliantly ♪
♪ For the sake of our nation ♪
I see some talented men
from Korea have arrived.
Welcome.
Yes.
Thank you
I am from Seoul...
Sorry... Sorry.
I am the manager of Hashima Mine.
Shimazaki Daisuke.
We welcome you from distant Korea
to fulfill your duty here.
As loyal subjects of His
Majesty the Emperor,
I grant you the honor of taking part
in the Imperial Army's war.
Here at Hashima Mine
for 50 years, this place has
led as a supplier of coal
to the industry of the
Great Japanese Empire.
This is a historic site.
The coal we produce here
is not merely coal.
A single lump of coal
is a drop of blood.
A weapon.
And a piece of history.
Sons of the Emperor,
I urge you to fulfill your duties
as glorious soldiers of industry,
and to not dishonor the
Imperial Japanese Army.
Hurry up.
Japanese Residential Area Comfort Station
- How dare you Japanese...
- Go away.
- Sister.
- Filthy whore!
Shame on you.
Don't get pregnant at the comfort station.
One woman got pregnant
at the Chinese station.
They cut her stomach and took the baby out.
And a few days later she was
receiving soldiers again.
We will now assign dormitories.
After locating your room,
prepare quickly and gather outside.
The account slips we give you
show the transport fees you
incurred while coming here.
Traveling costs from Seoul
and other cities to Busan,
the ferry to Shimonoseki,
and transport to Hashima Island,
have been covered by the company,
Korean Living Quarters
and will be deducted from your pay.
Housing costs provided by the company
will be deducted from your pay.
All personal items supplied to you
are covered by the company
and will be deducted from
your first month's pay.
All expenses for meals
are covered by the company
and will be deducted from your pay.
Hey, get up if you're done eating.
For the country's future and your future
national bond and savings fees,
health insurance and pension funds
are calculated in a lump sum
and will be deducted from your pay.
Insurance card
Savings account.
For the sake of those who
don't speak our language
we employ translators
and provide job training.
Various amenities
and necessary equipment are furnished.
All these items
will be deducted from your pay.
If your first month's pay
is less than the company's expenses.
Fees will be deducted from your next pay.
What the hell will we have left?
I'll just run up debts here.
Hey, get moving.
Consider today a workplace tour
to learn your duties.
We at Hashima Mine
do not underestimate you for being Koreans.
We believe you can excel
from the first day.
Stop! Masks on!
Put your mask on, damn it.
Masks on.
Shit, can't you walk? You praying?
Get up now!
My fucking glasses broke!
Your glasses broke, so you're talking back?
Are you? Are you?
Stop it, you asshole.
Just give him a break on
bath time and meal time.
He's just a kid.
Step aside.
What are you doing?
Everyone sit down!
Fucking hell.
Hey music man!
You speak Jap, right?
Get over here.
Translate for me
I'm ready to kick that
Yakuza wannabe's ass.
Translate, now.
I request to duel that Korean boss of
yours.
I'm that famous Seoul
gangster Choi Chil-sung,
I came here to beat your
Korean Yakuza boss.
I am Choi Chil-sung,
I'm here to challenge
that Korean labor boss.
We fight samurai style, and if I win
me and my boys will watch over the Koreans.
my boys and I will oversee the Koreans.
If I lose, I'll treat him as my boss.
If I lose, that Korean
boss will be my boss.
You assholes.
That was a swear word.
Think you're a circus ringleader?
Drag him off!
Wait.
That sounds like fun.
All you need to do is win.
There are new Korean girls
at the comfort station.
How about betting on a pass?
Comfort station?
Everyone stop!
Koreans fighting each other
is just what they want.
The more we fight.
The more we play into their hands.
This bastard isn't Korean
like the rest of us.
What are you looking at,
you stupid Koreans.
From now on
I'll be leading the Koreans.
If you back me, I'll
keep the Koreans in line.
Please support me.
See me at the labor office.
Hurrah for Choi Chil-sung!
And where did this freak come from?
♪ Boss! ♪
♪ Let's whistle for him, ♪
♪ new boss Choi Chil-sung. ♪
Everyone bow.
The beauties have arrived.
Everyone take a seat.
Sit.
Go ahead, sit.
Hurry.
Here.
This meal is to welcome you.
Why so melancholy?
You, who will give up your bodies
to our soldiers fighting in
the Great East Asian War.
And to our soldiers of industry
are indeed invaluable assets.
Take pride in yourselves.
We used to employ first-class geisha
or former actresses from film studios.
Now mostly Korean women work here.
But this innocence is part of their charm.
This mood is too heavy
for a feast of welcome.
Play that record I brought.
Yes, sir.
To help you feel comfortable
I brought a Korean record which I enjoy.
It's quite lively.
We prepared beds for you here.
So relax, listen to some music,
and get to bed early tonight.
Sister, this song...
This is me singing.
This song...
I sang this song.
Hey! What are you doing?
Give it back.
Tell them I used to sing this song.
Tell them I sang it, please.
Tell them.
She sang what's playing right now.
I can sing and dance, play
instruments, whatever.
I can clean and do laundry.
She can perform, play instruments
and is also good at housework.
Ask her what she did before.
He asked what you did in Korea.
I played music in Seoul. The Yamamura Band.
She performed at the Yamamura Band.
My father and the rest
of the band are all here.
Long live the Emperor.
Hurrah.
July 1945, OSS Training Camp
Korean Liberation Army in China
How is your training with the OSS soldiers?
I'm trying my best.
You've got higher marks than the Americans.
The Seoul infiltration
operation you've been planning
I'm sorry, but we need
you for something else.
Some OSS intelligence
was leaked to our side.
The U.S. has developed a new bomb.
They say its power is beyond imagination.
The blast radius is up to 200km.
If they drop that from a B-29
onto the Japanese mainland...
That's all unconfirmed talk for now.
The point is, the Soviets
are about to invade.
The U.S. has already taken Okinawa.
If the Soviets join in
Japan won't last long.
It's time to focus on winning the war
not the battle.
For a speedy liberation,
we must join together.
Yoon Hak-chul.
Only he can resolve the conflicts
between all the factions fighting
for Korean independence.
He handled fundraising at the KPG
but two years ago, he was
caught by the Japanese
and disappeared without a trace.
We assumed he was executed without trial,
but according to U.S. intel,
he was detained near Nagasaki.
At Hashima Coal Mine.
Go bring back Mr. Yoon.
We will always be together. Our Hashima.
Gather around, everyone.
If we screw up again, we'll
be back in the mines.
Do your best! And smile!
If you don't smile I'll have Chil-sung
take you back to the mine.
Get ready, quick.
Hey, why don't you eat that?
Raw eggs are gross.
Eat when I tell you, kid!
It's great for your throat.
Some people can't eat at all!
Hurry up.
Hey!
Abracadabra... ta-dah!
Look at that grin.
If you want food, you have to pay for it.
Newbies who arrived today,
just follow the man in front.
Fuckers don't feed us crap.
The fuck is he blabbering about?
Isn't that dynamite?
What'll you do with it?
Stop sputtering and be quiet.
The liquid that seeps out is sweet.
Need to eat at least that to survive.
What if your stomach explodes?
Give me a taste.
Help me here.
It's okay.
It's just the coal dust in my lungs.
That's why I cough out black sputum.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Hey, there's gas coming out.
So what?
Block off the gas! And pump out sea water.
At the center of Japan's leadership
in the Great East Asian
War is Hashima Coal Mine.
Long live the Emperor.
Long live the Japanese Empire.
For Hashima Mine
and its executives returning
to the head office.
Cheers.
Rock, scissors, paper! Rock! Rock!
We're even, try again.
Here, it's your turn.
Didn't you eat!
Are you alright?
Support his back.
Are you hurt?
It's sliding down!
Hey kid, out of the way.
No!
Huh?
What's that noise?
Run!
Run out quick! Bring your tools.
Don't drop your tools, bring them.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
How many times has Mine No. 2 caught fire?
Do I need to step in
every time this happens?
What about the passage to Mine No.3?
It hasn't spread there yet.
How much is Mine 2 producing?
It has the lowest production.
We're already 1100 meters
below the seafloor.
So it'll be hard to mine deeper.
Save me.
Save the young ones first.
Mr. Yoon! You must go up.
Don't let anyone die! Not one!
No.
That's the Korean section, right?
Seal them off.
Prevent damage spreading to other mines.
There are people here! You bastards!
There are people here!
Sir, Yoon Hak-chul is in the mine.
Out of the way.
I told you not to put him in the mine.
If he dies,
what should we do if the Koreans riot?
By whatever means necessary, get him out.
Hold on just a bit.
Hurry up and dig.
Are you going to work all day? Huh?
They're waiting for you.
Jong-go! There's a problem in Mine 2.
Damn, I worked all night!
Why'd they have to wake me up?
Isn't that where we plugged
the gas leak before?
Hey, just shut your mouth
and follow orders.
Ah, are you back on duty?
Fuck.
You sure this connects to Mine 3?
Shouldn't you know that?
What? You prick!
Blast through it.
What?
There's no other way.
We point the gas at these supports
and light it.
Newbie! Shut the fuck up!
I don't know if there's enough gas
to explode thoroughly.
You know...
I hid this thing here.
We can't drill any deeper.
We can't.
Gas keeps leaking, what if there's a fire?
That's why we called you technicians!
Okay, okay...
It's going in!
Keep drilling!
Pull.
Pull it.
The Koreans heard there was an accident
but they don't know yet who lived or died.
Announce we'll move wounded Koreans
to a main hospital in Nagasaki.
Then send them to the crematorium
and burn them with the corpses.
There are limits to how
many Koreans we can bring.
Given the war struggles.
We will not allow the company
to lose any more money
I'll be sure to contain the problem.
Chiba -san.
When do you plan to inspect our mine?
- The thing is...
- I'm sorry.
As I'm grateful for your
recommendation of our facility
I mean to send someone to
express my deepest gratitude.
I see.
You won't be disappointed.
Where is Yoon Hak-chul now?
He's coming! He's coming!
Here he comes!
If the company doesn't
release a list of casualties
and draw up compensation and safety plans,
I will refuse all talks
with Manager Shimazaki.
We support you!
We support you! We support you!
It's about time to leave.
Wait a minute! You give me this.
You're in charge of toilets now.
You'll scoop piss and shit.
Hey!
Fuck.
Someone tell this madman not to hit me.
Give me my money's worth.
I don't need
any Korean bitches glaring at me.
Come on, don't be like this.
You got trained by the American.
But without their help.
You think you can escort Mr.
Yoon out of here?
The plan was to use the network here.
And contact Korean agents
at OSS headquarters.
Through an agent planted on the
food ship that stops here.
We'll go by ship to the U.S.
base in Okinawa.
How do we know you're not on their side?
You say you're OSS-trained resistance?
I was a student soldier
sent to Japanese unit 7991 in China.
Then I escaped last July in
Xuzhou, then this February
I met KLA General Lee
Beom-seok in Chongqing.
Did he send any personal message to me?
He says he'll treat you to
your favorite trotter stew
and cold dishes at Hwapyung Restaurant.
When do you plan to move?
I'll send in another girl.
Just sit.
I said sit! I'm not here for romance.
Why not?
Do the marks on my chest make you go limp?
Hell...
Don't you need a Korean to
complain to, to breathe easier?
Fuck... even worse than the Japs
are these damned mosquitos.
At first I was dragged to China.
I had no idea.
They said I was going to work.
They drove me
to a Japanese army base.
Hell.
The mosquitos bit me like crazy.
Some mosquito bites can kill a person.
One bite, and your whole
body swells with fever.
However much you drink, your insides burn.
There was a girl from Heungyang,
the Japanese said she was
pretending to be sick.
Put her on nails and
rolled her back and forth.
She died in front of everyone.
I didn't want to end up like her.
I was too scared to tell them I was sick.
Figured I'd rather die
fast, so I drank lye.
But I didn't die.
It was a Japanese doctor
who stopped me from dying.
But then a Korean pimp washed me.
And threw me right back
at those Japanese guys.
It was a fucking Korean town clerk
who sent me to that comfort station.
When the unit retreated, I barely escaped.
But that Korean pimp
caught and sent me here.
So I need a Korean to complain to?
To breathe easier?
Biting the hand that feeds you.
You need to control your temper.
Sooner or later, things will get better.
Fuck.
Are you doing a lousy job on purpose?
Try finding any guy who
won't get off on this.
Dragging me out of the hospital to do this.
Okay, here
I send out so many of these,
why does so little come back?
Damned guards cut the rations.
You're not hoarding it yourself?
Shit...
Bro, just one cigarette.
You still didn't pay for last month's.
Fuck.
The damned Japanese raised their
pension funds or whatever.
We all had them raised.
So control your gambling! If
you're broke, just sleep.
Wait, pay up before you go.
Damn it.
Give this to the attendant
for 10 cigarettes.
Yes, sir.
Manager Shimazaki is calling you.
Sohee!
What is it? Oh no...
A splinter.
Be more careful, kid.
What's that smell?
I've been thinking of this for a while.
After today's accident,
I thought I should meet you
and propose something
before it's too late.
I see.
About your daughter...
In the recent U.S. bombing
of our head office,
Chiba-san lost his daughter.
Rather than having her stay here
where it's so dangerous,
I was thinking
to send her to Chiba-san
as an adopted daughter.
Mr. Lee,
we're in a war.
In wartime, winners don't always survive.
Survivors are true winners.
On the next freight ship out,
let's send Sohee.
Huh?
♪ Meeting in this world of woe ♪
♪ What is your wish? ♪
♪ Will being rich ♪
♪ Make you happy? ♪
Airplane.
The post office key?
We'll pay whatever you want.
Hell, how would you know what I want?
We'll give you this in advance.
Wow, advance pay?
I need to know what this is about.
We need to check a package.
I don't team up with
people who keep secrets.
If you need to check a package,
isn't it easier to just bribe
one of the labor officers?
- Well...
- We need the telegraph.
The telegraph?
I'm going on patrol, how about you guys?
Know how to use it?
Just get us the key.
A newbie wants to use the telegraph.
A Korean who looks like
an independence leader
bribes me...
What's going on here?
Forget it, then.
- I already know, how can I forget?
- Geeze.
Should I go ask the
boss to look into this?
Park Mu-young.
Mr. Yoon will escape from here.
All we need is the key, no trouble.
You decide.
If you don't cooperate,
we'll kill you.
Hey, Yamamura!
What are you doing? It's almost curfew.
Where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
The drawings are done.
Tell Maeda to see me tomorrow.
What, already?
I want one, too.
But what are you doing here?
They're fighting over gambling debts
I'm trying to mediate.
Damn idiots.
Shake hands.
I'll take care of this, you go on.
All right, then.
Have a good night.
You don't need to pay
but I have one condition.
When he escapes,
take me and my daughter.
What are you talking about!
I take it that old man won't be swimming?
Since you want the telegraph,
you must have something lined up.
Just kill me,
or have the Japanese kill you,
or take my daughter and me.
This time, you decide.
If our plan is leaked,
I'll kill you myself.
One, two, three.
Where the hell did he go?
Can't he leave me alone?
Hey, go to my spot.
Hey painter.
Where's the guy who made
me a lock that time?
Is he on the night shift?
Why don't I see him?
Bang!
They sent him to the tool repair factory...
to work as a technician,
since he's good with tools.
Bang!
Tool repair factory? Shit.
Good afternoon.
I need a favor from the locksmith.
Go ahead.
What brings you out here?
You want another lock?
No, I've got a really important key.
I'm scared of losing it,
so I'd like a copy.
Hand it over.
Yes but... I need to bring it back.
Something smells fishy.
How come you get all the luck?
Which woman's home?
You're quick.
Her husband carries the key around.
You know how it is.
Here you go. See you later.
Hello!
We'd still be nice to
Sohee without these gifts.
I know, but treat her well.
What are you sighing about?
Come here.
I talked to your supervisor lady.
You'll move to her room.
So when I call you at night,
you can run out quickly.
Can't you ask the manager
to let us stay together?
Why? Did he do something?
It's just that I'm lonely here...
The other women tell me I'm annoying.
Even when the manager takes care of me.
Damn bitches.
That's why I told you to
behave well with other people
and be careful what impression you give.
What are you crying about?
Don't you know all that I'm doing for you?
Think you're the only
one who's got it hard?
Why do you always say
everything's my fault?
Never mind. What do I say to you?
Anyway...
Always be ready.
So you can run right out if I call you.
Then we can be together, all right?
Got a good movie for us?
Yes, a love story!
Good evening.
Bro.
Want to see a dirty picture?
Uh, good!
Come this way.
The outside door, the office,
and the director's room.
You remember my terms?
I have eyes everywhere, you know.
Hey, boss!
What is it now?
Nothing, I want to show you something.
What the hell? It won't open?
Gang-ok, that rat!
Hey, assholes!
Who is it? Stop right there.
Hashima Eagle contacted.
Preparations to transport Eagle complete.
Number of passengers?
Yoon and Park, two people.
Sending food transport
ship in 48 hrs, 5AM.
Find Takagura on transport ship.
Wishing safe return, end
Korean Account Records
Seems the war is going badly.
When was the last time Japan
used good paper like this?
What do propaganda pamphlets
have to do with the war?
The U.S. still has enough money
to make pamphlets with good paper.
Aren't wars ultimately won
by those with the most money?
Give me the relevant documents
for me and the other Koreans.
Ah...
More leaflets littering our island.
Those are bombers.
Citizens and employees,
turn off lights and stay indoors.
I repeat.
Citizens and employees,
turn off lights and stay indoors
I repeat...
It's time.
Why so cheap this time?
Too many people involved
now, I want to wrap it up.
Where's the attendant?
Let's go.
Damn those bastards!
Sir, it's time for your medicine.
Sir?
Quiet around here.
Sohee!
What is it?
Gang-ok? Come on in.
All right. Where's Sohee?
Quick...
Let me see Sohee.
I'll come back for you.
Shit.
When did you last see Park?
What?
Mr. Yoon is missing.
I couldn't say goodbye to anyone.
What kind of operation is this?
I had to keep everything completely secret.
And I have something to ask you first.
I found Koreans' pay records.
Korean Account Records
in the post office safe.
In the post office safe.
The pensions and bond payments
taken from their paychecks
don't go to their accounts,
but to someone else's.
Your name is entered on their contracts
and half the money flowing
into your account
is forwarded into Manager
Shimazaki's account.
Are you aware of this?
Since coming here
I heard that pay is embezzled
by the manager and several others...
But an account in my name?
Even dead workers' compensation
is going in there.
Without their families being
told of their deaths.
Shimazaki... I never
thought he'd go this far.
Looking through the documents,
I kept seeing your signature.
Who could have made those files?
Didn't it occur to you that
Shimazaki could've made it?
No labor strike or escape
plan has ever succeeded here
I wonder why.
If you set up a leader of the Koreans
and then use him,
then this kind of control is possible.
Can you explain how a man caught
delivering huge sums for the KLA
could have received no
trial from the Japanese
and ended up here?
This is just what Shimazaki wanted.
Should I answer for you?
You fool!
Shimazaki knew someone
like you was coming.
You converted.
If you weren't on their
side, you'd be in jail.
Park Mu-young.
No one will follow you once they find out.
Why do you think
Shimazaki agreed to negotiate
over their protection?
Why?
Negotiate?
So dragging little boys off to
mines and stealing their money
was a negotiation?
If you're so convinced of my guilt
then right here,
shoot me.
You scoundrel! Trying
to run off without us?
I warned you!
That if you betray me, I'll report you!
You stay there!
Gang-ok!
Listen closely to me.
This is an American spy
with no connection to Korea.
If you report him
the two of you can escape.
If Shimazaki finds out, you all die!
What was your real goal in coming here?
Sohee!
When I shout,
run to Manager Shimazaki
and tell him everything.
He's on Shimazaki's side.
God damn fuckers!
Then when does the ship come?
Daddy.
Sohee, it's okay. Just stay still.
Why do you take the girl!
Let go of her.
Drop the gun first.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine, go watch over our men.
Park has betrayed us!
Put down the gun, now.
Our men are on the way.
Stop being stupid.
Try reading this.
What kind of plot is this?
Shut up, you scoundrel!
Coming to save someone like you...
Don't you feel sorry for them?
Ito Takamichi Yoon Hak-chul...
I will report your treason to the
Provisional Government of Korea.
You bastard!
Run, quick!
This way, quick.
This way.
Hurry.
You Koreans, wait there.
Block the Koreans.
I'm Japanese.
Only Japanese can...
Shut the gate! Get in, quick!
Move aside.
Shut the gate.
Asshole.
What the hell, why are they shooting.
Open the gate.
Sook, get up!
You want to die?
Let me go.
Sook!
Stop.
Don't move.
Don't shoot.
I'm Ito...
Yoon Hak-chul.
Sir.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you hurt?
How are you?
I'm okay. Let's get away from here.
About that account book...
Don't worry about that.
I'll go back and get it.
Did you see what was in it?
Sir, I believe you to the end.
Help!
That man, he shot...
Quiet.
Sir, are you all right?
Sir, what will we do?
How could this happen to us?
You there! Did Gang-ok die too?
Someone thought they saw his corpse.
So we're looking...
Gang-ok, where are you?
Damn it.
Daddy, I'm thirsty.
Why are you giving me that?
- Any food here?
- Probably.
Drive out the Koreans!
Does the line work?
Hold out as long as you can
with the food and water you have.
Our manager's unrecoverable.
Are you telling us to just die?
Yesterday the U.S. dropped
a new bomb on Hiroshima.
A new bomb?
Word is coming in
that it's tremendously powerful.
There's no official report yet.
But it's said there are 100,000 casualties.
And no living thing survived.
The Americans have created
something unimaginable.
Are we going to lose this war?
After Hitler's death and
the fall of Germany.
Industrialists who helped the Nazis.
Are being lined up and
tried as war criminals.
If you have any materials
that can be used against us
burn them.
If it's a war crimes trial.
Shouldn't we kill the Koreans
who could testify against us?
That'd be the most effective solution.
But with Shimazaki in that state
can it be done?
If you take care of things properly
then surely you can take his place.
Drive out the Koreans!
Drive them out!
You little prick.
You ruined everything!
Does it hurt a lot?
I can't believe this.
Corpses will be burned to prevent disease.
So finish identifying the bodies.
What about Japanese corpses?
Why is it only us who are
burned like garbage?
So as not to create more panic
for now, only you and I must
know of the manager's death.
Take this for now.
I couldn't find what you described
so I just took anything.
I hear a Japanese schoolgirl was murdered
Korean attendant Song
Jong-go says he saw it.
And the suspect is Korean.
That's good news.
Now we have a justification
to crack down on the Koreans.
Hey!
Sohee!
Bro, you're alive?
You think I'm dead?
Why'd you want to meet here
and not the kitchen?
There's someone who can't know
the two of us are alive.
Have this.
What the hell? Eat this?
Hey, take a can from my shelf.
It disappeared in the bombing.
Huh? What about the cash?
All of it?
God damn it.
It was a life-or-death situation.
Why didn't you get it? Where have you been?
It's a long story.
Is Yoon asking about me?
Until the situation stabilizes
I will carry out the duties
of our wounded manager.
During this vicious American attack
when everyone is heartbroken
an innocent, pretty young girl
lost her life to a savage who
couldn't control his lust.
Can you see this innocent victim's family?
If you've any conscience, come forward!
What evidence do you
have that it was a Korean?
Witness, come forward.
Identify the suspect.
He was with us yesterday.
You scumbag!
Don't overdo it, you thug.
Ah, I want some cold soy noodles.
With savory broth... salt on top
I like it better with sugar.
All right, sugar it is.
Pull out a mouthful of those noodles...
With radish kimchi on the side...
Oh, let's stop this.
Only makes me hungrier.
When we get out of here,
let's go eat noodles first.
Then, we'll go back home?
Of course.
That's why your dad is helping me.
But right now...
There's something I need
you to help me with.
Will you help me?
Mr. Yoon.
If you get a chance to leave
this island, you'll take it?
If I take you to the U.S. occupied zone,
can you tell them I helped you
to look after the laborers
and supported Korean liberation?
If the manager is dead,
you'll probably get his position.
Is that really necessary?
I've thought it over
and we're both smart enough to know
how this war will end.
In return for getting you out
give me the money you
pocketed with the manager.
Can I leave right away?
The coal transport ship is almost repaired,
our communications are back,
and it's no problem to leave here with you,
but if I want to take
my family from Nagasaki
I'll have to follow the
head office's command
and deal with all the Koreans.
Deal with?
The Koreans who remembers
what happened here
must be killed.
Where did that old man Yoon hide it?
Records of Korean Laborers
Hey!
You lost your position
as the Korean leader
and took out your grudge
against a Japanese girl
but she fought back
and you strangled her.
Is that so hard to admit?
Hey! Just say it's true and
sign with your thumbprint
then I'll treat you like my older brother.
Song Jong-go...
I will fold you like a blanket
and chop you into pieces, you prick.
Gather all the remaining dynamite.
Tomorrow we'll put all
the Koreans in the mine.
Tomorrow morning...
Yamada plans to force all the Koreans
into the mine and kill us.
Women of course, and even children.
I beg you.
I won't ask for myself
but please take Sohee away from here.
Surely you can manage to take her.
I'm going to escape
with all the Koreans here.
In this place where we sweated and toiled
we have a right to proper treatment.
Today's arrest of Choi
Chil-sung as a murder suspect
is no different from what
all us Koreans have suffered!
Therefore, I
requested Manager Shimazaki
to stop Koreans from
being unfairly accused
and demanded an open trial.
- Out of the way.
- Let's go.
And furthermore.
I will reach an agreement
with the manager.
First.
We will be given the same quality food
as the Japanese.
Second.
The coal quotas raised last month
will be lowered.
Third.
Full time off on holidays.
Fourth.
Work to repair the island
will be compensated.
And finally! Injured young
workers will all be returned
to our homeland Korea.
We'll send them home.
There's just one condition.
Given what we will receive,
we need to show our sincerity.
Tomorrow is Hashima Mine's first opening
since the bombing.
The manager has asked
as a show of our unity
and for a new start
that all Koreans including
women and children
join the opening ceremony inside the mine.
What do you all think?
I object!
- Huh?
- Who is he?
Yoon Hak-chul never met the manager today.
The manager is dead.
If you enter the mine tomorrow
acting manager Yamada will have you buried.
What?
Park Mu-young, stop trying to stir chaos.
The U.S. has invaded Okinawa
and the war is almost over.
Yoon Hak-chul and Yamada
plan to bury you here
and then escape to the U.S. army.
Friends!
That man is a spy trying to
divide us Koreans! A spy!
All of you here
are decisive witnesses
of Hashima's war crimes.
Therefore, this company
plans to bury you in the
mine to destroy all evidence.
People!
Tell me!
Who do you trust?
You fucker!
That old geezer is a real fox.
Listen up, everyone.
Park is an independence fighter
who came to rescue Yoon.
But... if you can believe it,
Park discovered that Yoon
was Shimazaki's informant,
so Yoon shot him with a gun!
And this here!
Written by Yoon and the manager.
Lists all of the money they
skimmed off your paychecks.
People who died of
accidents, hunger, sickness, violence.
People who died trying to escape.
You stole their compensation.
This man Lee Gang-ok,
to kiss up to the Japanese
sold his own daughter.
And that spy
is completely unknown to us,
coming from who knows where.
That's right.
How do we know
Gang-ok and that newbie aren't spies?
Calm down.
All of us need to band together.
Let's keep our heads and not be fooled.
These unknown guys coming in
and slandering our Mr. Yoon
I saw it too.
Put down the gun, now!
Our men are on the way
I saw it.
I saw you shoot him and Choong-ho too.
Jang-woo, have you been bought off too?
Why betray your own country?
Do you really have to sell me?
Stop it, Jang-woo! How could you do it too?
What if I show you this?
4088 Yoon Hak-chul.
Torn off your shirt by
Choong-ho as he died.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
They're deceiving you.
I saw it too! He's a bad man.
That girl saw such an awful thing?
First, let's look at those documents.
This is nuts.
You need to prove what they say isn't true.
Ito Takamichi, Yoon Hak-chul.
That money you worked for
is dirty Japanese money.
Guilty of treason.
That money was for Korean independence.
Was that so wrong?
Bleeding the people dry!
It was for us!
Pretending to lead and
deceiving the people.
You fools.
For betraying the nation...
You think killing me will bring liberation?
I punish you in the name of Korea!
I'm the one who gave you
guys all everything.
So what are we going to do?
No one's ever managed to escape here.
Think we can all just
hold hands and leave?
Yoon has always tipped off the manager,
that's why they failed.
If we take the coal transport
ship in the harbor
we can succeed.
Wait a minute.
Who's going to drive that big ship?
Hold on, we got a few boatmen here.
I've sailed fishing boats.
I know the route, so with
5 or 6 men to row...
Hold on.
That freight ship is not a fishing boat.
It's not just that, if we all run for it.
Won't they start shooting
and stabbing us? What then?
The guards who come to Hashima
were all judged unfit for the battlefield.
And after the bombing
they're still spooked.
There are much more of us
and we got military training...
Instead
how about we try negotiating
with the Japanese?
To be honest, Japanese are
more enlightened than us,
if we try dialogue...
Dialogue my ass!
If they were sensible, would
we be living this way?
Remember the Kanto Earthquake?
They spread rumors that
Koreans poisoned the wells.
How could they say such
a thing and treat us like crap.
You say that because you
have skills and lived easy.
Who says I lived easy?
You're just trying to divide us, painter!
Hey!
Just decide who'd leave or stay.
This is wasting time.
He's right.
Those who want to go, can go.
Those who will stay, stay.
You really think they'd
kill so many people?
- Right?
- Yeah!
Daddy, aren't we going?
Damn it, I'm going to blow my top.
You stupid Koreans!
If you made it this far,
shouldn't you try to live?
Have you all grown
so used to being stepped on?
My goodness.
This girl and I want to live.
We'll go ourselves.
Wait! I'll go too.
I lost my leg and became a cripple
but I won't let them bury me here.
But Mallyon, what if
they really kill us all?
Even if just one of us survives, we win.
Just one.
My life was ruined
but I won't die in their hands.
Wait
I'll go too.
Are you really staying?
How can you trust them?
You should think it over.
Come on, we'll try talking to the Japanese!
Let's go!
There's no time, so we
won't try to persuade you.
Are you crazy? What's going on?
You telling them of our
plan is only trouble.
So please understand.
And besides
it'd be best if they found you tied up.
Don't need this.
Stabbing me first then
apologizing is useless.
Careful, careful...
Wait, I don't see Choi Chil-sung's gang.
If they tell the labor attendant...
They said they're going to rescue Choi.
Huh?
What'll they do then?
Let's hurry.
Boss.
What are you doing here?
They say they'll try you.
Let's go before things get worse.
Think of this as a drill, like in training.
We're going to move in groups.
When we're ready
women, the wounded,
and children will move first at our sign.
Our final goal
is to cross the coal belt over the wall,
board the ship, and escape.
This is dynamite they
prepared for the mine.
Explosives team, tie them
to the lantern batteries.
It will strengthen the blast.
The wounded, use tatami
mats to make shields.
Mallyon and the women will make
rope from fundoshi underwear.
Weapons team, take tools and
oil from the tool factory.
Lee and his band will gather
bottles for bottle bombs.
Those who can steer the
ship, help me take control.
The rest of you, wait for our signal.
It's dangerous, don't touch.
Why do you always yell at me?
Why are you here?
If you're ready, I'll bring everyone.
Don't do this, come with us.
You really think 400 people
can sneak onto a ship?
With all those wounded people?
Then do you want to start a war here?
We'll all die tomorrow anyway.
If you try to kill Jong-go, you'll die too!
Hey.
Did Park go without finishing them off?
They weren't here before.
Damn it.
Who's there?
It's me!
Shishido, it's me.
Gang-ok.
Why are you out so late? Go back inside.
I can't believe it either.
Get over here, quick.
With the big event tomorrow
Yamada said to bring the girls
and pour everyone a drink.
Since you guys have it hardest
I brought some girls... you know?
Really?
Where's the alcohol from?
Shimazaki had it stashed away
and Yamada took it out.
Just one drink for each of you.
If it's just one, better not to have any.
We'll give it a taste.
Come this way.
Bro! Quickly!
Women and the wounded first.
Can we really do this?
I don't see any guards.
I spent so much on Korean girls
if the manager finds out he'll be mad.
Who will know we started the fire?
They'll think the Koreans
kicked over a candle.
While they were sleeping.
Out of the way.
Go back.
Hey, it's women and the wounded first
I'm wounded too.
And she's a young girl.
Shouldn't we board first?
Bro! Don't you have any shame?
Take a look at these people!
Damn it.
Then at least let Sohee go first.
No!
Go.
Get up there, kid.
The sun will be up soon.
If you see a cripple go,
you can follow, right?
You'll be fine if you follow me.
So you come next.
♪ Doong-ge, Doong-ge, Doong-ge ♪
♪ My baby, Doong-ge ♪
♪ I am afraid of him being caught ♪
♪ Don't cry, Doong-ge ♪
♪ Will he ride in on the wind? ♪
♪ Will he ride in on the clouds? ♪
♪ Come without a sound ♪
♪ Come without a trace ♪
♪ We wanted to be together ♪
♪ We wanted to live as one ♪
♪ If not in this world ♪
♪ I'll meet you in the next world ♪
♪ Doong-ge, Doong-ge, Doong-ge ♪
♪ My baby, Doong-ge ♪
♪ I am afraid of him being caught ♪
♪ Don't cry, Doong-ge. ♪
Get to the coal depository.
The Koreans are escaping.
They've been spotted.
I'll join you, so you go first.
I keep my promises.
As they board the ship
we'll watch their backs.
You guys in the front, move.
The Koreans started a fire!
The Koreans are escaping!
There! Over there!
Check the back! Quickly!
Don't move in the back.
Snipers! Explosives!
Hold on.
It's a real war.
Kill every last one of them.
You rotten bastards.
Sohee, stay right here.
Kill every one of them.
- Stop shooting!
- That way!
Fuck, just let us go home.
I said this would never work!
From the very start!
Sohee! Hide, quickly!
Go back, you.
Lift! With all your strength!
Go over the wall and into the water.
Snipers and explosive team, move!
The rest of you, lift.
Light them here.
Let's fight to death!
1, 2, 3.
Dae-yeop
Lift it.
Sohee, hide here.
Follow me, guys.
Bring this.
Help me.
Spread it out.
Throw!
Grab the rope and follow me.
Bullets! I'm out of bullets!
Bayonets!
Charge!
Bastards! We don't deserve this!
Daddy!
Get back there Sohee, it's dangerous!
Pull the rope!
1, 2, 3...
Pull out.
Chil-sung, you asshole!
Come back here, bastard!
Pull it back, quick!
Pull it back!
What are you holding back for?
Move!
Pull the rope!
Pull!
Now push it!
A little more!
Lift it up!
Push!
That's it!
Climb up.
Everyone climb up.
Let the wounded climb up.
Sohee, where are you?
Daddy.
Sohee.
Hey.
Come on guys!
Get up!
Bastard!
Sorry for not keeping my promise.
You can rest now.
I'm on your side!
Kill all the Koreans,
whatever side they're on!
Kill them all.
- Bro! What do we do?
- Keep climbing.
Sung-il!
Lee Gang-ok.
Sohee, stay there!
Stay there.
Daddy! Daddy!
I've got you now.
Dirty Koreans!
Why aren't you grateful?
Why!
It's all over now.
Your manager and Yamada are dead.
Now we're going back to our home!
Daddy.
Boss...
I'm not going to die.
Why are you crying?
Stop!
Go over there, Sohee
I'm older, so let me ask you a favor.
Give her some soy noodles with sugar.
That's what she likes best.
Please look after my girl.
Sorry I couldn't give you anything.
Don't turn your nose up at raw eggs.
Sing a song for me.
Daddy, Daddy!
Daddy!
You said you wouldn't die!
You promised!
Daddy!
August 9, 1945, 11:02 AM Nagasaki
Oh my gosh... look at that.
A lot of Koreans live there too.
Hashima's coal mine
opened in September 1890.
From the 1937 invasion of China
to the end of World War II
it contributed greatly to Japan's
military industrial sector.
In the 1970s Japan adopted
new energy policies
and closed the mine in January 1974.
Sohee.
Look at me, girl.
Battleship Island, as a part of Japan's
Meiji Industrial Revolution Don't laugh!
became a UNESCO World Heritage
Site in 2015. Don't be nervous.
One of UNESCO's conditions is by the
end of December 2017 Answer me.
Round your lips.
but Japan has yet to comply
With confidence.
Just like before.
to post notices about
forced labor and other
historical facts. Did my
little girl prepare well?
Answer me.
Ready.
2, 3!
♪ Meeting in this world of woe ♪
♪ What is your wish? ♪
♪ Will being rich. ♪
♪ Make you happy? ♪
♪ Under the clear blue sky ♪
♪ Hundreds of thoughts on your mind ♪
♪ Everything is just a dream ♪
♪ Dreaming ♪
♪ Meeting in this world of woe ♪
♪ What is your wish? ♪
♪ Will being rich. ♪
♪ Make you happy? ♪
♪ Exaggerated laughter and chatters ♪
♪ Indulging in lust ♪
♪ Letting everything go ♪
♪ Will that make you happy? ♪
Fixed & Synced by bozxphd..