Subtitles by explosiveskull
(ALARM BUZZES)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(AIRCRAFT APPROACHING)
(SPRAY HISSING)
(HISSING STOPS)
(DRONE HOVERING)
(POT BOILING)
(TAP RUNNING)
(TAP STOPS)
K: I hope you don't mind me
taking the liberty.
I was careful
not to drag in any dirt.
SAPPER: I don't mind the dirt.
I do mind
unannounced visits.
You police?
Are you Sapper Morton?
Civic number NK68514?
I'm a farmer.
I saw that.
What do you farm?
SAPPER: It's a protein farm.
Wallace design.
Is that what I smell?
Grow that just for me.
Garlic.
Go on, try some.
No, thank you.
I prefer to keep
an empty stomach
until the hard part
of the day is done.
(CONTINUES BOILING)
K: How long you been here?
SAPPER: Since 2020.
K: But you haven't always
been a farmer, have you?
Your bag.
It's colonial medical use.
Military issue.
Where were you? Calantha?
Must have been brutal.
Plan on taking me in?
Let them take a look inside?
Mr. Morton,
if taking you in
is an option,
I would much prefer that
to the alternative.
I'm sure you knew
it would be someone in time.
(SAPPER SIGHS)
I'm sorry it had to be me.
- (POWERING UP)
- SAPPER: Good as any.
K: Now, if you don't mind,
if you could just look up
and to the left, please.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BANGING)
(SAPPER CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
- (CHOKING)
- (GRUNTING)
(CHOKING CONTINUES)
(GASPING)
(SAPPER YELLS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SAPPER GASPING)
(SAPPER CHOKING)
(BOTH PANTING)
- Please don't get up.
- (GASPS)
SAPPER: How's it feel
killing your own kind?
I don't retire my own kind
because we don't run.
Only older models do.
And you new models
are happy scraping the shit
because you've never
seen a miracle.
(BODY THUDS LOUDLY)
(SIGHS)
(BOILING CONTINUES)
(SNIFFING)
Just photograph everything.
(BEEPS)
Madam, please.
AUTOMATED VOICE: (ON RADIO)
Incoming LAPD re-codec hash.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You're hurt.
I'm not payin' for that.
- I'll glue it.
- And?
(K SPITS)
One of the tail-end Nexus 8s.
He looks like he could
take your head off.
He tried.
He went AWOL after Calantha
with a few more in his outfit
I wouldn't mind closin' out.
- Just him?
- Just him.
Come on home
for your baseline.
K: One moment, madam.
(SNIFFING)
(DRONE HOVERING)
(SNAPS FINGERS)
K: 30 meters to maximum depth.
JOSHI: What is that?
I'll send a dig team.
Come on home before the storm.
(RADIO CHATTER
IN OTHER LANGUAGES)
MAN: Officer KD6-3.7.
- Let's begin. Ready?
- K: Yes, sir.
(ALARM BLARES)
MAN: Recite your baseline.
K: And blood-black
nothingness began to spin
A system of cells
interlinked within cells
interlinked within one stem.
Fuck off, skin-job.
K: And dreadfully distinct
Against the dark,
a tall white fountain played.
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
MAN: Cells.
K: Cells.
MAN: Have you ever been
in an institution?
- Cells.
- K: Cells.
MAN: Do they
keep you in a cell?
- Cells.
- K: Cells.
MAN: When you're not
performing your duties,
do they keep you
in a little box?
- Cells.
- K: Cells.
MAN: Interlinked.
K: Interlinked.
MAN: What's it like to hold
the hand of someone you love?
- Interlinked.
- K: Interlinked.
MAN: Did they teach you
how to feel finger to finger?
- Interlinked.
- K: Interlinked.
MAN: Do you long for having
your heart interlinked?
- Interlinked.
- K: Interlinked.
MAN: Do you dream
about being interlinked?
K: Interlinked.
MAN: What's it like to hold
your child in your arms?
- Interlinked.
- K: Interlinked.
MAN: Do you feel that there's
a part of you that's missing?
- Interlinked.
- K: Interlinked.
- MAN: Within cells interlinked.
- K: Within cells interlinked.
MAN: Why don't you
say that three times.
Within cells interlinked.
K: Within cells interlinked.
(RINGING STOPS)
MAN: We're done.
Constant "K."
You can pick up your bonus.
Thank you, sir.
AUTOMATED VOICE: (ON PA)
Caution, keep clear.
ANNOUNCER 1: (ON PA)
Connect to off-world
any time, any place.
Packages start at 20 minutes.
Many options available.
(ANNOUNCER 2 SPEAKING KOREAN)
ANNOUNCER 3: Joi goes anywhere
you want her to go.
ANNOUNCER 1: Connect to
off-world any time, any place.
(ANNOUNCEMENTS CONTINUE
INDISTINCTLY)
(HORN BLARES)
- (MAN SHOUTING)
- (WOMAN SPEAKING HUNGARIAN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BEEPS)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS
ON PA)
(SUMMER WIND PLAYING)
JOI: "K"? I didn't hear you.
You're early.
- K: You want me to come back?
- (JOI CHUCKLES)
JOI: (CHUCKLES) Just go scrub.
Yes, ma'am.
JOI: How was your meeting?
The usual.
- How was your day?
- (JOI SIGHS)
JOI: I'm getting cabin fever.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
99.9% detoxified water.
I had an accident at work.
I think I ruined my shirt.
JOI: I'm sure
I can fix that for you.
Let me take a look at it.
(SIGHS)
I need a drink.
Do you want a drink first?
JOI: Mmm-hmm.
Pour me one, will ya?
I'm trying a new recipe.
I just need
a bit more practice.
K: Don't fuss.
(SUMMER WIND
CONTINUES PLAYING)
JOI: I should have
marinated it longer.
(SIGHS) I hope it isn't dry.
Did you know
this song was released
in 1966 on Reprise Records?
It was number one
on the charts.
It won't be much longer.
Just putting on
the finishing touches.
Okay, it's ready.
I hope you're gonna like it.
I told you not to fuss.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
And yet...
Voilà! Bon appétit.
I missed you, baby sweet.
Honey, it's beautiful.
Just put your feet up.
Relax.
Was a day, hmm?
It was a day.
Would you read to me?
It'll make you feel better.
- You hate that book.
- I don't wanna read either.
Let's dance.
Do you wanna dance, or do you
wanna open your present?
What present?
This one.
What's the occasion?
Let's just say
- it's our anniversary.
- Is it?
No, but let's just
say that it is.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Okay?
Happy anniversary.
An emanator.
(BEEPS)
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
(JOI LAUGHING)
Thank you.
Honey, you can go anywhere
you want in the world now.
Where do you wanna go first?
(ANNOUNCER SPEAKING KOREAN)
(JOI CHUCKLES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
I'm so happy
when I'm with you.
You don't have to say that.
(DEVICE BEEPS)
JOSHI: The dig's come through.
We have a new lead.
Get down here.
- (BEEPS)
- (WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Carbon read: 14.6 GPH.
NANDEZ: Your box
is a military footlocker
issued to Sapper Morton,
creatively repurposed
as an ossuary:
a box of bones.
Nothin' else in it but hair.
The soil samples indicate that
she's been buried
for 30 years.
Bones all dismantled,
fully cleaned,
meticulously laid to rest.
"She"?
Cause of death, Coco?
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
No breaks,
no sign of trauma, except
a fracture
through the ilium.
It's a narrow birth canal.
Baby must have got stuck.
JOSHI: She was pregnant?
COCO: Hmm.
So he didn't kill her?
Mmm. She died in childbirth.
(DIAL CLICKING)
What's that?
Go back.
Closer.
What's that?
Huh.
Notching in the iliac crest.
It's fine-point,
like a scalpel.
That looks like
an emergency C-section.
The cuts are clean.
No sign of a struggle.
He was a combat medic.
Maybe he tried to save her
and he just couldn't.
He didn't seem like
the saving type.
He went to the trouble
of burying her.
A sentimental skin-job.
Sorry.
So where's the kid?
You scan the whole field?
NANDEZ: (SCOFFS)
Just dirt and worms.
No other bodies.
Maybe he ate it.
JOSHI: That's not possible.
She was a Replicant.
Pregnant.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
The world is built on a wall.
It separates kind.
Tell either side
there's no wall,
you bought a war.
Or a slaughter.
So, what you saw
didn't happen.
Yes, madam.
It is my job to keep order.
That's what we do here.
We keep order.
You want it gone?
Erase everything.
Even the child?
All trace.
You have anything more to say?
I've never retired something
that was born before.
What's the difference?
To be born is to have a soul,
I guess.
Are you telling me no?
I wasn't aware
that was an option, madam.
Attaboy.
Hey.
You've been getting on fine
without one.
What's that, madam?
A soul.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS
ON PA)
SAPPER: And you new models
are happy scraping the shit
because you've never seen
a miracle.
Just checking in
on an old serial number.
Confirmation DNA?
K: I got hair.
Oh! An old one.
Pre-Blackout. Huh.
That's gonna be tough.
Not much from then.
And what's there is
(CLICKS TONGUE)
thick milky.
LUV: You can customize them
as much as you'd like.
As human
as you want them to be.
But your operation is strictly
a drill site, isn't it?
I wouldn't waste your money
on intelligence,
attachment or appeal.
Unless you'd like to add some
pleasure models to your order.
(DEVICE CHIMING)
Would it be possible to
reschedule this call, please?
ARCHIVIST: Everyone remembers
where they were
at the Blackout. You?
K: That was a little
before my time.
Mmm. I was home with my folks,
then ten days of darkness.
Every machine stopped cold.
When the lights came back,
we were wiped clean.
Photos, files, every bit of
data... Ffft! Gone.
Bank records, too. (CHUCKLES)
Didn't mind that.
It's funny it's only paper
that lasted.
I mean, we had
everything on drives.
Everything, everything,
everything! Huh.
My mom still cries
over the lost baby pictures.
Well, it's a shame. You
- must have been adorable.
- Hmm... Ah.
Uh... (CLICKS TONGUE)
Pretty fractured.
Not much on it.
One of the last gens,
pre-Prohibition.
Standard issue.
Made by Tyrell.
And?
Unremarkable.
K: "Unremarkable"?
LUV: There must be something
else we can find for him.
Another prodigal
serial number returns.
A 30-year-old open case
finally closed.
Thank you, officer.
I'm here for Mr. Wallace.
I'm Luv.
He named you.
Must be special.
I'm here for Mr. Wallace.
Follow me.
The ancient models give the
entire endeavor a bad name.
What a gift, don't you think,
from Mr. Wallace to the world?
The outer colonies
would never have flourished
had he not bought Tyrell,
revivified the technology.
To say the least
of what we do.
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
I see you're also a customer.
Are you satisfied
with our product?
She's very realistic.
Thank you.
Here. All the junk is in here.
Lucky for you,
Mr. Wallace is a data hoarder.
(WHIRRING)
No one's been
down here in ages.
(DOOR CREAKS LOUDLY)
Sorry about that.
All our memory bearings
from the time.
They were all damaged
in the Blackout.
But there are
sometimes fragments.
YOUNG DECKARD:
You got a little boy.
He shows you
his butterfly collection,
plus the killing jar.
RACHAEL: I'd take him
to the doctor.
(DISTORTED)
YOUNG DECKARD: There's a wasp
crawling on your arm.
RACHAEL: I'd kill it.
YOUNG DECKARD:
You're reading a magazine.
You come across a full-page
nude photo of a girl.
RACHAEL: Is this testing
whether I'm a Replicant
or a lesbian, Mr. Deckard?
YOUNG DECKARD: Just answer
the questions, please.
(VIDEO ENDS)
It was unclear what she was,
at least to someone.
This was a test.
We were difficult
to spot then.
Was there anything unusual
about how you found her?
To warrant an official
investigation?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
You know how people are
about old serial numbers.
Everyone just sleeps better
when they know
where they got to.
She likes him.
Who?
This Officer Deckard.
She's trying to provoke him.
It is invigorating being asked
personal questions.
Makes one feel
desired.
Do you enjoy
your work, officer?
Please thank Mr. Wallace
for your time.
(LOCK CLICKS)
K: You worked
with Officer Deckard
back in the day.
What can you tell me
about him?
He liked to work alone.
So did I.
So we worked together
to keep it that way.
That was it.
Anything else
you can tell me?
He wasn't long for this world.
How so?
Something in his eyes.
Any idea how I could
contact him?
None.
He's nyugdíjas.
Retired.
What happened?
Probably got what he wanted.
To be alone.
Welcome back, sir.
You wanted to review
the new model, sir,
before shipment?
WALLACE: An angel
should never enter
the kingdom of heaven
without a gift.
Can you at least pronounce,
"A child is born"?
Hmm.
(SIGHS)
A new model.
Well, let us see her, then.
(GASPING)
(SOBBING)
The first thought
one tends to fear,
to preserve the clay.
It's fascinating.
Before we even know
what we are,
we fear to lose it.
Happy birthday.
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(WALLACE SHUSHING)
Now, let's have a look at you.
We make angels
in the service
of civilization.
Yes, there were
bad angels once.
I make good angels now.
That is how I took us
to nine new worlds.
Nine.
A child can count to nine
on fingers.
We should own the stars.
Yes, sir.
(WALLACE SIGHS)
WALLACE: Every leap
of civilization
was built off the back
of a disposable workforce.
We lost our stomach
for slaves
unless engineered.
But I can only make so many.
That barren pasture,
empty
and salted...
(REPLICANT SHUDDERS)
...right here.
The dead space
between the stars.
And this, the seat that
we must change for heaven.
- (STABBING)
- (GAGGING)
I cannot breed them.
So help me, I have tried.
We need more Replicants
than can ever be assembled.
Millions, so we can be
trillions more.
We could storm Eden
and retake her.
Tyrell's final trick:
Procreation.
Perfected, then lost.
But there is a child.
Bring it to me.
Sir.
The best angel of all.
Aren't you, Luv?
- (ENGINES REVVING)
- (INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS
CONTINUE)
(WOMEN MOANING)
The man with the green jacket.
The one who killed Sapper.
Find out what he knows.
(WOMEN MOANING)
Hi.
Hello, hello, A-Boy.
You alone?
(SPEAKING FINNISH)
(IN ENGLISH) It's okay.
It's fine.
Wanna buy a lady a cigarette?
Oh, you don't even smile.
Didn't you hear your friends?
Don't you know what I am?
Yeah.
Guy eating rice.
What's that?
It's a tree.
Oh. Never seen a tree before.
It's pretty.
It's dead.
Now, who keeps a dead tree?
Hmm?
You're not gonna kill me,
are you?
Depends.
What's your model number?
Why don't you look under
my eye and find out.
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
Oh!
You don't like real girls.
Well, I'm always here.
(TAPPING)
(NOTES PLAYING)
(TAPS)
(CLICKS)
Hi.
You can't take those.
Of course not. Proper channels
and paperwork. It's all here.
Hold this for me.
- Mmm. Yep. Here you go.
- Mmm.
(GASPS)
(GAGGING)
JOSHI: Coco is dead.
Bones are gone.
It's out. Already out.
How long'd that take?
So, what do you have for me?
And don't say nothing.
I found that.
A sock?
(SIGHS)
- Where'd you find it?
- Sapper's.
Anything else?
I burned everything else.
Then what's this?
What's that date?
Is that a birthday?
Is that a death day?
I don't know yet.
Am I the only one that can see
the fuckin' sunrise here?
This breaks the world, "K."
- (JOSHI SIGHING)
- (LIQUID POURING)
(SIGHS)
You know,
I've known a lot of your kind.
All useful, but with you,
I sometimes forget.
We didn't have any of you
where I was a kid.
Do you remember anything?
Before you were under me,
you have any memories
from before?
I have memories,
but they're not real.
They're just implants.
Tell me one.
From when you were a kid.
I feel a little strange
sharing a childhood story,
considering
I was never a child.
Well, would it help you share
if I told you it was an order?
I have one
about a toy that I had.
A wooden horse.
With an inscription
underneath.
All I remember
is a group of boys
trying to take it away
from me.
So I run.
I go looking for a place
to hide it,
and the only place
is this dark furnace.
It's very dark
and I'm very scared,
but this horse is all I have,
so I go in anyway.
(PANTING)
Later on, those kids find me,
and they beat me to tell 'em
where it is, but I don't.
And that's it.
JOSHI: Hmm.
Little "K,"
fighting for what's his.
It's a good one.
Look at me.
We're all just lookin' out
for somethin' real.
What happens if I finish that?
Shouldn't I get back
to work, madam?
(CHUCKLES)
Check back in after DNAbase.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
K: Officer KD6-3.7.
(AUTOMATED VOICE
SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Request.
DNA records:
children born 6-10-21.
Looking for anomalies.
(AUTOMATED VOICE
SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(SIGHS)
You have
the satcrystal backup?
(AUTOMATED VOICE
SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Okay.
- Run it raw.
- (AUTOMATED VOICE RESPONDS)
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
Mere data makes a man.
A and C and T and G.
The alphabet of you.
All from four symbols.
I'm only two:
1 and 0.
Half as much but twice
as elegant, sweetheart.
You don't prefer your madam?
Mmm.
You were listening.
Maybe.
You didn't like her enough
to tell her the truth.
6, 10 and 21.
There's nothin' to tell.
How many times
have you told me that story?
Your memory?
The date carved beneath.
6, 10 and 21.
Coincidence?
A dangerous coincidence.
I always knew
you were special.
Maybe this is how.
A child.
Of woman born.
Pushed into the world.
Wanted.
Loved.
Well, if it were true,
I'd be hunted
for the rest of my life
by someone just like me.
It's okay to dream a little.
Isn't it?
Not if you're us.
- Stop.
- (AUTOMATED VOICE RESPONDS)
K: Put up 4847
and 2181, side-by-side.
(AUTOMATED VOICE RESPONDS)
They're identical. Translate.
A boy and a girl.
It's impossible.
JOI: Why?
K: Two people
can't have identical DNA.
One of these isn't real.
It's a copy.
They were both processed
at the Morrill Cole Orphanage.
It says the girl died there.
Genetic disorder.
Galatians Syndrome.
And the boy...
(SLIDE CLICKS)
...disappears.
Where's the orphanage?
You wanna go for a ride?
K: Well, here we are.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(LOUD RUMBLING)
Buckle up.
(ALARM BLARING)
(HARPOON CLANGS)
"K"?
(CRASHES)
(DISTORTED WALLACE JINGLE
PLAYS)
"K"? "K"?
(DISTORTED)
"K"? "K"? "K"? "K"? "K"?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(WHIRRING)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
- (BONE CRACKING)
- (MAN SCREAMING)
K: Stay back.
(MAN SHOUTING ORDERS
IN OTHER LANGUAGE)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(MEN SCREAMING)
LUV: Fire again.
Fire again.
Fire.
(MEN SCREAMING)
200 feet to the east.
Fire.
Go north.
Stop. 20 degrees east.
Stop.
Zoom in.
Closer.
Oh, come on.
Get up.
Do your fucking job.
Find the child.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(AIRLOCK ENGAGES)
(DOOR LOCKS)
K: Watch the car.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(CHILD COUGHS)
(CHILD COUGHING)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
MR. COTTON: Every last piece,
or I'll put you outside
where the sky is raining,
where it's raining fire!
You're in here to work.
And if you're not working,
I don't need you.
I don't need any of...
Hi.
(CHILDREN COUGHING)
MR. COTTON: The nickel
is for the colonial ships.
Closest any of them
or any of us is gonna get
to that grand life
off-world.
And I encourage play, I do.
Keeps 'em occupied and it
makes 'em nimble, right?
(MR. COTTON CHUCKLES)
But it's work.
It's work that molds them
into a child worth havin'.
(CHILD COUGHS)
So come on, now.
What sort do you have in mind?
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
'Cause I got all kinds.
(UNFURLS BADGE)
- Oh, no, no, no.
- I'm not buyin'.
No, no, no.
This is just my game,
and I play it fair.
No. No, I mean,
bigger than you...
Bigger than you
have tried to shut me down.
Bigger than you.
And they were men, at that.
A little boy came through here
about 30 years back.
- I need to see your records.
- Hmm.
Legitimate placements,
private sales, everything.
Don't keep records
that far back.
- You don't?
- I don't.
Sorry. (CHUCKLES)
Can't help you.
- (EXHALES) You can't?
- Nope.
(GUN COCKS)
I think you can.
(GRUNTS)
I think someone like you
keeps a long memory.
Now you can tell me
what you remember,
or I can put a hole right here
and take a look.
(MR. COTTON MUTTERING)
They were laughin'
and what was it you said?
What did you say?
(STAIRS CREAKING)
Are you comin'?
Where is it?
Oh, God.
Where, where, where, where?
I don't see it. Here.
It's gone.
(STAMMERS)
It's the entire year.
I didn't do that.
That wasn't me.
I didn't. Wasn't me.
(K SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES IN DISTANCE)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
JOI: I always told you.
You're special.
Born.
Not made.
Hidden with care.
A real boy now.
A real boy needs a real name.
Joe.
"Joe"?
You're too important for "K."
Your mother
would've named you.
Joe.
(SIGHS)
- Joe.
- Stop.
How do I know if a memory
is an implant or not?
Who makes the memories?
(INSECT BUZZING)
(CLICKING)
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
Dr. Ana Stelline?
(HOLOGRAM PINGS)
A visitor.
K: Is that okay?
ANA: Yes.
It's just unusual.
Nice to meet you,
Officer KD6-3.7.
Sorry. It's a compromised
immune system.
A life of freedom,
so long as it's behind glass.
Is that why
you're not off-world?
Yes.
My parents had our passes
in pocket, but I took sick.
So it was a new life for me.
And they put me in my cage,
filled it with everything
they could to keep me happy.
Except company, of course.
And I was used to crowds.
What can I help you with?
Thought you might be able
to help me with a case.
Oh, that's the most
interesting thing
I've been offered
to help with in ages.
Do you mind if I work
while you talk?
Of course.
ANA: I promise
I hear every word.
They say you're the best
memory-maker there is.
Well, then, they're kind.
I love birthday parties.
K: You work for Wallace.
ANA: Subcontract.
I'm one of his suppliers.
He offered to buy me out,
but I take my freedom
where I can find it.
(CHILDREN GIGGLING)
Why are you so good?
What makes your memories
so authentic?
ANA: Well, there's a bit of
every artist in their work.
But I was locked
in a sterile chamber at 8,
so if I wanted to see
the world,
I had to imagine it.
Got very good at imagining.
Wallace needs my talent
to maintain a stable product.
I think it's only kind.
Replicants live
such hard lives,
made to do
what we'd rather not.
I can't help your future,
but I can give you
good memories
to think back on and smile.
It's nice.
It's better than nice.
It feels authentic.
And if you have
authentic memories,
you have real human responses.
Wouldn't you agree?
(BOTH INHALE)
(BLOWING)
Are they all constructed
or do you ever use
ones that are real?
ANA: It's illegal to use
real memories, officer.
How can you tell
the difference?
Can you tell if something
really happened?
They all think
it's about more detail.
But that's not how
memory works.
We recall with our feelings.
Anything real
should be a mess.
I can show you.
Sit.
Now, think about the memory
you want me to see.
Not even that hard.
Just picture it.
Let it play.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Someone lived this, yes.
This happened.
I know it's real.
(SNIFFLING)
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
God damn it!
(CHAIR CLATTERING)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
OFFICER: (ON LOUDSPEAKER)
Officer KD6-3.7.
Madam is calling you in.
You're under arrest.
Drop your gun
and keep your hands
where I can see 'em.
MAN: Cells.
K: Cells.
MAN: Have you ever
been in an institution?
- Cells.
MAN: When you're not
performing your duties,
do they keep you
in a little box?
- Cells.
MAN: Interlinked.
K: Interlinked.
MAN: What's it like
to hold the hand
of someone you love?
Interlinked.
MAN:
Within cells interlinked.
K: Within cells interlinked.
MAN: Dreadfully.
K: Dreadfully.
MAN: What's it like to
be filled with dread?
- Dreadfully.
- K: Dreadfully.
MAN: Do you like being
separated from other people?
- Distinct.
- Dreadfully distinct.
- Dark.
MAN:
Within cells interlinked.
K: Within the cells
interlinked.
MAN: Within one stem.
K: Within one stem.
MAN:
And dreadfully distinct.
K: And dreadfully distinct.
MAN: Against the dark.
K: Against the dark.
MAN: A tall white
fountain played.
K: A tall white
MAN: You're not even
close to baseline.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Out! Close the door.
What the fuck is with you?
I put you on a case.
I impressed on you
the importance of that case,
and then we pick you up
fucking around
outside an upgrade center?
Scan said you didn't look like
you on the inside.
Miles off your baseline.
Do you know what that means?
I found the kid.
He was set up
like a standard Replicant,
put on a service job.
Even he didn't know
who he was.
- And?
- And it's done.
What does that mean,
"it's done"?
What you asked.
It's done.
(SIGHS) Fuck.
You just stopped a bomb
from goin' off.
You did good.
I can help you
get outta this station alive,
but you have 48 hours
to get back on track.
Surrender your gun and badge.
And your next baseline test
is outta my hands.
Thank you, madam.
K: You were right.
You were right
about everything.
Shh.
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hmm.
Thought you weren't
interested, worky man.
You liked her. I could tell.
It's okay.
She's real.
I wanna be real for you.
You are real for me.
You have a special lady here.
MARIETTE: Okay.
Let's do it.
MARIETTE: Look at you.
JOI: Quiet now,
I have to sync.
(GASPS)
FEMALE ANNOUNCER: Joi is
anything you want her to be.
Joi goes anywhere
you want her to go.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(DOOR SLAMS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
99.9% detoxified water.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS QUIETLY)
(WHISPERS) It's from a tree.
JOI: I'm done with you.
You can go now.
Quiet, now.
I've been inside you.
Not so much there
as you think.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Coffee?
(CHUCKLES)
They'll be comin'
after me soon.
I'm coming with you.
But not like this.
If they come here
looking for you,
they'll have access
to all my memories.
You have to delete me
from the console.
My present.
Put me there.
I can't do that.
Think about it.
If anything happens to this,
that's it.
You're gone.
Yes.
Like a real girl.
Please.
Joe, please.
I want this.
But I can't do it myself.
(SIGHS)
Break the antenna.
(BEEPS)
(DOC BADGER SPEAKING
OTHER LANGUAGE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I don't need a real horse.
I just...
I just wanna find out
where it's from.
DOC BADGER: (IN ENGLISH) Okay.
(SNIFFS)
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
- (TYPING)
- Radiation from a reactor?
It matches a dirty bomb.
K: There's only one place
that dirty.
Mmm-hmm.
Nobody lives there.
(DOC BADGER
SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
- K: Go to five.
- (CAMERA CLICKING)
Four, 30 degrees to the left.
Tilt up.
Elevate to 400 feet.
Radiation analysis.
Move forward.
Tilt up.
Stop.
Move forward.
Go to five.
Seven, move forward.
Six.
Stop.
Go to seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Heat analysis.
Life.
JOI: What is it?
Guess we're about to find out.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
Too dark in here.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I like him.
He's a good boy.
Where is he?
(SIGHS)
I have no idea. He's off-duty.
Check around.
I checked
anywhere a good boy
might go.
JOSHI: You're too late.
It's gone.
He destroyed it.
Everything about it.
Well, except
for the box of bones
that you already took.
Which, I'll wager,
wasn't enough. Here you are.
(GASPS)
You tiny thing.
In the face
of the fabulous new,
your only thought
is to kill it?
- (JOSHI GROANS)
- For fear of great change?
You can't hold the tide
with a broom.
Except that I did.
(SHOUTS) Where is he?
(GASPS)
You're so sure.
Because he told you.
Because we never lie.
I'm gonna tell Mr. Wallace
you tried to shoot me first.
So I had to kill you.
Then do what you gotta do.
Madam.
(GASPS)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SIGHS)
Location: Officer KD6-3.7.
(BEES BUZZING)
(BUZZING STOPS)
(HINGES CREAK)
(BALL RATTLING)
(BALL CLATTERS)
(PIANO PLAYING)
(PLAYS NOTE)
DECKARD:
"Mightn't happen to have
"a piece of cheese
about you, now?"
Would you, boy?
Treasure Island?
He reads.
That's good.
Me, too.
Not much else to do
around here at night anymore.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
"Many is the night
I dream of cheese,
"toasted, mostly."
What are you doing here?
I heard the piano.
Don't lie.
It's rude.
You're a cop.
- I'm not here to take you in.
- Oh, yeah?
Then, what?
I just have some questions.
What questions?
(CRASHING)
(SIGHS)
Stay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BEEPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
(MUSIC PLAYS AND STOPS)
(MACHINE POWERING DOWN)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (MUSIC STOPS)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS AND STOPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
K: Look,
I don't wanna hurt you.
But you're not makin' it easy.
(MUSIC PLAYS AND STOPS)
(GRUNTING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
ELVIS:
♪ Like a river flows
♪ Surely to the sea
♪ Darling, so it goes
♪ Some things are meant to be
I like this song.
♪ Take my hand
♪ Take my whole life, too
We could keep at this,
or we could get a drink.
♪ For I can't help
♪ Falling in love with you ♪
I'll take the drink.
K: This is really somethin'.
DECKARD: The whole town
was somethin'.
One time.
Forget your troubles,
see a show,
gamble a little.
Win some money,
lose some money.
They made money
seem like candy.
You like whiskey?
I've got millions
of bottles of whiskey.
Here.
Bleeding.
Is it real?
I don't know.
Ask him.
Ya got a name?
Officer KD6-3.7.
That's not a name.
That's a serial number.
All right.
Joe.
What do you want, Joe?
I wanna ask you
some questions.
Like what?
Like what was her name,
the mother of your child?
What was she like?
- You two live here together?
- Too many questions.
I had your job.
I was good at it.
It was simpler then.
Why you makin' it complicated?
Why don't you just
answer the question.
What question?
I didn't figure you
as one for bullshit.
What's her name?
Rachael.
Her name was Rachael.
What happened to the kid?
(SIGHS)
Who put it in the orphanage?
Was it you?
I was long gone by then.
You didn't even meet
your own kid?
Why?
Because that was the plan.
I showed 'em
how to scramble the records,
cover their tracks.
Everyone had a part.
Mine was to leave.
Then the Blackout came,
paved over everything.
Couldn't have found the child
if I tried.
- Did you want to?
- Not really.
- Why not?
- Because we were being hunted.
I didn't want
our child found,
taken apart, dissected.
Sometimes, to love someone,
you gotta be a stranger.
To strangers.
(COIN CLINKS)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ It's quarter to three
♪ There's no one in the place
♪ Except you and me
♪ So, set 'em up, Joe
♪ I got a little story
♪ You ought to know
♪ We're drinkin', my friend
♪ To the end
♪ Of a brief episode
♪ Make it one for my baby
♪ And one more for the road ♪
(DOG PANTING)
(WHIMPERS)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
DECKARD: What'd you do?
Who'd you bring? Huh?
K: No one.
Oh, yeah?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Target locked.
They know you're here.
I came alone.
(RUMBLING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Bad dog.
(GRUNTS)
Stop.
I do hope you're satisfied
with our product.
- I love yo...
- (SHATTERS)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(BEEPING INTENSIFIES)
(BEEPING STOPS)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
MARIETTE: Hey, there's someone
who wants to meet you.
You can trust us.
You must want me to look up
and to the left.
MARIETTE: This is Freysa.
She fought with Sapper
on Calantha.
K: I recognize you.
Did you help him
hide the child?
Oh.
I was there.
I saw a miracle delivered.
A perfect little face
crying up at me.
Mad as thunder.
Were you with her?
Rachael?
FREYSA: I held her
as she died.
We hid the child and made
a vow to keep our secret.
That's why Sapper
let you kill him.
I knew that baby meant
we are more than just slaves.
If a baby can come
from one of us,
we are our own masters.
More human than humans.
FREYSA:
A revolution is coming.
And we're building an army.
I want to free our people.
If you want to be free,
join us.
Deckard, Sapper, you, me,
our lives mean nothing
next to a storm that's coming.
Dying for the right cause
is the most human thing
we can do.
You led Wallace to Deckard.
You cannot allow Deckard
to lead Wallace to me.
You must kill Deckard.
Deckard only wanted
his baby to be safe.
And she is.
When the time comes,
I will show her
to the world,
and she will lead our army.
"She"?
Of course.
Rachael had a daughter.
With my own eyes,
I saw her come.
I dressed her in blue
when it was time
for her to go.
It was a boy that you hid.
That is just a piece
of the puzzle.
You imagined it was you?
Oh.
You did.
We all wish it was us.
That's why we believe.
ANA:
Someone lived this, yes.
DECKARD: I showed 'em
how to scramble the records,
cover their tracks.
FREYSA: With my own eyes,
I saw her come.
I dressed her in blue when
it was time for her to go.
ANA: There's a bit
of every artist in their work.
(GROANING)
(EXHALES)
WALLACE: Always jumping,
that one.
Never a thought of what to do
if it made land.
All the courage in the world
cannot alter fact.
I have wanted to meet you
for so very long.
You are a wonder to me,
Mr. Deckard.
I had the lock.
I found the key.
Yet the pins do not align.
The door remains locked.
I need the specimen
to reach it, Mr. Deckard.
The child.
I need the child.
To teach them all to fly.
"And God remembered Rachel,
"heeded her
and opened her womb."
RACHAEL:
Do you like our owl?
DECKARD: It's artificial?
RACHAEL: Of course it is.
DECKARD: Must be expensive.
RACHAEL: Very. I'm Rachael.
DECKARD: Deckard.
WALLACE: Is it the same
now, as then,
the moment you met her?
All these years
you looked back on that day,
drunk on the memory
of its perfection.
How shiny her lips.
How instant your connection.
Did it never occur to you
that's why you were summoned
in the first place?
Designed to do nothing short
of fall for her
right then and there.
All to make
that single perfect specimen.
That is, if you were designed.
Love
or mathematical precision.
Yes.
No.
(SIGHS)
I know what's real.
(SIGHING HEAVILY)
It was very clever
to keep yourself
empty of information,
and all it cost you
was everything.
But you can still help me.
You had help in the hiding.
Where did they go?
I know you know something.
Help me,
and very, very good things
can come to you.
You don't have children,
do you?
Oh, I have millions.
You think I have
nothing to offer but pain.
Only I know
you love pain.
Pain reminds you
the joy you felt was real.
More joy, then.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Do not be afraid.
An angel
made again.
For you.
RACHAEL:
Did you miss me?
Don't you love me?
Her eyes were green.
WALLACE: Off-world,
I have everything I need
to make you talk.
You do not know
what pain is yet.
You will learn.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WALLACE JINGLE PLAYS)
JOI: Hello, handsome.
What a day, hmm?
You look lonely.
I can fix that.
You look like a good Joe.
FREYSA:
Dying for the right cause
is the most human thing
we can do.
Because you've never seen
a miracle.
AIR-TRAFFIC CONTROLLER:
You're entering
Los Angeles Airport
restricted airspace.
Confirm your identity.
PILOT: Transport S-14-4-XD.
Confirmed.
PILOT 2: Base, this is
06 outbound departure...
Where are we going?
Home.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Drive two down.
Backup engaged.
Warning.
LUV: Can we make it?
PILOT: We're too low.
Take us back.
Get us up.
LUV: Open the door.
(GUNSHOT)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(LUV GRUNTS)
I'm the best one.
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
Off-world is waiting.
(CHOKING)
(GROANS)
(YELLING)
(GROWLING)
Joe. Joe!
Joe!
You shoulda let me
die out there.
K: You did.
You drowned out there.
You're free to meet
your daughter now.
All the best memories
are hers.
Why?
Who am I to you?
Go meet your daughter.
You okay?
Just a moment.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Subtitles by explosiveskull