SHOWBOX presents
a GENERATION BLUE FILMS production
executive producer YOU Jeong-Hun
produced by KIM JHO Gwang-soo, LEE Sun-mi
In 1789,
a blood-sucking monster appeared
and wreaked havoc on the country.
This is an account of that monster.
It sucked human blood and could fly.
It was mighty strong and
healed instantly upon injury.
CLASSIFIED
The only way to kill such a monster
was to burn it.
Life by blood. Death by fire.
Blood gave it life.
Fire killed it.
Over there!
Find him at once!
Scour the hills!
- Over there!
- Get him!
That way!
Get him!
Hunt him down!
Find him before the dawn.
Where is it?
Who
am I?
Search everywhere!
Find him before daybreak!
Hurry!
Do you know me?
Find him! Hurry!
What is this?
Who are you and who am I?
Over there!
Shoot her!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
DETECTIVE K: SECRET OF THE LIVING DEAD
What are you looking for?
What's here for us to do this, sir?
There's a vampire here.
Vampire? What's that?
A blood-sucking monster!
Bloodless bodies were found
in villages this circus visited.
There must be a vampire here.
That makes no sense!
I heard the magic you do is quite famous.
Well,
let's see what you've got.
Yes, sir! I'm sure you'll be pleased.
WOL-GYO GARDEN
THE FANTASTIC DUO
Real swords?
Yes! He puts a man in
a box and stabs it!
That's crazy.
The box is too small.
There'll be room to avoid the swords.
Don't worry.
There's no room to avoid them!
Magic is just trickery. Trust me.
But I can't trust you!
Help me! Help!
It's too tight in here!
Mommy!
Sir!
Please let me out!
There's no room to hide!
Take it out, jerk!
Oh my!
It's blood!
Is he dead?
Are you all right?
I avoided them all.
Blood...
He's bleeding!
I said the box was too
small, you son of a...
Seo-pil!
Help! My daughter is missing!
Eon-nyeon!
Please find my daughter!
Where are you mommy?
Mommy! Where are you?
Mommy!
You evil vampire!
You killed innocent lives to save yours!
How dare you!
My hunch was right.
Your curiosity will be the death of you!
This time, I'll strike your head!
Stop!
Father.
Let's stop now.
No, son!
Not a vampire, but a porphyrya patient?
With low oxygen in the blood,
you get heart palpitations,
shortness of breath, and heart enlargement.
You killed innocent lives
to fill your lack of blood!
My son is innocent. It's all my fault.
Though you did it to save your son,
your sins are no different
from those of vampires.
Do you expect to live after what you did?
HONG TAE-MUN
What vampires?
Are you going through puberty again?
Having strange thoughts?
Vampires exist.
It's because you're not busy.
You lost your post.
The women you come on to, dump you.
Do something!
Such a pity that you think
the world is so puny.
In 1742, a report was made
about Scholar Choi and his servant.
The servant saw a mysterious light.
Then Choi vanished without a trace.
And the peculiar plague years ago...
The world is full of
unbelievable incidents.
Who's to say vampires don't exist?
Do you have proof?
30 years ago,
a Westerners' ship headed for
China ran aground in Joseon.
There are records of
vampire sightings then.
Come on, sir.
Cut the nonsense and do
your detective work.
Aren't you paying me rent?
Stop roaming and go back
to your nice house.
Then I'll have to get married!
If you must, why not?
I don't wish to marry without love.
Then tell your father that.
- He decided who I'll marry.
- So what?
You're good at speaking your mind.
Can't you talk to your father?
It's your life, sir!
Just say no!
Say you're not marrying a
stranger without love.
I did!
I told him it's my life and
he can't decide for me.
And?
I got slapped.
He's firm.
I thought the Premier would be different.
Your Majesty!
PREMIER KIM SHIN
Anticipation for the Full Moon Fest
is high throughout Joseon.
People of all ages are working hard
to prepare a greater fest than
the one 30 years ago, sir.
Recently, 10,000 people worked
on fortifying our forts.
It must be hard for them to work
for the Full Moon Fest too.
Thus, I shall grant a small reward
to the workers.
Set rice as the only tributary.
And have aristocrats pay
for the military cloth as well.
I, Premier Kim Shin, request
to speak, Your Majesty.
His Majesty's mercy and heart
for the people is like heaven.
However,
if aristocrats pay the same as peasants,
what makes them different, sir?
It'll destroy class distinction
and shake the basis of Joseon, sir.
Please, Your Majesty!
Please retract your command, sir!
Even the king can't have his way with him.
Any functional problems in getting married?
Why you little!
Excuse me.
Who?
It's scorched rice tea.
Thank you.
It has a rich, deep flavor.
I did a great job making it.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the daughter of the
owner of Yeon-mi Lodge.
How could we be of help?
Recently, while repairing
building in Ganghwa,
the roof suddenly caved
in and many workers died.
While burying the dead,
two corpses were discovered.
One was a skeleton and
the other was burned.
However, the burnt one
wasn't decayed at all.
But that's not all!
While they went to report it,
The corpse disappeared!
Only the burnt corpse vanished!
Then another incident happened soon after.
It was quite peculiar.
Some say a man burned
to death by an invisible fire.
He died but was not dead.
He lived but did not live!
Some say it's the revenge of those
who died in the Ganghwa Hall fire.
The Full Moon Fest is taking
place after 30 years.
My father has been ordered
by the court to prepare it.
However, he is ill and can't
see to such problems.
I've come to ask you to
solve the mysteries for us.
It won't be easy.
Serial killings can't be ruled out.
I heard you are the best
in all of Joseon, sir.
I'm not the best.
I'm the best of the best!
It's sad that I can only
explain myself that way.
He's a little arrogant.
I see.
Let's talk accommodations.
Will it have two rooms
or one with living room?
One with living room, sir.
Inside bathroom or outside?
Inside, sir.
And breakfast?
Provided, sir.
Deal! Let's go.
GANGHWA ISLAND
3 DAYS AFTER
HONG TAE-MUN'S DEATH
You haven't found it yet?
I know who has it, sir.
Please give me a few more days.
GANGHWA HALL
Do you know me?
Who are you?
The guest door is that way.
The owner's daughter asked me to come.
I'm a detective.
It's about the mysterious deaths here.
Your sister asked us to
come and investigate.
I don't know why she did that.
I don't know of such things.
I'm Kim Min.
He's a very famous detective, sir.
He solved the fake silver case and
even had dinner with the king.
I don't think he knows.
What if I explain it like this?
He got drunk before His Majesty and said,
'This isn't your country, pal!'
After the rude fiasco,
he was sent into exile.
That's him.
He's Premier Kim Shin's...
I'm Choi Jae-kyung. Please come inside.
- Your fame has reached even Ganghwa Island!
- Why you!
YEON-MI LODGE
SONG PIL-GEUN
Sir? Did you poo in bed?
Or is it horse dung?
What is this, a barn?
It's not what she promised.
The bathroom is so far! I
almost peed on the way!
It's the busy season.
It's perfect for a rude fool.
And what's with this breakfast?
Shouldn't they give us fried eggs at least?
This is why you don't make
deals with a middleman.
I'm taking a few towels when I leave.
Sir?
My sister asked you to come
without discussing with me.
CHOI IL-KYU
OWNER OF YEON-MI LODGE
What happened to your father?
He's been like this for a month.
Even the best doctors don't
know what is wrong with him.
A book on exorcism?
The magistrate is busy with the fest
and has no plans to investigate.
When two men burned to
death by a peculiar fire...
Two?
When did this happen?
A man died by the same fire last night.
What is the Full Moon Fest that
the magistrate can't investigate?
In the past, royal officials
would all gather to celebrate.
His Majesty will be coming this time.
The magistrate must want
to keep things quiet.
Please catch the killer
before the Full Moon Fest.
Just by me being here, the
killer is practically caught.
Pardon?
I'm called a detective and a shaman too.
For I can find a killer just
by looking at the corpse,
I'm like a possessed shaman who knows all.
Shall we begin?
Is he usually like that?
Worse, sir. He must not be feeling well.
Less bragging than usual.
POLICE SEEK DETAILS ON THIS MAN
- You know Sir Song Pil-geun?
- Yes.
He was burned by the ghost fire!
There's no such thing as a ghost fire!
- His servant saw everything!
- What?
The body burned, but he saw no fire!
No way!
Sir!
Are you all right?
You must've gone weak, sir.
I thought you'd fly all the way back home.
Don't exaggerate.
- The footstep is...
- It's mine.
Right.
I knew that.
Don't tamper with the crime scene!
The burn mark looks like a man!
Do you know what's the most painful death?
Burning to death.
But the way he died shows no
sign of squirming in pain.
It means that he couldn't
move before he was burned.
- An invisible fire...
- And...
I know the killer always
returns to the crime scene.
Sir?
See the bamboo hat behind you?
He keeps looking this way.
Bamboo hat!
You'll just hit me and go?
How rude.
Rude?
Me?
You hit me and didn't say sorry.
Still, how dare you try
to touch my clothes?
How dare I?
How dare you!
Wait!
Mind your language!
Where are your manners?
Stay out, servant.
Servant?
Hear that, sir? She called me a servant!
Sir! Be careful!
Are you all right, sir?
I'll get you!
Do you know me?
The monk?
The Buddhist monk on the poster?
Did anyone come for his body?
You're the first to come for him.
So, all you know is that
he's a Buddhist monk?
Why do you ask that?
Very well then.
Wait! Show me your identity tag!
Who are you, sir?
Didn't Sir Choi Jae-kyung mention us?
You're the detective from the capital?
Yes.
There's no case I can't solve.
- I'm the best detective in...
- Excuse me, sir.
Where did she go?
I wish to see Song Pil-geun's corpse.
That's impossible, sir.
The magistrate gave orders
never to show it to anyone.
Of course not! If the magistrate said so.
On second thought, maybe
he didn't say never.
There is no such thing as never.
- You could sneak a peek at night.
- Good.
- I'll come back at night.
- Yes, sir.
What did you draw, sir?
Isn't she the woman from before?
That lady...
Did you notice?
Well,
she was a bit odd and very strong.
She's gorgeous.
Not again.
Why draw a pretty woman
at a time like this?
I need it to investigate.
Investigate what?
If you want to meet her, just say it.
She's there wherever we go!
That means she's connected
to this case somehow.
- Then...
- Maybe...
She could be chasing us.
Us? Why, sir?
Sir! It's me!
You must find out who she is
and why she's after this case.
Yes, sir.
This rough chap looks suspicious.
It's a woman.
And she's pretty.
Are you going blind in your old age?
Forget it.
I'll find her. You can go back home.
No, sir!
I'll find this fool! I mean this woman!
Look.
There is soot in his nose.
He was burned when he was alive.
It appears we're here for the same purpose.
Would you like to take a look?
Or shall we fight and bring in the guards?
An invisible fire...
It seems he was fatally
wounded before burning.
Then the scar must be somewhere.
While burying the dead,
two corpses were discovered.
The burnt one wasn't decayed at all.
Only the burnt corpse vanished!
Is it a real vampire?
The arrow precisely struck the heart.
He didn't just want the
blood, but to kill him.
'Yeom' means to stain.
Why did the killer leave a sign?
Perhaps a forewarned murder?
This letter has something
to do with staining or dyes.
Go to the painting plant and
meet the painters for clues.
I'll search the dye house here.
HA BYUNG-EUN
Why are you here?
How long will you follow me?
I saw someone on fire too.
Where?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure where, who,
or why I remember that.
He must've been killed by something
that looks human but is not.
Something that looks human but is not?
Are they really strong and fast?
And heal fast if they're hurt?
You know about vampires?
Vampires?
Vampires are immortal.
They don't get hurt or die.
Immortal?
I have a question.
You're definitely in my memory.
Who am I?
In becoming a monster,
your memory was lost.
If you want your memory back,
drink blood.
Are you all right?
You fool!
How dare you disturb the
laws of this world!
I know that you're behind
the ominous deaths!
How dare you try to live
by killing innocent people!
Innocent people?
Who?
How dare you!
Think you can get away with
murder because you're immortal?
I know how to banish you!
Do you want to remember?
Then watch this!
Sir! What happened!
We must get the arrow out.
Hold him down now!
That's a good idea.
But aren't we in the same class?
Stop giving me orders!
Hurry up!
I will, but watch it.
Sir?
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Isn't she odd, sir?
Did you sense it too?
You too, sir?
Yes.
I thought she was strange from the start.
She goes around alone.
She talks down to you and gives commands.
She's out of this world, sir.
It all adds up to one thing.
What?
She's crazy.
Crazy girls don't wear flowers
on their heads these days.
Try all you want, but you can't fool me!
If you want to remember, drink blood.
She fought off a vampire. Is she one too?
No, she's can't be.
If she is, she can't be fine in the sun.
And she wouldn't have saved me.
If he catches the monster
before I find my memory...
But she's similar to him.
He's arrogant, but has a useful brain.
She's quite arrogant.
But her ability to fight
him is quite useful.
With my brain and this woman's
body, we can catch the monster.
Work with her?
My brain and...
Seo-pil's body!
Damn it!
This woman's body!
Oops. Did I say that out loud?
It's not what it sounded like.
- I mean your...
- If you help me,
I'll help you catch the monster.
But
you can't ask anything about me.
Agreed. But help you with what?
I lost my memory.
I want to know who I am.
Fine.
But there's one problem.
What is it?
You don't call me sir.
Then don't call me ma'am.
Really?
That works.
Wait. Maybe not.
Is she really crazy?
By the way,
how did you know the dye maker would die?
The arrowhead from Song's corpse
had a letter which means 'to stain'.
My clever head figured out
it's a clue to his next killing...
The arrowhead!
Oh no! Brother!
Who's that?
- Must be the dead man's brother.
- What?
He only has a younger sister.
Right. He does.
Then who am I?
Well, I'm...
I'm his sister.
Then who is he?
- Well, I'm her Hus...
- My servant.
His name is Bang-ja.
Greet me.
Hello, ma'am.
He's dressed in disguise to protect me.
He will be examined soon. Please be quick.
- Of course, sir.
- Let's go.
Thank you, sir!
A servant?
Find the arrowhead, Bang-ja.
Are you all right?
Our lady lost consciousness
from the shock of his death!
Oh no, ma'am!
I'm fine. Put me down.
No.
Put me down! Let me off!
Pretend you're asleep, will you?
People will think it's odd if you don't.
You really don't remember anything?
I don't even know my name.
Then let's make one.
My name?
We'll have to go around together like this.
I can't just call you 'hey you'.
And I'm an outstanding name maker.
Listen and choose.
Bertha, Dorcas, Edna, Gretel...
Don't get cute with me.
Let's see.
Your fair skin is like the moon.
'Wol' means 'moon'. And you're young.
How about Wol-young?
That's a pretty name.
Simplified 'A-gyo'...
It could mean someone
who makes ox hide glue.
It could also mean shinbone.
So, it could be a hunter or a butcher next.
That's so weird.
I haven't seen her eat in days.
Even if your parents die, you feel hungry.
Why won't she eat?
I knew a crazy girl back home.
She'd run around everywhere
without eating for almost a week.
And you know how strong they are?
They can drag a couple of men no problem!
You should be careful, sir.
Don't get involved because she's pretty.
Hi.
The flower suits you.
Now, let's see you smile.
Smile.
Don't act pretty. Just
smile like the others.
See? She's crazy.
- Let's go home.
- Yes, sir.
Hot! Hot!
I'll protect you, sir!
Stay still!
Sir!
What about me?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You got cut. How could you be fine?
- Let's see.
- It's okay.
Don't be stubborn! Give me your hand.
Who were those men?
Why change subjects? You saw it.
Some people can heal faster than others.
What if I'm not human?
What if I'm a monster like him?
You're not a monster.
Vampires can't last in the sun like you.
They crave human blood, but you don't.
So, you're not a monster.
What do you know?
I can't control my powers.
I can even sense the air
passing through me.
When I smell blood, I feel
a suffocating thirst.
At this rate,
I could bite your neck like that monster.
You may become a monster after biting me,
but my neck is fine.
Your fear of becoming a monster
means you're not one yet.
All I see is a good person who's
afraid of becoming a monster.
Aren't you afraid of me?
I trust the human in you, Wol-young.
I trust you will not to become a monster.
You're stronger and more
upright than any man.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'll always keep my neck open to you.
Why don't you use the front gate?
I searched throughout Ganghwa.
I can't find her, sir.
This is...
No sign at all?
No, sir.
I think she left Ganghwa.
Give me that.
Look.
Still can't find her?
Get it now?
Have you seen her?
Forget it. Go back home.
No, sir. I'll stay and protect you.
It's okay. Just take
good care of yourself.
Then I'll be going, sir.
- Use the gate!
- Yes, sir.
Wait.
Am I the monster in this book?
Does this look like me?
I don't look like this!
My teeth are straight.
And it says vampires burn in the sunlight.
But I'm fine!
That's for vampires who
sucked human blood.
So, if I suck blood, I'd
be afraid of sunlight too?
Vampires must drink blood to survive.
If they don't, they'll go weak.
Then
they'll die!
Look.
You're scared of me, right?
Yes.
What's so funny here?
I could hear you outside!
Think of our history together!
All those nights together!
How can you ditch me for a crazy girl?
You'll regret leaving me someday, sir!
You're so lucky, bitch.
If I ever bite someone, he'd be the first.
By the way, sir.
I must have menopause.
I keep getting hot flashes.
See? I'm burning inside!
I'm hot! Get back!
Don't do this!
Get back, sir!
What are you staring at?
Get ready! We have to go!
Don't be a burden on us.
She won't budge.
Why you!
Stop! You're asking to die!
What's with you, sir?
What are you doing?
Stop it, sir!
Are you a pervert?
What's wrong?
Get away! Stop!
Did it really say 'A-gyo' on the arrowhead?
Why? You think I can't even read?
Just let me see.
No way! I'm mad you think I can't read!
I'll bite you!
It's a simplified character.
Simplified characters were made to...
Wol-gyo.
You read it wrong.
I knew it was Wol-gyo.
Of course, I knew.
I was right again.
This pond is called Wol-gyo.
Ganghwa Hall used to be here.
Ganghwa Hall?
Some say it's the revenge of those
who died in the Ganghwa Hall fire.
Then the next victim must
be connected to this place.
If the fire here was plotted
to kill innocent lives,
he's killing those
involved to get revenge?
That ghastly fool!
He must have his reasons.
The monster must've once been a human too.
Like me.
There's sadness in his eyes.
Didn't you lose your memory?
How do you know about Ganghwa Hall?
I'm not sure.
It just came to me.
I saw Ganghwa Hall here.
The arrowhead pointed to Ganghwa Hall?
The next victim is connected
to the fire 30 years ago.
Ask realtors and find out
why Ganghwa Hall is gone.
I'll investigate more on Ha Byung-eun.
He must be Ha Byung-eun's father.
Why hold a sacrifice instead of
wishing his son's spirit well?
Nan?
Have you forgotten?
Did you think it was over?
You watched me die, but lived comfortably?
Just as you murdered my wife and son,
I'll destroy you and your family!
Forgive me!
I deserve to die!
I couldn't protect you to the end.
I'm sorry.
Son!
- Ganghwa Hall?
- Yes.
I heard Ganghwa Hall
burned down 30 years ago.
What happened?
It wasn't just a fire.
It was treason.
Treason?
They say that the Crown
Prince was poisoned there.
So, the Jeong family was annihilated
and a pond was made there.
The Jeong family owned Ganghwa Hall?
He killed your son!
Who is he?
Jeong In-yul!
The Jeong family has been loyal
to the king for generations.
Jeong In-yul and his father
were very loyal too.
But they were executed
for plotting treason.
Jeong In-yul...
He's back from hell!
A royal award?
For those who reported the
Crown Prince's murder?
Hong Jeong-ho, Song Gap-young, Ha Il-ju...
Hong...
Hong Tae-mun, Song Pil-geun, Ha Byung-eun!
He killed the sons of those here in order!
There must be two more names.
Choi Il-kyu?
- The owner of Yeon-mi Lodge?
- Yes.
The land and building
belonged to the Jeong family.
But after they died, everything
went to Choi Il-kyu.
Then the next target must
be his son, Jae-kyung.
He knew his turn would come,
so he read up on monsters.
Jeong In-yul...
He's getting revenge on those
who reported the treason.
Today's the 12th!
What about it, sir?
Hong Tae-mun died on the 3rd.
Song died on the 6th.
And Ha died on the 9th!
There's no time!
We can't fight a vampire
with our bare hands!
Then how do we stop it, sir?
Strike it with silver or burn it!
If you don't burn its heart,
it could be revived with blood.
The killer will come here tonight.
He has extraordinary skills
and won't be easy to fight.
You must shoot...
You must shoot him with fiery arrows!
Yes, sir!
Jeong In-yul!
You and your father
poisoned the Crown Prince!
But you want revenge?
Rather than repent,
you took innocent lives!
You will pay for your crime!
Pay for my crime?
You'll die here too!
Pain, you say?
What do you know about never-ending pain!
How dare you tell me to pay for my crime!
Put him down.
Though you seek blood now,
were you not once a man of honor?
Since your memory isn't back,
you must not know how you died.
Why?
Think your death was different from mine?
When you remember how you
died and who killed you,
you'll become just like me.
No.
I won't be a monster like you.
Drink blood.
Find your painful memories
and get revenge on the
day of the full moon!
You must live!
You want to turn me into a real vampire?
Why did you try to give me blood?
I wanted to save you.
Why?
What if I bite you?
You'll become a vampire too.
Do you wish to live on innocent blood?
Even so, I would never drink
someone else's blood.
Then I'll bite Seo-pil for you,
so you won't be lonely.
Being with the crazy girl,
you've lost your mind, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
SIR HA IL-JU AND CHOI IL-KYU DIED
No warnings this time?
There must be another target.
Seo-pil? Wake up.
Let me hold your hand.
I said wake up!
I'll bite Seo-pil for you.
Get dressed, already!
Yes, sir.
Someone will die in 3 days.
We must find the last informer before then.
Choi Il-kyu must have the royal award too.
Why hide a proud certificate?
Was he ashamed of it?
The full moon is in 3 days.
It's when the spirits'
powers are the strongest!
Wait!
The Full Moon Fest...
His Majesty will be here!
Sir?
Please run away.
I can't protect you any longer!
What do you fools want?
Sir!
Stay back. I'll handle them.
But...
I'm immortal now, sir.
My body is on fire.
I can't control my new powers!
- Seo-pil! Actually...
- Listen!
I'll have mercy and give you time to run.
Or else today will be
your last day as humans!
Foolish thugs!
I'll feast off your blood!
I drew the bite marks on you!
You have what I want.
If you give it to me, I'll go quietly.
This will help you decide.
Stop!
When I awoke in the mountain,
a monk gave it to me.
The case 30 years ago...
Maybe the perpetrators and
victims should be switched.
Those thugs are trying to hide something!
What did they want? What was inside?
It was a scroll with strange secret codes.
Secret codes?
My clever brain would've solved it!
What a pity.
Dang!
- Why you little!
- What?
I remember!
Secret codes are written
with certain patterns.
If you find the pattern, it can be read.
Where's that clever brain of yours?
Huh, sir?
I knew it!
I was wrong.
Could you write up another one?
Right here! Just bite him!
Get back, sir.
You're confusing me!
Wait!
They used Korean alphabet!
The 1st and 3rd lines are consonants
written with vertical symmetry.
The middle line has vowels
drawn with triangles.
The circles mean 'A'.
The triangles mean 'O' or 'U'.
Circles with lines mean 'E' and so on.
POISON THE CROWN PRINCE AND FRAME
JEONG IN-YUL AND HIS FATHER
I knew it!
Those who reported the treason
were the real traitors!
What do you mean?
It's a conspiracy pact.
The Crown Prince's death was fabricated!
Those who poisoned him
framed it on Jeong In-yul
and his father as treason!
So, Jeong In-yul is
getting revenge on them?
What do you know about never-ending pain!
I don't know how he became a vampire.
But by killing the traitors' sons,
he wanted them to suffer
more pain than death.
He'll kill the last traitor's son next!
Song Gap-young.
Ha Il-ju.
Choi Il-kyu.
And
Kim...
And who, sir?
Kim Shin?
Your father, sir?
Jeong In-yul knew me.
How dare you tell me to pay for my crime!
He knows I'm the last informer's son.
Kim Shin?
What brings you here, Min?
Give me blood.
I want...
blood.
The subjects are watching.
Let them.
I should hold my beloved's
hand on a night like this.
Mother!
Father!
Prince!
Our son must've had a bad dream.
What happened 30 years ago?
Jeong In-yul is the one who called me here.
Jeong In-yul died!
I saw it with my own eyes!
If you don't tell me,
I'll hear it from him.
I did it for you!
Did you make a wish?
Yes, sir.
I wished for His Majesty's
JEONG IN-YUL
quick recovery, Your Highness.
You make me an unfilial son.
How is that so, Your Highness?
The world knows you tend to
His Majesty every night.
I just did what a subject should.
I was kidding.
Your Highness?
What did you wish for?
I wished for Joseon
to be returned to its owner.
Joseon belongs to His Majesty and you, sir.
A king should not be the
owner of a country.
The people should be.
Joseon doesn't belong to the people now.
Those who must work for
the people rule them.
They make factions and fight
to keep what's theirs.
They try to control the
king and alienate others.
They frame their opposers as traitors.
They're the ones who own Joseon.
When I become king,
I'll take Joseon away from them
and give it back to the people.
I trust you will, sir.
See the lanterns?
Do you know what the people wished for?
The people make small cries.
It's their leaders who raise their voices.
Joseon doesn't need people
to talk for the civilians.
We need people to listen
to their small cries.
I want to make it so that civilians
will not suffer from hunger and pain.
Did you find anything?
It's been long since I
sent you to Ganghwa Hall.
Promise me first, sir.
You found a way?
Tell me.
Why are you hesitating?
Do you wish to see your
entire family be annihilated?
What is it?
The Crown Prince has passed away!
What?
But how?
Sir! Sir!
Please run away! Your
father's been arrested!
My father? Why?
That he poisoned His Highness...
That's preposterous!
Your Highness! You must leave at once.
What do you mean?
Where is His Highness?
The young prince is in danger.
Please change.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
You know very well that my
father would never do this.
He's been framed!
Those who killed His Highness
will be after the prince.
Your Highness!
Please follow me.
Your Highness?
Please sit here.
They won't come here.
Thank you.
How could you come in here?
Haven't you heard about this ship?
It's a revolt.
We must protect the prince
until things settle down.
In-yul!
Run away!
Protect them no matter what!
Hurry!
But it's treason, sir! I can't do it.
You fool!
It's not treason.
The Crown Prince becoming king is treason!
He's filled with absurd ideals!
If he becomes king, Joseon will fall!
A country does not thrive on ideals alone!
The only way to save your family
is to bring down the Crown Prince!
What are you doing?
Please...
Please let the prince live?
Open the door.
Open it now!
Just let the prince live!
Please save the prince!
No!
It would've been better to
die than to beg for life.
You fool!
If I didn't do that, our family
would've been annihilated!
I abandoned my friend and the Crown Prince
to save you!
You mean, this is all because of me?
You did all that for me?
Then what makes me different
from the monster?
I lived well in a family that
thrived on innocent blood!
Then I'm a monster too!
Scour the area!
Yes, sir!
Prince...
You must survive.
Search there!
Find them!
Don't let them get away!
Corner her and catch her!
Mother?
If snow falls before the balsam fades,
I heard you can meet the one you miss.
Prince?
Where did you hear that?
It doesn't matter for
me if the balsam fades.
Why?
Even if you can't meet the one you miss?
I'll live with you and Father forever.
I won't miss anyone.
You were Sun...
My son, Sun...
I didn't even hold your hand.
You died...
before even calling me mother.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Your Highness!
I, Jeong In-yul,
was disloyal in being
deceived by a greedy friend.
I will punish him for harming
the Crown Prince and prince.
I'll burn everything he
owns once and for all!
He will come tomorrow
during the Full Moon Fest.
That puts His Majesty in harms way!
We must reveal everything.
Even if I must die,
I'll reveal your crimes, Father!
Lock him away at once!
Sir!
Stay back!
I'm their owner's son.
They'll never harm me.
Stay back or else!
This sir...
This fool is dead!
I said stay back!
My toe!
- Are you all right?
- I have gout!
Giddy up!
What are you doing?
I'll protect you! Grab the reins!
Seo-pil!
My gout!
Were you scared?
Scared people will disdain
you if they own Joseon?
Scared you'll lose everything?
Scared my young son will
live and reveal your sins?
I've been waiting.
I could strike you in the heart.
Please don't hesitate, Wol-young.
You must be so angry to
have to come back like this.
I must die
so your anger can be
resolved in the least bit.
I hope this will pay for
some of my father's sins.
Your father did not
only take away my life,
but my son and husband too.
We just wanted to be together.
That's all we wanted.
But
you enjoyed the last 30 years
upon their unjust deaths.
You ask me to kill you?
Fine.
I'll kill you again and again!
I want to know who I am.
Perhaps you lived in the distant past.
Maybe 100 years ago?
That long?
Then I'd be so old.
Shall I call you granny?
No! I'd rather be called a monster.
It was exactly 30 years ago.
Trying to save you, I became a monster.
But you!
To fill your filthy mouth,
you killed the Crown Prince!
And my father and I!
Jeong In-yul!
I know the truth to your unjust suffering!
I'll reveal everything, so stop this!
The truth?
That's right!
Tonight!
The truth will burn you alive!
No!
Die you evil monster!
You call me a monster?
After knowing what your father did to me?
How dare you call me a monster?
30 years ago,
you became a monster to save a friend.
But now!
You kill innocent people for revenge!
And threaten His Majesty's life!
You're just a monster!
Now, die!
Your Highness!
You've done enough.
No, Your Highness!
He must die to finish my revenge.
Those who made us into
monsters are all dead.
Stop.
It's over now.
I don't know how to stop.
My father is still alive in my heart.
His Highness and the prince
must be alive in you too!
I can't stop here.
You know very well
that we should not have come back to life.
We're just monsters who crave human blood.
Though we've gotten our revenge,
we can only live on the
blood of innocent people.
We've done enough.
It's time to go.
I, Jeong In-yul,
shall go to the Crown Prince first.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Please go inside!
What is time?
Please hide from the sunlight!
Waiting is only possible in time.
But the balsam stain remains...
Will I meet the ones I miss?
I missed you so much.
30 years ago,
Kim Shin poisoned the Crown Prince
and framed the Jeong family.
Thus, seize all his assets and servants.
Although his son revealed everything,
Kim Min must also be
beheaded to uphold the law!
A MONTH LATER
I heard you've gone a little cuckoo.
Maybe a lot.
He's coming! He's coming for me!
Who? Who's coming for you?
He came in my dreams.
He said he's coming for me!
So weak for a young fellow.
If you're a man, state your name!
If you're a ghost, go away!
It's me!
I waited so long.
Your Majesty!
You're already dead.
Kim Min no longer exists in Joseon.
There are many things you
must do for me in secret.
What did His Majesty command?
A month ago, in Andong,
the dead started to come
back to life and eat people.
Man-eating dead?
Yes!
They exist but do not.
They are called zombies.
Oh really?
Good luck!
Wait! Come with me!
KIM Myung-min, OH Dal-soo,
KIM Ji-won AND LEE Min-ki
Directed by KIM Sok-yun