There is a cloud nation between heaven and the world
There is a place to stop people who have gone to heaven in their family memory.
Penguin mother who came to Yunguo not long ago
Every day we see the tears in the world from the clouds in the clouds
After a year, the rainy season began.
Mother penguin secretly sits on the rain train
Train to a small simple station
Oh,
Where did the child cry come from?
Hastily passed
There is a little penguin wearing a yellow raincoat crying
Mother penguin clutches little penguin
Shocked things happened that moment
Every day since then, Penguin mother and baby penguin are not separated
Play game together
Teaching penguin fishing methods
Live a very happy time
Unconsciously, the rainy season is coming to an end
Yunguo’s raindrop goblin came to find her mother quietly
The rain will stop
To return before the clouds disappear
If you can't sit on the last train, you're going to heaven.
Then you can't see the little penguin again from above
Although the mother of Penguin was very sad but she did not cry
The little penguin also smiles at the penguin mom
So the mother and baby penguin parted and smiled after hugging.
Penguin mother returning to cloud country
Look at the little penguin above every day
Never crying again
Mom
to  Zhihao
When is dead
Worry about how they will live in the future
When daddy is not easy
That danger is not let
But born hard
It was healthy before giving birth
That's right
See you again, mother.
You
See
Present
1 Year Later, Summer 2006
Su Zhiying
Sun Yezhen
Jin Zhihuan Gao Changxi
Li Youzhen Kim Hyunsu
Zhi Hao, get up.
Go to school
son
I went into my mother's closet again.
Eat to school
stand up
The national weather is sunny today
Seoul temperature 29 degrees
Qingzhou and Gwangju 28 degrees
Daegu is 30 degrees
It will be hot weather
There is a rainy season this weekend
Starting from Jeju on Saturday
Rain falls south of Micro City on Sunday
Will it rain every day during the rainy season?
Dad, it rains in the rainy season.
should be
Will it rain every day during the rainy season?
It usually stops when it rains
Isn’t it raining that it’s the rainy season?
Ah
When the rainy season starts, it will rain and it will stop
But the day when the rainy season begins will surely rain
When it rains on Jeju Island
It is the rainy season
Jeju Island is also our country.
right
Of course don't worry about it
The rainy season will surely come
Sit and eat
Daddy is happy too
what
When the rainy season comes, my mother will come
- Shiho. - Yes.
Let's wait and see
Let's eat it late. It's late for school.
Don't worry, Mom will definitely keep promise.
The book also says
Dad takes medicine
Oh medicine
I'll go
Are you hot?
It won't rain
I'll go
After school
I will go to Uncle Hongkuo
Listen to the teacher
Ok
Go away, eat it.
Give you
It's been a long time since
Always come
Where is this here?
Thank you, I will enjoy it.
That here
Here
what
This button
Yin Jing Coffee
I drank
Did you clean in the morning?
All cleaned up
well done
1 2 3 4
So handsome
what are you doing
Dig it?
Such a big person is still afraid of water
If you are afraid of water in the swimming pool
Go to the sauna and die hot
what happened again
what expression
Is there anything in school
It's nothing
Tell your uncle what happened
Can't daddy run?
No
Why daddy has so much to do
Do you think about the Spring Festival?
what is that
Not even if
How do you say to your dad?
Have you ever seen a light that will automatically turn on when someone passes by?
Um, I have on my porch
How can I light it?
I will shine if I move below
right
So people don’t shine when they’re not passing.
Will be bright
Is it bright?
Ok
Flies will fly in the past
If the wind blows, it will light up
How can your family be the same as the owner?
Anyway, if you keep on
What will happen?
broken
- Ah, is it broken? - Uh
That is, what if my dad’s always been on?
- It will be broken. - Well.
So only do the necessary things
So can't you race?
Tired
What about the car?
What to do if an accident occurs
Is the cinema too?
Recently, TV has a lot of good-looking
But suddenly why race?
I am the representative of our team relay race
Wow, it's amazing
To run with dad
What are you afraid of uncle?
Uncle legs are also short
Hello, Zhi Hao.
Are you talking about your uncle's leg?
You stand up
Touch here
- I can touch the bones - um
The average person's leg is only here
Touch my uncle
Not touch
Why can't I touch my uncle's leg?
do not know
Because the uncle’s legs are not only here
Maybe there will be such a long leg
like what
Like a penguin
So will you run fast with such a long leg race?
Will run fast
It will run quickly.
father
Why is my son so happy today?
An appointment with Toshihisa Hiruji will take part in the race tomorrow
- Relay race? - Hmm.
It was supposed to run with Daddy
Uncle Hong Jiu said that he would race
Legs are also very long
Is it true?
Uncle Hong Jyu Goodbye Penguin
Refuel
Thank you
Hello, we have a woman like Shen Rentang in our shop.
I am leaving
What's shy?
Please look
Don't worry, you go.
Thank you
Hello, Lao Zheng
come here
Many people are dissatisfied
It’s very dark when swimming and it’s always flashing
I also want to do it myself
But I have fear of heights
I can’t even change my home’s light bulb
In short, hurry up
Are you going to a sports meeting?
But isn't the Games every year?
Let's go next year
I'll explain it again. You listen well.
Uncle received a baton
It takes 3 seconds and 3 seconds to reach the fastest speed
Is it right?
So uncle
Hello, Zheng Zhihao.
Wow, the legs are really long
Let's see, I'm right.
That's not OK
This code number:
Uncle gave me a vest
why
Come to me
Why
Uncle is not my real family
Oh dad
son
Dad can run slowly
Um, I will run very fast
The final relay player prepares
Zhi Hao
Running
hurry up
father
Daddy is shameful
Do not
But daddy
Dad won't leave me out
Dad will never leave Zhi Hao walking
Really
of course
Swear to cloud country
Got it
Come up
Dad is tired
It's my father who wants to carry his son.
Let’s go
father
Let's go home and wash the quilt
Suddenly why
Aunts and Uncles say it will rain
- Wow, really? - Hmm.
Then let’s go home
Hold tight
What to look for
Didn’t mom say it?
If you have 10 together, you will realize your wish
What is our Chihiro wish?
Mom does not get sick
Thank you
Mother must be healthy
- Conventions - Conventions
father
It's raining, Dad.
Go to see mom
Zhi Hao
Wait, go together
mom
Where is my mom?
Where is my mother?
Haven't you come yet?
Let's go back
Don't go back
Will catch a cold
not going back
It seems that today mom has something
Come again next time
No mother said that she will come today.
Come back next time
Don’t say what my mom will say today
Let me down
Come on, let me down
Do not
what
Oh, mother.
What's wrong, I'm going to my mom
You are waiting here
Dad’s going to see it. Do you know?
Do not
Zheng Zhihao
Why come
It's mother, right. It's mother.
Wait, calm down, calm down
Can't be a ghost
What is the ghost?
Ah yes
mom
Zhi Hao
Do not touch Zhihao.
mom
Mommy mommy
Don't let it go
Get up, hurry up.
Look, mother, right?
who are you
Mom, don't you know me?
It's me. Zhi Hao.
Mom, am I your mother?
Why don't you pretend to know me?
Mum is not saying that if it rains after Cloud Kingdom, it will go back and forth.
What are you talking about?
Dad, hurry up and say, hurry up.
Sore
Mom, get up quickly.
I'll go home and show it to you.
Wait
Oh, go back first
This mom
Mom, I'm ours.
right
There are also many here
This is to be drawn to my mother when my mom comes back.
Zhi Hao
Everything you haven't touched there
Watch it slowly. Change clothes if it is inconvenient.
Shiho, I want to pee
Don’t want
Come and pee
I don't want to pee
Zhihao ah, why didn't mom remember?
It seems like I came from the cloud country
But Mom doesn’t even know that
what
Things Mum goes to cloud country
is it
Zhi Hao
Let’s keep it confidential
why
Can't let mother be stimulated to leave again
Do not say mother will leave again
so
Say we three people have been living together
It must also be confidential to other people
What do you mean?
If we help, my mother will soon find memorizing
Come
But Mom looks healthy, is it right?
It is more beautiful
Mom is very beautiful
Let’s go
That one
Did I live here all the time?
Um, of course, right?
- Right. - Right.
But what did you say about Yunguo?
It seems to be so happy to meet people who haven’t seen you for a long time.
Also said welcome
I also said that my things have never been set
Did I mess with life?
Oh, that
you...
I got sick
me
It's been bad for you to be in the hospital
Yunguo Hospital
Yunguo
But how did you go there?
Not in the hospital?
All recovered yesterday
Ah, yes
Was discharged yesterday
- So.. - Said to hide and seek
hide and seek
You like to hide and hide. You can hide and hide.
Yes, very good
mom
Are you ok
Daddy's right, Mom's got it right when she came down.
Yeah, it looks like the stones fall from the sky
Yes Stone
So you fainted there
Passed out
It seems that there is a temporary loss of memory
- It seems like - It seems to be
- Right. - Right.
Thank you
child
come here
How could the father and the son be even the same?
I do not have it
Cook fried rice in the refrigerator. Must have lunch.
Then rest at home
Suddenly doing too much...
I will take care of myself
Whether it's doing things or stunts
I am leaving
I'll go
mom
I returned from school
How come back so soon
Teacher missed today
Won
This time I let you
Progress is so fast
It will not really let you now
77 78 79
wheat
Meter
Mimi
Dad, nothing, just playing.
How do not eat
Want to eat fried rice cake made by mother
Mom cannot act now
No mother is very strong
Are you ok
Ok
Remote control
over there
I can’t say no, but I have to sleep with my mother
I took him out.
OK, let’s go.
Is it really possible
Ok
Okay, so good night.
That one
Do you sleep directly?
Don't want to wait for another sleep
So please take off
It turned out to be this meaning
There's Shiho here. I'm waiting outside.
Can't coerce
Fortunately, Zhi Hao slept
What are you doing?
Is the leg hot?
Ah, not that.
Give you medicine
but
Although I can't remember
But it seems that I am a mother and a wife
Don't worry too much
Memory should be quickly found
is not what it means
I am also married because I like you.
Is it weird?
very curious
Tell me what's going on?
Uh, we met for the first time in high school.
Three years of high school have been the same class
Summarize you in one sentence
The school's first
Not the occasional first
Is always the first
Is it isolated?
Not so
As ordinary we feel very difficult to get close
Then I was a special swimmer
Only go to class in the morning
But it's always sleeping so we haven't seen how many times
But how do we interact?
Let's look good
This will be fine
I think I can swim here
Can't swim over there
Oh, over there
How to do it?
Thank you
I myself fell in love with you
52 pages of the third question
It is 23rd today
No. 23 is not
No. 13 on the 13th to answer
Norwegian Forest
Norwegian forest
Chinese medicine will not eat older will be older
It's okay, I'm a child.
Do you like her?
she was
Lin Xiuya
You can see it.
Say what
Do you want to help?
What help
Hurry up, do you want to help?
okay
Because it is you, so I ask you again
Do you want to help?
You know what you think about it.
Incredible
According to the data I analyzed
More like you than Lin Xiuya
Zheng Yuzhen Lin Xiuya 9%
Lin Xiuya Zheng Yuzhen
98%
Incredible
So you can't just hit it
Just pretend to ask without concern
There is no extra pen
She will say
Then you say coldly
Lend me an eraser
Then she will think you are ridiculous
So you go along with the rhythm
- Is it right? - Yes
- Do not believe - believe
Hello Lin Xiuya
- There is no extra pen - No
As expected, it is not a good target
I hide my own mind
The less you can do in this situation,
Ultimately whoever prefers it will
Pose
Zheng Yuzhen
Hello, can you jump?
I am sorry
Because I use my left foot
That is not called using his left foot. Calling his left foot.
Come back
I'm not wrong
Hideya
Do you use your left foot?
Yes
Then
Let's show elegant with the left foot
Start
It's ok
I am sorry
what happened
I didn’t officially talk to you after three years.
It was the graduation day.
Didn't you still forget her?
What do you say?
What is it really?
- Are you crazy? - Don't say it.
- How are you still?
- Don't say it. - Hey. Hey. Hey.
You haven't written it yet
me
Yu Zhen ah, lend me a pen
If you want to write, write it too.
Do I write too?
Ok
Hideya she...
Ah my pen
I went to a nearby local university because of my athleticism
You went to Seoul’s university
Don't worry, Yu Zhen
I am more important than friendship
What do you say?
Don't you remember?
Okay, slowly
Mommy mommy
I thought my mother went to cloud country again.
It is hospital hospital
No matter how high school did not begin to love for three years
Ok
Therefore, once again in the summer vacation, he raised his courage.
Hey
Can't you?
You haven’t talked yet.
Your waste
As summer vacation passed
I really want to talk on the winter vacation
Chuncheon City, Gangwon-do
New Taipei City, Yongsan-ri
is gathered
address
94/02/08 (13:30)
enlisted
time
102 reserve team
enlisted
force
Gangwon-do, Chuncheon-si, Gangwon-dong
549-18 242-18
Address
Gangwon-do North of Y义dan-gun
No.39-21, Yanli 249-11
Origin
Zheng Xianyu
The relationship between
Names
740824-
1260982
Li Yuke's comic book v1.0\fs7\pos (46.08,151.04)\c&H13110E&} Zheng Yuzhen
̄
Hey
open
phone...
Hey
Zheng Yuzhen
Cheng Yin Senior High School Class II Zheng Yuzhen
My name is Zheng Yuzhen.
Maybe you don't remember
that is
Want to ask if you took my pen on high school graduation day?
That pen is expensive
Hello, Hong Hong.
Hong Hong ah
Hello, what do you want to hear?
What do you want to do?
I'll shape it for you
What is the shape?
It's not that I'm late. It was you who came early.
know
It's hot, why don't you go in and stay there?
Didn't you meet at the school gate?
Oh, yes, sorry.
No need to
Thank you
It's hot
You go well
See you
Hello Lin Xiuya
Are you not thirsty?
thirst
Let's live in a dormitory in Seoul
Not single occupancy
Ah, I’m tired of living alone.
Better than home
No one else
Right
In fact, the home is very aggrieved
Who hates me most for letting me do this?
No matter doing things or gimmicks, I will take care of myself.
No matter doing things or gimmicks I'm going to use them
What to laugh
Oh, that...
Norway
Do you like Norway?
Um, like it from the past
Lush forest coast fjord
Do you like it
dislike
Didn't you read "Forest of Norway" before?
what
That's just a novel book
Completely independent of Norway
Oh
But actually
I also thought it was a story written by a Norwegian forest cat.
Is there a book for Norwegian Forest Cats?
Um, very cute
It's a cat. It looks like a puppy.
Like a dog likes to stick people
The hair is also very soft and cute
Oh is it?
Do you like cats too?
Like like dogs too
me too
Your bus is coming
I see you go, I’m going
Too many people to take the next bus
Ok
This is the last car. Please hurry up.
I gotta go
I will return tomorrow after returning to Seoul
Wow, look over there
what
- Oh god. - Wow. Really fast.
Uncle
Wait, uncle.
Wait
- What does this person do? - Wait
Lin Xiuya
Can write a letter
Is that not a coloring paste?
What are you doing?
Will write to you
This year's rainy season was longer than expected.
It seems that there is something good
what
Nothing is good
Are you in love
What love do I talk about?
Is there anything good
Buttons 扣 Good heat
Are you a dummy
Wow it rains again
This is because of my dad
why
My dad will wash the car and it will rain the next day.
But also car wash every day
Our car is an American car
Wow nice
You are like my dad
what
My dad also likes to rain.
What about you
I do not like
why
Hair always rolls
Hello, Yu Zhen, Yu Zhen.
What's wrong with you?
Is there something more urgent than this?
Go away
You see that lady too
Character is also completely Shenshi Rentang
What kind of teacher
What is this quirky atmosphere?
Do you have a woman?
What woman.. really
Who is it?
哎呦 ok
You can write it on your face
Who told me to see
Come on, say it quickly
open
Hey, who can grab you woman?
Do you not know that I am more than friendship?
- Actually... - If Shuya came back I'll kill you
Is this why you think of this stinky kid?
How do you not say Hideya has memory loss
I am leaving
What happened to the kid
I'm sorry my friend was very shy
Dirty can not stand
Anyhow, how can I say so badly
No, I mean that uncle.
No woman is justified
Yeah, it's so dirty.
No, I mean you
me
There is only one woman in her life
Is there on my face?
I belong to the pure sentiment
It's not you, I mean people who just went out
Handsome face is a pity
Yes, Yu Zhen looks a bit handsome
Do not
I am talking about you
what
you
Daddy look at this
what is this
Listen very clearly
Is this dug out of your ears?
Dad, you too come
Lie down hurry up
Dad doesn’t use
Come on, lie down
father
Dad also has a lot of deafness
Shi Hao has a big ear hole like his father
Wow, really a lot
Yu Zhen
Zheng Yuzhen
Yu Zhenzhen Zheng Yuzhen
what
My love Zheng Yuzhen
Is this penguin?
Friends, you're dead, I can't live.
How can I die?
Zhihao ah, mother came
you've been drinking
I am sorry
No
what
Can not Go Out
what happened
Uncle Hong Jiu is very strange
what
Big head
Where have you been?
Hello, Hello.
To be honest, it is not so amazing to look elegant.
The figure is not amazing...
Brat
Go out and say it
Ah
I told you about Hongjiu.
He is a little drunk
Well, drink a glass of water
But why did you wear a penguin suit?
I will explain later
Go back and be honest
Hideya Hideya
Water here
Shuya
Hong Hong ah
Our father in heaven
May everyone honor your name
May your kingdom come
May your will
Follow the line and follow it in heaven
I'm wrong
Never again
Introduce the object
So please anger
Be careful to go back
Not a bad person
So
Not that I was writing to me at that time
what
Ah wrote
Cold
what
Frozen hands?
Not frozen
Gloves
Didn't wear it
Did you fight outside?
Cycling fell
To apply medicine
- I'm going to get medicine. - It's OK.
Stay here for a while
mom
No foul
Do you still want to go far?
Coming
It is coming soon
Nothing ah
Is this right here?
Wow
Great
Wanna see
A bit louder
Sorry
Turn off
Look together Watch together
It doesn't matter. Look together.
Oh, what's this?
My Birthday
My birthday
Deceptive
Not deceived
really
Uh, can't tell anyone
Now you know
Agreement
Cloud State
Penguin mother
Cloud country
what is this
Penguin mother
Cloud State
what is this
Penguin mother
Cloud country
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud countries
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud Country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud State
Penguin mother
what is this
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud country
Penguin mother
Cloud State
Cloud countries
Penguin mother
Cloud Country
Cloud State
Penguin mother
Cloud countries
Cloud State
Penguin mother
so cute
Wheat wheat
How can this play?
Come again
Must catch you
Start
Zhi Hao taps her mother will hurt
Do not
Zhi Hao, wait.
Pain
How can I bully my dad?
Surrender Surrender
Why do you want to post that
Want it to keep raining
Why do you want to rain
I like rain very much
father
What's wrong?
What is that?
Zheng Yuzhen
Zhi Hao ah succeeded
Escape
- Is it fun?
But daddy will be very tired
I'm okay
Daddy, a little faster
What did the mother just promise?
Is a secret
Zhihao is going to take a shower
father
Why did not say
Where does it hurt
When did it start to hurt?
After our third meeting
Go in, let’s go.
Wait
I wish you good results in national trials
do not get sick
Not...
Doctors say
There is a problem with the hormones in my brain
So I also took medicine and I also treated it.
But gradually worsened
As long as there is a little tension or reluctance
Will faint more times
It's all over.
Not only in the water
Even ordinary life is...
is it going well
Ok
A bit thin
No
I heard that I am not moving
Um, there are other plans
What's matter
No
It just became like this
Please
- Don't hide - nothing to hide
It's just tired of you
Really
It's just tired of me
You are not what happened
There is no such thing
Fortunately,
Since then we
Don't meet again
Since then I spent nearly a year trying to forget you
But I really can't forget
My state is a dangerous thing to go to Seoul alone
But if you can see you again
How I do not care
It looks like you're happy but it's not a bit
But also feel lucky
because I
I really feel that I can't deserve you anyway
Since then we have not contacted
I think so it ended
but
Soon after
Hey
I have been distressed
Will you continue to see you?
The brain shouted and let me hurry back
But the body will never move
Hideya
- I... - Don't worry, we will be good
The fate has been set
Soon after, I proposed to you
We feel sorry for every minute and second we separate.
You asked me to propose to you soon
In the end, I will take the initiative
You are not like that
I would never think of getting married
You disregard parental opposition
Abandoned study
Come here and marry me
After a long time, Zhi Hao was born
we
Can you always be happy?
Of course
- Did you know it? - Yes.
Do you participate too?
Um, my classmates will sing together
Should be very interesting
Mother will come
Of course, the son participated
You will also go
Uh, go.
Oh, it's the weather forecast
This rainy season feels very long
- Shiho is quick to eat - The rainy season will end in another week
Why is it closed?
It's noisy eating
Go to school quickly, eat soon.
all my time
Have to love each other.
Lin Xiuya
all my time
Have to love each other.
Lin Xiuya
It's me
Dad is back
too difficult
Because you caught too tight
Yes, then practice again
Grab it gently.
Wow, you can see
- Shi Hao can now do it for herself - um
Doing well
Zhihao ah, Dad is back.
Dad, I made a fried egg
Wow, really?
Really doing great
Try again
But daddy
- Did my dad have clover? - No.
Originally only eight
It is now nine
Is it my mother?
"The rain started to stop! Go back before the clouds disappear
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain is starting to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has stopped! It will disappear in the clouds. Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain is beginning to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has begun to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! Go back before the clouds disappear
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has stopped! Go back before the clouds disappear
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain is beginning to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! Go back before the clouds disappear
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the cloud Before going back
"The rain has stopped! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain began to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain started to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
"The rain is beginning to stop! To disappear in the clouds Before going back
Since when began to fantasy
The day of dreams
I am good at running
The fastest in our class
I want to participate in Olympic gold medals
Zhi Hao
Don't make a joke
Again
You are very right, son.
Let's grab two times
If it is too strong, it will be even worse
That's right
Do not use fingernails
- Is that okay?
Circle
Yes, very good
You two are like emperor penguins
Emperor Penguin Why?
Penguin mother goes to foraging after spawning in winter
Daddy Penguin will be between fifty and fifty degrees of stone
In order to hatch, you will put your feet on the eggs
Wow, amazing!
What do you do?
Take a look at Zhi Hao
Come on, hurry up.
what happened
I want to go to the bathroom.
Enduring emperor penguin will endure for months
Zhi Hao
Laughed
Look at mom
Look over my mother.
Zhi Hao
Wow, didn't you sleep this day?
I can't say I'm crazy
But if you do this, will you not leave?
After the rainy season is over, do you want to leave?
Whatever you want to try
What can't be done?
Hello there
You see for yourself
I do not know who always hit the suds in our car.
Today, iron balls have been used
Shih Hoh, are you really doing it?
look up
Are you really doing it?
My family book Bin saw
Why did you do that?
Tell me why I did it
Don't say it?
I am sorry
I will rigorously teach him when I go back
If you need compensation please tell me
It's all parenting. I feel distressed to tell you
In my opinion, Shi Hao has emotional problems
Get up early to consult about your child
Of course, Dad is doing very well
Children without mothers are obvious
I am sorry
What are you doing and crying?
Shu Bin said
His dad washes his car
It will rain
Mom will not go, right?
Did my father and I cling tightly?
Didn't she let her go and grab it tightly?
welcome
What do you need?
Do not be afraid
Will not eat your
I want to ask you something
What are you going to ask... mine?
I said no amazingly beautiful...
Because of children, so...
what is this
This shop will not close soon
What does it mean?
Because it takes a long time
Zhi Hao
mom
It's raining. How did it come out?
where did you go
Buy cake for her son to go to Uncle Hongku’s shop
Let's sing
Start
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
- Dear - Dear
We Zhihao
Happy Birthday
Zhi Zhi Hao Blow candles
quickly come
How will we grow up?
Maybe it looks like you look good.
What does it mean to agree?
Yiwei Primary SchoolHeart Art Festival
Hello, everyone. We are the only person in the 6th grade Li Junshu...
Yiwei Elementary School Art Festival begins now
Slow down
What can I do?
what's up
The next show is prepared by cute first-year classmates.
Reorganize the ‘dream of the day’ into a play
Really looking forward to
Please applause welcome
I believe in my dream
Although it looks hard
Close your eyes
Dream day
Occasionally difficult
I would like to cry
I will not give up
I believe in my determination
Always come
The day of dreams
How wonderful it is
I want to dream
I am good at playing football
My dream is to become a national player
Go to Europe and America to become a professional football player
Refuel
I am good at singing and dancing
Acting also has confidence
I want to be an idol singer
Become a good movie actor
I want to be the best Korean physician
Children's favorite comics
To become a model
I am good at playing karting Rainbow gloves
When I grow up and become a doctor
When my mom promised to be good, I often play games
Zhi Hao
Mom is coming
I am good at running
I am good at cleaning
Vacuum cleaner can not open very strong
It's not easy to suck in dust
I'm also good at washing clothes
Clothes should be aired
I'm also good at shampooing
Never use nails when shampooing
I am also good at cooking
Fried eggs should be lightly fried with small flames
If you squeeze hard, it will break
I
Will surely guard my father
And my mother agreed
Sore
sun
mom
to see the little penguin..."
then you can no longer from above
If you want to go to heaven, you will be able to go to heaven if you are in Hong Kong.
If you can not sit on the last train
mom
to see the little penguin..."
then you can no longer from above
If you want to go to heaven, you will be able to go to heaven if you are in Hong Kong.
If you can not sit on the last train
mom
Zhi Hao
How did you come from?
Mom will not drop Zhi Hao go right.
Zhi Hao
Listen to your mother
OK
Mom seems to be leaving
mom
I'm sorry I didn't recognize Zhi Hao faster.
Mom, sorry.
Zhi Hao Why
Mom, because of me
It's because I'm dead
What are you talking about?
Who said
Hear relatives said
Say mother because I'm sick
I'm sorry, if you know it earlier, you'll hear you more.
nonsense
Because there is how happy HAPPY HO MOM
But if I’m not born, I’ll live longer with my dad.
Zhi Hao
This is definitely not the case
mom
Even if you are not born, you will be the same.
Then in the world without Shiho
Even if you live for 100 years, you won't be happy
really
of course
Mom and Dad
It’s for Shiho
The encounter
So my mother is very grateful to Zhi Hao
Is it like that?
of course
Zhi Hao
mom
Go to Cloud Congress has been watching Zhi Hao's
To be a handsome adult
It's good to have a good father
I will never forget my mother’s
Ok
Thank you
How will we grow up?
Maybe look like you are very handsome
right
Hideya
Ok
I am sorry
what
Really
I want you to be happy
Can't I see that I am happy?
I can be with you. It has made me fully happy.
So you don't feel sorry anymore
Shuya
Wait
Zhi Hao will please you
I love him more and more
Wait
Hideya
Staying with us for a long time
When you want to become a burden to Shiho
When you come to cloud country to see me
The location next to me must be for you
father
Wow, it's better than my father
Come eat it
ketchup
Put it
Okay, okay.
Zhihao, go to school.
Son caught
Wow, Dad won
Stomach force
next
well
March 2, 1990
Things that could not be believed happened
Who I would like to like
谁 Who is the debut?
It’s impressive from the first day.
who are you
My name is Zheng Yuzhen.
Ah, Yu Zhen
You are Yu Zhen, a special swimmer
Then it happens to be
Boys in our class
Look good
I think I can swim here
You can't swim at the station
Start
stop
Thank you
Ah, good shame
Lin Xiuya
- There is no extra pen - No
Idiot
Think of a way to want to be a group
Also deliberately wrong
Hideya jumps with his left foot
Ah, it's okay.
Why do I do this?
If you want to write, write it
What else can I do?
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Thank you for being with me
My heart is very warm.
- Yu Zhen -
Zheng Yuzhen's photo
Hey
what
Zheng Yuzhen
Cheng Yin Senior High School Class II Zheng Yuzhen
My name is Zheng Yuzhen.
Although you do not remember
Zheng...
Who
Hello Lin Xiuya
Are you not thirsty?
thirst
Finally you dated
And you hold hands
then
We are a little closer
but
I received your letter a long time later
Sau Yah, it seems that I can't contact you for now. ,I am sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you cannot temporarily Contact, I'm sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sayah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sayah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being. Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it looks like it can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sayah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sau Yah, it looks like it can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being. Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you cannot temporarily Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Contact, I'm sorry
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being Contact, I'm sorry
Only one sentence of letter
Sau Yah, it seems that you can't be with you for the time being. Contact, I'm sorry
Since then, we will never meet again.
So after our three appointments were over
broke up
I really want to see you
Hideya
I'm going to review last year's exam questions. Do you want to go together?
It suddenly rained
That's right
Did you do a lot of review for the exam?
There is no review of so much
There will be more in the review paper
I also took the last test
Wait
Yu Zhen
Zheng Yuzhen
You came back to me again
The day you came to Seoul to find me
I had an accident
Then opened his eyes
mom
Shi Hao don’t let go
- Mom. - Don't do this.
I went to the future after 8 years
25-year-old lost all memory after an accident
Going to the future after 8 years
With 34-year-old you
8-year-old Zhi Hao met with her son
Although all are unfamiliar
All very clumsy
I fell in love with you again
The first time I kissed you
Love with you
Then separated again
Then he opened his eyes again
I am lying in the critically ill patient room
Six weeks into a coma after a traffic accident
Woke up miraculously
At first I thought I had dreamed
However, as time goes by
The moments of happiness are very realistic
Can't tell anyone
To be honest, even I can't believe it.
but
Gradually I think the future I see is real
Marry you
Live with lovely son
The appearance of a very good future
Although there is a snack
But I'm 32 years old
Throw down the deep love of you and Zhi Hao
died
I'm scared
I don't want to die so soon
If I just break up with you and live all the time
I will marry someone else and lead a different life
So will there be a different future where 32 will not die?
Will I be happier?
But I know
The accident did not make me die Let me survive
Maybe you and the future, you have the sincere expectation of Shiho.
Hey
Yu Zhen?
My love Zheng Yuzhen Zheng Zhihao
Please wait for me
See you now
Hideya
I...
Don't worry, we will be good
Well settled
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
I loved all my time.
I have loved all my time.
It is a beautiful life
Zhihao ah happy birthday
coming
Hello, Zheng Zhihao.
Uncle is not greeting people
Preparing for the first date is busy
Wow!
Uncle Hong Jiu
Wow, you are stronger than your dad
Thank you, Uncle
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
Zhihao, I wish you a happy 20th birthday.
Mom will support your beautiful love, come on!
love you.
- Yunguo’s mother
gave 19-year-old Zhi Hao
to 20-year-old Zhi Hao
gave 20-year-old Zhi Hao
My agreement with your mother has been kept.
to 20-year-old Zhi Hao
Thank you
But uncle
If you go right now
Please take me with you
Your son like you has the natural ability to use others
Let’s go
Daddy Daddy
I'll treat you tonight, don't eat, wait for me, oh, let me know.
Don’t worry about Dad’s date
drive carefully
it is good
Follow Your Dream And Me!
THE MISTU-MAN