Kung Fu is not a game,
gentlemen.
It is not a religion.
It's about who lives
and who dies.
You dig?
Now, in the street,
you're not gonna have
swords or spears.
If it's a brick,
we use a brick.
If it's broken glass,
we use broken glass.
The idea is to put
the other guy away fast.
That is the Wing Chun style.
If you master it...
you'll command respect...
wherever you go.
Hey, what was that for?
I heard you've been
gambling again.
Everybody gambles in Chinatown.
Not my students.
How much you lose this time?
Not... not much.
How much?
Couple hundred.
You gamble the way you fight,
no brains.
When the Chenghu town boys
come to collect,
you think they're just gonna
waltz into your punches?
Probably not.
Yeah, probably not.
All right, everybody,
get back to work.
Action!
What?
We ran out of film, Bruce.
Again, Frankie?
This is the big finish.
I know, we're using short ends.
Okay. Reload,
but make it quick.
Yeah.
What was the last ass I kicked?
Uh, gangster number four.
Okay. Steve, Vinnie,
you guys reset.
Okay.
The rest of you...
get back on the ground.
Hey, Sifu,
I think you got me in
the nuts on that one.
Well, how many times
do I have to tell you?
You have to step back
when I kick at you.
- Yeah, well, I'm not gonna be on camera.
- Roll's out.
It's not about you, dipshit.
It's about me.
Action!
One, two...
One, two. One, two.
Sifu...
I just wanted to say thank you
for letting me be in the movie.
No problem.
You're a natural.
You look great
getting your ass beat.
Thanks.
Can I ask you a question?
How am I doing in class?
You work hard.
You're even beginning
to develop your own style.
What kind of style?
A bad one.
Come, I'll show you.
Good.
It's good for the kune,
what about the street?
You think you're tough?
You think you're street?
Come on, show me
where your street is!
Relax, Mac. Mac.
Mac?
That's what you got to overcome.
Kung Fu is about discipline,
about channeling what's in here.
In here, out here.
Now, tell me.
Tell you what?
Where's all this anger
coming from?
It's nothing. I'm just
frustrated, that's all.
Hey, Mac.
Didn't mean to
embarrass you in there.
It's fine.
I embarrassed myself.
You know, if any one of those
punches would've connected,
you would've knocked me down.
You must've studied
boxing before.
No.
Somebody taught you
how to throw a punch.
Your Dad?
You could say that.
You know what
I was doing in there?
Getting inside your head.
If you can psych
the other guy out,
before you even
throw the first punch,
you already won.
You're good at doing that.
Look, I'm your Sifu,
I'm not here to tell you
how to live your life.
But I can tell you this...
in a fight, a chip on your
shoulder is just extra weight.
Hands on the outside.
Looking good though, right?
Not really.
But keep at it.
Now get your stuff, get out of here.
I got to start locking up.
Vinnie, Vinnie, Vinnie, my man.
Tony Yu.
Long time no see.
I saw you yesterday.
The Giants lost, again.
You owe Auntie Blossom money.
Get off me!
You don't mess with
the Chengu town, Vinnie.
Hey!
You boys done playing?
Clean your boys up,
go back to the north end.
Vinnie will
pay you back tomorrow,
unless you want to deal
with our unfinished business
right here and right now.
- I just hope you learned your lesson.
- Damn right.
Next time I'm going
with the Dodgers.
Vinnie, you're gonna get
yourself hurt one of these days.
McKee, China Gate order ready.
You drop off.
Mm-hmm.
Sure thing, Miss Wei.
You still don't use chopsticks.
He's a barbarian, Ma.
You the barbarian.
Fight in alley. Get your
feet off of my desk.
I love you, Ma.
Mm.
Wong Jack Man, he's leaving
the Shaolin temple.
Really? See, that's a guy who gives
Sifu Lee a run for his money.
I don't know,
I think Sifu still beats him.
What's it say?
He's on a pilgrimage...
to check out Kung Fu in America.
He is?
Yeah.
Where's he gonna be?
San Francisco.
Hey. Here.
Twenty busboy uniform,
eight dozen napkins.
Mm-hmm. Where are
my 60 tablecloth?
Calm down, they're still
in the truck.
I need tablecloth now,
every table dirty.
Okay. Okay, I got two hands.
Give me someone to help.
Thank you, for helping me.
You're new around here, right?
I'm Steve.
Do you speak any English?
No.
That was wrong,
I should've, um...
That's still wrong.
That sounds like English.
I'm not supposed to speak to
anyone outside the restaurant.
What's your name?
I am Quan Xiulan.
Xiulan.
Uh...
May I have those?
Baseball Digest?
Yeah, sure.
That's how you learned English.
I use what I can get.
Hand me the tablecloth.
Thank you.
That's dangerous, Mac.
You don't want to mess with a Bi Nu
girl who belongs to Auntie Blossom.
Who's Auntie Blossom?
Auntie Blossom owns the China Gate
but her real job is running rackets
for the Chengu town triad
out of the restaurant, I mean,
your girl belongs to them.
At least until she can pay them back
for smuggling her into the country.
That's messed up.
Hey, you want some?
What is it?
Barbecued seaworms.
Disgusting.
Hey, one man's disgusting
is another man's delicacy.
Oh, you know what the manager
of the Jackson café told me?
What?
Wong Jack Man is coming in
on the Jeremiah O'Brien
tomorrow.
How do you know that?
'Cause he's Wong's cousin.
Let's go meet him.
What are you gonna say to him?
We're gonna look like idiots.
I don't know. I just
want to shake his hand.
You're gonna tell Sifu Lee?
Probably not.
Excuse me.
Ni Hao.
No.
Thank you.
Perhaps another time.
I'm...
I beg your pardon.
You just asked me
to shine your shoes.
Vinnie!
Um...
A friend of mine was playing
a joke. A joke, do you...
Yes, I understand.
What may I do
for you, Mr. McKee?
Master Wong, I just want to
welcome you to America.
Did someone send a car for you?
I hardly merit such luxury.
You are Master Wong Jack Man,
aren't you,
from the Shaolin temple?
Yes.
Well, can I give you a lift?
Thanks for the lift.
Yeah, no problem.
Master Wong, I'm...
I'm just wondering,
it would be an honor
if you would perhaps give me
a lesson one day or...
You do not have a master?
I belong to the kune
of Sifu Bruce Lee.
Yes. I have heard
of Lee Jun-fan.
Yeah?
If you are a student
of Sifu Lee,
I doubt there is anything
I can teach you.
See you, man.
You prick.
I finally meet a living legend
and I ask him to shine my shoes?
Could have been worse.
Really? How?
I could have taught you to say,
"I hear you have a tiny dick."
Hey, wait.
Watch your mouth in here.
And what do you mean, you
finally met a living legend?
You see me every day.
I'm sorry, Sifu.
I was talking
about Wong Jack Man.
What the hell are you talking about?
Sifu, mouth!
Shut up, Vinnie!
How did you meet him?
I heard he was coming
to San Francisco.
And I went to, you know,
meet him to shake his hand.
Did he say
what he is doing here?
He said he came to observe.
Observe what?
He didn't say, Sifu, but he
did tell me he heard of you.
So, the Shaolin sent Wong
Jack Man to spy on me.
Why would they do that?
When I was a toadae of
Sifu Yip Man in Hong Kong.
Shaolin found out
my Grandmother was white.
You know what they did?
They made him stop teaching.
So when I come to America, I
open up my kune for everybody.
Maybe Shaolin
don't forgive me for that.
You really think Master Wong
came because you teach whites?
Why else would he be here?
Where they heck
did you learn that?
I'm learning it now.
But trust me...
I will get better.
Hey! You're going
out the back.
We got reservations, Fung.
Dig the threads.
And no joyriding.
My mom checks the mileage.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Can't afford this.
Just order some rice.
Yeah, but they charge
by the grain.
I just want to
get this message to her.
It's in English.
Yeah, she speaks English.
But she don't read English,
give me that.
Don't.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna write this in Chinese.
There she is.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Yes, sir?
Do you think I could get
a clean napkin, please?
Shut up. Shut up.
Slick. Really slick.
That's Auntie Blossom?
She doesn't look like a gangster.
She doesn't even
look like an aunt.
Well, she shakes down
half the shops in Chinatown.
And that scary guy behind her...
that's Bobby Chen,
her bodyguard.
Nobody messes with that guy.
Do you see those
two tree stumps behind me?
Mm-hmm.
That's Wai Fu and King Lau,
they run collections for her.
Word is Aunt B is gonna raise
the street tax again
and guess what?
Bruce Lee don't pay,
Vinnie Wei don't pay either.
Vinnie, you're no Bruce Lee.
Come on, let's go.
I ain't eat nothin' yet.
I can't afford this stuff.
What's bugging you?
Wong Jack Man.
Just ignore him.
I can't, Frankie.
He may be the only person
in this world
who can tear down everything I've
been working so hard to build up.
Has he challenged you?
Not yet.
So it doesn't matter then.
It does matter, Frankie.
A lot of people in Chinatown don't
like the fact that I teach whites,
that I married one.
And if Wong establishes
himself as a top dog here,
everything could change for me.
Sooner or later...
gonna have to fight him.
Xiulan.
You cannot do this.
They will see us.
I got you something.
It's an English grammar book.
Thank you.
I was tired this morning.
You were tired this morning.
He was tired this morning.
We were tired this morning.
Quan Xiulan,
do not speak to any outsiders.
Not as long as you're
under my roof.
Please, Furen,
when will my service end?
When I say that it ends.
So,
if King Lau ever sees you teaching
English to other Bi Nu again...
Hey!
Master Wong!
Mr. McKee.
Where you headed?
I have always wanted to see
the Golden Gate Bridge.
Well, hop on.
Really?
Yeah, come on.
Thank you.
It is truly magnificent.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
The bridge is the first thing
I saw when I moved here.
You're not from San Francisco?
I'm from Indiana.
What wonders
do you have in Indiana?
A big car race
in Indianapolis once a year,
and corn.
Lots and lots of corn.
Do they have Kung Fu there?
I never heard of it
until I came here.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Tell me about Sifu Lee.
He has big plans for Kung Fu.
He's making a movie,
and he wants to get into TV.
Kung Fu on television?
For what purpose?
To make more people aware
of the importance of Kung Fu.
Even in everyday life.
Ah...
What is the value
of Kung Fu to you?
The tougher you are,
the more people respect you?
Is that why you took Kung Fu,
to be tough?
Stand up for myself.
In northern Shaolin,
Kung Fu
is about self discipline
and self discovery.
For us,
Kung Fu does not reside
in the fists,
it resides in the soul.
Let me give you a lift
back into town.
No.
I think I will do
my Wang Shu here.
Wang Shu?
Sunset exercises.
Thank you, Mr. McKee.
Thank you.
McKee!
What's that supposed to be?
I was just warming up.
By turning yourself into a swan?
I never taught you that.
I just sort of picked it up.
From who?
Wong Jack Man.
Wong taught you that?
Sifu, I ran into him
and I showed him around town.
Well, you're such
good buddies now.
Why don't you do this?
You let him know I want to
see him after the tournament,
so we can talk, man to man.
Okay.
Master Wong.
Your cousin at the Jackson café
told me you were living here.
Come in, Mr. McKee.
Thank you.
I was just about to make tea.
Please join me.
Um...
Master Wong,
Sifu Lee wants to see you.
For what reason?
He thinks you're here because he
teaches Kung Fu to Americans.
What do you think,
Mr. McKee?
Well, that would explain why
you don't want to teach me.
Kung Fu
is not just a way of fighting,
it is a way of living
and thinking.
It was born among
the Chinese people...
and it belongs to
the Chinese people.
What's the problem
with sharing it with us?
Do you share your
atomic bomb secrets?
Well, Kung Fu
isn't an atomic bomb.
No.
It is more powerful.
The bomb comes from
the death force.
Kung Fu comes from chi,
the life force.
Life is stronger than death.
Master Wong,
nothing about you
is what I expected.
What did you expect?
I guess, at the boat, I thought you'd
be greeted by a whole delegation.
I am a monk.
Not a television star.
Thank you.
But then I heard you were
working at the café.
Please.
Nah.
Thank you.
You seem perturbed,
Mr. McKee.
Well, I'm just trying
to understand why...
Why'd you come to San Francisco?
I came to wash dishes.
That doesn't make any sense,
it's a terrible job.
It is honest labor
and it is necessary.
Yeah, but you're
a great Kung Fu master.
What I truly am...
is ashamed.
Why?
I allowed my pride
to overcome my discipline.
I hurt someone badly,
someone I respected.
It is a great sin.
Now, I must do penance.
I must humble myself to restore
the balance in my soul.
The balance in your soul?
Tell me, what does
Sifu Lee teach you?
He teaches us to kick ass.
Kick ass?
To take on a student
of such a man,
that would be
a humbling experience.
Please,
let me think about it.
What should I tell Sifu Lee?
Tell him...
I will speak with him.
You see this?
This is the karate guy...
I'm doing the exhibition with.
A North American champion.
Very big shot.
But I got a little surprise
in store for this guy.
The one-inch punch.
What?
By the time I'm done
with this karate cat,
all his toadae will be
standing here with you.
Get up!
Well, hey, Mac.
Did you see the crowd outside?
Yeah, a lot of people.
Well, after today,
Kung Fu is gonna be big.
Bigger than the hula hoop.
Bigger than Coca Cola.
And I'm gonna be the CEO.
I don't doubt that.
So,
you talked to Wong?
Yes.
Did he say what he's doing here?
He said he's here to restore
the balance to his soul.
How's he gonna do that?
By washing dishes
at the Jackson Café.
So, the great Wong Jack Man
screwed up.
That's what they do,
the old heads at the Shaolin.
They make you humble yourself
when you screw up.
He says he's gonna be here? Yes.
Good.
Then it starts and ends today.
And please welcome.
Wing Chun master, Bruce Lee!
Come on, Bruce Lee!
How you doing, Vince?
I'm good.
How long have
been knowing karate?
Twenty-two years.
Almost as long
as I've been alive.
Try not to hurt me.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is going to be a contest
between Kung Fu and Karate.
Now, Vince here
is a world champion.
So, I'm gonna have to ask him
not to be so tough on me.
That was just a lucky shot.
I'll go a little bit
slower this time.
How about this, Vince?
I tell you when it's coming,
so you can show your boys
how to block it.
You ready?
Here it comes.
It's coming.
One...
two, three.
That's not working.
How about this, Vince?
Now, you show me what you got.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the famous
Wong Jack Man,
master of the Shaolin temple.
He's come all the way to San
Francisco to see what I can do.
Well, Master Wong,
are you satisfied?
Yes.
Thank you.
Aren't you gonna share
some Shaolin wisdom with us?
I have seen what you can do.
I have also seen
what you cannot do.
What is that supposed to mean?
Whatever you choose it to mean.
Don't give me your Shaolin
navel-gazing, say what you mean.
Your technique is impressive.
Indeed, it is almost perfect.
But it has one limitation.
Oh, really?
What?
You.
You fight from ambition
and pride.
But you do not fight
from your soul.
And no matter how great
the skill you possess,
nothing will make up for that.
You want to show me
what you mean.
How do you suggest I do that?
Fight me.
Right here and right now, so
everyone can see who has the limits.
No. Thank you.
That is not why I came here.
Then why did you come?
Because your student invited me.
And now, with your
permission, I will leave.
I told him to invite you.
I didn't think you'd
turn down a challenge
in front of all these people.
There's no need to fight.
You have made your limitation clear
in front of all these people.
You don't settle things
with words, Wong,
you settle them with your fists.
You're irrelevant, Wong.
I'm the future, you're the
past and you know it.
Why didn't you fight him?
I came here to subdue my
pride, not to indulge it.
But you can't walk away
from a public challenge.
You must know when it is necessary
to fight and when it is not.
And how...
how do you know
when it's necessary?
When you find something
so important,
you would give your life for it.
Then you must fight
to protect it.
When you have found that,
then perhaps, I would teach you.
So this is where you pray?
Yes.
For my family
and my ancestors...
that they'll all be safe.
Do you pray?
No.
Not even for your family?
I don't have a family.
No one?
Well, my Mom died
six months ago...
and my Dad's been
in prison for...
twelve years.
I'm sorry.
So, what do you do for fun?
You know, something for fun?
What would I do for fun?
Come on.
Come on. Come on,
come here.
CHILD 1; I got it.
CHILD 2; No, I got it.
I got it.
Okay. Yeah, good.
Then you watch the ball.
Swing through it just like this.
All right, good. Good, good.
Yep. That was good. That was good.
Like that?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna toss
a couple to you, ready?
Okay, you ready?
No.
Well, too bad.
Here it comes.
It's okay,
it's your first time ever.
I cannot do this.
Look, just focus.
Just watch the ball
all the way into the bat.
And keep your feet on the
ground when you swing.
Yes! Ready?
Oh, my God.
Is that better?
Um...
Yeah, it is.
It's amazing.
How do you do that?
This is the
pressure point for...
that area.
When the ball hit you,
your chi...
was disturbed.
My chi?
Yes.
This brings it
back into balance.
You will feel better now.
How do you know how to do that?
I studied Chinese medicine
at home.
I came here, hoping to
learn western medicine
at a great university.
It's my dream.
Wait, wait, wait!
You changed, didn't you?
Where is the money?
HOW bad?
He's in bad shape
but they said he'll live.
They busted up
his Mom's business.
Why?
Because he didn't want to pay
any boss any street tax.
This is Chenghu town,
that was dumb.
He did it because of you,
because you don't pay.
Well, that's different,
they don't bug me for it.
Why not?
When I was a kid in Hong Kong,
I got in fights all the time.
That's why my Dad
started me in Kung Fu.
When I was 16, I got in a fight
with this bad-ass kid at school.
I beat the crap out of him,
I broke his leg.
Turns out he's the son
of a Chenghu town boss.
They tried to put a contract on me, so
my Dad had to make a deal with them.
Sent me to America.
If they leave me alone,
I leave them alone.
Auntie Blossom has these
girls at China Gate.
Her Bi Nus they're called.
Yeah, I know.
The triads trick 'em into coming
to America, they never let 'em go.
I met one of them.
And I don't want that happening
to her, can you help me?
You want my advice?
Leave her alone.
What do you think I should do?
You should speak about this
with your Sifu.
Yeah, Sifu Lee said
she's not his problem.
Master Wong, I know
this is not your fight.
But, maybe they'll listen
to someone like you.
I'm sorry, Mr. McKee.
I told you...
I came to wash dishes.
Yeah, how long
you gonna do that?
Until they're all done.
But they're never gonna be done.
Precisely, like your Bi Nu.
My debt will never be repaid.
Every dirty dish
reminds me of my sin.
But I must wash them
until my soul is clean.
You know, Sifu Lee was right,
you are irrelevant.
You're supposed to be some great
teacher but all you care about
is yourself...
and penance.
Once...
in China,
there was a demonstration
match between myself...
and a Tai Chi master.
I knew I was losing...
in front of all the monks.
My pride overcame my discipline.
I used a very lethal kick
called the Mong Shan.
I nearly killed him.
He will never fight again.
You were just
defending yourself.
It was a demonstration!
Full contact was prohibited.
But I could not bear
to be humiliated.
You were just following
your style,
using your technique.
Technique is a trap.
Style is a prison.
That is what I tried to tell
Lee Jun-fan.
Kung Fu is meant to liberate.
If it's meant to liberate,
help me liberate Xiulan.
Are you prepared to risk
your life to help her?
Show me your attacks.
Right here?
Yes.
Attack me.
Okay.
You are expending
a great deal of energy,
I'm expending none.
Because you keep moving.
Because I don't want to be hit.
NOW, I will stand Still,
you punch me in the face.
I can't.
Why not?
'Cause you're Wong Jack Man,
I won't be able to hit you.
Lesson number one:
Know your opponent.
I promise I will not
defend myself.
Now, hit me.
No.
Why not?
'Cause it won't be fair.
Lesson number two:
Know yourself.
If you know yourself
and then you know your opponent,
you need not fear the outcome
of a thousand battles.
In those two principles
you have the whole of Kung Fu.
And the rest is just...
eternity.
Steve.
Haven't seen you in a while.
You've been training with Wong.
Yeah.
Are you tired of my method?
Master Wong is helping me
with Xiulan.
I'll be back.
A man can't have
two masters, Steve.
Good luck.
Good luck with the movie.
Yeah.
We're getting some
pretty good buzz on it.
There's even talk about me doing
Kung Fu for a new TV show,
The Green Hornet.
Master Wong thinks Kung Fu
doesn't belong on television.
Of course not.
He wants to keep it bottled up
in the monasteries in China.
That's why he doesn't
want to fight me.
He says it isn't necessary.
Face it, Mac.
Wong's afraid of me.
Sifu, thank you
for everything you taught me.
Don't mention it.
Oh, and Mac,
tell Wong...
if he ever works up the courage
I'll take him
on anywhere, anytime.
I told him to Kung Fu no more.
Send him back to school.
He accountant.
Do something useful
for a change.
I believe you are friend
of Wong Jack Man.
Mr. McKee.
What is it?
Auntie Blossom said
if you fight Sifu Lee
she'll release Xiulan Quan.
I wish I could help.
Xuilan's being held prisoner.
Look, I know you came here
to do your penance.
But she's being punished and she
hasn't done anything wrong.
You said you didn't want to be
baited into a fight with no purpose,
now you have the power to free
a completely innocent person.
Isn't that more important
than washing dishes?
This is not karate, ladies.
This is Kung Fu.
You're not training for the Olympics,
you're training for the street.
So what are you gonna do when a
bad-ass comes at you in an alley?
Kick ass. Kick ass.
Master Wong.
So what do you do when a bad ass
comes at you in an alley?
You must ask yourself...
why is he doing that.
He's fighting against the world.
He's on the wrong path.
But what you do?
The role of a Sifu
is to bring him into harmony
with the world...
and with himself.
Suppose he's trying to kill you.
Then I suppose...
you kick his ass.
But having done that, you offer him
the possibility of enlightenment.
If he refuses?
You have failed him.
And yourself.
Have you come to offer me
enlightenment?
I have come...
to accept your challenge.
I have been given permission
to speak with you.
Auntie Blossom
is gonna let you go.
Why?
I gave her something she wanted.
But what about the other girls?
They're like my sisters now.
Oh, hey, Mac.
Come on in.
I figure you're training
with Wong full time.
I am.
Well, a teacher
doesn't give you the truth,
he only points you to a truth that
you have to find out for yourself.
If I pointed you to Wong
Jack Man, that's okay.
Is he ready for the fight?
I think so.
Well, he better be.
Chinatown made me the heavy favorite,
they're like Wong in Hong Kong, but
he sets even money.
You gonna bet on the fight?
I don't know yet.
Wong's a saint, I'm the street.
Never bet against the street.
Master Wong wanted me to speak to
you about the terms of the fight.
You're his second now?
Yeah.
What does he want?
No kicks to the face
or groin, no eye-jabs.
Does he want to play
a Strauss Waltz, too?
In return he agrees
not to use his kicks.
I finally get it.
He must've used his Mon Shan on
some old head at the Shaolin.
No, not at the Shaolin.
At a demonstration
against a Tai Chi master.
Did he kill him?
Almost.
That'll get you washing dishes
at the Jackson Café.
You tell Wong this...
no rules, no holds barred.
No limits, you guys'd
kill each other.
Then he'll have to concede
before that.
You know, I was thinking
San Francisco Civic. Sell tickets,
pack the house, press, TV...
You said anywhere, anytime.
Where does he want to fight?
He's been training at a warehouse down
by the docks, he wants it up there.
Maybe I'll open a noodle stand,
make a few bucks on the side.
No more than a dozen witnesses.
Fair enough.
We'll do it his way.
But you let him know...
I want the results published
for the whole world to see.
We're so pleased how you
set this all up, Marge.
A promise is a promise.
How about a drink for my Dad?
Of course, please.
The handle in Hong Kong
just cracked 12 million.
You did a good job, Margie.
Thank you.
What would you like?
I am far from Shaolin...
except for that word.
Fight's tomorrow, Master Wong.
You should get some sleep.
Whatever happens,
your Xiulan will be free.
She doesn't want to leave
unless the other Bi Nu
are freed as well.
She's a very noble person.
You have chosen well.
But I must tell you,
Mr. McKee,
lam not fighting for her,
or for you,
or for myself,
Lee Jun-fan was correct.
He is the future.
He will bring Kung Fu
to the world.
I can see that now.
He has talent.
Great talent.
And ambition.
But what sort of Kung Fu
will he bring to the world,
an angry thing?
A hurtful thing?
A thing to be bought...
and sold?
Unless...
Unless what?
he's willing to be reborn.
You worried?
About tomorrow?
Aren't you?
Bruce, just protect yourself.
Seriously.
Wong's the one who
better protect himself.
I heard you nearly
killed Wang Biao.
You think you can kill me?
I have no desire to do so.
Then you just killed yourself.
Why don't you stand and fight?
Because that is what
you want me to do.
These stairs go nowhere.
Like your style.
You've reached the end.
So have you.
Now you begin
to exceed your limits.
What limits?
It's over.
Not unless you kill me.
Who won?
Which of you won?
MAN". We're holding $ 15,000,000
in bets and we cannot pay off.
You force one of them
to admit he lost.
You got 24 hours.
At least your face is okay.
We can still get you on TV.
It took too long.
But you beat him.
When he had me in a headlock...
he could've killed me.
What'd he say to you?
"Do you understand?"
Understand what?
Your soul belongs to others.
You better hope I get my winner.
Or your body
will belong to others.
There's no winner.
I know. I'll find the money
to help Xiulan buy her way out.
Too late.
There's more at stake now.
If you don't get me a winner
by midnight tonight...
Quan Xiulan will be sold
to one of the houses.
Mr. McKee.
I'm sorry...
if I have caused you trouble.
It seems I have caused
a great deal of trouble.
I came here in a spirit
of humility...
in an effort to disappear.
And now...
could I have failed
more completely?
You won that fight.
It is not that simple.
My intentions
was to teach Lee Jun-fan
that his attitude is irreverent
and his style is inadequate.
If, in defeating him, I drive
him further in that direction,
then I have lost.
If, in losing to him,
I change his direction,
then I have won.
Do you understand?
We're not in a monastery
in China.
This is America.
And in America
we have winners and losers,
and right now we need
a winner and a loser.
Life is not always that easy.
You know whose life
is not gonna be easy?
Xiulan. Let me declare
that you won, please.
It would make no difference.
Bruce Lee
will never accept that.
Then will you say that you lost?
I cannot.
Not until I know I have won.
What about Xiulan?
That is a matter
for you to decide.
Mac, I'm sorry, I just... I don't
think there's anything you can do.
I'm gonna go down there
and get her out myself.
Just right before lunch, she'll
be setting up the dining room...
What happens if those triads
guys see you first?
- Well, do you have any idea...
- Yeah, wait a few days, I...
She's not gonna be there
in a few days. Steve!
Steve!
What?
You're gonna
get yourself killed.
I thought you were a dishwasher.
I was promoted.
Why are we at war?
You are at war.
I am not.
Certainly seemed like
we were yesterday.
How may I help you?
I just got a call from one
of my students, Vinnie Wei,
Steve McKee's friend.
McKee's over at the China Gate, taking
on the Chenghu town by himself.
Over a girl.
He'll get killed.
Then, he has found something
he's willing to die for.
Wong Sifu,
whatever went down between us...
he's your toadae
and he's my toadae.
He's our responsibility.
Meaning what?
Meaning we shouldn't be
just standing here.
But you said...
it is not your problem.
What has changed?
Everything.
Hey, who won the fight?
Got an answer, asshole?
Yeah, I got an answer.
You're great advertisement
for our training.
I'm fine.
Please...
just stay here.
No, no, no.
No more trouble.
Beat it.
What do you say, Master Wong?
Shall we beat it?
Now we settle
unfinished business.
I'll make it quick.
Did I ever show you
my one-inch punch, Tony?
One-inch punch?
You must teach me that one.
Hey!
This is a scene you don't see
in the chopsocky.
The one where the Kung Fu cats
get their heads blown off.
Ah!
Hey guys.
You really need an elevator
in this dump.
Where's Xiulan?
She's not here.
Do you think I would leave my
trump card lying on the table?
You want the girl,
I want a decision.
Now, who won?
If we answer...
you will set Quan Xiulan free?
That was the arrangement.
Then I admit that I lost.
Lee Jun-fan
is the winner.
Do you accept that?
No.
Are you kidding me?
You release all the girls.
No more Bi Nu in Chinatown.
All right. Deal.
Sonny, put the word out
that Bruce Lee is the winner.
And release the girls.
Do you remember me, asshole?
I remember breaking your leg.
So do I.
Was that the Mon Shan?
I don't know, you tell me.
Vinnie.
Hey, I got these for you.
You steal 'em from next door?
Two doors down.
What are you so happy about?
Well, I bet a thousand bucks
on Sifu and I cleaned up.
Who'd you bet on?
Master Wong.
I told you, never bet
against the street.
Sifu.
Take it easy, Mac.
I can imagine how you feel.
Actually I can't, I never
had my ass kicked before.
What is it like?
It hurts.
But all the girls were let go.
Thank you, both of you.
Hey, I took a grand off of my
Mom's bank account to bet on you,
and I better put it back
before she finds out.
Glad you're not dead.
Do you need anything?
No, I'm good.
But I do have to ask.
Do you really think
you won that fight?
Yes.
Why?
Wong showed me...
I had reached
a limit of my style.
I was only fighting myself.
He made me realize I had to
create a whole new style.
You know how water
takes the shape of anything
you put it in,
but it stays strong and pure?
Now that's gonna be my style.
Cool.
I was planning on being a star,
but I think I'd rather be
a legend instead.
Like Wong Jack Man.
Will you be back, Master Wong?
Yes, I think so.
There's much to learn here
and perhaps some to teach.
Will you still be here
when I return?
Maybe.
I guess we'll have
to see how things go.
Mr. McKee...
thank you.
Without you,
I think I may never have
finished washing dishes.
Master Wong, Sifu Lee understood
what you wanted to teach him.
So you did win that fight.
Kung Fu must be given
to the world.
Bruce Lee will do that.
And if he does not...
I may have to come back
and kick his ass again.