(skateboard scraping)
(crickets chirping)
- Dad?
- I can't stay here anymore.
(upbeat music)
♪ I don't want
to give you away ♪
♪ I was hoping that you
would stay you would stay ♪
- So who's Paul?
- He's the Headmaster.
- What kind of school is it?
- Private.
- How do you know him?
- College.
He dated your mom before I did.
After he forgave us we
became very good friends.
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ How to move on ♪
♪ You were covered with ♪
♪ Black and gray ♪
♪ Waiting for your
chance to run away ♪
♪ Run away run away ♪
♪ Left all alone ♪
♪ I wanna know ♪
- You know, I gotta
tell you, it's about
the fastest deal I've
ever done in my life.
You know, with a
house, most people
want to look every which way
up and down, round and round.
Not you guys, huh?
You come you look, you
like it you take it.
Super fast, huh?
(cell phone ringing)
- How long you been up?
- Awhile.
Yeah Paul dropped off
the box of clothes
from the lost and found, I guess
just until we can get
you some new ones.
- Do I wear a uniform?
- It's a fancy place.
(upbeat music)
- Please don't tell
me this is all boys.
(upbeat music)
- [Paul] Okay Wes,
we got books check,
schedule check,
unacceptable shoes check.
- We'll go shopping
right after school.
- Great.
So, you pick a sport yet?
- Yeah, I'm not really
a big sports guy.
- Well, I'm afraid
it's mandatory.
This time of year
your choices are
football, fencing
and cross country.
- [Wes] Okay, thanks,
Mr. Abernac.
- [Paul] Good luck, soldier.
- I don't know how to
thank you for this, Paul.
- No need.
How you holding up?
- Fine.
- Well hopefully a fresh start
will do you both some good.
- I'm sure it will.
(piano music)
- Yes, yes, the first
day hork, gotta love it.
- Alright, alright I'm seeing.
I'm seeing some taquitos,
some zucchini...
You really like
zucchini, huh, new kid?
- I see some jello there.
- That's enough forensic
analysis, gentleman.
- Gotta respect the first
day hork. (laughing)
- Welcome to cross country.
- How was cross country?
- Oh it was, whatever.
Won't this kind of
remind you of mom?
- It's not that I don't
want to be reminded.
I just want to have
some control over it.
I want you to have the car.
- What do you mean?
- Kid your age aught to
have your own set of wheels.
- How are you gonna get around?
- Previous tenant just
left it behind I guess.
- You know Dad,
I've never seen you
ride a bike in my entire life.
- Well I assure I am
perfectly capable of it.
- See you there.
(horn honking)
- [Driver] Ass hat!
- Sorry.
- God.
- Aw man, you got
Aminheimer for trig?
Better get some nose plugs, guy
smells like a dying warthog.
- Hey Mason, here
comes the circus.
- You know I always expect like
12 midgets to get
out of that thing.
- There's one.
(mimics circus music)
- Hey Goober, when do
the elephants get here?
- Aw man, my
favorite time of day.
Behold the muff truck.
- How come we don't get to
take classes at their school?
- Because we'd never come back.
Good morning. ladies.
- [Girl] Hey Mason.
- [Mason] Hey Kim.
- Hey yourself.
- What's up Missy?
- [Missy] Hey Tommy.
(acoustic piano music)
- Hey Lacey.
(guys laughing)
Shut up.
(speaking in foreign language)
- And the area of this circle
of course is Pi R squared.
And then multiply by
the height to give us
the volume of the
cylinder right?
Any questions? Yes?
- What's with the belt?
- That's just something I do.
- Freak.
(bell rings)
- And it looks like
we're out of time.
You have the
homework and it's on
the website if
you need to check.
(door shuts)
- So how goes it so far?
- Great, seem like nice boys.
- They're not.
They're spoiled little snots
who won't have to work
a day in their lives
unless daddy runs off
with the secretary and takes
all the money with him.
Just kidding, of course.
Bill, I don't want to
overstep my bounds but
have you had the chance to
talk to anybody about Jeanie?
- I mean,
you know once in a while
call my brother or--
- I mean a professional,
'cause I happen to know a guy.
Got a flawless reputation,
well respected.
Our health plan will
cover everything
so it won't cost you a dime.
- I don't know.
- Okay look, this
really isn't about you.
You see as long as I
keep up the appearance
of caring about my
staff it maintains
my carefully crafted
image of being a good guy.
- Got it, that makes sense.
- Yeah I knew
you'd understand so
good idea, terrible idea?
- I guess probably a good idea.
- I couldn't help
but notice that those
who didn't do well on the test
are also behind
on their homework.
So if you want to
improve your grade please
I would suggest you pay
attention to your assignments.
Make sense, right? Thank you.
I thought you would agree.
(door shutting)
You know I like to think
that I'm a good teacher.
But two students
working together
can sometimes be quite helpful.
How would you like to be Miss
Westmans's homework partner?
- Yeah sure.
- Lacy?
- Yeah.
- Thank you, you can go now.
- Okay so what's up with
that Lacy Westman girl?
- The Princess of Darkness.
- You mean my future wife?
- Dude she would have sex with
you and then eat your head.
- She going out with anybody?
- Yeah Mason.
- They are not going out.
- Oh really well what
would you call it?
- Using her whenever
he feels like it.
- Mrs. Oselle asked me to
be her homework partner.
- Shut up.
- Dude why the hell doesn't
stuff like that happen to me?
- Because you're nasty
and objectionable at
almost every level.
Oh man, we gotta catch up.
You're not gonna
mind if we smoke you?
- Go for it.
- Sucks when the little
guy beats you, doesn't it?
- Good luck with Lacy.
(doorbell rings)
- Hi, I'm Lacy's
homework partner.
- [Lacy] Mom, I got it.
- You didn't say anything
about a homework partner.
- Mom, I have
a homework partner.
Come on.
- You ride horses?
- Look we don't
have to make cordial
chit chat or become
besties okay.
The only reason
I'm doing this is
she said she'd give
me extra credit,
which I need, because if I fail
then I'd have to do
Junior year over again
and I'd rather put my
head in a wood chipper.
- Okay.
- You can use that chair.
I'm sure you've
heard I'm a kind of
freak, slut, basket
case, but I'm afraid
any hope you had of us
having wild gymnastic sex
are destined to be frustrated.
- Gotcha.
- My friends used to
call the version of me
before I met Jeanie
PJ for pre-Jeanie and
the person I became after we
met was AJ for after Jeanie.
Apparently PJ was this
kind of lifeless lump
and AJ was a great, fun guy.
- How long was it between
her diagnoses and death?
- 61 days.
- I'm sorry.
So Bill, neurons, neurons that
fire together wire together.
So when we're happy the
neurons in our brain
align in way that
tends to sustain
that feeling of well being.
The same idea also
applies to depression.
Like what you'd expect
during a period of grief.
Now grief is completely
normal of course.
But a year or more outside
of a grief inducing vent,
I like to see my patients in
more of an emergent posture.
The good news is that
we have a battery
of medications available to us
to help kick start you
in the right direction.
I'd like to write
you a prescription
for something called Lexapro.
It will boost the levels
of serotonin in your brain.
And it's likely that you'll feel
a little bit better by
the next time we meet.
Are you comfortable with that?
- If you think it'll help.
- You hungry, sweetie?
I can fix you a plate.
- You better get
it while you can.
When it comes to your
mom's macaroni salad
I wait for no man or boy.
- [Wes] So Mom tell us
why of all the things
you could have done
on your birthday
you chose something
as boring as a picnic.
- Because a boring picnic
let's me have my two favorite
people in the whole wide
world all to myself.
Just being me here makes me feel
so very, very very happy.
- Here it comes.
Another Jeanie Palet spontaneous
outburst of affection.
- I just can't help it.
(all laughing)
- [Wes] Okay okay,
make it stop please.
(somber music)
- You hungry, sweetie?
I can fix you a plate.
(somber music)
Okay you ready?
Rules for Wes, part
two, number one.
You will remember that
among life's many joys
it can also be very
hard but just know
it has nothing at
all to do with you.
You, Wes are a
bright shining star.
I'm sorry, can we just stop?
I just love you so much.
Don't ever forget that.
(somber music)
- You guys hear about
Taber's party this weekend?
- Please, it's an
exercise in futility.
I just want to touch
a girl, like this.
- Stop that immediately.
- You know what you
really need, Goob?
You need a girl
you can look up to.
(all laughing)
- Oh, speaking of which,
how's it going with Lacy?
- Dude I swear if
you transfer in
from North San Fran-wherever
and bag Lacy Westman
I'm gonna be so pissed.
- Yeah I really don't think
you need to worry about that.
- Dude, you're her tutor.
You're an authority figure.
Chicks love that.
- Think that may be your
fantasy Raf not hers.
- Seriously though,
what's the deal?
- I don't know man,
there is no deal.
I mean as far as I can
tell she hates my guts.
- [Gooby] Yeah man,
welcome to my world.
(speaking in foreign language)
- You know, it's funny,
you French are supposed
to be so picky about your coffee
but I see you sucking down a
lot of Folgers here, young lady.
- Well, we have to
make do don't we?
- Listen, I got some
primo box seats
for the LA Clips Friday night.
What do you say you an me go out
we get a couple of cadillac--
- Listen I'm very sorry
but I have to discuss
a student right now so
perhaps we can speak later.
Thank you.
Excuse me?
Sorry I know we
haven't officially met,
but if you could
pretend to talk to me
for a minute I would
very much appreciate it.
- [Bill] Okay.
- I'm Carine Oselle.
- Hi, Bill Palet.
- You know, I don't know if
you have that expression,
but in France sometimes we say
better a stranger
than someone you know.
- Oh yeah, I think our
expression is anyone but him.
- Your son is in
my class, French.
- Yes.
- He's very advanced.
- Well Wes's mother was fluent.
- Was she French?
- No.
Michigander actually but
when she was a little girl
she heard that French
was a romance language.
And she thought
if she learned it
her life would be romantic.
- Nice, and was it?
- I guess it was yes.
(party music playing)
- Darwinism is so depressing.
If you just so happen to be born
with the traits
girls deem desirable
then your chin deep in the booty
but if not then your
left out on the fringe
hoping that one of the alpha
males falls off a cliff
or gets eaten by a saber
tooth or some shit.
- Don't forget about being rich.
- That's very true,
instant short cut no doubt.
You know what screw this.
I'm going home so I can study,
get into a good college, get
a good job, and get rich.
It's my only hope at this point.
See you later, masturbator.
- Later.
(party music playing)
- Okay that should be...
(speaking in foreign language)
- Should this be...
Please leave.
- Look I don't want--
- Just wait outside.
- [Annabelle] She's
in trouble, isn't she?
- What do you mean?
- For failing French.
- She's not gonna fail.
- You're Wes.
- You're?
- Annabelle.
- There's a girl at my old
school named Annabelle.
We called her Banana Bell.
- That's what Lacy calls me.
- Can I call you that?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because it's a privilege
you haven't earned.
- No one really makes friendly
conversation in
this house do they?
(door lock clicks)
- That means you can go back in.
(door shuts)
- Promise me you
won't tell anybody.
- Okay.
- No I need to hear you promise.
- Promise.
- Yo Palet, you
realize it's been like
three weeks since
you last upchucked.
- Oh look at Wes,
growing up so fast.
- Wes, can I talk to
you for a moment?
Hi, I just wanted to ask how
things are going with Lacy.
- They're fine.
- Do you think it's helping?
- Truth is Mrs. Oselle,
I really don't know.
She doesn't say much.
- I see.
Just wanted to check in.
Thank you, Wes.
(speaking in foreign language)
Mrs. Westman, may
I speak with you?
How are you?
- Fine.
- Working with
Wes, is it helpful?
- Yeah.
- Good.
You know, Lacy, in a lot of ways
you remind me of me
when I was your age.
I think we should stick together
with all these crazy boys
running around right?
So tell me.
How are you?
Really.
(somber music)
Come here.
- I'm sorry.
- No no no, don't apologize.
It's good to cry.
Much better than keeping
all that crap inside, right?
What time you have
to be back to school?
- 2:15.
- That's good.
That gives us a little time if,
if you'd like to talk a bit.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because I like you and
because I think maybe
you don't have
anyone else to tell.
- Hey.
- Just doing some prep work.
There's too much
shade in the back so
plant the garden here, put
in some lettuce and beans.
- You okay, Dad?
- Yeah.
I don't know, maybe a little
out of it I guess.
Should probably tell the
doc these happy pills
are more like spacey pills.
What a drag your old man is,
huh?
Even on drugs, I'm no fun.
- Look, I really don't need you
to be Mr. Smiley
Face all the time.
- Be nice to get a break from
Mr. Droopy though, wouldn't it?
Tomatoes, lots of
tomatoes, of course.
- Right.
Well Mommatoes technically.
- Still the only
person I've ever known
that eats them like apples.
- Right.
Remember in sixth grade
I got in that fight
'cause someone called
her Hottie Tomatie.
- Yeah, you stuck up for her.
- Yeah.
- She'd be proud of you, Wes.
Making the adjustment to
a whole new everything.
- So exactly how much of
this are you digging up?
- I was thinking all of it.
- All of it, okay.
Well let's get to it then,
right?
- Feel free.
- What?
- Did you say something
to Mrs. Rousou about me?
- No.
Well she did ask about you?
- What'd she say?
- She asked how all
of this was going.
- What'd you say?
- I said I don't know.
- Why would you say that?
- 'Cause I don't, I guess.
You mad?
- Why would I me mad?
- I don't know.
Some people really
don't need a reason.
She say something to you?
- Maybe.
- You know,
whenever I talk to you
it kind of feels like
I'm on some dumb cop show
and you're like
the surly suspect
who doesn't want to
give up any information.
- She was just being really
nice and I was wondering
if you had said something
about what you saw.
- I promised I wouldn't.
(knocking on door)
- Yeah?
- Dinner time.
- I'm not hungry.
- [Barbara] You are
hungry and you're eating.
I'm not raising an anorexic.
- She said you are
hungry, you're eating,
and she's not
raising an anorexic.
- Yeah I heard her.
Mom Wes is here.
- [Barbara] So, he
eats doesn't he?
- Well this should
be interesting.
- Sorry for the complete
absence of flavor, Wes.
It was Lacy's
fathers turn to cook.
- Lacy, why don't you
tell your mother that
paying the mortgage,
credit cards, tuition,
every other bill that
comes in to this house,
it doesn't leave me much time
to cultivate my culinary skills.
- Why don't you
tell her yourself?
- So Wes, are your
parents still together?
- Barbara and Davis are
getting a divorce but
on the advice of council
neither is willing to move out.
- My mom passed away last year.
- I'm sorry to hear that, Wes.
- I'm sorry too.
The difference is
I actually mean it.
- Tell me about the belt.
- That's a Jeanie thing.
She used to tease me because
my belt would kind of
drift over that way
as the day went on.
Said I should just
start out the day
with it where it
was gonna end up.
So one day I just
started out with it there
and made her laugh.
She said it was
only fitting because
I was a little off
center to begin with.
- She had a good sense of humor.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So I find that grieving spouses
usually fall into
one of two groups.
One describes
their loved one as
someone who filled
a void in them.
The other describes
them as someone who
added a dimension to the
person they already were.
Which would you say
best describes you?
- It's both.
- Which would you say you favor?
- All of the above.
- Okay, fair enough.
I'm just looking for
something to help us move on.
- From what?
- From your wife, Bill.
The only way you're
going to feel better
is if we figure out someway
for you to let her go.
You recognize that don't you?
- Yes.
- Okay.
As for the Lexapro finding
the right medication
can sometimes be a trial
and error process so
I'm gonna switch you
something called Cymbalta
see if that works
better for you.
- Fine.
- [Oselle] Bill?
- Hello.
- What a coincidence.
Back home I'm used to
running into people
but here it always
gives me a surprise.
- [Cashier] Next.
- Excuse me.
Hi Palet, P-A-L-E-T.
- $10.
- Bill I'm sorry to
bother you like this but
I have a favor to ask.
You know Coach Keith,
big muscles small brain.
- Extra large coffee mug.
- [Oselle] Yes,
ridiculous that mug.
- More of a jug really.
- I think you could
actually bathe a cat in it.
Anyways he asked
me out for Friday
and I'm desperate for
a reason to say no
but I'm afraid I'm
running out of excuses.
- Oh so you want me
to be your excuse?
- Would you mind terribly?
- No that's, sure that's fine.
- Unless you're busy of course.
- No I'm not busy ever.
I generally eat in the evenings.
We could eat together.
- Yes we can eat together,
that sounds very nice.
- Great okay, I'll
see you tomorrow.
- Yes see you tomorrow.
- Alright number four.
- I have no idea
how to say that.
(speaking in foreign language)
Do I have to say it like that?
- Like what?
- Like I'm an
effeminate French man
who's in love with himself?
- Oh that, yeah yeah, you do.
You have to say it like
you're an effeminate
French man who's in
love with himself.
- Then I've got the perfect
homework partner don't I?
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
- Why do you do that?
- [Lacy] Do what?
- Your arm.
- 'Cause I'm happy,
well adjusted,
and really excited
about my future.
Of course I'm a
little upset that
I didn't make
cheerleader this year but
there's always next
year and I feel like
if I work really really hard
it could definitely
happen for me.
- So you're telling me
nothing has happened at all.
- Nope.
- You do realize what
a fail this is right?
Not to mention how personally
disappointing this is for me.
You've been with this
girl for over 10 hours.
That's more time than Goober's
spent with a girl
his entire life.
- Hey Palet, tops on
your strategy man.
- What strategy?
- You know, start off
with the psycho whore
and work you way up from there.
Yeah I just hope you're
banging her by now.
Trust me it doesn't take half
the work you're putting in.
- That's the other thing
I hate about evolution.
Why does the dominant male
always have to be a dick?
What does persistence
dickishness
have to do with
furthering the species?
- Hey Mason.
(loud crashing)
(all talking at once)
- [Paul] Break it
up, break it up.
Get off, break it up,
come on break it up.
That's it, that's it,
that's it, break it off.
- Easy easy, boys.
- [Paul] What the hell's
the matter with you guys?
So which one of you Nobel
Lureates started this?
- That depends, sir ,do you
mean verbally or physically?
- Shut up Raffi!
I don't really care
who started this.
I already talked
to the other three.
And if there is so much
as glancing contact
between any of you knuckleheads
both parties will be expelled.
Is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
- Expelled, as in gee why
didn't I get in to college?
Oh right, I got expelled.
Now I can spend the
rest of my sad life
selling mangos from the
side of the freeway.
In the meantime welcome
to disciplinary probation.
You'll also be serving weekend
detention on litter patrol.
Everybody happy?
- Yes, sir.
- Goober.
- Well sir, according
to the honor code
we're supposed to be
honest at all times.
But if I told you I
was happy I'd be lying.
I'm very happy.
- Be gone.
(crickets chirping)
- The truth is I
always imagined that
I would be fantastically
good at marriage.
- You weren't?
- Well it began pretty good and
we found out I could
not have children and
it wasn't so good after
that so I became a teacher.
If you can't be a mother
to one be a mother to many.
How long were you married?
- 33 years.
- Practically a lifetime.
- Well I guess so but
never felt that way.
- What an amazing thing
to be able to say.
(speaking in foreign language)
We're talking about
the food, but you know.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Okay so I obviously
didn't understand
more than two words of
that but this is a little--
- Awkward.
I mean I love the
French but one thing
that drives me crazy is how
they babble on endlessly
as if anyone around who
doesn't speak French
is simply a piece of furniture.
- Well I do have
more in common with
a La-Z-boy chair
than I like to admit.
- I am that way too.
I mean give me a nice cozy
chair and a good book.
And you'll need a tow
truck to get me to move.
- So I guess we
have that in common.
General unwillingness to move
unless absolutely necessary.
- Sometimes I look
at those little fish
you know stuck to the side of
the aquarium, you know the...
And I'm like maybe it's
not such a bad life.
- Really, a sucker
fish, not a bad life?
- No, I mean, okay of
course it's bound
to become a little monotonous,
but think about it.
How stressful can it be?
- Well that is
definitely a valid point.
- I mean you have only one job.
(both laughing)
Do you like it?
- Yes excellent, very good.
- I can do a guppy, a guppy.
- [Bill] Oh guppies are fun.
(kettle whistling)
- Hey.
- When'd you get back?
- A little while ago.
- So, how'd the big date go?
- It went well.
- Well?
Is that a smile I'm seeing?
- She's very nice.
What can I say, maybe these
happy pills are working.
- That'd be good, right?
- Yeah, sure.
How's the running going?
- I'm starting to
kinda like it actually.
Just wish I was a
little better but...
- Maybe that's something
we can work on.
- We, like me and you?
- Yeah like, doctor Rollins
said I should starts exercising.
Maybe we could run together.
- Yeah, yeah, if you want.
- Okay, now what
about this fight?
- Yeah, no, I know Dad,
it's just,
God this guy he's such a, he's a
what's that thing
Mom used to call
someone she like
really couldn't stand?
- Dingus.
- A dingus, Dad.
This guy I mean he's so much
worse than a dingus it's crazy.
- Okay, but
that doesn't make it
a smart thing to do.
- I know, yeah, it's
just it was stupid.
Okay.
Hey Dad, do you mind if kind
of throw some advice your way
if you're gonna
start dating women?
You gotta lose
those tighty whiteys.
- Why?
- Well because it's
practically a universal law
that no man has ever
looked good in man panties.
- I'm not sure I
agree with that.
- Well it's just the thing is
it's not really an opinion.
It's kind of a fact.
It's like you can't like
disagree with it, you know.
- [Bill] I don't know.
- Don't start, don't start with
that Dad please stop, okay.
Dad I'm begging you
stop that immediately.
- It's too late it's started,
once it's started--
- Yeah yeah ,alright,
that's my cue.
Alright, night.
See you tomorrow.
- Pleasant dreams.
(upbeat music)
- You always run this fast?
- This is not fast.
- Okay, what about breaks?
You take breaks?
- Nope, no breaks.
- This is just not gonna work.
- You okay?
- Yeah yeah, go ahead.
- You sure?
- Go go go, enjoy.
- [Wes] Alright.
- Oh, good Lord.
(upbeat music)
Hey hey, how do you like this?
Come on, Usain Bolt,
let's pick up the pace.
- Dad you're on a bike, okay.
- Yeah, I'm also
way older than you.
What the heck?
Are you trying to ditch me?
Come on, pick it up.
Pick it up, pick it up.
(knocking on door)
- Hey jackass.
Starting a fight
to defend my honor.
Like you're some doofus knight
from medieval fantasy land.
- He's a dick.
- Your a dumb ass who's lucky
to still have all his teeth.
- Where are you going?
- [Lacy] You'll see.
- What is it?
- Find out.
- Are you serious?
- I'm trying to reduce
your dork factor.
Do you have any idea
how ridiculous you look
driving around without
a passenger seat?
- This is awesome.
I mean,
where'd you even find it?
- Some creepy old
man on Craiglist.
You totally owe me.
- Yeah I do.
Thank you.
- Awkward.
- I was gonna hug you.
- You're allowed.
(acoustic guitar music)
- [Wes] Shit.
- [Lacy] Watch your language.
- Why? You say
shit all the time?
- Shut up.
- Wes what's taking so long?
- The holes don't line up.
♪ Down this road ♪
♪ Towards the light ahead
that leads us straight into ♪
- Are you sure this
isn't driver's seat?
- No.
♪ Full speed ahead just
like you always said ♪
♪ Turn the page ♪
♪ Welcome to the golden age ♪
♪ Go live your life ♪
♪ For the rest of
us who can't keep up ♪
♪ And got left behind ♪
♪ Say it loud say it long ♪
♪ Say it for
everyone who told you ♪
♪ Never sing this song ♪
♪ Welcome to the golden age ♪
♪ Go live your life ♪
♪ For the rest of
us who can't keep up ♪
♪ And got left behind ♪
- [Raffi] I'll slice and
dice you, you vile little orc.
- Why do they call
it litter patrol
if they never pick up litter?
- It's more about being
prepared to pick it up.
- [Annabelle] That's litter.
- Well he likes to give
it a head start first.
- Fine, I'll do it.
- Thanks for coming.
It's a lot less boring.
- You mean you don't
enjoy homoerotic
jousting with your buddies?
- You know, I'm just not quite
as good at it as they are.
- I seriously doubt that.
- So Mr. Abernac, he's having
a birthday dinner for may dad.
And I figured you
know after all the
amazing help that I've
given you in French
that maybe you could come.
- Oh my God, did
you just invite me
to a calculus teacher's
birthday party?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
- I don't know, Wes, I mean,
I'm a big girl and all but
that just sounds batshit crazy.
You know math teachers you
get them drunk and then
next thing you know
they're playing
spin the compass and
hide the protractor.
- [Raffi] The girl is mine.
- [Gooby] Nay, all young
wenches belong to me.
- So is that a yes or?
- A yes I suppose,
if you can promise me
I'll live through it.
- Everything was
delicious, Missy.
- [Bill] Yes, very
good thank you.
- I'm glad, everyone deserves
a good dinner for
their birthday.
- Speaking of, one more.
- Ah.
- Wes, I just gave
the man bookends.
Why in the world would you
try to compete with that?
- Ah.
- Those are hot.
- [Wes] They are.
- Wes is trying to
convert me to boxers.
- Bill please tell me you're
not still wearing grippers.
- I guess I am.
Thank you, Son.
- Your welcome, Father.
- Well done, Wes.
Now if you could just do
something about the belt.
- No no no, don't lose the belt.
- Are you kidding?
It looks like my calculus
teacher downs three shots
of vodka before he gets
dressed every morning.
- Well it's actually gin, Paul.
- Excuse me, but a man
without quirks is boring.
- She's right.
Everyone's entitled to a
few little weirdnesses.
- Like father, like son.
- Excuse me, weirdnesses?
- Hello, backward car seat.
- Hello, you're the one
who gave that to me.
- Okay, pretending
to be a pirate.
- Okay that, that wasn't me.
- Whatever, effeminate
French accent.
- There's a lesson here, Wes.
If you expose your
vulnerabilities
to a woman, you
will be eviscerated.
They are a ruthless
cold blooded gender.
- Okay it has nothing to do with
the temperature
of our blood okay.
Men are just afraid
of strong women.
They think because
we stand up to them
that means we don't
like them when
half the time it means
it the exact opposite.
- You know, Bill, for
such a mild mannered guy
you sure attract
some feisty women.
I remember being with Jeanie
one night at some bar.
And this giant lecherous redneck
would just not leave us alone.
And finally she said you're
bound to have better luck
at the Natural History Museum.
There's a few gals in there at
the neanderthal
exhibit who would think
you're the greatest
thing that walks upright
and talks at the same time.
(all laughing)
- She did have a way with words.
Thank you for the ride.
- Thanks for inviting me.
Your wife sounds like
a very special person.
I cannot think how big
a hole must be left
after losing someone like that.
- Thank you for saying that.
I actually bought
you some flowers
but then I forget
I left them inside.
- Is that some kind of sneaky
way to invite me to come in?
- No, no, I--
No, but, would you
like to come in?
(crickets chirping)
- [Wes] You know
I cannot believe
you said I like
pretending to be a pirate.
- Please, if I wasn't there you
totally would have
been doing it.
- Yeah okay, it's probably true.
- So what's the deal
with your dad and Carine?
I mean she's clearly
got a crush on him.
- Yes.
- What?
- I don't know.
He tries to fake it but
inside he's still just nuked.
- You both must be.
- You know, for a long time
we barely even talked.
We didn't go anywhere,
we didn't do anything.
Then one day I just
started doing stuff again.
I kind of felt bad about it.
Like maybe he'd think I
didn't deserve as much.
That wasn't it,
I just can't think about
it all the time you know.
All that does is just
makes it even worse.
(crickets chirping)
What?
- I don't want to do that.
- Why not?
- Because if we do
then you tell somebody
and then they tell somebody
and then pretty soon
the whole school will find out
and then it just
becomes another episode
of let's drink crappy
beer and make out.
High school bullshit
that doesn't mean
anything to anybody.
- So you think I'm the guy that
goes to school and
tells everybody.
- No, I don't know maybe.
- I'm not.
- Yeah, I know I'm just.
- Just what?
- I'd like this to
be better than that.
Look, I like you, okay.
You're gonna make
me say it out loud.
I'd like to go slow.
- Okay.
So.
What you're saying is
that you like me so much
that you don't want to kiss me.
- Something like that.
- Okay.
I mean at least
not again tonight.
- That's right.
- But,
maybe,
possibly,
later.
- Yes Wesley, maybe
possibly later.
- That's all I needed to know.
- I like what you've
done with the place.
- Yes, thank you.
I think it's called
negligent minimalism.
- I hear it's all the
rage in German prisons.
(both laughing)
Would you excuse me?
- Of course, yeah.
- [Carine] Bill.
- Yes.
(piano music)
- [Dr. Rollins]
Was being with her
something you wanted to happen?
- Yes.
- [Dr. Rollins] Why?
- I thought it might
take my mind of things.
- Did it?
- No.
- You feel like you were
doing something wrong?
- Yes.
- [Dr. Rollins] Why?
- Because it just made
me think of Jeanie.
- Think what exactly.
- That Carine
could never be her.
- No one is replaceable, Bill.
That doesn't mean
someone else can't play
a special role in your life.
Listen, we'll try
a new medication.
And an augmenter
on top of it but
I'm worried one of the
things holding you back
is your own belief
that feeling better
would be a betrayal of Jeanie.
- I don't think that's the case.
- The larger point I'm
trying to make here is that
to have a chance
at feeling better
you have to want to feel better.
- Dad?
(contemplative music)
Dad?
- Yeah.
- [Wes] You okay?
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
It's pretty late.
- I said I'm fine, Wes.
(contemplative music)
I just need a little air.
I'll come in soon.
- [Wes] Okay.
(contemplative music)
(cell phone buzzes)
(parents yelling in distance)
- [Barbara] Do you have
any idea how you sound?
God forbid you spend
one single moment
thinking about
anybody but yourself!
- [Davis] Exactly what
I'm talking about.
It's just because
I don't believe
that my life has to
be a living hell.
That's make me wrong.
- [Barbara] Sometimes
you have to be an adult.
(pebbles hitting glass)
- Hey we just picked
up a shit ton of beer.
What do you say?
(loud rock music)
Didn't I tell you?
The girl can drink.
- Give me another.
- There we go, yes,
there we go, drink up.
She's outdrinking you, Rios.
(all talking at once)
- [Boy] Come on Rios.
- Come on, juice
box, what's this?
(loud rock music)
- Come on, man, let's go.
- Rios, bring him back here.
(loud rock music)
(Lacy crying)
(piano music)
- Hi, it's Lacy.
I don't understand
what I'm doing.
(piano music)
- You're a smart wonderful girl.
Just because people around
you want to hurt each other
doesn't mean you should
do the same to yourself.
You understand that, don't you?
- Hey man I'm just
trying to understand
whether or not you're with her.
- I promised I
wouldn't talk about it.
- So that means
there's most certainly
something to talk about?
See that right there.
I knew it.
How often do you
get to see this?
True happiness.
Don't you think that's great?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Nothing. I agree it's cool.
- [Rios] That was great.
- [Boy] Yeah who we
picking up next time?
- [Rios] Whoever Mason
wants, right Mase?
- [Lacy] Hey.
- I'm not doing the
homework thing anymore.
- [Lacy] Wait, why?
- I don't know, Lacy,
why don't you ask Mason?
(door slams)
- Wes, wait.
Look, I don't know
what you heard but--
- [Wes] Yeah, I heard enough.
- Hey, well, I'm sure
that was bullshit.
- [Wes] Yeah, right.
- Don't laugh at me.
- How can I not?
At first you tell
me you're afraid
I'll talk about us and
then what do you do?
You go out with the one
guy who's guaranteed
to tell the whole
God damn school.
- We didn't go out,
it wasn't like that.
- Then what was it?
- It was just an excuse
to get drunk and--
- And what?
- And I don't know,
it was just stupid.
- Stupid high school bullshit?
- Yeah.
- Like you wouldn't do with
me but you will that jackass.
Who do you do all
this for anyway?
- Do what?
- What you do with Mason,
what you do to yourself
'cause it sure as hell
isn't doing you any good.
So who's it for huh?
Is it for your parents?
'Cause I'm pretty
sure they're too busy
hating each other
to give a shit.
- Well, I'm sorry
I can't be like you
and just pretend like
nothing bothers me.
I guess I'm just one of
those unfortunate people
who's actually affected by life.
- Okay, for your
information I am affected.
The only difference
is I don't think
the answer is cutting
myself to pieces
or being Mason Bank's first call
when he's looking for an
easy piece of late night ass.
(slap landing)
- Look, I may be
incredibly messed up,
and I may do some
incredibly stupid things,
but at least I'm not
a self righteous prick
who goes around pretending like
he's God's perfect little gift.
- Good luck in French.
(engine roars)
(tires squeal)
(labored breathing)
(whistle blows)
(cheering and applauding)
- Good job today, fellas.
- Thanks, coach.
- Hold up, Wes.
You want to do better don't you?
- Doesn't matter.
- It only matters if
it matters to you.
Look, I'm not exactly
the Vince Lombardi
of running coaches but
I could tell you this.
Cross country is all about pain.
Not denying or it pretending
it doesn't exist but
recognizing it for
exactly what it is
and then finding a way
to push through it.
- Thanks, Mr. Abernac.
- Bill?
Hi.
- Hi.
- I wanted to thank you again
for inviting me to your party.
I had a very nice time.
- Good.
- There's a free concert on
Saturday at McGiffen Park.
Chopin, Verlouse,
perhaps you'd like to go?
- I don't think
that's a good idea.
- You mean the concert or?
- No, I mean
you and I spending
more time together.
I don't think that's a good
idea for either one of us.
- I'm sorry if I pushed you.
- You didn't.
- I did and I should
have known better.
Saturday, it doesn't
have to be a date.
I mean
- Carine, please.
- We can listen to music and--
- Please.
You're a lovely wonderful woman.
Any man would be
crazy not to see that.
But I just, I can't do this.
I need you to understand that.
- Yes ,I do.
- If Y is equal to
the sine of Pi X then,
then we take the integral
from negative two.
No positive two to the
endpoint of five over two.
Then we have the,
no okay there
should be a DX here.
(sighs)
But that's not,
that's not right.
Okay, a definite integral from
positive two to the end...
Yes you still have to
square it, don't you, Bill?
(contemplative music)
- Yo, Mr. Palet, you alright?
- Yeah, I just,
just need a minute.
(suspenseful music)
- In the old days
they would have
called it a nervous breakdown.
- I thought he was
getting better.
- Unfortunately
it's not uncommon
for an upswing to
proceed a downturn.
The thing is Bill's
connection with Jeanie
was so profound that
his grief is extreme.
So much so that the emotional
is now becoming physical.
- Which means what?
- That if we don't find
a way to turn this around
as bad as it is now,
it can get worse.
(horns honking)
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- As long as your dad is here
I want you to stay with us.
- I'll be fine.
- Look Wes, we all
could use somebody
to lean on from time to time.
- I really appreciate that,
Mr. Abernac, but
leaning on people
really hasn't worked out
all that well for me so far so
just not gonna do it anymore.
- So we can continue
trying new medications
but clearly we need to do more.
I want to see you in my
office three times a week.
And I'm going to
insist that you start
going to one of those support
groups that we talked about.
I also think that
we should discuss
electroconvulsive therapy.
Now that may sound extreme.
But the fact is it's
a far more refined
treatment than it used to be.
Its very safe.
And it's proven to
be highly affective
in treating sever
depression that's
unresponsive to other
forms of treatment.
Given the severity of the
break you just experienced
I believe it would be a mistake
for us not to consider it.
(machines beeping)
- Mr. Palet?
Mr. Palet are you still with us?
There you are.
So I'm going to give
you a muscle relaxant
All you have to do is
relax and take a nice nap.
How does that sound?
- Okay.
(contemplative music)
- He relished the
moments and I know that
I'm ever thankful to God
that I had the
opportunity to spend
the best part of my
life with this person.
It's just not the same.
(upbeat music)
(bell tolling)
- Mr. Rios, I think you
will find it difficult
to pass the final if
I kick you out of it.
Wes?
How's your father?
- He's fine.
- If there's anything I can
do I hope you'll let me know.
- Don't be last.
Okay, let's finish
hard, let finish hard.
(whistle blows)
Alright, bring it in.
Alright, for those of you
hoping to qualify for SPC
the trinity quads will be
your final opportunity.
It's also a race
in which we have
yet to place higher than fourth.
It's a rather uncomfortable fact
given that only four
schools participate.
So please if you bear
me any good will at all
make sure that you eat a
large carbohydrate filled meal
and that you're not
late for the bus.
Martinez.
- [Martinez] Yeah, coach.
- [Paul] Okay, that's it.
- Hey Wes, is it true your
dad is not coming back?
Dude, that's what
Bobelchek said.
- Bobelchek's a
brain dead moron.
- Yeah but, your dad
he's gonna be okay, right?
- Yeah, of course.
He so depressed he had
to be hospitalized.
They're done finding a
medication that can help
so they're just
shooting electricity
straight through his
brain, but yeah, Goob.
I'm sure everything's
gonna be just
hunky dory from here on out.
(whistle blowing)
So, how's the group going?
- Good.
- What do you talk about?
- Things people
have been through.
- What about the ECT?
You think it's helping?
- I'm not sure.
- Feel any different?
- Not really.
Dr. Rollins says it
doesn't work for everybody.
- Why don't you just
get it over with then?
- Get what?
- Dying.
That's what you're
really doing right?
I know you're depressed.
And I know that I'm
supposed to be supportive.
- I'm not asking
you to do anything.
- Yes you are.
You're asking me
to just accept it.
Just sit back, just watch
you die just like Mom.
- I know this has been hard.
- Yeah, you think?
I mean first my mom dies and
then we just pack up and leave
out of the blue out of nowhere.
- Wes you're mom and I--
- Were everything.
Okay, I know.
I get it.
But do you honestly think that
this is what she would want?
Mom was amazing.
You think I don't miss her every
single second of
every single day?
But here's the headline, Dad.
She's gone forever and
she's never ever coming back.
- Wesley, I am so sorry.
- I don't want sorry!
(dishes clattering)
I want my dad back.
- I'm here.
- No, you're not.
And you haven't been
for a long time.
If I'm gonna have to spend
the rest of my life alone
tell me now 'cause
if you're just gonna
give up and die than
maybe I should too.
- Wes, please don't say that.
- I'm serious!
That's what this
is all about, right?
If there's a point to
all this, the living?
I mean whether it's
worth it to even try.
Well, make up your
God damn mind, Dad.
If the answer is no why
don't you just fucking
kill yourself and
get it over with?
(glass breaking)
(suspenseful music)
(door slams)
(music fades)
(contemplative music)
- [Official] Runners set.
(gun fires)
(contemplative music)
(phone ringing)
- [Michael] This is Michael.
- Hello Michael,
it's Bill Palet.
- [Michael] Bill.
What a surprise.
How are you?
- I'm okay, how are you?
- [Michael] Doing well,
doing well, thanks.
- Good good.
Listen, I'm calling
because I know
you were always a real
supporter of Jeanie's work.
- [Michael] Oh yeah.
- And I wonder if the museum
would like to have it.
- [Michael] Well,
we'd be delighted.
Any specific pieces
you had in mind?
- All of it, everything.
- [Michael] I'm sorry,
did you say all of it?
- Yeah.
- [Michael] Bill?
- I know you'll take
good care of it.
- [Michael] Of course.
(upbeat music)
(cheering and applauding)
- That's it, you did it,
you did it, kid.
That was just God
damned extraordinary.
I'm telling you, that was just
absolutely God
damned extraordinary.
Did you guys see that?
That was incredible, incredible.
(labored breathing)
- Dad, Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I didn't mean what I said.
- I know.
I know.
- I'd have never said it.
- It's okay, you
had every right.
Listen Wes, Wes, Wes, hey.
I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry I missed you race.
And I'm not gonna miss any more.
- [Official]
Congratulations, Son.
- [Bill] Look at that.
- Can you believe it?
- Yeah, sure.
You Wes, are a
bright shining star.
(doorbell rings)
- She passed the French final.
- Glad to hear it.
- But she's still in
kind of a bad mood.
- Looks so official.
- I know, right?
- So are you like a jock now?
- Yeah.
Figured it was time
to kind of rebrand.
- Yeah, I mean, you did
take awkward new kid
about as far as you could.
- And plus you had brooding
loather locked up so
that was never really an option.
Heard you passed French.
- Yeah, just kept hearing your
dorky voice in my head going...
(speaking in foreign language)
Can we please try this again?
- You promise me
something first?
No more Mason.
- Thought it was gonna
be something difficult.
- No more hurting yourself.
- Yeah Carine's been trying
to get me to see some doctor.
- Promise me you'll go.
That was okay?
Too fast for you?
- Shut up.
- No, I'm just making sure
'cause
I don't want to rush
into things, okay.
- Shut up or I'm
keeping your medal.
- I was gonna give
it to you anyway.
(piano music)
- [Raffi] Hey, welcome
back, Mr. Palet.
- Thanks.
- Let's here it for Mr. P.
- [Bill] Carine.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I was hoping I
would find you here.
- Well, you did.
- Yes.
Do you like ice cream?
I know that's maybe the
dumbest question I've ever,
anyone has ever asked anyone.
Who doesn't like
ice cream, right?
- Not me.
- Right.
Meaning that you do like it?
- Yeah, I do.
- Good because we were just
about to go get some and
I was hoping you'd
like to join us.
- Who is us?
- Oh I have Wes
and Lacy with me.
You know, I figured if
you came along it'd be
a little less of that awkward
chaperoney kind of vibe.
- Is that the only reason
you are asking me to come?
- No, it's not.
I'm asking you because
I would really like
to spend some time with you.
(piano music)
♪ I don't know which
way the river bends ♪
♪ But I'll follow
until the bitter end ♪
♪ Across that ocean
bent and broken ♪
♪ Just to find you my friend ♪
♪ Sometimes all the wheels
can just fall right off ♪
♪ The price is too
high to afford the cost ♪
♪ But there's no need
to feel like all is lost ♪
♪ I'll take you home ♪
♪ You will never
have to fear cause ♪
♪ I will always be
right here with you ♪
♪ You can try ♪
♪ To erase me from
your troubled mind ♪
♪ But I won't leave I'll
be right by your side ♪
♪ Every time you try
to say goodbye to me ♪
♪ There's no need to
feel like all is lost ♪
♪ I'll take you home ♪
♪ Right through the
storm to your front door ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ You will never have to fear ♪
♪ 'Cause I will always
be right here with you ♪
♪ You you ♪
♪ I will always be
right here with you ♪
♪ Sometimes all the wheels
can just fall right off ♪
♪ It's hard to get it going
when the going gets tough ♪
♪ But there's no need
to feel like all is lost ♪
♪ I'll take you home ♪
♪ Right through the
storm to your front door ♪
♪ I'll take you home ♪
♪ Right through the
storm to your front door ♪
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪ You will never have to fear ♪
♪ 'Cause I will always
be right here with you ♪
♪ You you ♪
♪ I will always be
right here with you ♪
♪ You you ♪
♪ I will always be
right here with you ♪