Breaking news
a robbery took place at
the Louvre museum today
one high value artefact has been stolen
police say a suspect led police
on a high speed chase
for approximately 18 km
before the man was caught
a museum official states that the stolen
artefact known as the "eye of the forest"
which, together with the "wings of
destiny" and the "rope of life"
forms a three-piece precious necklace
known as "Gaia"
this 17th century necklace was made
as a gift from Spain to the Chinese emperor
it was later divided up
and smuggled out of the country
looks like you managed to keep in shape
thank you!
Need a ride?
I'll walk
of course
after five years in the pen
I imagine you needed some fresh air
it's good to be free
just because you're out of prison
doesn't mean you're really free
yeah!
I could say the same to you
tail him
impressive work
didn't even bother with the alarm
probably just tapped right
into the wireless system
and disabled the security cameras remotely
any fingerprints?
No, sir
very impressive indeed
must be how you earned this
I'm hoping we can help each other
where is he headed?
Screw you, cop
you know I didn't do this
you got no evidence on me
thank you
now I have your fingerprints
at the crime scene
pretty damning evidence for a jury
where is he?
Comm check
crystal clear, comm secure
head to the lighthouse
you'll find everything you need there
"watch list"
want me to Photoshop your picture?
Make sure it looks natural
congratulations!
You just turned over a new leaf
stop animal cruelty!
Stop animal cruelty!
I'm in
I'm almost in position
how's our new partner doing?
She should be here any minute
drinks on me!
Hello there. Anybody home?
Good morning
welcome
allow me to introduce you
the most beautiful thief of the year
red ye
I barely know you
and you're addressing me by my full name
since we still have some time
why don't we have a chat?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Married?
Are we here for work
or is this match-making?
I'm starting to have serious doubts
about this guy's work ethic
oh, please
you don't even know me
Po Chen
born 1989 at yuan general hospital
in Kaohsiung, Taiwan
your father worked at a newsstand
he died when you were 12 years old
you dropped out of school at 16
wandered the streets
until you met Dan Zhang
and you became his protégé
rumor has it, you're a virgin who's a Virgo
judging from the way
you just tried to hit on me
that's no surprise at all
you think I wouldn't do my homework
before joining a new crew?
Well, if you had done your homework
you'd also know that
I'm the best hacker in the game
okay?
Only insecure people need to brag
actions speak louder than words
got it?
I'm impressed
pretty thorough investigation
lady
you're up
show time!
Stop animal cruelty!
Alright, stand by
aw higher?
Last chance
going once...
Going twice...
Sold for Eur 200,000
thank you, Mr. Jameson
now for the highlight of the evening
please welcome Ms. Tingting
and her one of a kind
the "wings of destiny"
thank you
I hope by auctioning this treasure of mine
to help build
the largest wildlife zoo in Europe
many endangered animals
can be lifted out of misery
"target locked"
3.1 million
3.2 million
Po, check it out
Pierre
we know him well, he's a French cop
he specializes in international theft
Zhang
he's here for you
my old friend
4.5 million
do you guys have a plan B?
Zhang
your call
let's stick to the plan
lam the one he is trying to hunt
demon, come join us
copy
6 million going once
going twice...
Sold!
There, zoom in
heho, Zhang
ls that the suspect
you're talking about, inspector?
Should we have him escorted out?
Not yet
red
you're up next
fur is for beautiful animals
not ugly people!
Tingting loves to wear fur!
Stop animal cruelty!
Storm the auction house!
What are you up to?
Transport the auction
pieces back to the vault
bring the guests to the VIP room
Po, the "wings of destiny" is on you
stop killing animals!
There's a robbery in progress
open up
inspector
we've been here the whole time.
No one has attempted to...
Call your captain
found it
how much longer do we have to wait here?
Red, your location
I'm on the way, are you still inside?
I'm still there
- Yes
- open the vault
someone is stealing the "wings of destiny"
that's impossible
listen to me
this whole protest is a ruse
open it!
Perhaps if you'd be kind enough
to share some of your information
you're wasting time
open the vault!
I want everyone on high alert
go!
Open the vault
come on
oh my god
lock down all exits to the hotel
parking lots, everything!
I have the package, let's regroup
be patient
since Pierre is here
let's up the ante
your turn, demon
excuse me
- watch!
- Oh, sorry...
It's okay, guys
thank you!
You're welcome
may I sit here?
Sure
it's alright
Cannes is full of fanatics
yes
as a matter of fact, I'm
a huge fan of yours
really?
Of course
I've seen all your movies
what is the name of the movie...
Come on...
Stop that car!
Move!
Go...
Stop!
What?
Your necklace
stop!
His driving is pretty damn good
out of my way
move!
Think of something
now I know what your plan B is
that's good
now you can slow down
all the security footage at the hotel
have been deleted
good job
you're still not retiring?
I still need "Gaia" to
find out who set me up
seems like you already
have an answer in mind
beware "Gaia" may be a cursed artefact
still going back to Kong?
He's been waiting a long time for my return
Dan Zhang
what an honor to meet
the legendary Dan Zhang
you're so handsome
can I have your autograph?
Do you want my autograph, or money?
Money
I was told you play fair
I've been looking for a new partner
let me join you guys
she was pretty good this time
didn't Kong tell you
before he sent you here?
That was my last job
I'll find you if I come out of retirement
your welcome gift is like a rocket
you should give it a try
I'll try it for you
it is in this very tunnel,
the Cantaron's tunnel
a car crash between vehicles took place
stemming from a car chase
involving two alleged thieves
and a police officer, acting on his own
as you can see behind me,
rescue team arrived on the scene
details are still unclear at this time
damn it, Pierre.
This is your idea of "observing"?
Sit
you know why
I'm the one with this office right now
and not you?
You're a better ass-kisser than me
maybe
but I'm not your partner anymore
I'm your superior
from now on,
you'll share your Intel and collaborate
ls that clear?
What the hell are those?
Chinese stress balls
helps me to relax
you should give them a try
I want to bring on help
good, take anyone you want
not a cop
an expert
someone who can lead me right to Zhang
who said anything about outside, I...
You wanted me to collaborate
with cops!
If you lose him again,
I won't be able to save your ass
understand?
These cracks were not caused by hand
seems pretty straight forward to me
this painting is from the 19th century
its canvas is coated with
a protective rabbit skin gesso
which is highly sensitive to humidity
as you can now see for yourself
ls it covered by our policy?
I'm sorry. But...
Failure to maintain proper humidity
levels in the gallery
ls considered human error
I'm sorry, but it's not
covered by our policy
if you'd like us to investigate further
please let us know
Amber Li?
Inspector Pierre Bissette
what can I do for you?
You have knowledge about a particular case
that I believe could be useful to me
I was assigned to
the case of Tingting's necklace
somehow I don't think that's
what you are here for
do you know this man?
You already know the
answer to that question
did he steal it?
I think you already
know the answer to that question
has he tried to contact you?
Am I a suspect?
No
I haven't had any contact with him
since he went to jail
I didn't even know he got out
I know how it feels to be betrayed
nice try inspector.
Don't play mind games with me
you don't know the first thing about me
I know that Zhang targeted you
then used your inside information
to steal the "eye of the forest"
so you want to use me as bait
you know him better than anyone
with your help...
I don't know him any better than I know you
good luck, inspector
call me, if you change your mind
thank you
how have you been?
I'm doing okay
yes?
I'll help you on one condition
when this is all over
you make sure Zhang gets locked up for good
deal
now tell me
where is the "rope of life"?
Are you willing to travel?
Good to see you back
Kong is waiting for you
uncle Kong
I've been waiting for you
I know
I can always count on you
well done
a new hobby you picked up?
Not a bad way to kill time
you should consider it after you retire
Taiwan boy
you two are still working together?
Uncle Kong
good work
before your incident
I knew you wanted to retire
but I couldn't count on
anyone else to get this done
this cheque
I should've given it to you years ago
don't worry. It's safe
it know it's less than you expect
I took some out
for this
after you got caught
I put the word out to track down the guy
who stole the "eye of the forest" from you
it took a while
it was this bastard
ls that a tongue?
Yes
so the rumour is true. You did it
there's a honor code amongst thieves
I can't kill
but I can pay others to get it done
money well spent
you're like a son to me
did you ever find out who
tipped off the cops?
Don't try to guess
if you have absolutely no idea
you're better off not knowing
I want to know
it was your fiancée
Amber
I suppose I deserved it
ls there a chance for one more job,
so I can score a big one before I retire?
Of course!
If you combine these three artefacts, it'd take
you lifetimes to spend what "Gaia" is worth
all we need now is the "rope of life"
you have to be sure about this
there can't be anymore missteps
you know what's fascinating
about nesting dolls?
You begin by making the smallest one
the shape and size of this core figure
determines the fate
of the rest of the dolls that follow
it's interesting, isn't it
that's destiny
understood
let's hear the plan
now that you've taken the cheque
why not get out of the game
while you still can?
What can I say
I'm greedy and I like money
a fortune is worthless to a dead man
do you really believe that
Amber betrayed you that day?
You wanted to retire because of her
Amber is a good person, and I'm a thief
but I can't fool her forever
we're being tailed, don't look back
let's split up
okay. See you later
give it to me
give you what?
The "eye of forest",
the "wings of destiny", Tingting's necklace
you're so sure that I'm responsible
why would they lock you up if you weren't?
You never gave me a chance to explain
you've never visited me
once in the past five years
I'm not gonna listen
to your so-called explanations
then what are you doing here?
I'm helping the police
with their investigation
so they will lock you up for good
if they have any evidence that I did it
they can come and arrest me
stop following me
it's complete
yes
interesting
enough
try this one
"Gaia"
look in the most recent folder
that's him
the guy who owns the "rope of life"
you know him?
I've met him briefly
that's pretty high tech
should we tell Kong that we're backing out?
No
Why?
The operation is compromised
scrap the original plan
we're going for plan B
plan B?
Nature calls
you don't need to go?
I'll hold it in
they say holding it in is bad for you
I knew this would happen
what is this?
A female urination device
for the wilderness
now you can pee standing up
what do you think?
Now we can pee together standing up
are you insane?
What's that?
A female urination device
ls it useful?
You're sick
Po
Come on
that's him?
Whatever you do
find out as much as you
can about the castle
and where he keeps the "rope of life"
piece of cake
buddy“.
Stop...
Stop!
What was that?
That was your plan?
To not talk to him?
How are we gonna be
able to get the "rope of life"?
Let's go
you'll never understand
what women are thinking!
Mr. law, please, a word?
Sir
are you still the owner
of the "rope of life"?
I believe you've been
targeted by a group of thieves
these are no ordinary thieves
they have already stolen the two
other components that make up "Gaia"
I see
now all they need is yours
inspector
if they can get pass the state of the art
security systems I installed
let them have it
excuse's moi
prick
hi
Have we met before?
Is that the best pick up line
you can come up with?
What's wrong?
Is it the wine?
It's not the wine. It's the venue
what's wrong with the venue?
People need to be in a certain mood
to enjoy fine wine
the place is nice enough
but it's lacking two key elements
and what might those be?
Music and...
Friends
not only do you know wine
you know how to enjoy life
let me introduce myself
Charlie law
I own this winery
I've heard all about you
I work for a wine magazine
rose
I'm a wine critic
I assume I won't be
getting a good review from you
sorry
- it was nice meeting you, I should go
- wait
now that we have music
all you need is a companion
care to be my friend?
I already have plenty of friends
how about
we do an interview?
Would you be interested?
Call me
bye
why isn't he calling?
He will soon
how do you know he'll call?
How do you know he won't?
He...
"It's me Charlie. I'll call you now"
see?
Hello?
Hi, rose. It's Charlie
hey, what's up?
I'd like to schedule the interview
tomorrow
great!
I'm busy
the day after tomorrow?
Sure
would you like to come to my office?
Text me the address
my driver can pick you up
why'd you hang up?
He didn't even finish
you're so annoying
wait! Where are you going?
Checking whether the facial mask
worked its magic
he's calling back!
You answer it
she was just...
Could you please stop doing that?
Sorry, stress relief
doctor's orders
does it work?
Not really
you seem really obsessed with him. Why?
I'm not obsessed. He's a thief, I'm a cop
my duty is to catch him
that's it
I'm just curious
sorry
if I made you uncomfortable
you know when
Zhang stole the "eye of the forest"
I chased him through the streets of Paris
almost had him
when a car crashed into me
I was trapped in the wreckage
I thought for sure I was going to die
you know why I want to get him so bad?
Because he's the worst
kind of thief there is
the kind that has Patience, and integrity
the kind that if I don't get him now
I'm afraid I won't ever get him
it's her
now what?
We wait and we follow her
there's interference in the feed
how about now?
Good
this way please
take a good look
copy
you mind if I record the interview?
Not at all
alright
let's begin
Mr. law, what year were you born?
on the 31st of this month
I'm throwing myself a birthday party here
I'd like for you to be there
maybe
let's get on with the interview, shall we?
When was the first time you tasted wine?
16 years old
do you remember what kind it was?
No, but it was expensive for sure
so as long as the wine's
expensive, it's good?
Not just wine, it applies to everything
money means a lot to you, doesn't it
of course
Mr. law
how would you describe your occupation?
Making money
big and small
for example this castle
I live here
but I also open parts of it for tourists
what's the most valuable item
in your collection?
Have you heard of the "rope of life"?
No, but now that you mention it...
I have an idea
how about I take a picture of you
and the "rope of life"?
It'd make the article more enticing
now?
Yes
sure
follow me
right this way
it's secret passage
must be standard for the rich
your security system here
must be one of a kind
everything is linked up to
the security control center
there are cameras in there
that are connected to my cell phone
good morning, Mr. law
here is my collection
out of all the artefacts
this is my favorite
it's stunning
it must be very expensive
a lot of people
would kill to get their hands on it
as it's one of the most coveted
pieces of jewelry in the world
buddy is my most trusted
security team member
yes, we've met before
buddy is actually very friendly
he's just a little playful sometimes
try calling his name
buddy!
Let's start talking some pictures
okay
alright
ready
sorry, there's a reflection
from the glass
no problem, I can open it up
looks very high tech
alright, again
give me a high-spirited pose
wait a minute
fine
alright
give me a pose with a homely feeling
perfect. Now some full body shots
great
let me get a top shot
sure
imagine you're presenting it with pride
can you step to your left?
A little more
just a little more
more?
Are you sure you can still see me?
Perfect from this angle
during the Nazi occupation of
Czechoslovakia in world war ll
the castle was inhabited by the Nazis
an underground secret passageway
was built as an escape route
it connects the basement of the castle
all the way to the winery
in fact, the wine cellar
was used as a bomb shelter
here she is, coming out
that's way off
hello inspector
I see your time behind bars
did little to rehabilitate you
not true
I tried painting
but I'm just better
at stealing art than making it
once a thief, always a thief
easy
I wouldn't be here if I didn't want to talk
I'm listening
Amber
that's your business
mine is to bring you in
you dragged her into this mess
that makes it your business
give this to her
and keep her out of this
what's going on?
He still cares for you
you said you know how
it feels to be betrayed
who was it?
Since when are you interested in bonding?
When I was a boy,
my father was the greatest man I knew
everybody loved him, respected him
he traveled a lot... For work he said
used to bring me trinkets and tell me that
one day I'd go with him
I was 14 when the police came
raided our home and seized everything
I don't know if the trinkets
he gave me were stolen or not
doesn't matter
cops took them all away
my dad too
he went to jail
left us with nothing
did you ever confront your father?
He died in prison
people like Zhang and my father
they destroy lives
it isn't just objects they steal
it is trust as well
well, I don't have to tell you this
why did you agree to help me?
One day
someone offers you an opportunity
to put away someone you
tried so hard to forget
but couldn't
so you take it,
because it is the right thing to do
I just didn't realize how hard it would be
as much as I hate him
I still...
Say no more
I understand
it looks like our pal Charlie's
throwing a party at the castle
I have to go
I'm going with you
I want to
he)'
what kind of fingerprint scanner is this?
It's a pain to wear
help me lace this up
come on
this is a high-risk operation
which operation isn't?
If anything happens
I mean, if one of us gets caught
I can't save you
you don't have to save me either
this is a rule set by Zhang
that's a strange rule
it's too tight
let's give it a try
you need to hold on tighter
what are all these red flags?
Surveillance cameras
their range is around 5o meters
and they cover
the whole perimeter of the castle
that's really difficult to get in
that's why we won't be
going in on ground level
then how would we get in?
Getting inside is not impossible
we can enter from the winery
that's adjacent to the castle
in there? Are we gonna suffocate to death?
The winery needs some new barrels
that's how demon will sneak us in
the manhole leads directly
to the underground passageway
that will take us
to the castle's security control center
Po
Once I get there, I'll take out the guards
then turn off the surveillance cameras
and the security system
happy birthday to you
Zhang will enter the vault
from the watchtower
exactly
got it
and who's going to open the vault?
You've already planted the seed
laser system is down
you look absolutely gorgeous today
thank you
I know that you've got everything
so I didn't bring a present
you coming tonight is
the best present I could ask for
happy birthday
thank you
scared the crap out of me
what the hell just happened?
It's a long story
go... Go
women are just gifts to you, aren't they?
Of course not
then what are they?
Like you
they should be gift receivers
the scan failed
try it again
so you have a gift for me?
Let's go back to China together
wearing the "rope of life"
okay, it's done
say goodbye
excuse me, I need to use the bathroom
transmitting
I'm outside the vault
time for spidey
what's happening?
Charlie's dog is attacking spidey
we're running out of time
sorry doggy
you made me do this
Mr. law
the policeman is here again
he says it's urgent
Mr. law
Zhang, your old friend is here
Po, we're running out of time
red is in trouble
send over the fingerprints
Zhang
now!
So I'm just part of your plan
check your vault
everything is fine
buddy?
You've been robbed right under your nose
come with me
they're heading your way
they will reach you soon
get yourself out of there
what about red?
Leave now! Before they catch you
find them!
Alert, all personnel!
What about the rule?
I broke it, but don't fall in love with me
let's go
wait
I won't kill him
I don't know how to swim!
Don't move!
Stay on your knees
you will have to kill me
you think I won't?
Try me
don't be stupid
think of Amber
ls that why you brought her?
You're smarter than I thought
get in
what are you looking at?
Nothing, I just don't get it
you saving me makes me think that
there's still a possibility
to make this work
can I be together with a thief?
You haven't changed one bit
I need to find the guy who screwed me over
without the complete "Gaia",
he won't show himself
if he doesn't die, then
I can't live in peace
are you okay?
I'm alright
but you're in a bit of a pickle
you just became an accomplice
hey!
Hey!
You alright?
I'm good
only one parachute left
go with them, I'll follow after
I'm not going with them
listen to me
just let me talk to Kong
I'll figure everything out
and explain later, okay?
Go
I'll save you the trip
Zhang
did you forget about your uncle
because of this woman?
I have what you want
hand it over
hold on
you want the goods? Where is the money?
Hand me the goods
no, there's no turning back
if you give it to him
come on, bring it over
he was talking to me
red? What are you doing?
He hired me first
take her with us
Amber!
Think twice before snitching
when you're in jail
I have her as leverage
Po, use spidey!
Hands up! Get down on the ground!
Now!
Go now, make sure you find her
- what about you?
- Just jump!
Still refusing to cooperate?
Five minutes
okay
where is "Gaia"?
We know your mentor Kong has it
go, take a break
where is he?
I don't know
but I do know how to find him
you can't get him without my help
and Amber?
Let me out of here
I'll save her and take down Kong
if we lose Kong this time
he sells "Gaia"
we will never find him
never
why should I trust you?
Do you have another choice?
One condition
bring back "Gaia"
the buyer is here
keep an eye on her
uncle Kong
I'll be there in bit
be quick
I'm going in, you stay here
what about red...
So what's the plan anyway?
Plan B
hi
Tell us
why did you side with Kong?
He saved my life before
there are many things
where we have no choice
the universe depends on a balance
and we are all subject to Karma
Karma leads us to
where we are now
you wouldn't be here
without me
five years
have I not repaid my debt to you?
There is no such thing
as "paying back" in a family
what are you planning to pay her back with?
Great
everyone's here
it's a family reunion
let me tell you
the Russian doll behind you
ls a proximity bomb
the distance sensor
ls attached to "Gaia"
once the transaction is done
and "Gaia" gets out of a
one kilometer range
the bomb will go off
and this will be
what you repay her with
you stay here and watch them
when I give the call, meet me downstairs
understood
hello!
Your operation in the Czech Republic
drew a lot of heat from the cops
don't worry
this place is safe
the original buyer
from the middle east got cold feet
luckily I found a new buyer, Mr. Yelyuk
last minute change in buyer
ls not how we do business
he's fine
Mr. Yelyuk is a very rich man
he's offering 20% more
nothing to worry about
you know what this machine does?
It cuts Cannon barrels
when I was a young man,
I used to work in a factory like this
this damn thing can cut through anything
I know you have something I want
let's see it
I was like you
looked up to him like a father
he sold me out five years ago
looks like it's gonna be you this time
save your story
I only care about money
think about it
why did he leave you here?
You really believe after the transaction
you will be getting your share?
To him, you are one of us
pull the trigger if you don't believe me
take it easy
just family business being taken care of
family business
lower your guns
carry on
proceed
"bank transfer"
hand over "Gaia"
or I'll kill her
you shot her down like a dog
if she can't even handle a few of you
what's the use of her
what do you take us for?
What do you take me for?
If I raised a dog
at least it would know how to fetch
you left me for a bitch
I have rules for training my dogs
your rules don't apply to me
why does it have to suit you?
- Translate this to Yelyuk
- don%
does he have a younger brother?
Don't listen to him
did his brother disappear five years ago?
- Shut up!
- Hold on
I'll listen
five years ago
after I stole the "eye
of the forest" for him
I was ambushed
by a thief
he stole the "eye of the forest" from me
Kong had him murdered
so what?
The problem is
that thief was his brother
would you come here if you knew?
How do you know this?
Kong not only killed your brother
he also cut off his tongue
his tongue had a tattoo
just like the one you have on your neck
I didn't know he was your brother
he stole from me so I killed him.
That's the rule of the game
you can understand that, right?
You are the one not playing by the rules
you hired his brother
- and then you killed him
- shut up
how dare you shoot at me?
I should be asking you that question
listen carefully
I am risking my life to come here
you are right
Kong is the one who betrayed you
he hired the eastern European boy
to steal the "eye of the forest" from you
what are you afraid of?
Shoot me
he's all yours
remember what I said about that machine?
It cuts through anything
Spideys ready!
Three
two
one
stand still
come out now
come out, you traitors
I will kill you
hand over "Gaia" to me
go!
Stop the car!
"One kilometer"
he was defeated by his own greed
how are we going to keep you free
from prison without "Gaia"?
Why do you always do this?
Keeping me in the dark
can't you give me a heads up
I promise you
from now on, whatever I do
I'll ask you first
Ms. Li
may I kiss you?
Are you out of your mind?
Women are complicated
like I said
plan B
what is plan B?
Just play it by ear
"'gaia' returns home"
"from an unknown benefactor"
good morning
you have a package
thank you
come on guys! I'm done before you
we got to give it a shake
now what?
Plan C!