Help!
Stop!
God!
Help!
Every 23rd year, for 23 days,
it gets to eat.
And the things it leaves behind,
like the thing it left
in Poho County that night,
the nightmare on four wheels,
was a horror all its own.
Go get the sergeant.
Sergeant!
We got the truck open.
Five...
Goddamn slaughterhouse on wheels.
Police scanner.
It's been listening to us.
Whatever it is.
Some of this stuff, I don't
wanna know what it's made of.
Where the hell's that tow truck?
En route.
Coroner's still down near the jail.
Should I get him up here?
Those aren't for sewing.
I don't wanna know for what.
Get that goddamn thing in the impound!
Oh, my God.
I don't believe it.
Jesus Christ, where the hell have you been?
How many you lose tonight?
You hold it together and you answer me.
Three officers, an inmate down in the jail...
And then the kid.
The one he flew off with. Name of Jerry.
His name was Darry Jenner!
His sister's a train wreck.
She's inside waiting for her folks,
they're driving in from Stillwater.
Where's the last place you saw it?
Don't touch that, and stay back!
Show me.
We threw everything we had at it, Danny.
All the fire and manpower
this building had to offer.
And it just made a whole lot of noise
and flew off with exactly what it wanted.
Sheriff!
Don't you want us tailing that truck?
They just towed it out of here.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Can't raise 'em.
They're not answering any frequency!
- Where are they taking it?
- To impound, where else?
Jesus Christ, we couldn't leave it
sitting there! You saw what it did!
We gotta get an armada around that thing.
You make it happen, now! Anybody, everybody!
Get on out there! Move fast!
Just a goddamn minute Danny.
You tell me how the hell
you know about any of this!
'Cause what happened here, happened before!
You think that thing torched that church
tonight because it wanted a campfire?
It was destroying information!
Trying to get rid of what
it doesn't want us to know!
And that truck?
That truck is that thing's rolling history.
Which is why we get it
in the impound and tear it apart!
It ain't gonna make it to the impound!
Looks like a Rio.
An old Chevy Cab-o.
Cab over engine, I'd say 1940s.
That cow-catcher's gotta be custom.
You wanna tell me what the hell a truck
like that needs a cow-catcher for?
If you knew what was inside that thing,
that wouldn't be your only question.
Dana, listen up and listen good!
I'm sending units to you right now.
Code 3, you read me?
- Code 3!
- Come again Sergeant?
Just tell that driver
to put his foot on the gas
and drive like hell to....
What the hell?
- What is that?
- Jesus Christ!
Holy shit!
Fear...
has a scent.
And I've seen that thing inhale it.
Like it could sample fear,
right out of the air.
Dispatch, this is Lang with
the impound vehicle, please respond.
That's how it picks what parts of us to eat.
Captain are you in range?
And it eats...
This is Dana.
We have a situation with the impound vehicle.
To rebuild itself.
You hear that?
It's coming back.
What the...
Stop! Stop!
Frank! Frank!
It never hunts in the same place
for more than a day.
It's done with Poho County.
All we can do now is head north
and follow the birds.
It's not much, but it's all we know.
Ravens and crows.
They travel when it does.
Davis, I've looked that
ugly thing eye-to-eye.
23 years ago.
I know it.
And it knows me.
Why do you do this?
It hurts too much.
- Seeing you like this...
- Mom, just listen, okay?
Time's up.
It's coming back, just like I said.
- Why?
- Stop asking.
It doesn't matter.
You tell me why it's coming here.
Pieces of it left behind.
They're full of secrets about it.
That's what's buried up here?
A piece of it?
There's no more time. It's coming here,
and you can't be here when it does.
- How do you know it's coming?
- I'm a part of it now!
How many times do I have to tell you that?
It knows what's buried here,
and it will come and take it back.
Oh, killing you wasn't enough?
Why didn't it take it 23 years ago?
It ran out of time!
It always runs out of time.
I can't keep telling you this.
If you won't leave to save yourself,
then do it to save Addison.
Addison?
What are you talking about?
Do you think we have any money?
Kenny...
are you listening to yourself?
Are you listening to yourself?
How are we supposed to do that?
Where are we supposed to go?
Ugh, just leave!
Just pack up and go!
Pack up everything...
Leave it where?
It knows it's here, Mom, 'cause
I'm a part of it, and it's a part of me.
Today, tomorrow, or sometime soon
it is going to walk up this hill
and it is going to dig this thing up
right where I'm standing.
And when it comes...
it'll kill anyone that's still here.
Go away, mom.
Now.
Good morning, handsome.
Hey, you hungry buddy?
Damn.
Come on.
Gotta go talk to Grandma.
I don't want to do it alone.
Grandma?
Are you okay?
I'm taking the truck into town.
We need hay.
Who's going to pay for it?
I was thinking maybe we still
had some credit at Hooks'?
He called again.
We owe them more than we can pay.
Cal did say that he...
Grandma, no.
Addy...
I already told you,
I'm not selling Rocket, Grandma.
Selling him would be like
giving away my own child.
What a good mother might have to do
so that child wouldn't go hungry.
I want you to go away for a few days.
Maybe stay with Gracie?
Why?
Can you?
Is there something that you
don't want me here for?
Yes.
Unexpected company.
You've got your team.
You got experienced men who know this thing.
The team is more than law enforcement.
The team of shopkeeps, farmers, anyone
who's looked this thing eye-to-eye
and lived to tell about it
and wants to do something about it!
Davis! Davis!
Hey!
You the best goddamn sharpshooter in all
of Poho county, or any other county.
You got questions about that too, now?
When I raised my gun to that thing,
I couldn't pull the goddamn trigger
'cause I couldn't believe
what the hell I was looking at.
This thing rewrites all the rules, Danny.
And going after it...
It scares the hell out of me.
A brave man is either scared...
or he's a goddamn liar.
Boss.
Michael.
This his old man's truck?
It's an old vulcan cannon.
She's amped up to shoot 20 millimeter
rounds, 6,000 rounds a minute.
You test this thing?
Mikey.
Is this thing tested?
This thing throws up a wall of fire.
A wall of fire that nothing from this world
or the next can get through!
Not without being torn into a million pieces.
She may not fly,
but this is our killing machine.
Davis!
He watched that thing fly down
and punch a hole in his old man.
He stood there and watched it pull
the heart right out of his daddy's chest
and swallowed it, right before his eyes.
Miller was only ten years old!
You're not losing your mind, Davis.
You just got blooded last night.
Now you want to guess
how much blood I got on my hands?
You've seen that thing, now.
So you got blood on your hands too.
And no matter what you do,
it's gonna stay there.
Whether you walk away or not.
Rendezvous at station one!
North!
Howdy!
Can I bag some hay off you?
Sure, stranger.
Our horses are up in Boulder.
You're not up there
with Rocket winning trophies?
Can't even afford the gas
to drive up there right now.
What's the matter, your grandma?
Yeah, she was up on
the hill again this morning.
Screaming at the wind, calling it Kenny?
Didn't he die like 20 years ago?
Mom!
You know you got a rabbit in that trap?
- That's what it's there for.
- So it's suffering!
You just gonna leave it in there?
Mom!
- Mom, he's got a rabbit in the trap.
- Hey, Addy, long time no see.
- Mom said they were eating up her garden.
- I didn't say you should trap them.
- You didn't say I shouldn't!
- How's your grandma doing?
He doesn't care about the garden.
He traps them because he likes killing them!
He's sick!
I mean, who likes to trap
and kill things for fun, huh?
Psychos, maybe? He's too stupid
to even know he is one.
Alright, stop. And you, take care
of this before you leave.
By which I mean, let it go.
It's not in any pain.
Don't leave it in the trap.
It's cruel, honey.
Stop!
It's a rabbit, mom. Do you know
how small their brains are?
- Ten times bigger than yours?
- Well, then you let it out!
And I hope it bites you.
It's a wild animal, idiot.
It's kill or be killed.
Just let it go and stop trapping them, okay?
You're all a bunch of women.
Kirk.
Get back here.
Tell 'em about the law
of the jungle, will you, Addy?
Kirk, get out of the car and let it go.
What's out in the hay barn?
Dad took what we had.
That's okay.
I'm on my way to Hooks' anyway.
Oh, are you?
Yes, and shut up.
Buddy Hooks' got a huge crush on Addy, Mom.
But neither one of them are brave
enough to do anything about it.
You wouldn't want to come
with me to Hooks', would you?
And get in the way?
Do you like him or not?
He does have a really cute butt.
And from that springs love!
Idiot.
What the hell is that?
Somebody just ditched it out here?
Hell, I would.
What do you think's in it?
Rust and cow shit.
No way.
Oh, hell no!
"No way" what?
Look at that license plate.
"Beating you?"
"B-Eating You," and no fucking way!
Right.
No way, that story's bullshit.
No, no. I heard it really happened.
Yeah, I did too.
Real people disappeared.
20 years ago.
23, and it's just a story.
What story?
The guy who drove around and ate people!
In a scary-ass old truck
with that license plate.
Jeepers creepers.
What?
Wasn't that the song
the guy sang or something?
Look, it's homemade.
At least one idiot every Halloween
makes a license plate that says that.
You think it just drove in?
The tracks look fresh.
You think somebody could be in there?
Yeah, it's warm!
Of course it's warm, you dipshit.
It's been sitting out in the sun.
Who'd dump it out here?
Who wouldn't?
Hello?
Can't see shit.
I'd say we beat it in case they come back.
Anybody in there?
Hey! Hello in there!
What the fuck is wrong with you man?
What?
I was just knocking.
Well, don't! Idiot.
What's this thing on the front?
What thing?
This thing I'm peeing on.
It's a cow catcher.
They put it on front of trains
back in the old days.
Who'd put it on a truck?
This thing is made up
of so many different parts.
It's like a frickin' Frankenstein truck.
Man, I say we get the hell out of here.
Wait, break the windows first?
Hell yes, we do!
We gotta kill Frankenstein's truck, right?
Dibs on the windshield!
Kiss my ass, you ugly old bitch!
Oh!
You see that?
Thing tried to kill me,
nicked my fuckin' ear.
Maybe it tries to kill things
more stupid than it.
What the hell?
Those can't be real.
Those flies are real.
That smell is real.
Oh, jeez...
Hey, you.
You gonna be driving up to see us?
Go Eaton Valley, right?
So, ten bales of Alfalfa?
Right.
No Grandma today, huh?
How's she doing?
You're not on the load list.
D'you want to talk to my dad?
Do you want me to?
I should put her on my load list.
You know why she lives
with her grandma, right?
Addy couldn't get along with her stepdad,
so instead of kicking him out,
her mom ships her ass out here
to live with her crazy grandma.
Can you really blame me, though?
I mean look at her.
The heart wants what it wants, am I right?
Yeah.
And mine wants you to shut the fuck up.
So...
I'm just going to go to Carlin's and see
if we have some credit out there.
Hey, just wait a minute...
What happened?
Bernardi's.
Load it up and get it out there now,
he's waiting for it.
What are you doing?
She loves that horse more
than anything in the world,
and right now it's got nothing to eat.
'Cause they're broke!
You think we're ever going
to see the money that they owe us?
The state's not even
sending them checks anymore.
And how do you know that?
Biggs down at the post office.
How do you think?
Make your point, dad.
You can do better.
That's my point.
Got some hay for you!
Turn that thing around!
Let's get your horse some breakfast.
Whats the problem?
I thought you said you have a hungry horse.
Get it out!
We gotta call someone!
- Just get it the hell out!
- What do you want us to do?
Alright, it's long enough. I can pull it out.
Do you want me to pull it out?
Just call someone!
There's no fucking service out here so
shut up about the goddamn phone, alright?
Kirk, look at me!
Just do something!
Like what?
What the fuck do you want us to do?
You want us to try and pull it out?
Alright, hold him up.
Oh, shit.
Okay on three, you ready?
Hold him steady, come on!
On three I'm going to pull like
a son of a bitch, you guys ready?
One!
Two!
Oh, sh...
Fuck!
What the fuck?
Help, help!
No, no, Help!
Help!
Red!
Red! Red!
Help!
No! Help! No!
No!
No! Help!
- Don't leave me.
- I'm not!
I don't know what to do.
Maybe we could cut the cable.
With what?
Try the phone again.
- Oh, my God...
- Come on!
So this is the famous Rocket, huh?
He's a beauty.
You understand what I'm saying, don't you?
Every word you're saying.
Yeah?
Well, in that case,
do you think Addy here would ever
be interested in seeing a guy like me?
In the city...
my mother and I had a cat.
Addy...
I liked the cat.
Crapped in her boyfriend's shoes
every chance it got.
What happened to the boyfriend?
She married him.
They got rid of the cat.
Look I...
I'm not great at this,
and when I get nervous I start
talking too much.
I...
Is that your grandmother?
Thank you for the hay, but please just go.
Okay.
You wouldn't want to come?
I mean, I gotta get the rest of this stuff
up to Bernardi's. You ever been up there?
It's really something.
I mean, only if you want to.
I'd love to.
Okay.
What are you doing?
- I need to know what you found.
- Mom, what are you doing?
And why it killed you for it.
No, you don't.
You don't want to see what it'll show you.
Go!
Away!
Hey!
Stop!
Come on, Gaylen, you out there?
I got a lot of units
headed out to station one.
What is that, a roll bar?
You reinforce this thing?
First time I met Gaylen was 23 years ago.
On the worst night of her life.
Her son Kenny and his date, Dara Cleeway,
disappeared on the way to the prom.
All they found was
a red pickup and no bodies.
When Gaylen finally believed
what happened to Kenny,
she asked if she could join the team.
That was the beginning for me.
Like last night was the beginning for you.
No!
Oh, my...
That looks like Wildfire.
That's a $200,000 horse.
Yeah, and that looks like Nightmare with her.
What are they doing out?
I don't know.
Where is everybody?
Buddy!
Hurry!
Go tell the sheriff to get up here, and fast!
Bring everything he's got.
Get out of here,
and keep your eyes on the sky!
Do it!
Lock your door.
What's going on?
I don't know.
There's men under that trailer.
Roll your window up.
What's happening?
Come on!
Stop making noise!
Who's that with you?
Addison Brandon.
What's going on?
I got guns in the barn.
Guns?
For what?
Do you think you could make a run for it?
I'd do it myself if it weren't for
this leg and this goddamn cane.
What about those guys under the truck?
They won't move.
They think they know this thing.
They got a name for it.
Mr. Bernardi, what...
who are you hiding from?
I don't know!
I've seen it and I still don't know.
Something came down and got Babaloo.
Came down?
Spooked the horses so bad
they jumped both the fences.
It tried to come down and get me too.
What did?
Let me tell you, I put up a fight.
What are we talking about?
I dropped them out there somewhere...
Gaylen!
Gaylen Brandon!
Hello Gaylen!
Mrs. Brandon?
Gaylen?
I've been calling you.
What the hell is the matter?
He's here.
Is that what you came here to say?
'Cause if not, he will be.
What happened?
Just tell me one thing.
Did you bring something that can kill it?
He found it 23 years ago.
Kenny.
The night before he died.
It fell from the sky.
He didn't tell me he took it home
or that he hid it in the hay store.
The horses wouldn't stay in the barn with it.
Mom, get the horses!
He wouldn't say what was happening.
Mom, just get the horses!
He must've touched that thing,
and that was why he
was so angry and frightened.
He wanted to kill it, whatever it was.
Maybe he thought he did.
I trapped him.
It's under there.
Be careful!
If you touch that thing,
if you put your hand on it...
You see.
You see...
how it came to be.
And what it is.
Buddy...
Bud?
Stay down.
Quick, can you see anything?
What?
There's knives and stuff on both sides.
Can you reach one and I cut your rope?
I tried, but it's hard for me to move.
You think her dead kid came over the hill this
morning to tell her to vacate the premises?
What if she's right?
What if she can learn
that thing's secrets just by
touching that piece of its own flesh.
You're going to go over there
and hold hands with it, aren't you?
Just like she did.
What do you think this is if it isn't a war?
One that absolutely won't stop until
that damn thing doesn't exist anymore.
This thing gets away again...
I'm either going to be dead
or too damn old next time.
What if the secret to what this thing is
is the secret of how to kill it?
Hurry!
Sometimes he comes back fast.
It's usually with another body
and you don't want to be here for that.
Kirk?
- No fucking way, Addy.
- Oh, my God.
My leg. I can't walk on it.
But I can drive myself just get...
get me out of this.
I checked.
They're dead.
He thinks I'm dead too, and probably you.
Why aren't we?
I was passed out when he
wrapped me and threw me in here.
But from what I could tell, I think he was in
too big of a hurry to care if we are or not.
Yeah, well, let's get out of here.
No!
Only he opens those.
You try, it'll split you in two.
This whole fucking truck is a death trap.
Maybe the front.
Try the driver's door.
What do you see?
It just looks like a door handle.
There's a chain, should I try that?
Try what?
I don't know, maybe it does something.
I think maybe the horn.
Try the door handle.
Say a little prayer that one
of these doors opens.
Get behind him.
Get.
Behind him.
Put your hands on him.
Danny.
I know where you're going.
You will come back.
Danny!
No!
Look at me boss!
Sheriff!
- Boss!
- Danny!
Danny?
Danny, look at me.
I'm next.
Boss?
Are you out of your goddamn mind?
With all due respect, sergeant,
you stand down.
You don't tell me to stand down.
You don't know!
Not like us.
You got no takeaway in this.
Alright.
No!
What are you...
Stop, stop!
Get him off!
...anybody out there read me?
Repeat, this is Deputy Michael...
Get off me!
Any team members out there
at all copy me? Repeat!
- Deputy Mike McGrail...
- Go!
I've got a flipped vehicle
in a field off Kearney Road,
and I mean upside-down and still smoking.
- It's headed to the Nine.
- Who is this? Is that the sheriff?
This is Team Leader Miller. We copy
and are putting rubber to the road.
Maybe 15 minutes away.
No lights, no sirens!
If this thing hits the Nine
we're going to take it by surprise.
You and Brady, you come in from the east.
Miller, you and Jenkins see if you can
find a road that gets you in front of it.
The point is to stay alive.
It's what your old man would've wanted.
You find Addy and the two of
you get the hell out of here
and don't come back
until I tell you different.
So you're just okay now?
I just saw you rolling around on the ground
like you were having a brain scramble.
I can drive, Danny.
Danny!
Danny, goddammit,
move over and let me in there!
I got no idea!
Sheriff's up in Kissell, says they
can't even get a man down here.
Bud is really scaring me.
He's in some kind of shock or something
and he's not snapping out of it.
- I'm getting ready to run him...
- I let her go.
I let her go.
I couldn't hold on, Dad.
I let her go and now she's out there
with that thing somewhere!
Now just... sit.
I left her out there!
Sit down.
I left her, dad!
Sit down and stop, stop talking.
All I know is that the truck
looks like it's been rolled.
It's missing a goddamn...
Jesus Christ!
Bud!
It's not about what I saw.
If I even knew what that was...
It's just how much bigger it is.
How much older.
It's ancient.
Talk to me Jenkins, please.
Nothing!
Goddamn, nothing!
Holy Mary, mother of God.
You son of a bitch.
Be straight with me.
Can we kill this thing?
You still a sharpshooter?
You bet your sweet ass I am.
Hang on!
Get me up closer to that son of a bitch!
Take his tire out!
Hit him again!
What the hell are they made of?
Again!
Son of a bitch!
- Hold on!
- Jesus!
What the hell?
Mikey?
Oh, come here you big ugly bastard.
- Oh, my sweet...
- Christ!
Everything ricochets off that truck!
Mikey come in!
Mikey, listen to me!
That truck is not to be fired on!
Straight at it, Jenky!
Go!
Mikey, come in!
Michael, don't shoot at the goddamn truck!
Mikey!
Do you read me!
Mike, Mike come in!
Mikey, come in!
Michael, pick up!
Mikey, do you read me?
Don't shoot at that goddamn truck!
For my old man and a thousand others,
you ugly motherfucker!
Hold on!
Put your belt on!
Danny?
Danny!
Gah, Danny!
Take this!
Son of a...
Cover me.
Davis!
Get down!
Don't give him what he wants.
Swallow your fear.
Don't give it to him.
You cover me as best you can,
and then you haul your ass out of here.
It can't get both of us if we split up.
Split up?
We both gotta take him, Danny!
We need the firepower!
Hey!
Hey, you!
Davis!
Get the hell out of here!
Move!
Whatever you think you can do, you can't.
You're not going to stop me...
So go away.
They took her, mom.
It's got Addison now.
What?
Where's Addy?
You have reached the Tri-County
Sheriff's Department, servicing Bannon,
Kirtulla, and Poho Counties.
This line is for emergency calls only.
If this is an emergency,
please hold the line.
Addy?
Every 23rd Spring, for 23 days,
it gets to eat.
That's what we know.
And the terrible things
it leaves in its wake...
missing fathers and mothers.
Brothers, sisters, daughters and sons.
We know that, too.
The creature reshapes our minds
and changes the course of our lives.
What are you doing here?
They're picking me up here.
I didn't miss 'em, did I?
They're picking you up here?
So I could say goodbye.
They don't care, it's on the way.
Really, are you doing okay?
I'm out of the house.
Out in the sunshine.
And back with your old boyfriend, huh?
They say he's gone, you know.
Do you really believe it?
Gone for another 23 years?
Think we'll still be around here to find out?
I'm going to worry about you.
I can't believe they're letting you go.
For the last time we made it to state,
I don't think the armageddon
will keep us from going.
Is that your dad talking?
Oh, I got family up in Bollander.
I might stay an extra day.
I'm gonna miss you.
Well, I'll miss you more, I bet.
Keep an eye on my truck for me.
At the end of those 23 days, in an open
field by a broken-down school bus,
it once again ran out of time at
the rusty tip of a homemade harpoon.
But most of you know this already.
But I record these words as a testament.
This 23rd Spring is a call to arms.
We will not fail, and we will not fear.
My name is Trisha Jenner,
and this time when it comes,
I will destroy the thing
that killed my brother.
So...
come and get me you son of a bitch.