After everything we’ve seen,
there isn’t much that rattles either of us anymore.
But this one..
this one still haunts me.
Two months prior
to our involvement,
the Lutz family had fled
their home in the middle of the night
claiming that the house was haunted.
The Church had reached
out to us for help.
They wanted to see if we could
confirm the activity
that had been reported by the Lutz.
Okay, are you ready?
Then let's get started.
I’d like you to sit quietly
and close your eyes.
Envision yourself in a halo of
glowing white light.
It will protect you.
The year before the Lutz
moved in,
a young man named Ronnie DeFeo,
had brutally murdered his
entire family in this house.
We hoped to discover
if the killings
had been motivated purely by anger
or if,
as Ronnie DeFeo testified in court,
he had been under the influence
of something demonic.
What did you do?
(whispering) Shoot, shoot, shoot..
Honey, are you okay?
What are you seeing?
Lorraine!
Lorraine, what is happening?
- I have to see.
- We’re through.
We’re through.
It's time to come back.
What is happening?
He wants to show me.
Lorraine! Lorraine!
Honey? Honey?
Honey?
It’s okay.
This is as close to hell as
I’ll ever want to get.
Kit and I are going to sneak
outside with his friend Michael.
He wants to meet you, by the way.
No way. If my momma ever
found out, I’d be dead!
So then don’t get caught, you priest.
Hey, hold this.
Gonna give you back the spirit board
that we made.
I think I'll let Kit
french-kissed me.
What? No way!
What you two doing?
Janet, give that to me!
And get inside, both of you.
Go!
Ma-Ma-Ma-Margaret...
Margaret! Johnny!
Janet! Billy!
Hello, how was your day?
Not good.
Why? What happened?
It's a long story,
I’ll tell you later.
All right then.
Wh-wh-what’s up,
Bi-Bi-Bi-Billy?
Shut up, Peter!
- Lesbo.
- What, are you're talking about your mom?
- Thank you Camilla.
- No problem.
He’s just a wanker, ignore him.
K—K-K- Kay…
ENFIELD ELEMENTARY
GREEN STREET
HODGSON RESIDENCE
ENFIELD, ENGLAND - 1977
I cannot pay my rent this month.
You have to..
No, I talked to them,
and they put me through to you.
I am being calm!
Well I don’t understand
why you can’t help me.
No! He has not paid a penny
at all
for maintenance in three months.
We're home!
- Owh I see, that's bloody brilliant.
- Hi Mom!
Thank you, good afternoon as well.
Janet...
As things weren’t bad enough for me,
I got a call from your headmistress,
I wasn’t. I
wasn’t smoking,
- I promise.
- Did you get the biscuits?
Did you just not hear me? I talked
to Mrs. Moore on the telephone,
How you can stand there and lie to me like that!
- I'm not lying!
- Yes, she is!
It’s all over the school.
She was smoking with Camilla.
Shut up, you're such
a liar Johnny!
Mom, you-you said...
No Billy, I did not get
the bloody biscuits…
cause I don’t even have money!
Mom’s coming.
Quit messing with that
and brush your teeth.
All right.
Sounds like the whole city
is burning down in here.
- Look what I found?
- Biscuits!
But-but you-you said,
we don’t have any money?
Well, I’ve been meaning
to quit smoking anyway.
- Margaret?
- Yes?
You got your school
uniform for tomorrow?
Yes Mom, I'm getting it.
- Johnny, brush your teeth
- I did already.
Come on, Billy.
Time for bed.
I'm coming mom.
Whoah, where'd that come from?
Camilla and I
made it at school.
That… doesn’t look right.
It really works, I swear.
We already asked it all sorts of stuff.
Come on, I'll show you.
All right.
What should I ask?
I don’t know.
Whatever what you want.
Okay.
My sister and I want to know,
are there any spirits here that
Is dad ever coming home?
Are there any spirits here
Don’t worry about it.
It’s just a stupid game,
it isn’t real.
- Ugh, why’d you pounding on the door?
- No.
You balmy.
She said she wasn’t smoking!
I don’t mean to
agonise over it, Peg.
Gods knows, are you shared
a fag in school, didn’t you?
Oh, lots.
It’s not what she
did that bothers me.
She doesn’t listen to
what I say anymore, Pegs.
Just a phase, ain’t it?
I mean, I could punish her, but then I’ll feel guilty
because I know It’s not really her fault.
She loves her dad.
And she took it very hard
when he left, poor thing.
But I can’t just let it go
either, can’t I?
I’m loathed to ask, but have you
told Richard about it?
I would, if I ever saw him.
Sod.
Now it’s like I’m having to do both jobs,
I'm half the mom I was
before, I'm just…
rubbish, Peggy.
You’re not, Peggy. Don’t
be too hard on yourself.
Please stop it now!
We’re back with real life Ghost Hunters,
Ed and Lorraine Warren,
talking about their experiences
at the Amityville house.
And now we’re gonna talk to
my next guest,
Dr. Steven Kaplan,
who says that the investigations
the Warrens conducted into
is a load of hogwash.
Why is that?
Well, it’s been well established that
Amityville was a blatant hoax.
Well, it has never been proven.
Yes it has!
The Lutz family made everything up
so they can profit off of all the publicity.
That's just not true!
Look, we see this
all the time.
It's very easy to
sit on the outside,
and pick apart their story.
But it’s something very different to have
I don’t need to go to the moon to know
that is not made out of "green cheese".
Listen, Ed Warren’s
never seen a house
that he didn’t think was haunted.
By the time his wife is done
blowing smoke and ringing bells
they got everybody else to believing in ghosts too.
What exactly you are doctor of anyway?
Come on Warren, try and show
a little class, will you?
I'm not going to show
class with somebody
who is sitting here telling
lies about my wife and me.
Be very careful who you call a liar!
What are you gonna do about it?
We go on these shows
to inform people.
But every time I open my mouth,
- another one of those little ass..
- Ed!
Academics...
pops out, try to undo
everything we’ve done.
- Could you please take a breath?
- I know, I know..
I know, I'm counting to ten,
counting to ten.
Alright Billy, you ready
to do a speech?
The Crooked Man
? There was a crooked mad man
? he walked a crooked line
? He found a crooked six…
It’s all right.
Ready?
? He found a crooked six pence…
? Upon a crooked stair
? He bought a crooked cat...
? which caught a crooked mouse...
? And they all lived together
in a little crooked house.
The Crooked Man
Good boy!
You are getting so good.
- Now you may have a biscuit.
Alright, come one.
Off to bed with ya.
- Good night mom.
- Good night darling.
Now don’t eat too many of those, or you’ll
I…
won’t.
You promise?
- Alright, boys.
- Good night, Mom.
No.
Help.
Please stop.
- Janet.
- Please!
Janet, Janet, wake up,
you are dreaming.
This is my house.
No! No it’s not.
Get away!
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Playing a game with Billy.
Leave Billy alone.
Janet, who are you talking to?
You have to go away!
- You're the one trespassing!
- Janet, wake up!
I'll tell my mother
if you don’t stop.
- I'll break her neck!
- No!
Please!
- Join with Billy!
- No.
No!
Hey Janet?
- It’s all right.
It’s okay.
Go back to sleep.
Stay away from me!
Leave us alone!
Do you hear me?
Shut up. What are you doing?
There's no one here!
This is my house..
Mom!
Billy, what's wrong?
- There-there’s someone in my tent!
- What?
There-there’s someone in my te-tent!
You see? Nothing.
You just had a bad dream.
That's all.
Go to your room.
Oh my God!
Janet!
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
I think I’ve been
sleepwalking again.
What do you mean again?
Are you all right?
You are burning out.
Come on. Let's get
you back upstairs, eh?
I think it’s best you don’t
go to school tomorrow.
Come on. Let’s get
you back in bed, eh?
Hodgson's Residence .
Hi Mom.
Yeah, a little.
I just had some,
I’m not
really that hungry.
Yeah, I'm here.
Do you know when you’ll be home?
Right.
Bye, Mom.
My house!
You're up early.
Yeah, I couldn’t sleep.
- Are you inspired?
- I wouldn’t call it that.
I had this crazy dream.
I saw this thing.
When I woke up,
couldn’t get it out of my head, so..
I thought maybe this might help.
Hey, I know I'm no Picasso,
but didn’t think it was that bad.
We need to stop.
We could still do the
lectures but, no new cases.
At least not for a little while.
All right.
Could I ask why?
Because if it’s the tv shows
we won’t do that.
- Good morning.
Morning.
Do you trust me?
You know I do.
Then please trust me now.
Okay.
What’d you doing that for?
In case if I’m
sleep walking again.
Mom?
Johnny?
Janet, what’s wrong?
What is it?
There's someone in the room!
There is no one.
What you're talking about?
Mom! There's someone
in our room!
The bed is shaking
up and down.
Janet, I swear to God if
you’re making these up!
He bit me!
Look!
Oh my God!
You two been playing with this?
Taking turns, scaring the
wits out of each other?
No wonder I can’t get good night’s sleep!
But Mom...
No, I do not want to hear another word!
Now get back to bed
the lot of you!
NOTTINGHAM'S RESIDENCE
I seen it with my own eyes.
That bloody thing went
clear across the room.
- What?
- Well?
It was cold. I’ve been
through the house.
From top to bottom,
there’s no one there.
What about Margaret
and
Janet’s room? Did you…
Yes, I gone there. Every room.
Even went down the basement.
What he's doing?
Oh. We taught him to ring the bell,
when he wants to go.
Do you want to let him out, Billy?
Lo-lo-look!
Po-police are at our house.
What are they doing here?
- Well, I called them.
- What?
Well there’s got to be someone
- Probably.
- Yeah.
So ma’am, you didn’t
personally see the man yourself?
No.
But I don’t think she’s making it up.
Not anymore.
Well, look there has to be
some sort of explanation.
Sir, that’s why we're here, okay?
Bring me a chair from the kitchen.
It’s coming from inside the wall.
Them what? Mice maybe?
Big bloody mouse.
Well, there’s uh...
Nothing we can do about that.
We can file an incident report and
But that's about all.
A report?!
Oh, that’s brilliant!
A report of my house. That's
For God’s sake.
Listen.
I think this is a bit beyond us.
The priest at our Church is a
family friend.
I ask him to call on you.
Judy?
Honey?
What’s wrong?
Mom..
Who is that?
Go back..
Who are you?!
Tell me who you are!
Mom! Mom, wake up!
What do you want?!
I’m sorry, Lorraine.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
- Mrs. Hodgson?
- Yes?
My name is Kent Allen, we’re with
the
television news program Wide Angle.
I was hoping to have a word with you about the…
disturbance at your home last week.
How did you find out about that?
The police constables filed an incident report.
It’s had raised a few eyebrows.
I’d rather not have my business spread
all over the tele, if you don't mind!
- Good day.
- Is it still happening?
Because if it is, getting your side of the story,
I might be your best chance of finding help.
- Is it on?
- Okay.
CALLE GREEN
ENFIELD, LONDON
Behind the doors of this
seemingly normal house,
in Pondus End, North London
is a family, living in a nightmare.
PRIMARY ENFIELD
- I looked up and through the window,
plain as day, I see the younger girl Janet
HAZEL
GUARD SHORT CRUISE
- been flying around in the air,
like she is floating.
GRAHAM MORRIS
PHOTOGRAPHER
- So we ran back inside
and sure enough,
there’s little toys lego brick
flying all around the room.
One of them hit me right in the face,
so hard  it drew blood.
I saw the chair slide by itself
across the floor
PETERSON
OFFICIAL OFFICIAL HEPPS
at a distance of several feet.
PETERSON
OFFICIAL OFFICIAL HEPPS
- I check the chair for wires,
but could find nothing to explain it.
Maurice Grosse is an engineering consultant
and has been investigating these claims
for the Society for Psychical Research.
MAURICE GROSSE
ENGINEERING CONSULTANT
- Well, I do not think there is any
doubt at all.
The sheer number of documented
incidents in this case
is absolutely staggering.
But Anita Gregory,
a parapsychologist and lecturer at
the Polytechnic of North London
is not convinced.
ANITA GREGORY
parapsychologist / LECTURER /
SKEPTICAL
- Our principal characters
here are all children
and children can be
very ingenious pranksters.
At the centre of these frightening activities
is 11 year-old Janet Hodgson.
I’ve recently interviewed Janet
and her 14 year-old sister Margaret.
What happens next,
will astonish you.
How does it feel,
living in a haunted house?
I don’t know.
You don’t get used to it.
See, we were just a normal
family before all this.
It’s been getting worse since the
Mr. Grosse started talking to it.
How do you mean?
Like asking a question.
Saying nod twice for yes,
once for no.
That sort of thing.
And I wonder what will happen if
we tried talking to it now?
Is anybody there?
Is anybody there who
wishes to communicate?
I say again,
is anybody there?
Nothing?
Well it isn’t a juke box, is it?
Janet, are you all right?
Janet?
Janet, are you feeling all right?
Stop calling me Janet!
Isn’t that your name?
Janet is asleep.
and I'm talking.
Well, what should I call you?
What is your name?
You don’t belong here.
My name is Maurice Grosse.
Who are you?
This is my house.
Get out now.
No, this is not your house.
Now, what’s your name?
Knock, knock.
Very well.
Who’s there?
Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill.
Bill who?
My name is Bill Wilkins.
and I'm 72 years old.
Where do you come from?
I come from the grave.
How did you die?
I went blind and
had a haemorrhage
and I fell asleep and died in
the chair in the corner.
Why have you come here?
I like to hear them scream.
Why didn’t you just leave us alone!
Shut up, you old cow.
Janet, darling..
- Darling, are you all right?
- I'm sorry.
Janet?
THE HOUSE OF BIZARRE INCIDENTS
Peggy, what am I gonna do?
Well, you don’t need to think
about it tonight and...
you and the kids can stay
here as long as you like.
Ma-mom...
Billy, aren’t you supposed
to get ready for bed?
I-I thought you might like some biscuits.
Thank you.
? He bought a broken cat
which caught a broken mouse
Baron?
was a crooked man
and he walked a crooked mile.
No. Mom!
- Mom! Mom
- What? What happened?
What is it?
- The crooked man!
- What crooked?
What are you talking about darling?
The crooked man.
Calm down and just tell me what has happened.
- What happened?
- What is it?
I don’t know, I think he has been
walking around…
The crooked man stepped forth and...
rang the crooked bell
And thus his crooked soul...
spiralled into a crooked Hell
Murdered his crooked family...
and laughed a crooked laugh
Janet!
Oh my God!
No!
Someone get an ambulance!
This is my house
Get out now!
No, this is not your house.
Now, what’s your name
Knock, knock..
Very well.
Who’s there?
Bill, Bill, Bill, Bill
Bill, who?
My name is Bill Wilkins
and I'm 72 years old.
What do you make of that voice?
Sounds confused.
Is it senile?
The voice on this tape,
is coming from a 11 year-old girl.
The family reached out
to the Church for help?
Yes, but...
Truthfully, we have been
reluctant to get involved.
The case has turned into a
media circus over there.
And they are calling it
England’s Amityville.
Great.
Are you afraid it’s a hoax?
The Church’s ability to help people
depends on it’s reputation.
So what do you
want us to do?
We’d like you to fly to London.
For three days to act as a..
our unofficial eyes and ears.
Now you don’t have to do anything.
If it is a hoax, you just
turn around and leave.
But if it is not..
then there is a
family in London
that desperately needs our help.
Well thank you for
your faith in us.
- Just let me know.
- Okay.
I told him we’ll talk about it.
There's nothing to talk about.
Honey, you heard him.
They do not want us to get involved,
There have always been
cases we’ve turned down,
There have never been a
family that we refused to help.
I had a vision in Amityville.
It was the same one
I had 7 years ago.
I had a premonition
of your death.
Wait, that's why you locked
yourself away for eight days?
You saw my death?
You’ve seen it too.
The demon in your painting is real.
We have both seen the same
inhuman spirit.
It’s a warning,
if we keep doing this...
You’re going to die.
Your visions are a gift from God.
And if God is showing you my
death, he’s doing it for a reason.
Maybe you were meant to
prevent it from happening.
Come on. We don’t
run from fights.
If we go, if we do this,
you have to promise me that
we are just there to observe.
If everything turns out
we’re gonna tell the
Church and we’re gonna get out.
Promise me.
Promise me, Ed.
I promise.
Mr and Mrs Warren,
I am Maurice Grosse,
thank you so much for coming.
I believe you’re gonna be
staying in the Hodgson house,
is that right?
Always better to be on the mix.
Oh, yeah I agree.
This is it.
Here we are.
Ed, we managed to capture
some amazing things.
I think you’ll be very impressed
with what you see.
Great, yeah I'd like to listen
to those tapes again too.
There’s really interesting stuff in it.
Vic Nottingham. Hi Vic.
- How are you? Ed Warren.
- Hello mate.
How are you?
And this is Peggy, Peggy Hodgson.
- Nice to meet you, Ed Warren.
- How do you do?
- My wife Lorraine.
- Hello.
Well, I’ll be off here Pegg.
Will you tell the kids I said hello.
Yeah of course I will.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too, Hon.
So here we are, Peggy.
Well do come in.
It’s just me and Janet here now.
My other kids are staying with them.
This is where the girls used slept, but...
- We don’t use it anymore.
- Why not?
Well most of the activity
centred in this room,
we were quite afraid that someone might get hurt,
that’s why we kept it locked.
I understand that Janet
has levitated?
Does that happened in here as well?
- Yeah..
We’ve got photographs of that as well.
I would like to hear Mrs. Hodgson’s
The neighbors donated them all.
I hung them up hoping to keep
things from moving around.
- Does it work?
- No.
We can hear it all night.
Hi there, I'm Lorraine.
Mind if I have a sit?
Do you know why I’m here?
Well, your mom’s told me about
what’s been going on..
and I'm here
to help if I can.
Would you like to talk about it?
You know when I was about your age,
I was visiting my mom in a hospital,
and.. I saw an angel.
Yeah.
It was..
standing next to a little waste bed,
and just gently touching his cheek,
and it stopped then
it looked right at me.
Of course my mom and the
nurses did not believe me...
but I knew it was real.
Look, I know how it is.
I know what it’s like to lose your
friends, because you're different.
But I also know that..
One person can change everything.
And you just have to open up to them.
How did you know you could trust
the people you have been talked to?
I didn’t.
Sometimes I got hurt.
And it took a long time, but..
I finally found someone who believed me.
What did you do then?
I married him.
I'm just so tired.
I can’t sleep here.
I used to go to the medical at school.
And they let me sleep there.
Because I was so worn out.
But now I can’t even do that.
Everyone’s afraid of me.
I got no friends.
No place I can go to.
It makes me feel like I'm not normal.
You know, whatever’s
doing this to you..
wants you to feel this way.
But why?
Because.. that’s what makes it stronger.
Around the time
this all started..
Janet started waking up
here, in the middle of the night.
This is the spot Janet said
Bill Wilkins died,
right here.
Where’d you get it from?
My ex-husband bought all the furniture
with the house when we moved in.
If you don’t mind me asking,
is your ex-husband still in the picture?
No.
Sorry to hear that.
Is there any chance of
reconciliation?
He had twins with a woman
from around the corner.
I’m gonna take that as a "no".
Yes, it’s been a lot to do with.
He took all the music
the day he left.
I know most feel like that sometimes..
No, I mean he literally took
away all the records.
My kids used to love listening to
his Elvis collection.
They've been through so much.
And now all these is happening on top.
Yeah, the timing
isn’t a coincidence.
Negative event like this
often feed off on emotional distress.
They like to kick you when you're down.
Well that hardly seemed fair.
No, it really isn’t.
Do you know when the voice
is going to speak?
Sometimes.
And when it does, does it feel like
it’s coming from inside you?
No.
Well it's coming from behind me.
Like I’m being used.
Does it ever say things,
just to you?
That only you can hear?
What is it saying?
It says it wants to hurt you.
When did it say that?
Right now.
Do we really need that?
We would like to be able to prove to the
Church that
she is not making the voice herself.
So by holding the water in her mouth,
we would be able to show
that it is not some form of ventriloquism.
Does she have to be in the chair?
Just..
make me sick seeing her sitting there like that.
You know it's hard, but the spirit
has shown an attachment to the spot.
It will be easier for Ed to contact her,
if she is sitting there.
You'll be alright.
Are you ready for this?
I guess so.
It’s December 21st, 1977.
This is Ed and Lorraine Warren,
sitting with Peggy and Janet Hodgson,
also present, is Maurice Grosse.
Alright, let’s get started.
If there is something here that
would like to communicate with us,
we are all ears. Speak up.
What do you want with this
girl and her family?
It says it won’t talk, if you all
are looking at me like this.
Strange! I wonder why not?
It hasn’t been shy of talking up until now.
How about if we all turn our backs?
Think it’ll speak if we all do that?
Maybe.
Well.
Let's try this again.
So what do you think Bill?
We’ve given you your privacy.
Now come on out and talk to us.
Here I come..
Am I talking to the spirit that
is
oppressing this family?
Is that what I am?
Is that what I’m doing?
Yes.
And I’ve come to put a stop to it.
Do you know who I am?
Ed..
Eddie..
Edward.
Ed, is fine.
Your father called you "Edward".
Not true.
My father called me Ed,
just like everybody else.
Come on Bill, you're
not psychiatrist..
and I’m not here to talk
about my father.
Let’s get down to business,
what do you say?
Why don’t you just leave
these people alone?
Because this is my house.
It’s not your house.
Yes, it is.
I’ve come here to see my family
but they’re not here now.
That’s because you're dead.
If your family did lived here,
they’re long gone now.
Ed..
Where are they?
I don’t know. If I did
maybe I can help you.
I don’t need your help.
Then why don’t you just move on?
I don’t believe in that.
Why not?
What would be so wrong
with going to Heaven?
I.. I'm not a heaven man.
Well I’ve got news for you Bill..
See, I don’t care what you believed in.
You see this?
Help! Me.. let.. go..
Help! It.. let.. go..
Are you sensing a presence?
No, just the opposite,
I’m not sensing anything.
We could be looking at..
hysterical neurosis.
That would explain the
multiple personalities and..
hallucinations.
That doesn’t feel right either.
I can’t explain it, in my heart,
it’s telling me to believe them.
I heard that voice,
with my own ears.
But all I can sense
is their own fear.
I can’t seem to see beyond that.
I don’t think I can sleep
this far away from you.
Well you’re gonna.
I’ll give you something to look
forward to when we get home.
Oh love, I wish you
wouldn’t do that!
It helps me sleep.
At least I know I'm not going anywhere.
I didn’t smoke, mom.
Hey?
That day with Camilla at school.
I was holding the cigarette,
but I wasn’t going to
take a puff, I swear.
I just wanted to look
cool in front of her.
It’s stupid.
Oh, love!
I’m sorry I didn’t believed you.
Oh God!
Help!
Janet? Oh my God!
Janet?
- Help!
- Janet!
Janet!
- Mom!
- Janet!
Help, get me out.
There is somebody in here.
I can’t open it!
Mom, help me!
Janet!
- Mom! Mom!
- Janet!
- What’s going on?
- There is someone in there with Janet.
I can’t get it open!
Get the key!
Go!
Janet, hold on!
We’re coming!
Help me!
- I got the key!
Come on!
Janet, we’re coming.
It’s ok.
Janet!
Take it off me.
Please take it off!
My God!
It was someone in here!
I saw it with me own eyes.
He did this to my girl.
This is the bite where
Janet received the first night.
It has faded a bit here,
Yeah, it's pretty distinctive,
two missing teeth.
That's right. It's too big
for one of the children.
You think this
was the spirit?
This Bill Wilkins?
I tracked down the home owner,
and it turns out the
owner’s
father lived there.
His name was William Wilkins.
And he died of a haemorrhage
in
the brain in that chair.
Everything she said is true.
All public information, by the way.
She could have heard the
whole story
from a neighbor.
And what about the claim that Janet has
been
teleporting around the house in her sleep?
About as valid as the claims of
her levitating off her bed.
Were any of you there
when it happened?
No, but I have
pictures of that too.
Yeah, there you go.
I set my camera up
in the girls' room
and then I went downstairs
with the remote control
and fire it off whenever
I heard any commotion.
I have to admit,
well her knees are bend..
the upright position of her body,
looks like she is just jumping.
What are you saying? You were there last
night, you saw with your own eyes.
Well..
Peggy was the one who saw
someone attacking Janet.
But she teleported herself into a
room
locked from the outside
for goodness sake!
And what about her voice?
How the heck do you explain that?
I think..
the first time she
was making that voice..
was in front of
television cameras.
And she couldn’t do it
with water in her mouth,
until you looked away.
So, she could have spit it out,
take another sip
before you turn back.
Last year I was conned by Welsh family
pretending to be possessed by demons.
Honestly, I don’t know what
was worse, the demons,
or the people who preyed on our
willingness to believe in them.
The Demons..
are worse.
But you must admit it is suspicious.
You sincerely believed that
And what about Peggy?
Oh, she is just using the whole thing as an excuse
to get better housing from the council.
She already applied!
Look, I’m not saying it’s a hoax.
Sometimes what we do,
requires a leap of faith.
To believe when
nobody else will.
So, you really do believe them?
Yes, we do.
But the Church can’t do
anything without proof.
That’s what we need.
Right. I'll make some telephone
calls, see if I can
get hold of some video
recording equipment.
In the meantime, Ed and I can be
spending time with Peggy and the kids.
Cause they need to be a family again.
Hi Mom, we’re back!
Oh, you did what?
What’s all this?
- Mr. and Mrs. Warren bought us some wine.
Oh, Blue Hawaii.
Hope you don’t mind,
a little American culture.
Not at all.
Billy! I missed you!
Hi guys. I missed you.
So have any of you ever been
Pete, at school. He is
always picking on Billy.
And dear tell me, what do
you do
when that happens?
T—t-t-they stick up for me.
Good, because the spirit in this
house is a lot like that bully.
Yes.
And he’s got it in for Janet.
So you guys got to stick up for her,
the same way they stick up for you.
Family sticks together.
This on the other hand,
is a lost cause.
Oh, bloody hell!
Now all sorts of things stopped working,
for no reason at all.
Well, we’re gonna have music
in here, one way or another.
Whose guitar is that?
It was Dad’s, but he
said I could have it.
Yeah, do you mind?
No.
A little rusty, so
got to promise not to laugh.
Especially you.
? Wise men say
? only fools rush in
Thank you.
Hey, don’t laugh now.
? But I can’t help falling
in love with you
Shall I stay ?
? would it be a sin?
? If I can’t help falling
in love with you
? Like a river flows surely to the
Hi Peggy, we're here.
sea ?
Darling so we go
? Some things are meant to be
Everybody now.
? Take my hand, take my whole life too
? For I can’t help can’t help
falling in love with you
? For I can’t help
falling in love with you...
Thank you very much!
Oh my God!
It's so small and light!
Why do you do this?
Help people like us?
When you were little,
were you ever worried that there might be
something hiding under your bed at night?
Well..
In my bed, actually had
something under.
Yeah..
Something grabbed my hand and
It was too dark to
see under there,
but let me tell you I r
an out of there so fast..
You know what my dad did?
He dragged me right back into the room,
and told me I had to face my fears.
And I was scared to death,
but then I remembered what this
nun had told me in catechism.
God will be there for all who need it.
So..
I grab this crucifix out,
from my nightstand, right..
And I tell whatever’s under there..
that it better leave
or God was gonna kick its butt.
Best thing my father ever did for me.
Of course he only did it because
he really didn’t believed me.
It took me years to finally
find someone who did.
And you know I did then?
You married her?
So you’ve heard this story before?
How are you getting on in here?
Good!
We’re done here.
fixed the closet door too.
And if you’d like, I can take
a look at the washing machine.
Oh no, I couldn’t ask
you to do that.
- It's a disaster down there.
- Come on.
How bad can it be?
Bloody hell!
Everything’s still quiet in there?
Yes, thank goodness, yes.
It would be something now, wouldn’t it?
If we were able to prove
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that there is a life
beyond this.
It would be historic.
Is that why you’re doing this?
Because you want to be a
part of something "historic"?
This isn’t a laboratory.
This is someone's home.
And I think helping that family
No, I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean that.
My daughter died in a car crash
several years ago.
Afterwards, I started to..
experience things..
I think she wanted
to communicate with me.
And yes it would help if I knew
that she was..
I do not know.
Somewhere.
That’s not it.
Oh, great!
I think I found it.
It’s right here.
(Thumping)
Uh..
God.
Alright.
Yeah.
What’s that?
Ed?
There's something behind you.
Come here!
It grabbed me.
It was in me. It tried
to pull me under.
Oh my god, look!
- Oh God, you’re scratched.
- It’s not a scratch.
It's a bite mark, it bit me
just
like it did with Janet.
- Hey Janet, can you get me another one?
- Yeah.
Janet?
What’s wrong?
Don’t you see it?
See what?
In the kitchen.
Tell me what you see.
It’s playing with the knives.
Hiding in the dark.
Johnny?
Johnny, what are you doing?
Johnny, no!
Johnny don’t go!
Remember what Mr. Warren said.
We can’t let it bully us.
This is our house.
Johnny!
Johnny, please come back!
What’s the matter?
What happened?
Janet’s gone!
She was just right here!
- Come on!
- Oh no!
No.
- Mom!
- Johnny!
Ed, what’s going on?
Johnny’s in there!
- No!
- Mom!
Johnny!
- Johnny!
- Okay. Please step back!
Where are they?
Johnny?
Johnny!
- Oh, darling, come here.
- Mom!
Are you all right?
It’s alright, darling.
Where is Janet?
Janet!
Guys, I'm picking up something in here.
Oh Ed, watch it.
It.. want.. me..
want me..
- Janet!
- It’s okay, it’s okay. Come on.
Come on.
Come on out.
I got you..
Janet.
Yeah..
It's over.
How did she get in there?
It’s alright, darling.
What’s that?
Can I..?
What is it?
She's faking it.
What?
I have proof.
So much for your leap of faith.
What?
My girl didn’t make this up.
I’ve seen things.
She was caught red
handed faking an event.
No, it's not possible.
Have you seen it in there?
How can a 12 year old girl
throw a table across the room? It’s…
It's over! Do you understand?
For the sake of your daughter, don’t
make this harder than it already is.
She couldn’t have pull this off alone.
Oh how dare you!
What you think I put her up to this?
What about the police?
Are they on this too?
It’s alright.
What about you two?
You believed us, don’t you?
We want to help.
But the Church take one look at that video,
and that will be the end of it.
They’ll want to distance
themselves from anything that..
remotely resembles a hoax.
I want you to leave, please.
Now go and get out!
Get out the lot of ya!
Get out!
Perhaps you could somehow
reach out to the spirit
make contact with it yourself.
I can’t.
Believe me I tried.
I’m sorry. I’m just not
sensing anything here.
So that’s it then?
You hold out a lifeline to them and
then you just throw it away.
We don’t like this anymore than you do.
We’ll tell the Church about everything we’ve seen,
but the only piece of concrete evidence we got
is a video of Janet
faking an incident.
Hasn’t it been literally
dozens
of genuine incidents?
You might want this.
- doesn’t change the fact...
- No, it changes everything.
We are agents of the Church here.
They’d be calling us home even if
You’ve done really good work here Maurice.
You were here for them when no one else was.
Thank you.
But sometimes you need
to make a leap of faith.
Believe, when nobody else will.
This doesn’t feel right.
I know.
Did you really do it?
But why?
It said it would kill you.
If I didn’t make them leave.
Don’t you think it’s a little convenient
that she just happens to fake an
incident in the one room in the house,
that had a video camera pointing at it?
Yeah.
Damn it!
Lorraine?
Help me set up these tape recorders.
Thread it through and start it from the top.
Alright.
Remember those strange garbled
messages
we got from Janet?
You know from.. Bill.
- Yes
- There were two of them, right?
This is the first one.
Help! It.. let.. go..
- We thought it was referring to
himself, right?
- Yes.
Listen to the second one.
It.. won't..
me... won't.. me..
If I’m right about this...
Help me! It won’t let me go!
I come here..
to see my family.
But they're not here now.
I think..
I’d like to go now.
- But I can’t.
- Why not?
It wants her..
so badly.
It almost has her.
Tell me how to stop it.
I'm giving..
and I’m taking.
I was there at your first breath.
It didn’t asked for me.
But I'll follow you
till death!
Wait, I don’t understand..
Please..
Oh God. Honey, you're bleeding!
What is happening?
The old man’s spirit
is just a pawn.
He’s been enslaved
to weaken Janet’s will.
Enslaved? Enslaved by who?
Something inhuman. Something that’s taking
a blasphemous form to attack my faith.
There is a demonic presence in that house.
You need to get Vic before he
leaves.
We need to go back!
Okay.
Mom, help me, please!
Mom, please!
Mom, help me!
Help!
For God’s sake,
leave us alone!
Margaret?
Margaret, no!
Margaret, come on honey.
- Come on.
- Mom?
What is happening?
Come on let’s get out.
Go to Peggy’s house!
- Are you not coming?
- I can't leave Janet.
No, Janet!
Mom!
Janet!
I don’t understand it, I mean first
you said it's not real..
Now it is.
Our sight are being blocked by the inhuman spirit.
The old man’s spirit,
couldn’t break though until
we left that house.
Everything they have experienced has been
a manifestation of that demonic.
The old, the crooked man,
are just facade,
trying to keep us from seeing
the real evil in that house.
In my vision, he wanted to help
me
but he was too afraid.
And he kept speaking in a
kind of riddle.
Something like..
I am given and I am taken,
I was there, at your first breath.
You didn’t asked for me.
But I will follow you
until your death.
Your name..
you didn’t asked for it, it was given
when you were born.
That’s it! Knowing the demon’s name..
gives us power over it, and we can cast it out.
Yeah. Sure, but don’t
know it’s name.
Or maybe we do.
Why else would he gave us that clue?
He must think that we knew it somehow.
So what do you do now?
An inhuman spirit powerful enough
to cloud Lorraine’s sight..
is more than a match for me.
We need to bring Janet to the
Janet!
Margaret?
Oh thank God you’re here,
Janet is in there.
- Ed, are you okay?
- Yes.
I'm gonna go around the back.
No, Ed! No!
- Peggy, stay here.
- No, no..
Wait in the car with the kids.
Wait...
Janet!
Get in the car.
Come on, come on!
You too Peggy, come on!
Ed?
Come on!
Ed!
It won’t open.
- Let me try.
- Shit!
We have to break it down!
- Alright, wait here…
- Break it!
Ed hon, wait right there.
- Wait, Vic will be right back.
- I can’t wait!
I’m going on to her.
No, Ed don't!
Stop!
You can’t fight this alone.
She needs our help.
Ed, please! Please just wait for me..
Please wait for me.
I can’t lose you.
I'm so scared.
I know.
Me too.
But I have to help her.
But what about my vision?
I know I made a promise to you honey..
but I have to do this.
I love you, Lorraine.
Ed, no!
No!
Don’t go!
<Ed!
No!
No. No..
Help
Janet, where are you?
Help!
Janet!
Help me!
In the Name of the Father,
and the Son
and the Holy Spirit.
What’s your name?
What’s..
I do know your name.
I asked you.
Tell me who you are!
And you told me..
You told me your name.
And I wrote it down!
I need my Bible.
Why? What’s happening? What?
The demon’s name
gives us power over it.
V-A-L-A-K
Valak.
Janet!
? There was a crooked mad man
? he walked a crooked mile
? He found a crooked six pence
? Upon a crooked stair
? he bought a crooked cat..
? which caught a crooked mouse
? And they all lived together
in a little crooked
Vic! Vic!
Let me through!
- Lorraine No, wait!
- I'm going in.
Let me go in! Lorraine!
Ed!
Lorraine!
Janet!
No.
Janet, no!
Don’t!
I got you.
Oh my God!
No!
- Janet!
- Ed!
Ed!
Lorraine!
Your name gives me
dominion over you, Demon.
And I do know your name.
You are Valak.
The difiler.
The profane.
The marquis of snakes.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy spirit.
I condemn you back to Hell!
No!
Ed!
- I have you.
- Ed!
Dear God.
Janet!
- Oh my gosh!
- Alright!.
- Ed, are you okay?
- Check on her.
Janet? Oh my God!
Is she alright?
I'll call an ambulance.
Sit up.
Here you go, take a big deep breath.
Take a deep breath.
There you go.
He'll be fine.
She looked alright.
- You saved her.
- No.
You saved us.
Didn’t I tell you it was meant to be?
But you believed in me.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Thanks for coming back for us.
Come here, sit down.
Sit down.
You know..
This has kept me safe
since I was a kid.
I want you to have it.
And when you grow up..
You find someone who needs it,
you give it to them.
Deal?
I'm so lucky.
You said one person
could change everything.
But..
I’ve got two.
Translated by opt