This spray will freeze
the trigger mechanism...
give us a split second.
So on the count of three...
what I want you to...
Merlin!
(PANTING)
Merlin, what the fuck
have you done?
Our journey together
began many years ago...
when your father
did the same thing for us.
Our journey began
with a mistake I made.
Give me the can.
That's an order.
Can's empty.
Split second's over.
You two need to get going.
No, no, no.
There's got to be another way.
HARRY: He's right.
Mission comes first.
Bollocks, mission comes first!
Eggsy!
This is no time for emotion.
Remember your training.
Or we all die.
Now get on with it.
Do as you're told.
Move it!
Go.
It's been an honor.
Good luck.
MERLIN:
♪ Almost heaven ♪
(GUNS COCKING)
♪ West Virginia ♪
♪ Blue Ridge Mountains ♪
♪ Shenandoah River ♪
Poppy, come in.
POPPY: Roger.
♪ Life is old there ♪
GUARD: Are you expecting
another lawyer?
♪ Older than the trees ♪
GUARD: There's
a guy here singing.
♪ Younger than the mountains ♪
Singing?
♪ Blowin' like a breeze ♪
♪ Country roads ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ To the place ♪
♪ I belong ♪
POPPY: Bring him to me.
♪ West Virginia ♪
♪ Mountain momma ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ Country road ♪
GUARD 2: Poppy,
we got a situation here.