(GROANING)
(POWERING DOWN)
Give me the code!
I can't.
Only Poppy knows it.
Well, then you're no use
to me, are you?
For the record, Charlie...
I'm more of a gentleman
than you'll ever be.
But right now, it's time
to drop the gentle bit.
This is for Kingsman.
For my mate Brandon.
For Roxy.
For JB.
And for Merlin.
Good night, bruv.
(NECK SNAPS)
(PANTING)
Hey, fellas.
You're going to
give us the code.
(GASPS) Mmm.
Or what?
'Cause you don't seem like
the kind of gentleman
who would hurt a lady.
Perhaps not.
Call me old-fashioned...
I don't consider genocide
especially ladylike.
Right. Enough small talk.
Give us the code.
Sure.
No. I don't think so.
Ooh!
Ow!
Heroin.
You know, where I come from...
this shit you've been peddling's
ruined a lot of lives.
But yours is even more deadly.
But it feels so nice,
it's gonna make you
lower your guard.
Mmm.
Our colleague, Merlin,
may he rest in peace...
managed to synthesize your
horrible little formula...
and speed up its effects.
So I would say you have
just under eight minutes...
before paralysis sets in
and your breathing stops.
But, of course,
you know all about that.
So here's the deal.
You release the antidote worldwide,
and we make sure you get a dose.
I have to give you
the code to live?
Honey, you're so smart.
You should work for me.
Right. Give us the code.