(BARKING)
(YELLING)
No, Miss Poppy!
(SCREAMING)
Good job!
(PANTING)
See my salon across the way?
Head there for your makeover.
(SIZZLING)
PRINCESS TILDE: Eggsy,
I hope you're hungry.
Oh, babe, I was gonna
grab breakfast at work.
This looks lovely,
but I'm running late.
I just thought maybe
we could practice?
For tonight.
Practice?
Mm-hmm.
Eating?
You said you've never
eaten at a palace before.
And Pappa is sort of picky
about table manners.
Well, as it happens, babe,
I've got this shit on lock.
I know what every single one
of them knives and forks is for.
This is a butter knife.
It's the only one
you need to remember,
the rest of the cutlery is easy.
You start from the outside,
and you work your way in
with each course.
And never let anyone
describe you as "H.K.L.P."...
What's that?
"Holds knife like pen."
A habit erroneously believed
to be upper class
dining etiquette.
It is quite the opposite.
White wine, pudding wine,
red wine, water and pop.
Or whatever tipple
takes your fancy.
Am I supposed to wait
for everyone else
to be served
before I start eating?
HARRY: Only if the dish
being served is cold.
Or if the Queen is present.
Otherwise tuck in.
EGGSY: Got to be honest...
never really thought
the royalty bit would be relevant.
Harry would've been chuffed.
Oh. I wish I could've met him.
You miss him too,
don't you, Mr. Pickle?
Mmm?