(laughing)
Huh? Yeah.
Take Poppy Adams and her so-called
Golden Circle down with them.
No drug users, no drug trade.
It's a win-win situation here.
But, sir, we're not talking about
a handful of hostages.
We could be looking
at the deaths
of hundreds
of millions worldwide.
Hundreds of millions
of criminals,
burdens to society.
Am I right, McCoy?
Absolutely, sir.
But, sir, that's...
What about people who were
just experimenting?
Folks who self-medicate?
Functioning
professionals? Kids?
Oh, spare me the crap, Fox.
(CHUCKLES) The fact is,
this presidency has just
won the war on drugs.
Congratulations, sir.
Thank you.
And that deserves a toast.
FOX: This is
totally unethical, sir.
PRESIDENT: Fox, shut up!
McCoy, declare martial law.
We need to keep control,
commandeer stadiums,
schools, civic centers...
order a press blackout.
And put the military on standby
to round these junkies up.
Whether they broke
the law or not,
those victims are human beings.
Tequila.
He's a great guy.
And a great agent.
Right now, he's lying in deep
freeze waitin' on our help.
We can't make
this personal, sir.
Personal?
Agent, we can't stand by
and let folks like him die.
These people,
we're their only hope.
Now, we have
to find that antidote.
Poppy's stockpiles, well,
they could be anywhere.
HARRY:
She must have some on hand.
Locate Poppy...
and obtain a sample
for analysis.
Maybe it can be replicated.
GINGER: Sorry to cut in, guys.
But Charlie is on the phone
with his girlfriend.
Looping you in now.
CLARA: Don't worry.
I'm on a payphone...
covered in a fucking blue rash.
Why didn't you tell me?
All you said was,
"Don't take any drugs."
It was a music festival
for fuck's sake.
Fuck. Shit. Shit! Okay.
Listen. You need to get
to the lab in Italy.
Do you remember
where we went skiing?
Yes. Yes, I remember.
Yeah. Meet me there
and I'll give you the antidote.
(SIGHS)
Okay.
All right. Jet's ready.
Whiskey, Galahad, get to Italy.
You two need to fix
this code name thing.
And with all due respect, sir...
I don't think Galahad senior
is ready to return to fieldwork.
I did actually mean...
Of course.
And with all disrespect...
I'm not going anywhere
without him.