for our own agents...
in the event of a head shot.
The gel protects the brain.
Then, in the lab,
we use nanites...
micro-bots,
to repair tissue damage.
There are side effects.
Partial amnesia...
regression to the younger self.
With no idea who he was,
there was nothing we could do.
But now you guys are here...
there's a good chance
we can bring him back.
POPPY: You're late.
Why are you still wearing that?
Until you get rid of
the perimeter landmines...
I'll keep wearing the suit,
thank you very much.
POPPY: Scaredy-cat.
Shut up and sit down.
Let's go!
(BEEPS)
CHARLIE:
Crocodile Rock, please.
Fuck you!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GROANING)
Hey, hey, Elton, language.
Okay, as fabulous
as your catalogue is...
I think I want to hear
some Gershwin.
(SIGHS)
(PLAYING PIANO)
I still can't believe...
you got away with
kidnapping Elton John.
I know! But with Valentine
abducting those celebrities...
it seemed silly not to take
advantage of the confusion.
Shit. Has Elton
got the blue rash?
Lights.
(PIANO PLAYING STOPS)
Hey, Elton.
Have you been a bad boy again?
Mmm-mmm.
You're lying.
Look at your hands.
What is it?
It's proof that my plan
is gonna work.
It's also the first sign
of a slow and horrible death.
(GASPS)
Don't worry, I can fix it.
Tell me who you partied with.
(SIGHS)
It was Angel.
Huh, not very angelic.
Gonna have to clip his wings.
(SIGHS)