Harry's like a computer
that needs to be rebooted.
We need to recreate a shock
or trauma from his past...
to trigger his memory.
MERLIN: I hope you're right.
(GASPS)
Uh, excuse me.
There seems to be
some sort of a problem here.
Help! Somebody!
What the hell is
going on? Help me!
Help!
Oh, God!
Stop! Fuck!
Get him out now.
No, no, wait. His instincts
are gonna kick in.
(MUFFLED YELLING)
No. I'm sorry to do this.
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
Are you okay?
What happened?
Harry, you've forgotten
who you are.
We thought this might
jog your memory.
Look, when you were young,
you had a choice.
To either be a lepidopterist
or to join the army.
You chose the army.
That led to Kingsman.
You became a Kingsman agent.
I doubt whether
I'd work for anyone
who drowns their employees.
I want to go home.
I want my butterfly collection.
I want to see Mother.
GINGER: There's nothing more
we can do.
It's time to let him go.
EGGSY: Babe, I wish
I could stay longer,
but I've got to go on
with this mission.
Wait, wait, wait.
Before you go,
I wanna show you something.
EGGSY: Aw!
I know he could
never replace JB...
but...
Oh, my days.
I hoped he might make you happy.