Get it?
"Viva las..."
Mmm.
(SLURRING)
Come snuggle with me.
I like you.
(DISTORTED) I don't think
that's terribly likely.
(LAUGHING)
She's OD'd.
You gave her too much.
Did I?
You know, I really don't have
as much experience with all this drug stuff...
as people think.
Better be the right code.
(SIGHS)
"Viva las..."
So?
Don't move, kid.
You try anything funny,
and I'll turn
this thing electric.
Now give up your guns,
fellas. Slide 'em over.
Whiskey.
We are all
on the same side here.
You've had a head injury.
The exact same thing
happened to Harry.
You're havin'
some sort of brain glitch.
Nope. My brain's
all good, kid.
And you know what?
I reckon the same was true for your friend
Harry over here.
Real fine instincts,
I'll give him that.
So stay still...
or I'll dice him up so small,
you can take him
home in a bucket...
and still have room
for what's left
of your buddy, Merlin.
Well, that's just fucking great.
You're working
for the president?
That asshole?
(CHUCKLES)
Hell no. It's a matter
of personal principle, agent.
No more drug users.
And the Statesman
share price rockets.
So those are your principles?
Making money?
Our agencies were
founded to uphold peace.
To protect the innocent.
Do you wanna know
who was innocent?
My high school sweetheart.
Love of my life.
Pregnant with my little boy.
He'd be about your age now...
if his mama hadn't got caught
in the crossfire...
when two meth head freaks
decided to rob
a fucking convenience store.
A world without
those people in it...
sure smells like peace to me.
You break the law...
you pay the price.
Good riddance...
to all of them.
That's why I got
to destroy that case.