It's a lasso.
EGGSY: Whatever.
Come on.
(CHAMP LAUGHS)
Go on. Vamoose.
WHISKEY: Yes, sir.
Drink it.
(SIGHS)
(GASPING)
Wow.
CLARA: It's working already.
(sighs) Thank God.
Agent Whiskey.
Antidote confirmed
at the target's location.
Good luck.
WHISKEY: Hold up.
We need you down here, Galahad.
To secure the control room.
EGGSY:
Probably a good idea, Harry.
Call you from the top, yeah?
Buongiorno!
Buongiorno.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(BEEPING)
Hey!
(IN ENGLISH)
So sorry about this.
At the controls. In position.
Keep this cable car here
till we get back.
HARRY: Roger that, Eggsy.
Clara's definitely here.
We're getting warmer.
Harry Hart, Harry Hart,
super spy, super spy.
Looks like we've got a door.
GINGER: Yep.
There you go.
I'll cover.
Hi, there.
Whew.
Sorry I'm late.
You guys did not make
this place easy to find.
Who are you?
I'm here to collect
this antidote.
For Singapore?
Yeah.
You are Wu Ting Feng?