It's a day
of worldwide celebration
as millions rejoice...
after they or their loved ones
were saved from death.
(MOTHER SIGHS)
(PARENTS EXCLAIMING)
FEMALE NEWS ANCHOR:
Distribution of The Golden Circle antidote continues...
and field hospitals
are emptying...
as victims return
to their homes tonight, cured.
Come on, Liam. Man, come on.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
(both laughing)
I love you, man!
I love you!
I'm never touching
that shit again!
What happened?
Did I miss something?
You sure did.
From now on, Tequila,
I suggest you stick to booze.
FOX: The president
actively sanctioned
the deaths of hundreds
of millions of people...
and lied to the public.
I am proud to be responsible
for his impeachment...
and I will do everything I can
to ensure a smooth
transition of power.
CHAMP: In honor
of this historic occasion,
we have purchased...
a distillery in Scotland.
(UNCORKS BOTTLE)
This shows the world...
that Kingsman is now
joining the liquor business.
Before we were cousins.
Now we're brothers,
working side-by-side.
All our resources are now yours.
You can rebuild.
Yeah, y'all shittin'
in high cotton now.
(CHUCKLES)
(CLINKS BOTTLE)
Agent Tequila,
this is a formal occasion...
where's your tie and jacket?
Sorry, sir.
Maybe the Kingsman boys
can dress you properly.
To our union!
ALL: To our union!
(SNIFFLING)
Final order of business...
we would be honored
if one of you would be
our new Agent Whiskey.
Yeah, this two Galahad thing
is just fucking confusing.
(BOTH STUTTERING)
Well, I'm very honored...
Champ...
I'd like to throw
my hat in the ring.