I'm really sorry.
(LAUGHING) My apologies, boys.
I hope there ain't
no hard feelings.
I was just doin' my job.
Welcome to the Statesman,
independent intelligence agency.
Just like y'all, I reckon.
But our founders went
into the booze business.
Thank the sweet Lord above.
This is Ginger Ale.
She's our strategy executive.
Hello.
I'm Agent Tequila.
This is the part
where you untie us.
MERLIN: Thank you.
Harry.
Hello.
Hello, mate.
Harry.
How do you do?
Have we met before?
Harry, it's okay. It's fine.
They know that we know you.
I think there must be
some mistake.
It's been such
a long time, Harry.
I need to get
my brogues resoled.
Yeah, and my oxfords
are done in as well.
Why are you telling me
about your shoes?
I'm a lepidopterist.
You're a what?
I study butterflies.
MERLIN: Well, you wanted to be before
you joined the army, but...
Harry, look at me.
It's good to see you.
We'll be back soon.
So these fellas right here
are our doomsday protocol?
Turns out, our founder's
tailor was Kingsman.
What the fuck
have you done to him?
Nothing. Only tried
to help him.
He's got retrograde amnesia.
Now, we knew from his eyeglasses
that he was intelligence.
We just didn't know whose.
How did he get here?
(ALARM BLARING)
GINGER: What the hell?
Tequila, I'm getting
a crazy spike...
of extreme low frequency waves
11 miles from here.
I'm gonna need you to
escort me there immediately.
I need your alpha gel.
TEQUILA: I'll go check the church.