(SIGHS)
100% effective...
and ready to ship out worldwide
at a moment's notice.
Get out of my room!
You have my word.
Get out!
I will do this...
if the following
conditions are met.
Get out of my fucking room!
First, you agree
to end the war on drugs,
once and for all.
All classes of substance
are legalized...
paving the way
to a new marketplace
in which sales
are regulated and taxed...
as per alcohol.
And second, my colleagues and
I receive full legal immunity.
Meet my terms...
and I look forward
to helping you
keep our beloved
country great...
boosting our ailing economy,
and easing spending
on law enforcement.
Or continue this
blinkered, outmoded...
and, frankly, disastrous
exercise in prohibition...
and live with blood
on your hands.
Save lives. Legalize.
I told you that shit
was no good for you.
REPORTER: Who is Poppy Adams?
After graduating
Harvard Business School...
Adams was briefly held
for serious mental
health issues...
before disappearing
without a trace.
Intelligent, ambitious,
ruthless,
lacks empathy,
superficial charm.
All the elements of a great CEO.
Or a psychopath.
Following the broadcast
of Adams's message
to the president...
there were scenes
of chaos today...
at medical centers
across the country and around the world.
DOCTOR: We have
no more beds available.
The hospital is
at full capacity.
The blue rash
is now being renamed.
"The Dancing Disease"...
as victims begin to exhibit
stage two symptoms.
Let's prep the cryo unit.
MERLIN:
You want to freeze him?
GINGER: Exactly.
REPORTER: Victims of the virus
caused by contaminated
recreational drugs...
flooded hospitals and clinics
in fear for their lives.
(CLAMORING)
REPORTER 2:
Curfews and no travel orders
are being considered
as authorities assess
the scale of the disaster.
Close it.
REPORTER 2:
But there has still been
no official response
from the president...
who remains locked
in emergency talks.
Prepare a presidential decree.
Tell intelligence and law enforcement
to stand down.
We're gonna dance
to this lady's tune.
FOX: Good.
We can make this work.
We spin it
that it's not a matter
of negotiation with terrorists.
No, what I'm proposing...