(HORN BLARING)
I apologize.
Just waiting for my friend.
I'll be back as soon
as I can, I promise.
Got to go save the world?
Yep.
Well, if you save the world...
you know what that means.
Yeah, all right.
Bye, buddy.
Got the passes from my contact.
You're gonna love Glastonbury.
Well, that's the easy part, kid.
Take a look in the glove box.
EGGSY: Fucking hell, bruv.
Thought everything
was supposed to be bigger in America.
Is this why you overcompensate
with these massive cars?
Goes on your finger.
The surveillance tracker
is in the tip.
Apply light pressure for three
seconds to release it.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
EGGSY: Okay, so according
to her Instagram feed...
Charlie's ex-girlfriend
is up ahead at the VIP bar.
Which one of us is gonna
plant the tracker?
Bands, boys.
Yeah, that's fine.
WHISKEY: I say we both
make an approach...
whoever gets on best,
goes for it.
Well, it doesn't have
to be a competition, bruv.
Why don't we just
go up to her...
shake her hand,
pat her on the back,
whatever, you know.
Job done.
The hand is not
a mucous membrane, Eggsy.
Neither is the back.
They teach you anything
at Kingsman?
What are you talking about?
Our trackers are designed
to enter the bloodstream.
They circulate harmlessly,
providing full audio and GPS.
EGGSY: Mucus membrane.
That's like up the nose,
isn't it?
What the fuck am I gonna do?
Stick my finger...
It's not just inside
the nose, is it?
No, Eggsy, it ain't.
Fuck.
All right,
I'll take the first crack.
Watch and learn, buddy.
(SCOFFS)
Good luck.
Here you go, ma'am.
Thank you.
Miss, I beg your pardon.
Now, I don't wanna pester you...
but I just have to know,
what time are you playing?
I'm not in a band.
Oh, God.
Who did you think I was?
Please don't say
someone ghastly.
God damn it,
now I feel like a fool.
I just assumed that a woman
with your charisma...
well, she just had
to be somebody.
Right.
Thank you.
No, it's okay.
I know you didn't mean
to make me feel
like a dumb-ass.
So I'll let you make it up to me
by letting me buy you a drink.
Follow my finger.
(CHUCKLES)
What are we doing?