(YELLING)
(PANTING)
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Not that.
This.
♪ The sun is out
The sky is blue ♪
Bon appetit.
♪ There's not a cloud
To spoil the view ♪
♪ But it's raining ♪
♪ Raining in my heart ♪
♪ Oh, misery, misery ♪
♪ What's gonna become of me? ♪
How is it?
It's delicious.
Welcome to Golden Circle.
♪ Raining in my heart ♪
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
EGGSY: Mmm.
(SPEAKING SWEDISH)
(CHUCKLING)
I think we should
do you the favor
of conversing in English, yes.
So, tell me...
what do you do?
I work for Kingsman,
the tailors, Your Highness.
You may address my daughter
as "Your Highness."
Please address the Queen and
myself with "Your Majesty."
Pappa, this is
a family dinner...
not some state function.
Well then, Eggsy.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What do you make
of the current situation
in the Indian financial markets?
Pappa!
EGGSY: Uh...
Well...
I don't think we can
underestimate the impact
of ECB's quantitative
easing measures.
And of course,
the liquidity wave
from the US Federal
Reserve rate hike...
getting pushed back.
(CLINKING)
Frida Kahlo.
Well, other than the 1939
acquisition by the Louvre...
she wasn't really acknowledged
until the new Mexicanisimo
art movement...
of the late 1970s.
(CLINKING)
Moorish revival.
Ah. The Palazzo Sammezzano.