What's the matter?
Nothing.
I just feel that
our spirit animals
need more time to get in sync...
and find a harmonious bond
on the spiritual plane.
Totally.
Yeah?
Or we could just...
fuck?
Clara, I don't think I can.
But you know what?
My crow is looking
for a place to nest.
MERLIN: Good work, Eggsy!
Tracker fully functional.
(CLARA MOANING ON SPEAKERS)
Don't worry, I've been
through this with Whiskey before.
Nice to be working with an agent
who knows what he's doing.
(SIGHS)
CLARA: Wow, Mr. Crow. My turn.
EGGSY: I'm sorry. I can't.
I'm in a relationship.
That's adorable.
Listen, so am I.
What happens at Glasto,
stays in Glasto.
I can't.
Bye, Clara.
(LINE RINGING)
(VOICEMAIL)
This is Princess T,
please leave a message.
MAN (ON PHONE):
Motor Manor Hotel...
Yeah, can you put me through
to Princess Tilde, please.
Oh, actually, sir, I'm just
looking at my computer...
and I'm afraid that the princess
is already checked out.
EGGSY: Thank you.
Fuck!
Harry.