You know what?
That was the best martini
I've ever had.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
(WHIMPERS)
EGGSY: It's all right.
Don't panic.
Just thought I'd bring you
a little leaving present.
What do you think?
He's lovely, isn't he?
(CHUCKLES)
Would you like to hold him?
Hello.
Do you think I should shoot him?
Are you quite mad?
What? What's the problem?
No! You can't!
Eh? What?
No, you'll have to shoot me!
Shoot you?
Well, I will shoot you.
No. No one's sick enough
to shoot a puppy!
Well, what about you, Harry?
You were sick enough
to shoot a puppy!
Do you remember?
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(GASPS)
EGGSY: You were sick enough
to shoot a puppy!
It was a blank.
Yes, Harry. Yes!
It was a fucking blank!
That's right. It was a blank!
I would never hurt Mr. Pickle!
Yes, Harry!
He lived to a ripe old age!
He died of pancreatitis!
You're not Mr. Pickle.
Eggsy.
Hello, Harry.