♪ West Virginia ♪
♪ Mountain momma ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ Country roads ♪
(GUARDS GROANING)
POPPY: Ooh.
He stepped on a land mine.
Can we get somebody out there
to clean that up?
Hello?
(PIANO PLAYING)
(GUNFIRE)
Crap. We're under attack.
Code five. Code five.
You two, off your fuckin' asses.
Guard the door.
Sir Elton, stay here.
We're under attack.
(ALARM BLARING)
Is it a rescue attempt?
Might be.
Yes!
(PLAYS UPBEAT TUNE)
ELTON:
♪ Wednesday, Wednesday ♪
♪ Wednesday night's
all right ♪
♪ Hey ♪
Isn't that supposed
to be Saturday?
What day is it today?
Wednesday.
Exactly!
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
Elton, just calm down.
Fuck you!
(GUARDS YELLING)
GUARD: Stay there, Elton.
ELTON: Fuck off!
Or I'll fuck you up.