(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Get out of the way, Elton.
Stay down.
It's not allowed to hurt me.
Thank you.
(EGGSY WHEEZING)
(SIGHING)
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Fuck you, Poppy!
Fuck you, Elton.
Kill Elton John.
Fuck!
Elton, take the ball.
(CRACKLES)
(GASPS)
(WHIRRING)
(BARKING)
Thank you.
Now, go off and save the world.
If I save the world,
can I have two tickets
to your next concert?
Darling, if you save the world,
you can have a backstage pass.
(GROANING)
Fuck you.
Time's up.
Fuck!
POPPY: Bennie, Bennie, Bennie!
Get them!
Got it.
(BARKING)
CHARLIE: Kill him, Bennie!
Here, heel! Heel! Good boy!
Come on!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Give me the code.
No. We're not done yet.
Lucky for you, Charlie...
one of us understands
what it means to be a gentleman.
(PANTING)
Let's make this fair.