(PANTING)
All right, they're going
for cover and reloading.
I'll fix their wagons.
Cover me, boys!
Wait.
Eggsy, I think he could be
working for the other side.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're having
a brain fart! Look!
Does that look like
he's working with them?
Harry, are you seeing
butterflies again?
I know what I'm seeing.
(GRUNTING)
(GUNS CLICK)
Good job
he didn't need our help.
Thank fucking Christ
I didn't need any backup!
I'm out of ammo!
Troop carrier coming in.
What've you got?
Fuck!
Shit!
There's a fuck ton of 'em!
What is this?
Looks like you packed for
a fucking slumber party, not a mission!
And they've got
fucking Gatling guns!
MAN: You have 10 seconds
to surrender before we open fire!
Guys, hurry up!
MAN: 10!
Hey!
MAN: 9!
Butterfly guy!
8!
You don't look like
Ginger fixed you right.
7!
I said I'm empty!
6!
Give me yours.
5!
Harry, give him the fucking gun!
4!
Harry, no!
Oh, fuck it! Fire!
Harry, get down!
I mean, honestly, Harry,
what the fuck is wrong with you?
He broke the vial on purpose!
You're a fucking idiot!
You're out of control, Harry!