Country and western music.
♪ Country roads ♪
♪ Take me home ♪
♪ To the place I belong ♪
(TOUR GUIDE CHATTERING)
Oh! Here's where we leave
the casks to age.
Unfortunately, we can't go in,
as it's a temperature-controlled
environment.
So let's move on to
our world class stud farm...
and meet three of
our Kentucky Derby winners.
(WHIRRING)
Biometric security scanner
just to protect
a few old barrels of whiskey?
Pull the other one, love.
Got it.
Are you getting anything?
Not yet.
EGGSY: Fucking hell.
MERLIN: It's a shame
it's not scotch.
Hang on.
According to this,
there's a huge
underground structure
right beneath us.
And if my calculations
are correct...
This...
is the way in.
Fucking hell, Merlin. Shit.
MAN: You know, my mama...
she always told me...
us southerners get our good
manners from the British.
I was thinkin',
ain't that a pity.
Y'all didn't keep nothing
for yourselves.
Y'all ain't never heard of
knocking before you enter?
Well, actually we had
an invitation. Didn't we?
Yeah.
Oh, did you now?
Yeah. It came in the
shape of a bottle.
We're from the Kingsman
tailor shop in London.
Maybe you've heard of us?
Oh, the Kingsman.
Yeah.
Huh.
That's where y'all got
them fine suits
and them fancy
spectacles y'all got on?
Exactly.
That's right.
Y'all look damn sharp.
Let me see
if I got it right, here.
You want me to believe that
it's normal for a tailor...
to hack through an advanced
biometric security system...
with nothing but a little
bitty old watch on?
I can promise you...
that dog don't hunt.
So why don't you go on and get down
on your knees...
and tell me
who you really work for.
(SPITS)
That's 1963 Statesman Reserve.