(GROANS)
(BEEPING)
(PANTING)
Who the fuck are you?
MAN: A bottle
in a secret wall.
You really expect me
to take that seriously?
See, I think
your story's horse shit.
Y'all just trying to cover
for a failed rescue mission.
You here for the lepidopterist,
ain't you?
Okay, so your
mystery bottle, huh?
Look anything like that,
right there?
Yes. Same brand,
much older.
All right.
Let's see here.
You know why the measurement
of alcohol content's
called "proof"?
Oh, fuck off!
Oh, for Pete's sake.
See, comes from back
in the old days...
when pirates wanted to test
the strength of their rum.
They used to pour a little bit out
on gunpowder.
(EXHALES)
That'll make you wanna slap
your mama right there, boy.
And if the gunpowder,
if it burnt when
they set it alight...
they considered it proof...
that their rum
was good and strong.
But see, I ain't got
no gunpowder on me, do I?
But I'm pretty sure
you boys'll make
just as impressive of a sound...
when I set your balls on fire.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Or you could just tell me who the fuck
y'all really are...
and how the hell y'all found us.
MERLIN: Look,
for the last time,
we have nothing to protect
but our honor.
So you can take
your cheap horse piss
that you call whiskey...
which, by the way,
is spelled without an "e"...
and is nothing compared
to a single malt scotch...
and you can go fuck yourself.
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
What about you?
Me?
Yeah.
No, I love
a Jack and Coke, bruv.
But I do agree with the part
where you go fuck yourself.
All right.
Y'all ain't got
nothing to protect
other than your honor.
Let's see what happens
when we change things up.
Fuck me.
Harry?
Y'all got three seconds
to tell me the truth.
MERLIN: Wait. No.
No!
Harry!
He can't hear you.
But I can, so talk.
No!
Get down, Harry!
MERLIN: Harry! Harry!
That's two.
Harry!
EGGSY: Harry!
Three.
Stop!
Their story checked out.