EGGSY: Hey, hey.
Looking good, Merlin.
Feeling good, Eggsy.
(CHUCKLES)
Right. This is yours.
That's for you.
Press the "S".
Minesweeper.
Courtesy of Statesman.
EGGSY: And what about these?
MERLIN: Careful.
Those are hand grenades.
As discussed...
this is for the endgame.
I'm entrusting it to you.
And I'm entrusting this...
to me.
NEWS ANCHOR 1: Millions of
Golden Circle victims worldwide...
are now entering
stage three paralysis.
NEWS ANCHOR 2:
In his latest statement...
the president promised
he was doing
everything in his power...
to speed up negotiations
and save lives.
But fears are growing
that for many,
it may soon be too late.
Our thoughts and prayers
are with the victims.
God help us all.
(SOBBING)
HARRY (WHISPERING): Right.
This is where we split up.
Pincer movement.
Merlin, you're with me.
Eggsy, you signal
when we're in position.
(CLICKS)
(BEEPING)
MERLIN: Don't move.
You move, we die.