(EXPLOSION)
This does not mean
you're off the fucking hook!
We need to go dark.
We don't know
who else at Statesman
could be working against us.
Shit! This is all my fault.
You weren't ready for the field
and I pushed for it!
He showed his hand.
You think he'd have let us live?
You should be thanking me
for saving our arses!
Saving our arses?
Try saying that
to fucking Whiskey!
(HISSING)
You are unbelievable!
Merlin, can you hear me?
MERLIN: Yes, Eggsy.
Whiskey's down.
He's been shot.
What happened?
He got caught in the crossfire.
I've applied the alpha gel.
We'll bring him in.
But first, I've gotta find a
way to get back up to that lab
and retrieve more antidote.
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
CLARA: Charlie, what's
happening? Where are you?
Everything's under control.
I'm sorry, Charlie.
I'm so sorry.
Please don't tell Poppy
it was me they followed.
CHARLIE: Don't worry, darling.
What happens in Italy...
(PANTING)
stays in Italy.
Thank you.
(EXPLOSIONS)
Merlin, change of plans.
Wu Ting Feng, Singapore.
Who?
EGGSY: Exactly.
It's the only lead we've got.
So I suggest
you find out who he is.
Come on.
Wu Ting Feng, he's
an assistant at a law firm.
MERLIN: Let's get through
their firewall.
GINGER: Yep.
Merlin...
have you ever wanted
to do more than this?
Are you serious?
Yeah.
This is vital.
Without us, they'd be lost.
I know, but you know
what I mean.
Get out there in the field.
Well, have you ever asked?
Of course I have.
But every time an agent's
position has come up...
Whiskey has voted against me.
No.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look, check it out.
Email in from Poppy,
from a senior partner
at the firm.
They're coordinates.
Cambodia?