Harald Blatand, whose name
translates to
"Bluetooth" in English.
And the Bluetooth logo
is his initials
in Norse runic symbols.
And, as I'm sure you know...
the Bluetooth logo
is his initials...
in Norse runic symbols.
ROXY: Oh, my God, Eggsy.
Why isn't he eating
his fucking pudding?
I need to research
this gold tattoo.
I found records of other people
with the same
body modifications.
All of them have
high level involvement...
with crime and international
drug trafficking.
And there's rumors of something
called The Golden Circle.
Hmm.
(BEEPING)
Best agent or best friend?
(JB BARKING)
BRANDON: Come on, JB.
Give it a rest, mate.
Stop scratching the door.
I'm gonna get the blame now.
There you are. Happy?
With the decks and all that.
(BEEPS)
Shit, boy!
(EXCLAIMS) What the...
Do you reckon, JB...
model material?
(EGGSY CHUCKLING)
I must say, you're really
not as I expected.
Well, thank you very much...
Your Majesty.
BRANDON: Eggsy?
Is that you, mate?
What the fuck is going on here?
You a gangster now or something?
Fuckin' hell. Is that Tilde's
mom and dad's house?
Tell you what. Whatever
you're doing, I want in.
(DEVICE ACTIVATES, BEEPING)
Put it down!
Why?
I said, put it down now!
What's wrong with it?
Shut it! Fucking shut it!
Eggsy.
I beg your pardon?
(RAPID BEEPING BEEPING)
Shut it! Shut it now!
All right, mate.
Chill your boots.
(SIGHS)
Eggsy, what...
Oh, no. Oh, my God, no.
I'm so sorry.
(BARKING)
You shut up and all.
You got me in enough trouble.
(ALARM BLARING)
(GRUNTS)
The next order of business...
Agent Percival.