I'm fine. Have a good day.
Okay.
Ah, Galahad! You're late.
We were wondering if you'd had
a second encounter with Charlie.
I wish. I'm looking forward
to finishing him off.
All right, gents.
Merlin, come in.
Galahad and Lancelot,
please remain
for Merlin's debrief.
Everyone else,
reconvene at 1900 hours.
So...
the man who attacked
Galahad in the taxi
was Charlie Hesketh.
Rejected Kingsman
applicant turned bad.
We last saw him back
at Richmond Valentine's HQ.
EGGSY: I've caught
a fucking spy!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Like everyone else there...
Charlie had a security implant
in his neck.
A weakness we had no choice
but to exploit.
Hey, Merlin.
Still fucking spectacular, eh?
Come on, guys, loosen up.
We saved the world.
MERLIN: Yeah.
Unfortunately, Galahad,
you also saved Charlie.
When you electrocuted him,
you damaged his implant.
Instead of his head exploding...
he only lost an arm
and his vocal chords.
Fucker should be thanking me.
And now he's back for revenge?
We don't think so, sir.
We believe he's being recruited
by an unknown organization.
Lancelot?
Got the police autopsy reports
from Charlie's colleagues
in the SUVs.
They're not just goons for hire.
Fingerprints removed.
Teeth filed smooth.
I did a face recognition.
Nothing.
And that thing?
A cosmetic tattoo
made of 24-carat gold.
They all had them.
Seems like we're looking
at some kind of underworld organization.
Senora Poppy has sent me
for my makeover.
Follow me.
Please take your shirt off.
(WHIRRING)