you may shed a tear in private.
(SIGHS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Okay.
What's the doomsday protocol?
We go shopping.
We're from Kingsman.
We'd like to buy some wine.
And use tasting room
number three, please.
Not one of my predecessors
has ever been
in this situation before.
Thank God.
A-ha.
Remember this?
EGGSY: Yeah,
how could I forget?
Whatever's in that safe
is the answer to all our problems.
Huh.
Is that it?
I suppose that must be
upper-class humor.
I don't get it.
Me neither. What the fuck
are we supposed to do now?
I think we should drink a toast
to our fallen comrades.
To Roxy.
Roxy.
Ooh.
To Arthur.
Arthur.
Mmm.
Should we do one for JB?
I think we should.
(MERLIN SOBBING)
I should have seen it coming.
Charlie, the taxi.
It's all my fault.
No, that's bullshit, Merlin.
It ain't all your fault.
You're the best, bruv.
Honestly, without you...
I'd have lost it
a long time ago.
(MERLIN MUMBLES)
I think we should
drink to Scotland.
I think we've probably
had enough, to be honest.
You're probably right.
Merlin.
Aye?