Babe, if you can hear me,
I want you to know
that I love you.
And if we get through this,
and you'll have me back...
I wanna be with you.
No matter what.
I promise I won't let you down.
It's all gonna be all right.
My favorite singer.
I don't bloody know.
How would I know that?
It's John Denver.
Merlin!
Have you got eyes
on that location yet?
Soon. The reconnaissance
drone's about an hour away.
Which gives us time
to sort out...
Bollocks, we haven't
time for anything.
I'm leaving now.
With or without you.
Hello!
(GUNS COCKING)
GUARD: Identify yourself.
My name is Stacey Prewitt.
I'm Ms. Poppy Adams' attorney.
Poppy, you expecting
a lawyer tonight?
Oh, yes. Please send him in.
But don't forget to
reactivate the landmines.
(PROTESTERS CLAMORING)
Good evening, Ms. Adams.
My lawyer is bringing you
the document right now.
Hurry up.
And once you countersign,
it becomes
an executive decree...
and you can't back out,
and then I release the antidote.
Can you give me any assurance
you can get it
out there in time?
And where's it gonna come from?
How long it'll take
to distribute?
I wouldn't worry about that.
I have secure stockpiles...
hidden in every
major city worldwide.
And when I enter
the access code...
my fleet of drones
will distribute
the antidote immediately.
So don't dilly-dally
signin' that document
'cause time is running out.
(laughs)
You dumb bitch!
You all right?
What was that
phone call you got?
Let's not, Harry.
I don't think
you'd sympathize...
and I'm not really in
the mood for a lecture.
All right.
How about a martini?
For old times' sake?
Yeah, all right.
I had a girlfriend.
I lost her.