(YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
Oh! Oh, no. Whoa! Whoa!
(SIGHS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
CLARA: Sorry we never
found your friends.
Well, we all go on
our separate journeys...
but, ultimately,
we'll all arrive
at the same destination.
Shall we check my tent?
See if they're there?
Uh... Yeah.
Oh, come on.
Wow.
This is amazing.
Come on.
Uh, you know what, I'm busting
for a pee actually. (CHUCKLES)
You could do it on me
if you want.
Uh...
Maybe in a bit.
Give me a sec, yeah?
Okay, but hurry up, River.
Been waiting all night for you
to at least kiss me.
(CHUCKLES)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey!
EGGSY: Hi, babe.
Uh, bit of a nightmare.
I've got to sleep
with a target...
but I won't do it, unless
you agree that it's all right.
You've got
to be fucking kidding.
What was I, target practice?
Babe, surely it's better that
I'm honest with you...
rather than me doing it
and not telling you.
Kind of got a bit of
a "save the world" situation here.
How the fuck is screwing someone
gonna save the world?
Well, it's a bit complicated...
but trust me, I would not be
doing it if I didn't have to.
Babe, please believe me.
I love you.
You are the person I wanna spend
the rest of my life with.
Is that a proposal?
Um...
Because I think I'd give you
my permission.
Having that security, knowing
that we were committed...
In that context, yeah.
Yeah, I'd feel different.
Right. Well, I mean...
I want to be with you,
but being
a public figure, babe...
like a prince...
It's a bit of a factor,
you know,
what with my job and stuff.
Oh, no, no, no, come on. Okay.
Uh, look, we need to talk
about this properly.
Just give me five minutes, okay?
Don't put yourself down, Eggsy.
I'm sure you can last
longer than that.
(SIGHS)