Be good, be cool.
Bye.
Thank you for that.
I'm Clara.
River.
Bloody hell, is that the time?
You know what, I'm so jetlagged
I don't know
if I'm coming or going.
Where've you been?
Anywhere nice?
South America. Been spending
a bit of time out there.
Training with the shaman,
and trying to really connect
with my spirit animal.
Yeah.
I'm a crow.
And, hang on, let me guess...
No.
Jaguar.
What? No! Oh, my God!
Yes?
How did you even know that?
Look, it totally is.
Check it out.
Oh. Ino Moxo.
Black jaguar. Very nice.
You know what?
I wanna buy you a drink.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MERLIN: Eggsy sent this
from Glastonbury.
And #bluerash is
trending on Twitter.
Have you found any correlation
between these cases?
Only recreational drug use.
Ah.
I know.
Not very Statesman-like.
Tequila here...
he is our resident bad boy.
You don't think
this could be related
to The Golden Circle, do you?
A drug cartel
poisoning its customers?
Doesn't make sense.
Mmm.
CHARLIE: Poppy, would you
pass the sugar, please?
POPPY: Okay.
But it's really bad for you.
Eight times more addictive
than cocaine.
Five times more likely
to cause death.
But it's legal...
so, you go ahead.
Knock yourself out.
Don't get me started
on tobacco and alcohol.
Peddle that stuff
and you're in Fortune 500.
But me? No!
I'm out here hiding
in the middle of
nowhere. Homesick.
Because I sell drugs.
Oh, Pops. You're doing this
because you're homesick?
POPPY: Yes.
I want freedom.
I want fame.
Our profits were
250 billion dollars last year.
I am the most successful
businesswoman
in the world,
but nobody knows who I am.
Pops, Pops.
It's not long now, eh?
You're right, thank you.
ANGEL: Sorry to interrupt you.
You wanted to see me,
Madam Poppy?
Yes, Angel.
In The Golden Circle...
we do not sample
the merchandise...
and we do not break the rules.
Which is why I have
invested in robots...
because they are
so much more reliable
and trustworthy
than human beings.
(WHISTLES)