I know it's against
Kingsman rules,
having a relationship.
When I was shot...
can you guess
what the last thing was
that flashed through my mind?
It was absolutely nothing.
I had no ties.
No bittersweet memories.
I was leaving nothing behind.
Never experienced
companionship...
never been in love...
and in that moment...
all I felt was loneliness...
and regret.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
Just know that
having something to lose...
is what makes life worth living.
Now, let's go
and save your girl.
I missed you, Harry.
Gentlemen.
I hate to break up a party.
We're nearly there,
so I suggest we get ready.
Follow me.
Oh, yes.
(GASPING)
Hello, gorgeous.
I'm Jack. What's your name?
How would you like to ride
home on a real cowboy?
I got a six pack
of cold ones on ice
and my roomie's out all night.
So you can scream my name
as loud as you need to, sugar.
I hate to do this to you, Jack.
Who's this pretty lady?
She's dead.
Cops said wrong place,
wrong time.
Hey, honey. I'm heading
to the grocery store.
My name is Poppy Adams.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Ginger.
Goddamn butterfly guy shot me
in the fucking head.
Why would he do that?
(PANTING)
Well, I'm guessing
you didn't fix him right.
And where the hell is he?
He's on his way to Cambodia
with Eggsy and Merlin.
That's where Poppy's base is.
Eggsy's gonna need backup.
Yes, he is.
Get the Silver Pony
on the runway
and ready to take off.