Close the door behind you.
MAN: At what point are you
going to start behaving
like a Statesman, Tequila?
You wanna go back
to being a rodeo clown?
No, sir. I apologize, sir.
I'm Champagne.
But anyone who knows
what's good for him...
calls me Champ.
Sorry for your troubles.
As your American cousins...
I'm placing all of Statesman's
considerably larger resources at your disposal.
Can you imagine us
in the clothing business?
(CHUCKLES)
Now, how can I help you?
EGGSY: First of all,
I've got to thank you
for saving Agent Galahad.
Wait.
You said that you were Galahad.
Oh, no, he's talking
about the butterfly guy.
That used to be his handle.
Oh.
EGGSY: Galahad always said,
"You've got to look at
the bigger picture..."
"ask 'why' as well as 'who'."
So if someone wanted
to take out Kingsman...
then they've got to be
planning something major.
So what do you know?
They're a drug cartel, we think.
The name Golden Circle
keeps coming up.
Mmm. We'll look
into them. What else?
One of our former trainees
is working with them.
Charlie Hesketh.
Total prick.
You got any promising
leads on him?
His ex-girlfriend.
I've been tracking her
through social media.
We believe she's still
in contact with him.
And she's going
to Glastonbury Music Festival.
Oh, good.
Agent Tequila,
break out your dancing shoes.
You have a new mission.
Yes, sir.
CHAMP: Hold up.
You feeling okay?
I'm a little tired,
but fine, thanks.
Galahad, you ready?
CHAMP: Your face...
You got...
What the fuck?
CHAMP: Oh, shit.
Head to the sick bay.
Have Ginger check you out.
(WHISTLES)
Hey, give him your glasses.
You're in luck, kid.
Put 'em on.
You get our finest senior agent
to join you instead.
Right now,
he's in our New York office.
Galahad, meet Agent Whiskey.
WHISKEY: Kid...
looks like we're hookin' up
with a chick at a rock concert.
My favorite kind of mission.
I'm sending my jet
to pick you up.