Let me translate that for you.
(GRUNTING)
What's wrong with me, Merlin?
I thought you fixed me?
Well, we rebuilt
your neural pathways.
But it'll take time to get
your coordination back.
(SCREAMS AND GROANS)
(WHIP CRACKS)
And the phantom butterflies?
You will experience episodes...
lapses of clarity.
You'll be back to normal soon.
(GRUNTING)
Whoo.
I feel like a tornado
in a trailer park.
CHOIR:
♪ Golden Circle proudly presents ♪
Mr. President,
my name is Poppy Adams.
I believe the UN has no teeth.
So I've selected you,
as leader of the free world,
to receive this communication.
And I invite you
to begin negotiations...
on the largest scale
hostage situation in history.
A few weeks ago,
an engineered virus
was released...
contained in all
varieties of my product.
Cannabis, cocaine, heroin,
opium, ecstasy...
...and crystal meth.
Some of you
are already infected.
And this is what you can expect
in the coming days.
After a brief
incubation period...
victims present
with stage one symptoms.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
A blue rash.
Next...
second stage symptoms appear.
(SNAPS FINGERS) Mania...
as the virus enters the brain.
(WHISPERS)
Very distressing to the victim
and those around them.
Stage three... (SNAPS FINGERS)
(GASPING)
Paralysis.
Muscles enter a state
of catastrophic seizure.
And once the muscles of
the thorax become affected...
breathing becomes impossible...
leading to a very nasty death
within 12 hours.
But I have good news to
the millions already affected.
It doesn't have to be this way.
I have an antidote.
(SNAPS FINGERS)