NEWS ANCHOR 1:
The government today urged.
Golden Circle victims...
to report to
the temporary field hospitals
now set up across the country.
NEWS ANCHOR 2: The president's
handling of the crisis
has been commended
by other world leaders.
Damn. Politics has
never been so easy.
Oh, Jesus, Fox.
What?
Oh, God.
Like I said, sir...
this affects all people
from all backgrounds.
I'm disappointed, Fox.
Disappointed and disgusted.
Mr. President,
I routinely work
a 20 hour day for you,
7 days a week.
Maybe some can do that
without chemical help.
Countless people
are going to die.
You can save them, sir.
Innocent people like me.
Not that innocent.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
He looks great.
Good.
Good news, gentlemen.
He'll be back on
his feet in no time.
I'm not certain
that's a good idea.
What do you mean?
I shot Agent Whiskey.
Deliberately.
What, why?
He was working against us.
And until we find out why,
I say we trust no one.
Merlin, Harry's sick.
This whole thing is my fault.
I thought he was ready.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry,
I've got to take this.
Listen to me.
This is not about
my mental health.
If there's a chance there's
a double agent in our midst...
or worse, if Statesman itself
has a dark agenda...
we have to safeguard
this mission.
We both know the president
wants these victims dead.
(CHUCKLES) Hey, baby.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey.
(PRINCESS TILDE LAUGHS)
Fuck.
Look, Harry, I trust you.
I always have.
But it's about this situation.
We need Statesman's resources.
And I need to know
that you are fit for work.
Babe, why didn't you call me?
Are you the banana man?
Listen, we're on
the verge of finding
an antidote.
It's gonna be all right.
Now, look left for me.
There's nothing wrong
with my brain.
Look right.