I can't, mate.
I'm allergic to dogs.
Bullshit.
Dogshit, actually.
(laughing)
That leaves you, Brandon.
What you doing tomorrow night?
Yeah, I'll look after
your dog, mate,
but I got one condition.
What's that?
You have a drink with us.
Yeah.
Got to do it, babe.
Got to do it.
(EXCLAIMS)
Brandon, happy birthday!
ALL: Happy birthday.
JAMAL: Yeah.
EGGSY: Cheers.
Shit.
POPPY:
My drugs are everywhere.
They were never my thing...
but here I am,
running the biggest
drug cartel in the world.
The only downside is having to
live in the middle of nowhere.
You know, these ruins
are technically undiscovered.
I just added a few touches
to remind me of home.
I grew up on all that
awesome 50s nostalgia.
Grease. American Graffiti.
Happy Days.
But I digress.
The thing you need to understand
is the hard work
and ingenuity...
it took to achieve
a global monopoly...
on the drug trade.
And that's all on me.
Not to toot my own horn...
I just think
it's really important
for new recruits
to understand...
the history
of The Golden Circle.
So. Lifelong friends, huh?
Charles, do you think
your buddy here
is worthy of joining us?
Ms. Poppy, I would
not have brought him
all the way to see you
if I didn't think so.
Excellent.
Well, you hungry?
Starving.
Wonderful! Right this way.
Make yourselves at home.
So, fellas...
I have a couple of things
that I wanna clarify.
You understand that
in The Golden Circle...
my authority is never
to be questioned, right?
And the importance
of following orders?
Do you understand that?
And the value of loyalty?
It's easy to nod, isn't it?
I don't like easy.
I like proof.
(SIGHS)
What's your name?
Angel, ma'am.
Angel, baby.
Hey.
Your old pal, Charles,
has messed up.
That's all I'm gonna tell you,
'cause that's all
you need to know.
So put him in the mincer, okay?
(LAUGHING)
(WHIRRING)