Eggsy.
Valentine has to be stopped.
No, I know.
He has a device.
It's all right.
It's sorted. Don't worry.
We got a lot of
catching up to do.
Well, well.
I suppose I should
cancel that taxi.
HARRY: Yes.
If you don't mind...
Merlin.
Welcome back...
Galahad.
EGGSY: Now that we've finished
the debrief, Harry...
here's a couple of
welcome back gifts.
First up...
a brand-new Kingsman watch.
Advanced software,
it can hack into anything
with a microchip.
It is the bollocks.
And Merlin...
MERLIN: I made you these.
A-ha.
Thank you, Merlin, Eggsy.
How do I look?
You look...
Like some faggot lookin' for
an eye fuckin'.
Now...
why don't you
get out of our bar...
before I take out
your other one?
Now, is that any way
to welcome a visitor
from out of town, moonshine?
Okay.
Suck my southern dick...
bitch.
Oh, I don't think
that'll be necessary.
Good day, sir.
Well?
What are you ladies waitin' for?
Manners...
maketh...
man.
Do you know what that means?
Then let me teach you a lesson.
Are we going to stand
around here all day?
Or are we going to...
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
MAN: You big...
(MEN WHOOPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Well, pick him up.