Yeah, I know, Harry.
I'm wearing it.
Listen, you can't just give up.
Give up?
No, on the contrary.
I'm about to achieve my dream.
Researching rare butterflies
alongside some of the finest
minds in entomology.
You know, you may as well
have me stuck up on this wall.
'Cause you're never gonna find a butterfly
more interesting than me.
Sorry?
When you and I first met,
I was just, like, a maggot.
Maggots turn into flies.
Perhaps you mean larva.
Larva, yeah, okay.
Whatever. The point is...
everyone wanted to squash me.
But not you.
You helped me
to become a caterpillar.
And now I've got wings.
I'm flying higher
than I ever dreamed.
And that is all thanks to you.
I hate to seem rude,
but I need to finish packing
and get some sleep.
Harry, you can't just walk away.
Kingsman needs you.
The whole world needs you.
I need you.
Eggy, whoever the Harry was
that you knew,
he's gone, I'm afraid.
Goodbye.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
That's not a martini.
It is in Kentucky.
Fair enough.
HARRY: Here's to you, Eggsy.
You're exactly
what Kingsman needs.
(LINE RINGING)
(VOICEMAIL)
This is Princess T.
Please leave a message.
Can I have
another martini, please?
Sure.
Thanks.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(SCOFFS) Give up.