River, what are you doing here?
CHARLIE: River?
EGGSY: Hi, Clara.
What happens at Glasto,
stays in Glasto.
You motherfucker!
Bye, Charlie.
Sound the alarm!
You fucking cockroach!
(ALARM BLARING)
Jam the door!
Give...
Fuck!
WHISKEY:
Galahad, we're coming.
All clear at the bottom?
Galahad, come in!
Open the fucking door.
They've locked.
Open the door!
Harry, come on, we're in.
Let's go.
Away, butterflies.
Butterfly? No, Harry. You've
got to shut the doors, please.
Come on.
We've gotta go now. Please!
Shut the fucking door, Harry!
Harry, are you there?
Well done, Harry.
Good. Thanks, man.
Come on. Now!
It's done.
Thank you.
You all good down there, Harry?
All clear.
Hello, Eggsy.
Enjoy the ride, bruv.
Oh, shit.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH YELLING)
All the buttons are dead.
Controls gone.
Everything's in shutdown.
You're on your own, Eggsy.
(LAUGHS)
(BOTH GROANING)
(YELLING)
(WHISKEY GASPING)
What the fuck is that?