POPPY: Yep.
Kingsman is crumpets.
Like toast, but British.
And to say thank you...
I got you a present, Charlie.
My guys made you this.
Bigger, badder, better.
I call it...
ARMageddon.
(WHIRRING)
Let's see if your game improves.
Ouch.
EGGSY: Someone decides
to wipe out
every Kingsman property...
every agent, and somehow...
conveniently,
you weren't at home.
I could say the same thing
about you.
What, you think I'd kill Roxy?
And my mate, Brandon,
and my fucking dog?
MERLIN: No.
You think I would?
This thing...
hacked us.
Clearly, this arm can be
remotely controlled.
I'm only alive
because my address
wasn't on the database
with the agents.
Whoever Charlie's working with
doesn't think that mere
staff are missile-worthy.
This ain't funny.
Roxy is dead!
Everyone's dead! Gone!
Do you even care?
Pull yourself together.
Remember your training.
There's no time for emotion
in this scenario.
Now...