(COUGHING)
MERLIN: It wasn't
a revenge mission.
Charlie could've just
killed you immediately.
Not boasting,
but I trained him well enough
that even he wouldn't
mess that up.
EGGSY: Merlin, I'm sorry,
we're gonna have to do
the debrief tomorrow.
I've got to get
to a dinner tonight...
and if I miss it, let's just say
Charlie might as well
have killed me.
Well, if you can't wait
for the police
to clear the park...
there's another way out
in the corner.
(GAGS AND COUGHS)
Fuck!
(CHUCKLES)
(EGGSY GROANS)
How important is that dinner?
(SIGHS)
Let me show you.
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
For fuck's sake!
(DOOR OPENS)
Babe.
I'm home!
I'm here.
What the hell happened?
It's a long story
that deserves a kiss.
(CHUCKLES) Not even JB
would kiss you right now.
EGGSY: If you really love me,
just one little kiss.
(GASPS)
You were really gonna do it?
Yeah.
Now, that is
true love right there.
Amazing. I'm gonna
go get changed.
GROUP: ♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
(CHEERING AND WHOOPING)
And Tilde made that
for you herself, bruv.
PRINCESS TILDE: Mmm-hmm.
The royal baker's not available.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, shut up, Brandon.
Especially if you
want some of this.
Oh! Wait. Is that that
Swedish stuff right there?
Yes.
No, no. I ain't drinkin'
none of that.
Last time here,
I was wrecked, man.
Yeah, but that's 'cause you
were a lightweight, Jamal.
(LAUGHING)
No, no, babe, I'm good.
Not for me, thank you.
Oh, what?
What's going on, man?
I'm meeting her parents
for the first time
tomorrow night.
(WHOOPING)